<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2827</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 15:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry youve had a negative experience. Im here to support you if you ever need it. Sending love to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 15:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, just scratches on the top of my wrist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Opinions on high school anxiety </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 15:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been suffering from exam-centered anxiety and panic attacks for a few years now. Perfectionism in conjunction with extremely low self esteem has contributed to this. I spend every night studying for hours, and can expect a breakdown a few times a week during the school term.

The issue is, I know nothing will get better from here. Ill never make it into university, let alone survive the rest of high school. From there, Ill never achieve a job that I want, and be stuck with minimal success and continual stress. The "best" part of my life is now almost gone, and  Im already watching my future crumble at my fingertips as my grades steadily decline.

So, what are your opinions on high school anxiety? Is it even valid? Does anything ever get better? Is life useless now? Should I give up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 15:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear that. I wish I could be there to give you a warm, comforting hug and let you know that you can get through this. One day at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 15:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, Im heading to bed now but please feel free to spill your thoughts to me in a chat. Ill respond when I wake up in a few hours - sorry I cant be there now. Please dont feel obligated though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 14:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the love. Sending some to you too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 14:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont go. You deserve to live. Talk to me if you need to. I am here for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 14:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, definitely. Often, when Im posting genuine comments on r/amiugly (in response to posts), Im met with hatred and replies like: "youre an attention whore", "hes ugly, stop lying". I really hate it sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 14:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont even know whether I should wait a few years. I feel like it should be over soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 14:38:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im already failing in high school - I feel like I have no life or future. Ill never make it into uni. Ill never have a successful career. Ill be left a sobbing, useless mess for the rest of my life - which may not last much longer, at this rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 14:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try to write them down. This always helps for me. I jot down whatever Im thinking - digital or pen and notebook, whichever I feel. I make sure to delete the writing afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 14:35:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know. Exactly how I feel. If I can barely survive now, Ill never make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 14:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Ill definitely try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 13:43:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mental health is already crumbling and Im still in high school. Ill never survive uni, let alone get accepted. My life is already disintegrating, and I hate my grades. Ill never be successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 13:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need advice  being productive over spring break </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 13:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have one more week of spring break left, and I have been relatively productive, getting little assignments done each day, and completing my to do lists. Unfortunately, my school provides no preliminary coursework to study, so I do not know how to prepare for the next term. It feels too overwhelming to review all the previous work  what do you recommend for being productive and prepared for a new school term?

By the way, I am about to enter 10th grade, and I have anxiety and mild depression due to school and exams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 12:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get a snack and a cold drink, organise my study space and computer, check my to do list and cross off finished items, and take a shower if I need a total refresh. Ill also go outside or read for a while to reset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:26:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. Theyre actually really sweet and supportive, but I feel like Im just a burden that makes everyone sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know exactly how you feel. Even "fun" things are dreaded, because they drain me so much. All I do is study, work, and read - my friends wanted me to come to the pool with them but I know how anxious and exhausted I will feel, so I declined. I dont even know what Im doing anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try to unwind, even though its hard. Relax each muscle, one by one - feel yourself going limp. Im so sorry to hear that you arent doing well - wishing you all the best, sending love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your emotions and mental health situation is valid. Dont let others tell you what you are experiencing. You are going through a difficult time currently, but youll make it. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, feel free to message me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Feeling more motivated today! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am on spring break currently, and I have one more week until school commences again. I am filled with anxiety about it, but feeling slightly better now. I printed some organisational papers, made piles of papers to review in preparation for the new term, and started feeling excited to work as hard as I can to achieve much better grades and stay on top of assignments. I hope this feeling lasts, as well as my productivity streak. I hope you had a lovely day, too! Just wanted to write this out to keep myself accountable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tidy up my desk, organise my computer desktop, read a few pages of a book, or work on my bullet journal! Its also good to get a snack or some fresh air. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. Ill try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:59:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so scared for university, because I feel like I will never make it. I just wish I could fast forward to being accepted and spending days studying on campus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 23:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the love and advice, Ill try! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please, if you want to vent to someone, Im here. Im going to sleep now, but Ill respond as soon as I wake up. Im happy to talk with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats amazing! Good luck! Im in Australia too - one more week of holidays. ): Im going into 10th grade, so anxious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See? Keep holding onto those little things that make you happy, even if its just for a moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:20:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Wishing you all the best as well. Are you on spring break as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:18:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so scared and exhausted as well. Im about to be in 10th grade, and I already am working at capacity. What will I do? I know that things will just get harder. Its so pointless for someone as worthless as me. I should end it all soon, before this happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont do it. Prolong the date. Keep persevering, one step at a time. Make yourself do something simple - take a bath, clean your room, make a new playlist, draw a dog. Do little things until you feel more clear minded.

What helps me is keeping suicide as a comforting last resort. You know that if things get too unbearable, you can turn to it, but for now you have to keep fighting through the world. You can do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:13:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so important. Its easy to think that saddening music can be cathartic, but in fact its just detrimental and promotes more anxiety/depression. Try to steer clear of it and consciously select more uplifting music that counteracts your mood. Thank you for this reminder! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How is your day progressing? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surprisingly, I had an okay day today. It could even be classified as good! I was productive; I crossed several assignments off my to do list. I stayed tidy and neat. I downloaded some organisation printouts to prepare for the next term, and I browsed study-related blogs to regain motivation. I am feeling slightly better about returning to school now, and facing another week.

Im planning to go to sleep, but feel free to vent about your day in the comments, whether it be good or bad. Im happy to hear you out, and Ill respond in the morning. Lets all support each other. I believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 15:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7 - you have a unique but cute appearance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 14:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. I am speechless. Thank you again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 11:28:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you do too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:59:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This post brought tears to my eyes. I am so sorry that you are feeling alone. You are obviously a kind and caring person who doesnt deserve that. Try to yourself for being nervous around others - youre trying your best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:56:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem. I hope you feel better soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:52:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats suicidal ideation. I experience this as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im reading. Im here. You are not a failure, everyone makes mistakes. You deserve life and love and happiness and satisfaction. You are trying your best, so forgive yourself. And please, try not to go. We all want and need you here. You have a future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, pedantic grammar observers unite! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck! I believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel more alone when Im with others most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this. Your support means so much to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is completely relatable for me, every aspect. I love to write and watercolour, but then I start comparing myself and everything shatters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the correction! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The prospect of suicide is such a comfort </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone else feel similarly? I find it so reassuring to know that if one day the world becomes too unbearable for me, I have an escape route. I'll wake up, write a few notes, and finish the act so that its clean-cut and done. This keeps me going every day. I can always uncap a red pen and circle a date on my calendar if need be. Its in the palm of my hands if I ever see my future crumble too irreparably. I wish I wasnt so close to this point though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neither will I. Please keep trying though. Well make it together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I agree. The only thing that I hate in my life is self-inflicted - my grades and future. Thats why I hate myself so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:23:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, thank you for this. Youre going to make me cry. Thank you so much for the sweet message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Fac ob cetera" could work
"Do (it) for others" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure! Thank you for reaching out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 06:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre welcome. If you ever need to talk, Im here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 05:42:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw that sounds so sweet. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 05:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry. I wholeheartedly wish it was better for you. My emotions are volatile and prone to anxiety and depression as well. You deserve better than this. Sending you love and support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 05:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds promising! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I am so sorry to everyone that I may have hurt. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 05:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To any of my acquaintances, particularly at school, I am so sorry. I know how horrible I am when I enter an anxious or depressive state. When you touch my shoulder gently to ask if I am okay, I jerk away as if it burns my skin. I wish I could be responsive, answer your questions, plaster on a smile and tell you that yes, Im fine. But all I can do is shake and shuffle away like a useless child, trying not to let hot tears splash on the linoleum floor. I wish I could open up to you, tell you not to think of me. Its not your fault that Im like this. You dont need to check on me, its my fault. The last thing I want is to be a burden to another person.

And if you dont care, if you dont even remember the times that I have cried quietly due to a drop in performance or a poor grade, then I am glad. I dont want to be in anyones thoughts when they should be living their own happy life.

Im so sorry. I wish I didnt exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 05:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depression is mainly centered around a sense of self-worthlessness for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 05:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel this way about exams, its terrible ): Im so sorry to hear that you are experiencing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 03:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats amazing. Thank you for sharing your story with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 03:49:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 03:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for this comprehensive message. Ill take your advice into account! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 02:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you did. Be proud of yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 02:10:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, that could be a good idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 02:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im glad that youre still alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 02:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would it be through messaging? If so, I think you can set up a chat with many people here on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:45:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 16F and have never done any of those things either. Youre not alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry. I know its hard, but try to ignore them. Theyre just being rude behind the cover of a screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you think so? I agree. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:24:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this. I needed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Were in the exact same situation. No one thinks anything of it because "all teenagers are angsty". It sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever it feels right! Maybe not the first date, but after a few if the chemistry is there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the matter? Why dont you like this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:21:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I care. Im here for you, even if its just online. I wish I could give you a warm, reassuring hug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes, I didnt consider that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:58:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you think that will help, do so. One step at a time. Youre doing fine, and you can make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes lower subscribers is better because it gets more exposure - it can get lost in a sea of other posts in high subscriber subreddits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope someone feels this way about me someday - this is the loveliest letter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The trauma of your death will be so overwhelming either way. Please try to keep pushing the date back week by week until you feel that there is something to live for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:53:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A blender is usually for liquids (smoothies etc) whilst food processor is for more tough objects like vegetables and dough. However, they are usually interchangeable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. Ill try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not sure, but it might be
The kings seek/initiate wars of passionate glory. 
I think that is wrong though, but cupidi can only be genitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:45:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have any context for the second one? Would "Bella" most likely pertain to war or beauty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. The leader made many bridges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, exactly the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can. One tiny step at a time. Forgive your failures, be kind to yourself. Another step. Youll get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:37:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its hard, because we all live busy lives with so many acquaintances. Of course, we want to look out for them all, but the majority slip through the cracks because we would burn out if we had to do that. If you want the support of your friends, be vocal about it! Try to talk to someone you trust. Im sure that they will be happy to help, and apologetic that they didnt see your suffering earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear that, but your response was amazing! Heres to multilingual people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:31:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah okay. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not hopeless, youre getting there. Be kind to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am as well. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry. I wish it was better for you. If you ever need someone to talk to, dont hesitate to message me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. Sometimes Im unaware of a whether they are trying to be a troll or not, though, and I wouldnt want to offend anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just mean that I envision a future with a romantic partner and love sappy romance novels and movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, completely. I dont take naps, but every morning I feel sick with stress Im not even sure why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I hope so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean "being a romantic"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know. The last thing I want to do is hurt or drain someone. Thats why I think I should never get into a relationship - Im drained even being by myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree. It just drains and hurts them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:15:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, I really needed this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats amazing! Im so happy for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like I will also hurt people. Thats why I feel like I should never get involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:13:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the reassurance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this. Your story means a lot to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear about that. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 16:20:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for your uplifting message. It has brightened my mood a little! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 16:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is perfectly accurate for me as well. Its so frustrating to see disappointing percentages after nights of hard work and tears, when your whole life is that grade, and the next, and the next. I barely know what to do anymore. I dont think I can survive the next couple of years, and I dont know if I even want to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 16:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww of course! If you ever need to talk again, dont hesitate to message me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 16:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont say that. You do deserve to eat. You are evidently a gorgeous human with a kind and caring heart and a conscientious mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 16:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt slowness often indicative of pain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 16:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reading! Whether it be novels, the news, or just magazine clippings, this always inspires me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 16:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so adorable. You sound perfect for each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, you are too kind to me. I really needed this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:59:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my - what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:58:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know the feeling - youre not alone, keep persevering  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But Id feel so terrible, even if someone did, for some reason, love me. I would only be a burden for them, draining happiness.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this! Really made my day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I was more intelligent. Im 16, and I already have no life ahead of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can you be loved with a mental illness? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont have much time to think of anything beyond schoolwork and the stress that comes along with it, but when I do, I often let my mind wander to a perfect, but likely impossible, future. I think I am a romantic, though I dont show that side of myself very often. Im constantly swamped with academic-related tasks and lengthy to-do lists, so thats all people see of me. I am a teenager, and do not want to find someone now - I only know approximately three boys in total, as my school is not co-ed. I barely know how to act around them, even though I dont "like them".

But then my thoughts darken. Why would anyone ever choose to love me? I dont think that it will ever happen. If I was someone else, I wouldnt even choose to be friends with me. Besides the fact that I have anxiety, mild depression and suicidal ideation, I am constantly stressed and appear downtrodden all day. Im probably a pain to be around due to my overall gloomy mood (though I can be cheerful at times). I think that I will have little hope for a romantic relationship later in life. This just adds to the many factors that are contributing to my already-crumbling future, as I have posted about before.

Though, now that I think of it, I would be happy to be in a relationship with someone who is suffering mental issues. But maybe this is only because I battle with them myself.

Sorry for this sappy, stupid post. I just wanted to collect my thoughts somewhere. Thank you for reading, if you made it this far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so adorable and sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! Id love to talk every now and then throughout the day. Im Elsa, 16F, and I love reading, writing, ancient history, linguistics (particularly French and Latin focused), and art journaling. If you want to be friends, please feel free to message me! If not, dont feel at all obligated. Have a lovely day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:22:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not alone, I swing from emotion to emotion wildly as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so sweet and romantic. I wish someone could feel this way about me someday. Im sure that he/she doesnt hate you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 14:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like even if it was a 50% acceptance rate, I wouldnt get in. Its particularly sad because I wish fervently to go somewhere like Oxford or UC Berkeley, but thats impossible. Sorry for ranting to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw that sucks. Youre not an awful person though, try to be kind to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats on your mind? Im sorry that you feel this way. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the exact same way. I really hate myself. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my goodness. Im so sorry to hear this story. I really wish I could help more, but I dont even know what to say. I wish I could be there to give you a hug and tell you that youre doing well. Keep persevering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Completely. I used to be intelligent, happy, and getting perfect grades. Now I am a sobbing wreck in all three departments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like the messaging is unnecessary. Its a more clunky system, and chats are easier! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You will find somebody! You are clearly sweet and caring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes - maybe making it casual like that will help. If youre feeling nervous, maybe text her in advance letting her know that you want to talk about something on that day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not awful. You deserve happiness. I know how hard it can get, but you have to keep persevering and try to be kind to yourself. One step at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on how comfortable you are with that person. Do you feel apprehension about approaching them in person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 12:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want desperately to go to university, but Ill never be accepted. Its useless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, Ill message you momentarily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can tell that you are loveable. You are evidently introspective and conscientious, as you have opened up and thought about your life. You are worthy of someone lovely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A romantic companion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so sorry to hear this. Whats on your mind? What is making you feel this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. I agree with this completely - I wish the world was not like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:04:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats going on in your life that makes it not worth living? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 07:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 06:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you - Ill try! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:56:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, exactly. Its so comforting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:50:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so strangely calming. I think Im going to set a date soon as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont. You deserve life. You are capable of making an amazing future for yourself.
Dont be angry with yourself because you cant go through with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But isnt everyone suffering? Everyone is stressed, so it seems. And theyre doing fine without therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forced to go to therapy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 03:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My parents are making me go to therapy again. Why does this have to happen? Everyone is stressed in high school. Im not special, and I dont deserve a moment of special treatment. Im just an annoying, anxious high school student with low intelligence and no future. Everyone is nervous about exams et cetera. I dont want this, or let alone deserve it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 03:45:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so glad I can help. Sending lots of love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 01:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds lovely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:55:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know ): its always in the back of my mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats amazing! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not at all. I dont even know who I am when I snap at people, and I feel so disgusting afterwards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like you are excusing internally rude behaviour. Dont look down on others. If intelligence is the one factor that dictates your relationships, then work on making others gradually smarter by not "dumbing yourself down" for them, and expanding their knowledge in a conscientious way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That all sounds good. I agree with this person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:23:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God, they sound like horrible people to judge you so ruthlessly at a moments notice. Try your best to ignore them, and keep working hard and developing skills. Take your time, and youll get there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow! That is incredible! Im so happy for you. What kind of business is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep the idea of suicide as the last resort in your mind. This is actually quite comforting for me, as I know its always an option. Once that is accepted, focus on taking it one step at a time, trying to appreciate each small thing in life. One day, hour, and moment at a time. Stay busy, see friends, remain clean and tidy, and be as kind as you can to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 00:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think approaching a girl randomly is the best - I would become uncomfortable. Try to go places where people who are passionate about similar things are, if that makes sense. For example, maybe if you love to read, meet someone in a bookshop. However, most things will work as long as you are friendly and caring, which you seem to be. Take it slowly, but be there for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 23:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre sweet looking! You have a handsome appearance with a friendly, warm smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 23:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the response! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:50:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre absolutely not a waste of time. You dont need to feel obligated to help anyone - you deserve to be cared for, and you dont need to repay anyone for that. I can tell that you are a lovely person, even though you are suffering right now.

Its quite late here in Australia, so Im going to try to get some sleep, but please message me if you would like to and well talk soon. If not, thats fine - just know Im always here if you need someone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:48:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, maybe ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. Im 16 and feel the exact same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how easy it is to be so harsh with yourself for mistakes and lack of strength, but please try to forgive yourself. You are facing a precipice of adversity due to your mental health, and you are evidently trying your best. Every step is progress, and you were so close. All you have to do is try again next time. Even if it doesnt work, youre getting there. You are a good person. You can make it through this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are you unsubscribing? Sometimes it is good to escape the negativity - you dont want to burden yourself with the pain of others. Whats on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But youve had times where you are okay. Theoretically, you can then have good times again. Take it one step at a time, and allow yourself to breathe. Try to forgive yourself for shortcomings, and keep progressing until you reach another stretch of happiness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree that some people may do this with selfish intentions, but the problem is that those people make anyone who comments encouraging messages seem insincere. Things can be misconstrued through text, so try not to write someone off just because theyre attempting to be caring. Many people dont know what to say, but dont want anyone to get hurt or die.

I agree with your overall point though - thank you for sharing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can do it. One step at a time. Breathe. Youll make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont. I dont want you to die. You deserve to live. You are a good person who has he ability to create a lovely existence despite the storm you are in now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I hope you do as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:11:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 12:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre very attractive! You have a great facial structure, and you look sweet and approachable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I hope youre okay too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know exactly what you mean ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wishing I could die </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds so nice. Waking up early, making a cup of tea, and sitting down to write some goodbye notes. Just simple and sweet, to let them know I care, and give them and myself some closure. Then clean my room spotless - wipe down the windows and rearrange my books, launder my sheets and remake the bed. Put some flowers in a vase, spray some perfume, leave. Take a bus to the cliffs with whirling winds, climb over the simple wooden fence, and stand on the mossy sandstone slabs looking at the ocean. Then, Id jump, let my body go limp, and end this life. Hit the waves and sink so that Im wiped clean from the world. It sounds so nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does this happen to anyone else? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 08:43:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Out of the blue, I feel rushes of stress and anxiety, and whilst I can sometimes attribute it to a certain cause, there are many times where I am a left worrying about nothing. Its so frustrating. Why am I so anxious? What am I anxious about??

Does this happen to anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not so good. Depression is creeping back in along with anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 09:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know what you mean ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 08:28:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No - everything right now is academic focused. My dreams include attending an excellent university and achieving a linguistics-related career, but that all seems impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 06:51:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nothing I do is ever enough, is it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 05:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I study every day for hours on end with extracurriculars almost every day. Well, she studies every day, has more extracurriculars, and has a job on top of that.

I read a book in French to try to extend my learning. Well, they went on exchange to France for months and will probably come back fluent.

Im in the accelerated math class and suffer extreme anxiety as I try to learn the content, and then end up with mediocre grades. Well, she is in the accelerated class, has perfect grades, and aces hundreds of math competitions.

I play sports and have been chosen for certain specialised programs. Well, they have been noticed by universities and are on a fast track route to an amazing future.

I labour relentlessly over playing the clarinet and learning music theory. Well, they are all playing at a professional level and have been sent on a worldwide tour to showcase their talent.

And these are only a few examples. I really am never enough. Im such a useless idiot. I deserve to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 23:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think so! You look a little sad in these pictures, but overall your facial structure, eyes, and hair is lovely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 23:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for the advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 07:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry. I wish I could be there to give you a big hug. If you ever need someone to talk to, please feel free to message me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 05:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 23:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. All of my friends are so beautiful, and then there is me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 22:57:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for all of the advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sending you the warmest online hug possible. Lots of love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please try to reconsider. We all love you and care about you. We dont want you to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im totally paranoid about that. Eek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its gradual, so you dont really notice it yourself. I began to feel more aware of my own body, I suppose, particularly in certain outfits, which made me quite nervous and self-conscious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are absolutely handsome and adorable! You look sweet and friendly, with lovely hair and a warm smile. Have some confidence! Love, Elsa (16F) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:37:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not a waste of space. You deserve to live. I know that because first of all, you are conscientious and introspective enough to say all of this. Secondly, you have survived to this point despite all these horrible things that are happening to you. You are stronger than you think.

I have to go to sleep now, but please message me if you ever need to talk more. Sending love your way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "The Legend of Ashitaka" by Joe Hisaishi and the New Japan Philharmonic. It somehow grounds me, even though it is quite sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant stand exams. My instant reaction is to cry out of frustration during tests, which is so frivolous and annoying. It looks like Im just doing it for sympathy, but in reality I cant help it. I end up with shaking hands and a wet test paper and less time to answer the questions. I really hate myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:29:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never thought Id see this conversation play out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:27:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats on your mind? Please talk to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I relate to that statement completely. Im not sure what to do. Just know that you arent alone - sending you a warm hug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not alone. Im here for you. Try to explain, if you can, why you think that you hate yourself. Im listening, and I care about you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do you make each day tolerable? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you have any, please leave tips in the comments pertaining to making unbearable days more tolerable when depression, anxiety and suicidal ideation are making you feel hopeless. I know that very few people will see this post or care - but its worth a shot. Thank you for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 15:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 06:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look nice! You have a lovely facial structure and good hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 11:44:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont commit suicide. And please dont do it by train, because you can hurt others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 11:01:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 10:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 08:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you are very attractive. You look kind and welcoming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 22:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not at all odd-looking! You have a good facial structure, nice hair, and the glasses complement you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 22:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this. I never would have thought of it like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 22:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its good to recognise that you are overthinking. Try to have faith in yourself - Im sure they arent as judgemental as you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 22:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 22:35:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for the encouragement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 22:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. Ill try!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 13:30:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck! Try to have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 12:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much, as always. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I often hate the success of others </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 10:59:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a person who experiences toxics envious thoughts constantly. I feel so absolutely disappointed in myself for almost wanting others to fail. Even my closest friend, for example - she recently got a job, something that I am too anxious and lacking in self-confidence to do. I felt completely nauseous upon hearing the news, even though I know I should be happy for her. Of course, I still smile and congratulate her, but inside I am crumbling.

Another example is end-of-year academic awards. I performed poorly this year, something that crushes me every day to think about, and I know that I wont get an award. I find myself filled with contempt for the intelligent individuals who are receiving top marks, which also manifests in more self-hatred.

What is wrong with me? Why am I like this? I am a horrible person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 09:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel exactly the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 07:00:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 06:00:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 05:52:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like youre going well so far. I know, it can be so difficult to get things done with anxious thoughts running through your head, but you need to forgive yourself. Keep trying your best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 05:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre very attractive - you should be confident! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 05:02:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much. Ill definitely message you if I ever need to talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 05:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. Whats on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 04:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats so good. Im proud of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 04:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ): this is so true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why am I so useless. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 04:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the past few days, I have been completely exhausted. I feel lightheaded and sick constantly, and even the smallest chores make me tired. I dont know whether it is anxiety, PMS, or something else.. What is wrong with me? Why am I so useless? I cant even deal with the tiniest things going wrong. Ill never make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 04:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear that. I wish I could be there to give you a warm hug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Wishing for a job" update </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 04:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend got the job. I feel sick to my stomach - Im so worthless, I could never do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 04:00:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please take care of yourself. I hope that youre doing okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 03:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats on your mind?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 00:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would I lie? What benefit could it possibly give me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 23:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would you say that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 23:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have nice, clear skin, a great hairstyle, lovely eyes, and an adorable smile. Dont doubt yourself!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 23:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your hair is a lovely colour, and your glasses look adorable. You have a great smile. Overall, you have a kind and friendly appearance! Most definitely not ugly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 23:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw, thats okay! Have a lovely day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 23:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have a unique look, but that makes you very handsome! Your hair looks nice, and you have clear skin. You look sweet and approachable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 23:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry. What has been happening recently? ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 13:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look great! You have absolutely nothing to worry about. Have a lovely day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 07:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im going into 10th grade soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 07:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made it through another school term, thank goodness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 07:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats definitely progress! Thats amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 07:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre so pretty and friendly in appearance! Dont doubt yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 07:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how hard it is to be productive or even get out of bed when youre feeling so stuck. You need to forgive yourself for this. Youre trying your best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 06:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont be sorry. You are trying your best. You are a sweet and conscientious person. You are enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 06:32:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear this - I wish that it was better for you. Yes, I definitely do. Even if theyre subdued, Ive always got those thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 01:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 01:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations. Im so happy for you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 00:54:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have confidence in yourself - you are handsome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 00:47:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so sorry to hear this. You are evidently an absolutely lovely, caring person with a kind heart, and you dont deserve this treatment. I wish I could be there to hug you and help, but all I can do is say that Im here for you. If you ever need someone to talk to, Im here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 00:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not useless. You are worth it. You deserve a life of love and happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 00:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats okay! Be confident in yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 00:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Thats a great idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 00:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 9  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wishing for a job </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 23:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am 16, and I have never had, or applied to, a job before. I hate myself because of it, particularly due to the fact that the majority of my peers are getting jobs. My friend and I were worried about this, and now I find out that she is going to a job interview this afternoon.

How do people like her do it? She saw what she wanted and just did it. Shes on her way to a job. Shes proactive, while I sit frantically worrying.

The main reason that I havent applied is stress, but more specifically the fact that I cannot comprehend why a company would ever want to hire me.I am not intellectually advanced, or particularly cheerful, or pretty, or experienced at all. I wouldnt even hire myself. How will I ever get a job, let alone a successful career in the future?

Also, whilst I desperately want a job, I am afraid of how it will interfere with my school life. I already spend the remainder of my evening after extracurriculars studying and working, and my weekends are filled with sports, music practice, article writing and even more work. I dont want my grades to decline even more.

Apologies for this lengthy vent. I just needed to write down my coagulated thoughts and try to make sense of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 23:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not ugly. You are handsome and friendly-looking! Try not to doubt yourself. 
Love, Elsa (16F) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 15:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Completely relate to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 14:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because I can see that you are caring and conscientious. You are interacting with others. You are admitting your feelings, even though theyre difficult. You are a sensitive and lovely person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 14:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not over. You still have a life in front of you. You deserve love and happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 14:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there anything I can do to help you? Im so sorry that you are feeling this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 14:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, whats on your mind? Im here for you if you ever want to talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 13:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're absolutely lovely looking! Don't doubt yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 13:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 13:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not useless. You are capable, conscientious and strong. Keep persevering - youre not a disappointment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 12:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You deserve to be here. I know youre struggling right now, but just take it one day at a time. Forgive yourself if you cant get up. Be proud of yourself if you can. Keep going, step by step. Im here if you want to chat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 12:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make a plan. Make some goals. Set them out set by step, and remind yourself why you need to achieve them. Get rid of toxic relationships, quite things that you dont like. Take it one step at the time. What do you want to change in your life right now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 12:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear this. I hope that youre doing okay. Please know that Im here to support you - if you ever would like someone to chat with, Im here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 08:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, thank you so much for that. I watched it all the way through, and I truly feel so much better. I struggle with the same issues, and your articulate and uplifting video is amazing. Thank you again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 08:30:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sounds a bit like hypochondria. ): I hope youre doing okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 06:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 06:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I care. Im here for you if you need to talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 02:35:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do not kill yourself. You deserve an amazing, happy life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 02:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry youre feeling this way. Do you want to talk? Whats on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 02:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, thanks for letting me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 02:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh that sounds terrible ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 01:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should! You are an amazing student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 01:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 01:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw. ): Try to use it to motivate you in the future! You can do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 01:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know exactly how you feel - my happiness is completely weighted upon my grades as well. Dont be so harsh on yourself though - you obviously are a hardworking, conscientious student who deserves that kindness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 01:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww yay! Keep it up, youre doing so well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 00:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry that youre feeling this way. If it is any consolation at all, Im here if you want to vent or talk to someone. Sending you lots of love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 00:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, thank you for the honesty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 00:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 00:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much, you are very kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 00:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please, please keep persevering. I know its difficult, but youre going to make it. You deserve a happy life. In a few years, you will be so glad that you decided to keep going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much, as always. You are incredibly supportive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for this burst of positivity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:30:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry that you are feeling this way, and I know exactly what you mean - I have experienced it before. If you ever need someone to talk to if you feel rejected, Im here for you. I believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I relate to this so much, and I want you to know that you are not alone. Just the fact that you are writing this post shows how caring and conscientious you are - you are obviously a lovely friend. Stay strong, and be kind to yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know exactly what youre talking about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry that youve gone through all of this. I cant even imagine the pain you must be feeling now. All I can offer is someone to talk to, if you ever need it - my messages are always open. Sending you warmth and love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. I know that it isnt much, but Im here for you and I care about you. If you ever feel lonely and want to chat, dont hesitate to message me. Sending love and support your way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear that. ): But please, be kind to yourself. Be proud of yourself for getting out of bed in the morning, and forgive yourself if you cant. Youre going through a lot right now, and you can use the love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For calming down, write out your thoughts whenever you need to, confide in someone else, and go to the bathroom to take deep breaths if you feel yourself start to panic. I know how difficult it can be to struggle with anxiety and panic attacks at school, but youre going to be okay. Stay strong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do your homework the day you receive it, write revision notes and summaries regularly, knock out assignments immediately, make flash cards, utilise spare time you have in the day and in class, do homework at lunch if needed, stick to your schedule, have a nice warm drink in a thermos to make class more bearable, wake up early to prevent rushing stress, use a planner, take care of your hygiene, be kind to yourself, sleep well, and be proud of yourself. You deserve an amazing year, and I know that you are capable of it. Sending you the best of luck, and love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A lengthy slew of toxic thoughts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 14:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I absolutely hate myself. Even looking back at Reddit posts that I wrote a couple of days ago makes me want to kill myself. Im such a repulsive waste of life - unproductive, worthless, and with a future thats crumbling before it has even begun. And what I hate so vehemently is the fact that Im feeling this way on spring break. How can I possibly survive another semester, let alone 3 more years, of high school?

I want another life so badly. I want to be an individual with a future, bright and shiny, lying ahead of them. I want desperately to be accepted into an incredible university. I want to be intelligent and knowledgeable and interesting. I want to pursue and find success in an amazing career in the realm of linguistics. But it crushes me as I wake up each day to know that none of this will ever happen. I am utterly useless, and unable to get through a day without raging, debilitating thoughts. How could a person that cant even make it through one day possible succeed in life? The answer is, I obviously wont.

And I hate how I feel the need to burden other people with this. I am so whiny, so disgustingly insensitive. I know that I will probably delete this later, but I just needed to say it somewhere. I am so sorry for being alive. Such a worthless human being doesnt deserve to breathe. I cant stand myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 13:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take care of yourself today. Do little things to make your day better, even if they seem trivial - brush your teeth well, wear comfortable clothes, take breaks in the bathroom to take a deep breath and relax for a moment. Youre going to make it. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 13:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you doing okay? Whats on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 13:15:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I completely am. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 13:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please try not to be so harsh on yourself. Here are a couple things to note:

 You are human, and it is impossible to be productive and hardworking for every minute of every day. Sometimes we just don't have that strength, and that is okay.
 A few missed homework assignments will not ruin your life. I feel similarly when I dont receive the grades I want - my anxieties snowball and become debilitating. But there are always ways around things, and there is no cookie-cutter path in life.

I am so sorry to hear about your family situation. I wish that it was better for you. I know that my words probably wont be of much help, but just know that I am here for you. I believe in you - keep persevering, and please be kind to yourself. Sending love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 13:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so sorry that you had to go through that. Just know that it is absolutely not your fault. You deserve better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 12:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for this uplifting story, I really needed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 12:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you absolutely do not deserve pain. what is on your mind currently that is making you feel this way? I'm here for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 12:19:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how you feel ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 12:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i know, it can be so difficult. but its going to make you a stronger and more interesting person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 11:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how difficult it is to see other people who look happy. but here are a couple things to remember:
1. they might not actually be so cheerful. some people are better at concealing their emotions.
2. you are capable of being happy. i know its difficult right now, but it will get better. you have control - keep making little changes until youre satisfied. i believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 11:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats amazing. i hope that life treats you well now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 11:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aw, im so glad i could help. if you ever need to chat, i'm here supporting you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 10:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey, I know it doesnt seem like it now, but one day youre going to have someone who adores to you, who cares for you and makes you smile. youre going to be okay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 10:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its absolutely okay that you werent as productive or outgoing as you would have liked to be today. you are trying your best. you are fighting through a lot of difficult things right now, so give yourself a break and dont be so harsh. you deserve it. i believe in you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 10:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im so happy for you!! congratulations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 10:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> as long as youre trying, thats all that counts. you are obviously a strong, hardworking person with drive and determination. I believe in you. keep going despite the tribulations - youre going to make it. message me if you need to talk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please please reconsider. you deserve a beautiful life. you are a lovely person. you can make changes and get out of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whats the matter?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 08:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel that all the time, youre not alone.  but youll make it through, and youll find someone who adores you and cares deeply about you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 08:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for this - i really needed it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 08:57:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good luck with your studying. if you need to talk, im here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 08:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the point of life is getting better and changing. even if youre not happy with where youre at now, you can keep tailoring your life until youre satisfied. for now, find comfort in the small things - cups of tea, dew-covered morning grass, warm hugs. you can do it. keep persevering  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 08:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its absolutely fine to let out your feelings. its absolutely fine to be unhappy with your writing - all first drafts are a work in progress. dont be so harsh with yourself - you are a lovely, hardworking person. i know you can do it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 08:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hi there - im so sorry that you feel this way. if you ever are in need of someone to talk to, im here  i support you. keep trying your best and persevering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 08:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> youre welcome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 07:25:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love hearing stories like this that arent the typical high school to uni experience. it fills me with hope that there isnt just one neat path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 07:23:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alright, best of luck - im here if you ever want to chat more. youre not forgettable, just know that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 07:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> every single person makes mistakes. every person has hurt others. what makes you stand out is the fact that you are remorseful - you are obviously sweet and caring and conscious of your actions. you absolutely deserve to live a happy life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 07:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it isnt exactly normal to feel this way in the severity that you do, but youre not alone. youre going to make it through this. were all here to support you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 07:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please dont say that. its not necessarily going to cycle back - it may get better in ways you cant even imagine now. give yourself more than two weeks. keep prolonging the date, keep looking forward to something that keeps you going. I believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel exactly the same way. just know, youre not alone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you are not whiny. you deserve to hold on. I am here for you and I believe in you. keep persevering, because you never know when life will change. its going to be okay. dont give up yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:48:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hi wilbur. I am so sorry to hear that you have suffered so much. you dont deserve it at all - you deserve an amazing life. I know its not much, but I'm here for you if you ever need to chat. I love you and I dont want you to go. stay strong - I believe in you. love, elsa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:46:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am absolutely sure that someone will adore you for the person that you are. I can tell that you are sweet, caring, and introspective, which are all lovely qualities. you deserve an amazing, loving relationship, and I can assure you that it will come soon. stay strong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so, so sorry that youre going through this. I wish I could help more, but all I can say is that I'm glad youre still alive. keep persevering. I'm here if you ever need to chat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know its not much, but I'm here if you ever need someone to talk to. sending love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please dont go. people will be hurt - you are a lovely person who deserves an equally lovely life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you are not worthless. you are an incredibly introspective and conscientious person with a caring heart, and you deserve a lovely life. stay strong. I'm here for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 06:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my less-than-perfect grades and the impossibility of ever attending an excellent university or obtaining a career that I want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 05:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go to the bathroom and take care of yourself. Drink water, splash your face, clean the wounds. Take a deep breath. Then just try to make it through the rest of the day, and head home immediately to reset and reassess. Im here for you if you need to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 05:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 05:06:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But think about all the amazing things youll miss out on that you cant even see yet. I believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 04:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im here if you need support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 04:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please, please keep persevering. I know its difficult, but youre going to make it. You deserve a happy life. In a few years, you will be so glad that you decided to keep going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 04:06:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw okay. Good luck. Stay safe, take care of yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 02:38:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can already tell that you are a lovely, caring person, because you are considering organ donation. Please just keep persevering - you are worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 02:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not a burden. You deserve an incredible, fulfilling life. Dont lose hope yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 02:36:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for the advice! Im actually not a procrastinator - I get things done right away so that my anxiety doesnt take over. My issue is perfectionism - I never know when to stop working on an essay or studying etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 02:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God, that sounds terrible. Im so sorry that you had to suffer that - you deserve a better life. I know Im not much help, but Im here for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 02:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You deserve an amazing, happy life. For now, focus on the small, good things about life - cups of tea, puppies, a warm sweater, spring, novels, kind people. Youre going to make it, and youre going to be so happy that you didnt kill yourself when you were 17. You are completely capable. If you need to chat, Im here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for taking the time to comment again, it means a lot to me. Thats very reassuring. How did the application process work for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry to hear that. Isolation doesnt really bother me, as Im quite introverted anyway and I dont know why anyone would want to be my friend. My largest issue is the stress and anxiety and worthlessness that comes with grades, which I know will just get more difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you can try some online chats or therapy messaging? Ive heard that there are a few free services like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. I wish you didnt have to suffer this situation, you deserve better. However, if youre ever feeling a bit lonely or aimless, Im here to chat. I hope youre doing okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am in a similar situation. I know it doesnt help much, but Im happy to be your friend, even though its only online. Sending love and support your way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same way. Im so sorry ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is university better than high school? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been feeling slightly better about life recently... a little excited for the future, which is rare. The anxiety still lurks in my mind, however - will university be what I hope it is?

I currently hate high school. I know that the stress factor wont disappear in university, but is it any more enjoyable? I want some of the aspects of university so badly - studying for hours in a library, walking through the campus in autumn, attending captivating lectures. But is it worth it to look forward to it so fervently? I feel like I will be disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry that this is happening to you. Sending love - if you ever need to talk, Im here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 01:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You dont either. Sending you love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 00:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please reconsider. You deserve an amazing happy life. I believe in you. I can message you in half an hour, if you would like to talk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 00:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear that youre feeling this way. If it helps at all, just know Im here for you and I believe in you. Message me if you ever need to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 23:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, absolutely! Out of the blue I feel sudden excitement and anticipation for the future, but then I start thinking again and my mind is filled with depression/anxiety again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 23:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course. I hope that it turns out to be a positive one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 23:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much - youre so kind. Its the same for you - if you ever need to talk, Im here for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 23:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep trying. Im sure they still care about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 15:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant explain how much this message means to me. Thank you. Thank you for taking the time to write it.

Im willing to put in the work to get where I want to be in the future - I will definitely try some of the language-related extension ideas that you have provided.

Thank you again, for the encouragement and new perspective. It has made me feel so much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 15:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, yay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 15:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know exactly how you feel. Im so sorry to hear about the job - keep persevering. Youll make it, i believe in you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 15:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats exactly how I feel. I dont know what to do either. |: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 15:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont go. Hold on a little longer. You are an asset to the world, and we need you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 15:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know its not much, but I can be your friend, even if its only online. I believe in you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 14:55:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so, so sorry. It hurts to feel forgotten, but youll get through it. I know it doesnt help much, but Im here for you if you ever want to talk. Sending you lots of love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 14:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I feel exactly this way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 14:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please keep persevering. I know it seems hopeless right now, but there are always other ways. I believe in you. I know that you can make an amazing life for yourself despite your grades. You deserve it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 14:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I relate so much to this ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 14:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is not your fault. I am so sorry to hear about that situation - just know you did nothing wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 10:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how that feels - I have anxiety and mild depression as well. But just know, youre not a burden. Im happy to support you and listen to whatever it is you want to say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 10:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so, so sorry to hear about your situation. I wish it was better for you - I wish I could help more, for now, all I can offer is my support. If you want to chat, Im here for you. (16F)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 10:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry that you feel this way. Im here for you, sending love and support. If you ever need to chat, let me know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 10:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, Im here if you need to talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 10:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 10:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 16  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:24:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im here if you want to chat anytime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not a monster. You deserve all the love in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know. But I assure you, you are so loving and caring - there will be someone for you. You just have to find them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can, try to find a job. It doesnt have to be amazing, just something to start. Keep saving up until you can get a better job with the experience youve got. You can do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:19:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not ugly. I know that you are not. Dont beat yourself up for how you perceive yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed completely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:17:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so sweet and romantic. I know exactly how you feel. I guarantee that you will find an amazing person, just from the personality that I can see you have through this comment. You are obviously caring and conscientious and kind, and someone will adore you and want to spend every day with you. Dont lose hope  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have a job currently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:56:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not your fault and you must not be guilty for it. I believe in you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont apologise, its okay. Im sure theres something you want to accomplish. You need to find something that makes you excited to live, even if its just a flower or a genre of book or anything to get you by. Create your perfect life. Whats stopping you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a bit younger than you, but I still relate completely. I cant really offer advice, but just know that Im here for you. Keep trying, keep making changes until your happy. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please reconsider. You deserve an amazing life. Please, please keep persevering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please, please dont kill yourself. I know it seems absolutely hopeless, but you have a whole life in front of you. If you hate your own life so much, start over. Save up, move away, build a life that youd rather have. I believe in you - I have full faith in you. You can do this. You can persevere. Im here if you need to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:42:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not alone. I care about you, and Im here for you. Message me if you want to chat or if you feel lonely - youre going to be okay, and I believe in you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay, keep pushing forward! Youre doing great so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you have to accept that these things are part of your life instead of fighting against that and wish it wasnt true. These things have shaped who you are today, even though they were absolutely terrible. Youre caring and intelligent and worthy of an amazing life- youve just got to try to move on. Youre doing well so far  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:29:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please, please dont cut. Your body is beautiful. Just think of everything you can do with it - breathe, hold hands with someone, run. You deserve to take care of yourself. You are strong, and I believe in you. Keep persevering, and be kind to yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. If you ever need to talk, Im happy to chat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:21:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel exactly the same way - particularly with the grades and everything. I wish I could just get a clean slate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:17:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not sick of you - Im here for you. Im so sorry that you are feeling this way. Youre going to be alright, and I believe in you. Im here if you ever need to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww this is so cute!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So sorry to hear that youre feeling this way. Im happy to talk whenever you need it. Dont feel guilty for not being productive - we all have those days, and depressive thoughts make it very difficult. Sending love your way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, Im here if you ever want to chat. It is amazing that you are able to open up like that - I hope youre doing okay. Wishing you all the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I care about how you feel. I relate to this so much. Hope youre doing okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 06:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please stay strong. I know its not much, but Im here if you need to talk to someone. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 06:43:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its going to be alright. Even though everything seems hopeless, things will turn around for you. Dont worry about the rejection, it happens to everyone - you will be absolutely adored by someone in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 06:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry to hear that youre feeling that way. ): If you ever want to talk, Im here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You deserve to live. You are obviously caring and conscientious and intelligent. You are an asset to the world and would be missed. Please try to keep persevering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please keep persevering. I believe in you. You are strong and intelligent and loving, and you can do it. I know its not much, but Im here if you ever want to talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry ): I hope you can feel better soon. If you ever need to talk, Im here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry youre feeling this way. I hope it gets better for you soon. Im here for you if you want to talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:35:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. My depression does manifest in my expression though - Im bad at hiding my feelings, which is something I hate about myself. When it kicks in, I get quiet and distant, and inside my head is in turmoil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would absolutely love that too. That would be a dream. But for now, we just have to get through it on our own. I believe in you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not alone. I know its just online, but Id love to be your friend. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 05:00:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats terrible. ): If you really cant stay home, try to make it through the school day - itll be over be for you know it. Then go home and let yourself relax. You deserve it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please please dont end your life. You deserve love and happiness. You are an amazing person. I know it doesnt help very much, but Im here for you if you ever want to chat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont say that. You deserve an amazing life of happiness. Are there any changes you could make to improve your life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Give yourself a day off. Relax, reset, take care. Clean your room, pamper yourself, read a book. Care for your mental health. Im so sorry that youre having a bad day ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:41:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre human, and youre allowed to make mistakes. You are not worthless or a failure. I know its not much consolation, but Im here for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can do it! Stay strong and try your best. You are completely capable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not stupid. Your feelings are valid. Are you doing okay? Im here to talk if you would like to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:38:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats terrible. You dont deserve it at all ): I hope that all of your future dreams come true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are you passionate about? What does your perfect life look like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much. It means a lot to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww ): I know how that feels, but youve got to keep going. You can do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont. I believe in you. You can make it through this!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know its not much, but just know Im here for you and I support you. If you need to talk, Im here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? Wow. Thats encouraging to know, thank you.
I tried the school councillor but she didnt help at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:59:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry. I know it seems hopeless right now, but I have full faith in you. Im here if you ever need to talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope youre doing okay. Im here if you ever need to chat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:48:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know. And my peers come over trying to help and I cant even breathe so I just act really cold and dont say anything. I feel so bad, I obviously am being so rude, but i cant help it. It just makes me hate myself more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I relate to that completely. I hope you have an amazing future  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:43:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont give up! Hold onto that passion and keep writing, even if it sucks. Youll find yourself again. Dont give up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please hold onto that will to live and keep going. I believe in you. Make changes in your life, make yourself happy. You are capable of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:41:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You absolutely deserve to post here. Any kind of pain is valid, and were here to help. Sending love your way - message me if you ever need to chat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay, good luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for the advice. Im in Australia actually - we have curriculum based tests, the HSC and IB. I just feel like if they see a bad mark theyll reject me point blank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw thats good. Keep it up, you can do it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dreams for the future. Even when they seem impossible, I cant bring myself to kill my self because I want so desperately to go to university and have an amazing job in linguistics. I know it will never happen, but it keeps me going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww, Im sorry. ): but Im here if you ever need to chat more. Wishing you all the best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know exactly how you feel. Its so terrifying - life petrifies me. But well make it though. Keep persevering. I have full faith in you. Sending love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:21:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sounds like a terrible situation. I know it seems like everything in life is working against you, but I have full faith in you. You can get back on track. Keep applying for jobs until you get an okay one. Work as hard as you can, save up, get a better job. When you can, move to the UK and pursue your dream.
Youre not a failure. Youre so strong for getting this far already, and you are obviously very hardworking. You can do this. I believe in you! Sending so much love. 
Dont lose hope yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For any specific reason?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was crying while reading this post - I am so, so sorry that you are feeling this way. I wish I could make it better - I wish I could be there and bake you a lovely cake and give you a hug and support. Unfortunate, all I can offer is someone to talk to if you want it. Im here for you. Sending love your way, I hope that you feel it soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you should do number 2, if its safe and will make you happier. You can always make changes to improve your life later! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sounds terrible. Im so sorry that youre feeling this way. I wish I could make it better for you - if it helps at all, Im here if you ever need to chat. Sending love and support your way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So sorry youre feeling this way. We all believe in you - stay strong and persevere. I have full faith in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need advice/experience stories: university </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 03:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (16F) University is my impossible dream. I want so desperately to be accepted somewhere excellent, like Oxford University. I want to be able to stroll around a beautiful campus on an overcast day, and to study for hours in an old library, and to excel in my courses, engaged in interesting content. I want to continue learning about linguistics, studying English, French, and Latin as well as etymology and writing.

But I still have another two years of school, and this dream seems absolutely unachievable. How could I get into university? Why would I ever be chosen over another person... a brighter, happier, more promising and intelligent person who has received awards and perfect grades? The answer is, I wouldnt. I spend all my life studying and working, but with no results except anxiety, depression and suicidal ideation. Anything below 100% feels like failure. 

Last week, I received my first C. It feels like someone has torn my heart out with bare hands and left me empty and useless. I know that this is probably trivial in comparison to others lives, but to me, it feels like the world is crumbling. I have absolutely no shot at furthering my education. I dont even deserve to, due to my utter lack of intelligence. I cant even explain how much I hate myself. I have no future.

If you have a few moments and you have gone to university... could you please explain to me what the admission process was like? From my standpoint, it seems like a hopeless, impossible gauntlet for a worthless student like me. I cant imagine ever being admitted, and it crushes me to think about every day. Im so sorry for being unbearably whiny and dramatic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 02:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I relate to this completely ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 02:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how youre feeling, and Im so sorry that it has to be like this. If you ever need to talk, Im here. Sending as much love as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 02:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 01:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, i relate to this completely. Im not mapping out a detailed plan and circling a date on my calendar, Im just thinking about it and casually considering it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 01:27:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem. Im here if you ever need to talk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 01:08:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe youre not giving yourself enough credit for how amazing you are. Youve obviously gotten her attention, and you deserve that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 01:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just be yourself - be kind and loving and cheerful. Talk to people, or message them online to start. Just from this, I can see how sweet and caring and interesting you are. Im sure that you will find some good friends soon. Wishing you all the best  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 01:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope youre doing okay. There is nothing wrong with letting your thoughts out - its good. Youre going to get through this, I have full faith in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 01:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont say she is better than you in every way. Youre probably different, but with your own lovely idiosyncrasies that make you interesting. She wouldnt show interest in you for nothing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:56:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you think she might lose interest in you? You seem like an interesting person who is worth getting to know - dont doubt yourself. Even if she isnt the perfect person for you, there will be others. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not pathetic or weak for needing support . That is completely valid and normal. We are all here for you, and youre not a burden at all. If you died, no one would breathe a sigh of relief. Everyone you know would long for you to be back, wondering what they did wrong to make you go. Please keep persevering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take a deep breath, its going to be okay. You need to slowly start finding things in life that make it worth living - the cool autumn breeze, your pet, the light shining through windows in the afternoon. Accumulate these little things so that you can start to feel more grounded again. If you need a change of pace, consider a short vacation if you can. I believe in you - you can most definitely do this and make it through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. ): But we have to keep pushing through until life turns around, because you never know whats coming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone will love you completely, and you deserve that. You seem introspective and conscientious just from this message, and Im sure that girl saw something in you. Dont lose hope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are you struggling with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same way - Im 16. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please, please keep considering. Your children will be irreparably broken, and your husband will miss you too much to bear. Please try to keep persevering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:17:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw, no problem. I hope we both feel better soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds great! Keep it up. (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much! I hope that you feel better soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id be happy to send you a message whenever I can - I cant guarantee every day, but we could talk whenever you wanted to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how you feel. ): its terrible when it feels like nothing works to get you out of a rut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:12:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its going to be okay. 
1. Acne doesnt define you, and you cant really control it, so lets put that aside for now.
2. Im so sorry to hear about your OCD - are you speaking to professionals about it? Im sure youre trying your best. (:
3. Volunteering is a great way to spend your time! Is it making you any happier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, thats a good start. Could you schedule anything nice in the next few days to look forward to before your doctors appointment?

The lifeline is always a good backup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. I think they just want the best because theyre worried that we arent happy, but it just comes across in a horrible way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you need a change of pace. Is there any opportunity to go on vacation soon? If not, find a friend whos vivacious and cheerful and just explore the city with them. Maybe their demeanour will inspire you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes exactly. I feel like this invalidates my depression so people think Im fine ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Use this post to vent if you need to. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not sure if this will help anyone, but if you need to vent, feel welcome to do so in a comment on this post. I am happy to just listen to whats going on in your life, or give advice if you want it. I am currently experiencing anxiety, mild depression and suicidal ideation.

Youre going to be okay, and I have faith in you. Lets get though this together! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not hopeless. You are so strong for making it so far, and you can continue to persevere. I believe in you fully - you are amazing and capable. Here if you need to talk more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:26:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum always gets mad at me for being sad or in a bad mood and that makes me feel like sobbing in a tiny ball. I wish people would understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry that you feel this way. I am stricken with fear about the IB (though I may take the HSC, which is equally terrifying). Im just too unintelligent to make it through high school - Im so weak. I think I have to die before Year 11 begins. ): sorry for the vent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:22:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay good for you! Keep it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:21:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats exactly what I was wondering. I hope it does get easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:21:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can do it. Stay strong, and take it one minute at a time. Best of luck!
Message me if you need to vent more. (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre going to do an amazing job. I believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best of luck!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please try not to harm yourself. Think about all the beautiful aspects of your body, and what it can do. All the organs and systems working together in intricate, complex ways to allow you to live. Take care of yourself. 

In terms of the depression - I am so sorry that youre feeling that way. All you can do is keep going and try to make little positive changes along the way. I believe in you. Lots of love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 15:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, feel that way almost every day. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just keep pushing through. Count down the days, work hard, and give yourself time to relax. Youre so close - think about how youll feel when youre done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good for you. Keep up the amazing work!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres nothing you can do now to reverse it, so I think you should just continue being friendly to those people, even if theyre mean to you. Smile at them and move on. Stay close to the friend who remained loyal to you. I believe in you - keep up the good work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats going on in your life that makes you feel this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same way. Its totally exhausting and draining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please try to hold on. You can turn your life around, make it new and exciting. Sending you love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem. Im here if you need to talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You still ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:25:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, completely relate to this. I cant stand school anymore - Im not going to make it through the next couple of years. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, me too ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 14:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here for you if you want to talk. Sending you lots of love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same way. I am so scared to finish high school because I have no future ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same way. Unfortunately, life really sucks sometimes, but youve just got to keep pushing through and persevering until it gets better. If you want to talk, Im here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So sorry to hear youre feeling this way. Im here if you need to talk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone makes mistakes. What you did was wrong, but you should be forgiven for it. Continuously apologise to her, and just stay quiet until it blows over. I promise that youll get through this. Just be kind and unobtrusive until people forget! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:48:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. Keep it up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try your best to open up to your friend a little to make you feel better. How long until you meet up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no! Should you go to the doctor soon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So sorry to hear that youre feeling this way. If it helps at all, you can message me anytime and just talk. Sending you lots of love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds like a good plan. And youre welcome - Im happy to talk to you for as long as you need! Is there anything else on your mind you want to vent about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats a good idea. You can do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:31:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear about this situation. Wishing him all the best. If you need to talk, Im here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it will make you feel better, allow yourself a day off to recharge. Your mental health is important! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem (: Im here if you ever need to chat more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats incredible! I used to play guitar - now I play the clarinet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats amazing! Do you play any instruments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I havent experienced a situation as severe as yours, but I do have anxiety, depression and suicidal ideation. I think that you should try to get a job. Start with something simple and build up from there. Keep going until you find one you love. Connect with new friends and allow yourself to be social again. Sending lots of love your way, i believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:15:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think thats pretty normal. Keep distracting yourself until you feel better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What did your father want you to be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think thats what makes a person interesting - so many of my friends just want to follow their parents life paths, but I think its more gratifying to choose your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its alright. Take a deep breath. It sounds like you may just be experiencing anxiety or a panic attack, though Im no expert  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, try to avoid alcohol. Do you like to read? Listen to music? Draw? Just anything to keep your mind occupied. I dont mind continuing to talk to you either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:09:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem. Youre welcome to message me if you need anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. Wishing you all the best  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can do it. Just 3 more hours. Is there something fun youd like to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:07:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello - so sorry to hear youre feeling this way. Im a 16 year old girl whos been struggling with anxiety/depression/suicidal ideation for a while now, and what your describing could be actually anxiety, or just stress due to a specific situation. Have you been nervous about something recently? Sending lots of love your way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay so I kind of involuntarily started fresh. My dads job sent my family back to Australia (where I was born), and this actually kickstarted my anxiety / depression / suicidal ideation because I hate my school. Its different for everyone though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keeping up with trends does not make you interesting. You are interesting because you are different! I would much rather be friends with you than the people you are describing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear that you are feeling this way. If its any consolation, I believe in you - Im here if you want to talk. Sending lots of love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know that you can persevere and make it through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 12:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats not true at all. Your mental health is incredibly important, and its not just that you cant take stress. You are going through a lot, but youre doing well so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw, why? Im sure youll do great! It will be so interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow thats great! What course are you taking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:47:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats so great though. One step at a time (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, sure.  coming from someone with mild depression, i know how hard it is for you. To beat depression temporarily and avoid procrastination, you have to force yourself to just start. Start planning, start studying, start that essay. Once you get past that, it wont be as difficult. Keep going for as long as you can bear it, and then give yourself a nice break. Walk around, eat, drink. Repeat until the work is done. I believe in you completely!
Is there anything else specific that youre having trouble with rn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are some good things about your life right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course I can. Sorry I was gone for a few minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:38:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sure you can. Keep persevering and youll make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. Take care of yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so glad. It makes me feel better too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:21:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats on your mind now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. Leave the lifeline as a last resort, but dont dismiss it completely. For now, why dont you try switching up your environment? Go on a walk, take a bus somewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you talking to me or the person who posted? Its only 7pm here in Australia. (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Occupy yourself with something you like, just for the next couple hours. Maybe cleaning, or TV, or a good book. Go outside and enjoy the fresh air. Anything to get your mind off of suicide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not disturbed. I have depression, anxiety, and suicidal ideation as well- you are just going through a difficult time. But you will get though it. Im here if you want to vent to someone. Lots of love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe call someone and get them to come over. Try to just have fun with them and let the feelings pass for now. If you dont want to do that, Im here for you. Feel welcome to vent to me, I dont mind. Sending you lots of love and support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If its any comfort, know that we are all here for yo. You arent alone in your pain - we can all share the burden. Just take it one step at a time for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 11:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know exactly how you feel. I hate when people without depression/anxiety/suicidal ideation try to help and then blame us for the way we feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it isnt a joke - what youre feeling is very real and valid. I think that you need to get out of your own head. Can you go to a park, or a little forest near you? Just to clear your head and give yourself a break. For me, it really helps to get out of a toxic environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:58:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To cope in the mornings, I force myself to get up and take a nice shower. I try to clear my mind of thoughts and just enjoy the hot water. Next, I open my blinds and windows and let the fresh air in while I tidy my room. These little things make me feel like I have a grip on life, so maybe theyll help you too. Wishing you all the best  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre going to be alright. I believe in you! Would you like tips on dealing with depression or procrastination? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you think that you feel this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats not the answer. First of all, youre not going to die alone. There will be someone who will absolutely adore you for just being you, and when you find that person, you will be so glad that you did not kill your self. Secondly, I know that depression sucks. Its a dark cloud over my life too. But it can be dealt with, and it can get better. You can do this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:46:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know exactly how you feel. It really sucks. Just know that you will get through it - I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sending love and support your way  Im here if you want to chat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:41:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its alright. Whats the matter? Take a deep breath.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please please dont kill yourself. Im here for you to talk to if you want. Sending you so much love - youll get through this. You can do it. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry that you are feeling this way. I cant really offer advice, but if it helps, Im here for you. Please message me if you want to talk. Sending you so much love and support  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:30:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id love to chat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey. I feel the exact same way, particularly about the struggles with school and grades. Im so sorry to hear that youre feeling this way - sending you love and support. If you want to chat, Im here for you. Im a 16 year old girl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre going to be loved. Just the fact that you are conscientious and introspective proves that. Looks honestly do not matter, and Im sure that you are handsome anyway. Dont lose hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id love to chat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:25:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a failure at 15 and I dont even know what to do. Just keep persevering, I believe in you. Sending so much love your way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:23:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear that youre feeling this way. If it helps at all, Im here for you. Message me if you ever want to talk. Sending you so much love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the matter? Im here for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont kill yourself. I know that everything  seems pointless and useless right now, but it will get better. Prolong that date. Keep prolonging it until you dont have to anymore because you love your life. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear youre feeling this way. Could you make any dramatic changes that might make you feel like you have a promising new life? I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good for you. Keep it up, we all believe in you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope youre doing okay. You deserve the world - keep persevering through your thoughts and feelings and someday things will turn around for you. If you want to talk, Im here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:17:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its going to be okay. Do you want to vent to someone? If so, Im here. Sending you so much love and support.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:17:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its going to be alright. Take a deep breath. If it helps at all, Im here for you. Im happy to talk with you - you can vent whenever you would like to.  Lots of love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 10:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm, maybe. Hope youre doing okay though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, definitely. A lot of the time, however, the anxiety continues out of the shower. I just hate how Im alone with my thoughts during that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, good luck. Feel welcome to message me if you ever need to talk more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When is your next vacation? Make sure that school is not overwhelming your health. Give yourself at least an hour each day to just unwind and regain control. I believe in you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear that you are feeling this way. If it helps at all, Im here if you want to vent to someone. Wishing you all the best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Read. Pick up some autobiographies from photographers and read articles online until you feel fired up and ready to pursue your dreams with all of your might. I believe in you- you are amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, its difficult. Maybe try writing it all out first and get that burden off of your mind. You can still keep some things private, but it may be good to let your loved ones know whats happening generally so that they can better support you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I feel exactly that way. But I guess all we can do it take what we have and make the best of it. You can only control some things in life, and the rest you just have to let go of. Im heading to a lesson right now, but Ill message you later. Stay strong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its okay. I know it seems impossible right now, but its very good to just vent as you are doing. This might not help you, but try it if you would like to: grab a pen and write down everything thats bothering you. Just let your mind flow onto the paper. Then go back through and cross off things that you cant control, and make plans on how to work on the other stuff. Youre going to be okay. Youre not dumb or a burden to your family. You are amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre not just a temporary person. Why dont you grab hold of your life and make the most of it? Use your passions and talents and build a future. You can do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I am as well. If i told my mum what I think about, shed burst into tears, Im sure. Just know that youre going to be okay and theres nothing wrong with feeling the way that you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel exactly the same way, but just remember that you will make it though this. I believe in you. Hold onto what you have left of your motivation and push through college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel basically the exact same way. With everything I do I feel like theres no point because Ill be gone soon, hopefully. But yes, I still have the burning wish to do well and go to university and get an excellent job. But all those things just seem so out of reach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, just start with the little things. Try to appreciate the smallest elements of your life that make you happy, like a sunny day or your pet. Youre going to make it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know exactly what this is, but I know that 1) its not your fault and 2) you must not beat yourself up about it. You are doing your best and you deserve the world. Stay strong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel exactly the same way. I used to be a perfect student - stressed, but not in a debilitating way. Now I have to rock myself in a ball until I stop crying after studying for hours every night. I can barely function during the school year, and I dont know what Ill do for the next two years.

Was there something In particular that you think caused the dip in your school performance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sure you are loved, even if you dont realise it. What would make you happiest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much again for taking the time out of your day to leave such supportive messages. This means the world to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it helps at all, Id love to be your friend, even though its just online. Im happy to hear you vent. I dont mind at all. If you do want to talk, Im here. 
Lots of love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What would your perfect life look like, if you could start over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:12:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely lean into the side of yourself that wants to get help. Hold onto that hope to pull yourself out of this and make an amazing life for yourself. You deserve it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont kill yourself. You will be missed. Here for you if you want to chat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:06:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont really know what to say other than Im here for you. Make a list of what your perfect life would look like, and spend every day trying to work towards that. Sending love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with the going back to the old me. I cant even remember what it was like to be truly happy. I mean, I laugh from time to time but besides that Im just a depressed, anxious mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it helps at all, Im here to talk. Id love to be your friend, even if its just online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sure you do. You are amazing. sending love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its going to be okay. Depression is not your fault, and you are more than that. You will make it through this. Is there anything specific going on thats making you feel this way, or is it just general?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant deal with school anymore either, but please stay. Please dont kill yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What would your perfect life look like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. I feel like Im my happy moments invalidate my depression. Maybe I dont even have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the exact same way. Here if you need to talk. ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wishing you all the best - I hope youre okay. Suicide isnt the best option - you never know when your dream partner or dream job may come up. Life is unexpected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay! Keep it up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. Ill die if someone finds it. No one really knows about my suicidal thoughts, depression, and anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id love to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the matter?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope youre doing okay. Im here if you need to talk. I feel the same way - the thought of actually killing myself fills me with such anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Language related subjects are my favourite - latin, french, english. My hobbies are watercolouring and writing articles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope youre doing okay sending lots of love - im here if you want to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 15 as well, and I am also absolutely miserable. I dont think its necessarily normal, but its not uncommon. Im here for you if you need to talk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. They dont know I am suicidal and depressed and they just think Im being rude. I hate myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this moving post. It brought me to tears </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry to hear that. Just remember, some people suck and its not your fault. Just move on and try your best  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. I cry about everything and care too much about everything, which leaves me burnt out and drained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry to hear this. Sending you as much love as possible  Im here if you need to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:34:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, completely. I can be laughing with my family one minute, and the next im swallowed by suicidal ideation and depression and anxiety. I barely know what to do because my moments of happiness make it seem like Im okay, so no one takes notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel exactly the same. I am in Year 10, and whenever I see the year 12 girls glowing with pride and excitement I feel sick. I know Ill never be like that, Ill be an unintelligent failure all my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry. You seem like such a kind person, I hate to hear that you are a loner. I would love to be your friend. Dont give up yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:27:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah same. Just looking into 11th and 12th grade makes me feel sick with stress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What grade are you in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. Ill try. I just feel like the future that I want beyond high school is impossible because of my grades, anxiety and perfectionism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i know exactly how you feel. its such a debilitating system - every mistake i make feels like a stab in the chest. 
sending you love and support - im here if you would like to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hope youre doing okay. sending you lots of love  im here if you need to talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im sure that you are so much more than you say. you are amazing and you deserve a lovely life. here to talk if you need me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:12:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> take a hot shower. enjoy the stream of water and the smell of soap. put on some freshly laundered clothes and clean and cook until your house is nice again. then do something you love. i guarantee that you will feel at least a little better. here to talk if you need it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hope youre doing okay. sending you lots of love  if you need to talk, im here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 01:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow. this story is jarring, but so moving. I cried a little reading it. thank you for sharing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 01:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure people need you. Don't lose hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 01:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what was your experience with the people around you as you tried to escape rock bottom? I used to be a top student but now I'm nothing, and I'm terrified about the judgements of others now that I have gotten a C in a class. I won't get an award at the end of the year as everyone expects, and every time I think about that I feel sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 01:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for this story, its very moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> every now and then I feel a tiny burst of motivation. a tiny glimmer of excitement about the future. it helps me despite my debilitating fear of failure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow. thank you for this moving account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is very important and effective, I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 23:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im so sorry about that. i hope we can both feel better soon ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 23:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. ill try! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 23:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you. ill try my best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 23:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> really? okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Such a Failure in School </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 16:40:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a high school student who needs to die. I just received my first C grade and I can feel my future crumbling already. Ill obviously never make it through the next few years, and university / a career seem absolutely unattainable. I have no idea what to do. I hate myself so much, and my evident stupidity. Ill never be anything. I am so swallowed by this anxiety, depression, and self-hatred. I wish that I was as successful and intelligent as my peers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 16:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> keep persevering. i believe in you fully! things will change and get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 16:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so glad youre still here. sending lots of love  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 16:32:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im in high school and i want to die. i just received my first C grade and i can feel my future crumbing already. ill never make it through the next few years, and university / a career seem unreachable, impossible. i have no idea what to do. i hate myself so much, and i hate my obvious stupidity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 16:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to put it simply, I am just too terrified to do so. my grades in school, if anywhere short of perfection, make me want to die. this week, I received my first C and I can feel my future crumbling in my palms. I do not know what to do with myself, and my anxiety is heightened with mild depression. I dont know what to do. Ill never make it through high school alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 14:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this story touched me. hope youre doing okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 14:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this story really touched me. hope youre doing okay now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 08:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much for the kind words, they made my day.
I just feel like I don't deserve to live anymore - I got my first C on an in-class essay assignment this week. I dont even know what to do with myself. I am clearly so unintelligent and university seems impossible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 08:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know that no one will really see this, but I need to let my thoughts go somewhere. this week, I got a C on an in-class essay assignment. my suicidal thoughts skyrocketed immediately. I have never received a mark so low, and it has sent me into a spiral. 
I have no control of myself anymore. my whole future is ruined, and all the good marks I have received before are useless now. I will never be able to get an academic award at the end of the year. I have no chance of making it into university or getting a career that I want. I hate myself so much, I wish I could just die. I do not deserve to live anymore. I am so angry and disappointed with myself and my obvious lack of intelligence. 
apologies for the extreme negativity everyone. I'm so sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 23:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate myself every day because of my grades. Anything below perfection leave me as a disappointed, crying mess. I don't know if I'll survive the workload until Year 12, because I feel like I am working at capacity now. I write down suicidal, anxiety-driven thoughts regularly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 23:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Writing everything on my mind down definitely helps. I grab a smooth black pen and a notebook and write until my wrist is sore and my mind is somewhat more clear. I hate looking back on all the pages, though; they are filled with anger and anxiety and disappointment. Wishing you all the best if you are also struggling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>