<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5897</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 17:30:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt drop out, but took some time off after a suicide attempt landed me in the hospital. Taking that time was really helpful and allowed me to return a better student, although at the time it was a really difficult decision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-13 22:46:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely doable, just be prepared for lots of mosquitoes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 21:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You definitely should!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 20:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I love this, do you have a website?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 15:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watermelon snow!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-26 16:40:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its most likely x-inactivation and not truly a chimera 
https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/X-inactivation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-12 17:25:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0165017399000600 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-12 17:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/article-abstract/577290 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-12 14:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi neuroscience student here! Swearing is typically more preserved in people with speech problems and even brain injury patients because its controlled by a different part of your brain than normal speech. Language is usually localized to the left hemisphere of the brain but emotional language (i.e. swearing) is controlled by both the left and the right hemispheres  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-06 06:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks I will do that! I definitely understand, I wasnt expecting so much medical advice I just wanted to include a picture of the bruise so people understood why I needed to stop the spiro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 20:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I have already seen a doctor and am waiting back on test results. My post was intended more to ask advice for alternative options for hormonal acne that arent medicine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 16:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still waiting to hear back from my doc but there isnt really any other explanation I can think of!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 07:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From left to right: sunflowers, ageratum, zinnias, more zinnias. All are annuals  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 05:08:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work with kids in a mental health facility (they get really violent, Ive already gotten punched in the head a few times) so Im really hoping they are on good behavior until I get this sorted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 05:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! This is all really great info that Ill definitely look into. Im already on a grain free diet due to other reasons (I get migraines) and I also dont eat dairy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 04:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It did at first but now just feels like a normal bruise (hurts when I press on it but otherwise doesnt bother me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 04:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sadly I cant do hormonal birth control due to migraine with aura :( but I appreciate the advise!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 04:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do have a lot of other small bruises but they werent as concerning as this giant one and another nasty one I had on my arm last week. But I hope youre right and its nothing to worry about!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 04:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant be on hormonal birth control because I have migraine with aura, and I have hormonal acne. So what would be a better option?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 02:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah normally I wouldnt be too concerned but I had a really nasty similar bruise on my arm for no reason last week. Also everyone doing the ropes course had bruising but nothing near this bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 02:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I take iron supplements every day already  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 01:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used differin in the past with no real improvement but thanks for the advice!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 01:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesnt really hurt now thankfully, thanks for the positive vibes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 01:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It wasnt a very significant trauma at all, hence why I wanted to get it checked out. I was climbing at a ropes course thing at work (I work with kids) and basically using my legs to pull myself into a higher beam (sloth style is the best way to describe it) if that makes sense at all hahahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 01:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I had no idea! Ive been taking the curcumin for well over a year with no issues, is it possible the Spironolactone increased that effect of the curcumin? Thanks so much for your insight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 22:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah based on my research it seems pretty rare that it would cause clotting issues but abnormal bruising is listed as a rare/serious side effect. Im not taking any other meds but I do take some supplements (methylfolate, iron, magnesium, curcumin, vitamin d)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 22:01:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got blood tests to check my platelet levels, waiting to hear back  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 22:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not entirely sure yet but it seems like a logical possibility that it could be the spiro causing the bruising. I got blood tests to check my platelet levels and electrolytes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 21:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I had a blood test yesterday to check my platelet levels... but this is kinda scaring me away from the med route  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Skin Concern] Spironolactone was really helping my acne but now I have this crazy bruising so I had to stop taking it :( Any advice as to alternatives? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 21:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sunflowers, ageratum, and zinnias (plus my pups) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 21:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-11 20:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boy Fish (aptly named) does the same thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 23:50:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For my job since Im working with children, a lot of whom have been sex trafficked in the past, they have pretty intense background checks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 22:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If she is actively suicidal she doesnt have to consent to be admitted to a psych hospital. Ive been involuntarily committed after a suicide attempt in Colorado and the hospital definitely helped me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 22:42:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old is your sister?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 22:40:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just started a job in the mental health care field, and one of the questions for the physical was if I had been hospitalized for psychiatric issues. Because my answer was yes (not like you can lie about that they can always figure it out) my physical was put on hold and I needed a note from my primary care doc saying I was mentally fit for the job. So it was a little more complicated and took longer than it would have had I not been bipolar, but it wasnt a huge issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 22:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> White Noise by Don Delillo. I read it in high school and it was my first exposure to the concept of hyper reality, it changed the way I viewed the world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 16:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I throw them on the wheel, kinda like Im making a bud vase but then round out the top making a small hole. I also leave the bottoms thick so I can carve it to a rounded shape. When I take it off the wheel I use my thumb to press in one side to make the bowl part. When its leather hard I use a needle tool to make the holes, and carve it to the desired shape. 

When it comes to glazing I use a very small amount of wax on all of the holes, and then after glazing I scrape any glaze that gets into the holes out with a needle tool. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 12:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the advice! I definitely get nauseous from it, any food youve found particularly good to take it with?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-24 14:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did try it but I havent been taking it consistently, kinda hard since I work second shift and right before bed is the time I usually struggle with the urges. I didnt really notice a difference on the days I took it but its hard to say. Let me know how it goes for you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-18 15:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is amazing! Youre very talented, I want to hear your other songs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-18 06:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Artemis Fowl series if you like young adult fiction  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-17 16:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say the same thing basically, I just finished it 2 days ago  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-16 16:27:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like making personalized mugs, you can carve their name or whatever you want into it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-16 16:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pygmy by Chuck Palahnuik. Only reason I read the whole thing was that it was one of 3 books I brought on a wilderness backpacking trip and I had already read the other 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-14 00:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its to prevent them from doing inappropriate things under the blankets mostly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-14 00:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Alchemist by Paulo Coelho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-13 15:48:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahaha I love this, I currently work in a residential program for girls 14-18 with complex trauma (basically a longer term mental hospital with more lax rules) and some of them flip shit almost daily over not being allowed to take blankets into common areas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-10 06:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/vaporwaveaesthetics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 22:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zen and the art of motorcycle maintenance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-05 14:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get a reusable water bottle! The earth will thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-18 16:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> N-acetylcysteine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-18 15:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi guys! I was just reading an article that mentioned this study: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/m/pubmed/27007062/ that found evidence that NAC supplements may lessen excoriation behaviors. Have any of you tried it? What were your experiences? Thank you, much love to you all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-05 00:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom read How to Win Friends and Influence People to me when I was young and I think it was pretty formative for me, although I havent re-read it as an adult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-23 21:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely, I feel like my memory has declined so much since I started having real episodes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-22 16:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is more likely to be x inactivation rather than chimerism: 
https://simple.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mosaic_(genetics) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-22 15:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its more likely to be an example of x inactivation, but if its a male cat definitely could be a chimera!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-22 15:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its called a mosaic in genetics, caused by a few different things but most commonly X chromosome inactivation. It is often easily observable in cats cats because genes determining fur color are on the X chromosome. This only happens to females because of the pattern of X chromosome silencing. When the cat is developing the stem cells independently silence one X chromosome, resulting in some cells expressing the fathers and some expressing the mothers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-22 01:51:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently discovered this Spotify feature and really love it, but it uses the same songs in the same order for me, do you know if theres a way to change that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-17 21:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An Unquiet Mind by Kay Redfield Jamison (shes bipolar), and The Quiet Room by Lori Schiller (she has schizoaffective disorder) they are both autobiographical and a really good insight into what the authors went through  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-13 05:40:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basically anything by Philip k dick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 19:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make sure you have good shoes and good running form, shin splints can really sneak up on you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 17:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think all of my friends know. Ive found that being super honest with everyone helps so much when Im going through a rough time since I dont feel like I have to try to hide it as much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 17:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What sort of relationship do you want with him moving forward? Do you just want some sort of closure or do you want him to be a part of your life? I think you should go into it knowing your ideal for the situation, and remain mentally prepared for his reactions. Has he ever apologized to you for the way he treated you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 03:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so cool, also just checked out your post history and damn dude you are an incredible artist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 03:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that place, went for spring break my senior year of college  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 03:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait is this coyote gulch?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 03:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Genetic genie can use your raw data from 23 and me  to find snps and guides you through what they mean. That being said, take everything you see with a grain of salt because there isnt exact consensus on what every snp means in terms of protein function  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 03:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah Im not sure why deplin is such a high dose, it seems like for most people its excessive even with a mthfr mutation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 23:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely dont get your hopes up too much, I had a similar situation where I thought folate was going to be the miracle cure but its way more complicated than that. I would suggest checking out Dr Ben Lynch (he has a ton of information on supplementation for specific SNPs - http://mthfr.net/ ). Also if your doc puts you on deplin definitely monitor how you handle it because it was initially way too much for me and caused some negative side effects. Ive found that over the counter supplements with folinate actually work better than an already methylated form for me, but everyone is different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 14:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What lucky workmates!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-20 20:39:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weekend trips are fun cause theres not as much stress if you forget something! 

Water purification
water bottles/hydration bladder 
Headlamp (check batteries before you go) 
Sleeping bag/pad
Stove (and fuel) 
Pot
Knife
Food
Shelter (tent/tarp) 
Rain gear 
Warm jacket and pants
Camp shoes (crocs, chacos, etc) 
Dry socks to sleep in 
Hat/gloves if its cold
Bear spray if youre in a bear prone area 
Med kit (with some things to treat cuts and blisters, tweezers, ibuprofen) 

One thing I like to do is wrap duct tape around my water bottle so I always have some handy

Oh and contractor trash bags work great for lining your backpack  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-09 22:39:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Im 22 too! Id suggest monitoring your memory externally somehow, such as journaling or talking to someone close to you because I had no idea how bad it really was until I stopped taking it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-09 18:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depakote made my memory absolutely terrible- to the point where I dont have any memories from when I was on it. I had to stop taking it because my blood levels got too high (even on the lowest dose) and my memory slowly came back. It sucks because I think it has been the most effective med Ive tried but I definitely wouldnt go on it again because of the memory issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Putting the cock in cockatoo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 02:20:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 02:23:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My randomly assigned freshman year roommate and I got along so well that we decided to live together a second year. She helped me through some of the hardest times in my life, and when I was in a mental hospital after a suicide attempt she was one of the few people who visited me despite her insanely busy pre med schedule. Saying goodbye to her was the only time I cried during graduation, and I miss her so much (although we do keep in touch)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-14 04:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sure there are funnier things but the only one that comes to mind currently is going for 4+ mike runs barefoot in a city while singing to myself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Paper snowflakes I made and hung from the kitchen ceiling with fishing line (hard to get a good picture with the lighting/background) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-12 05:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-09 00:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-08 20:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I should clarify- Not my first weld but my first vertical weave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My first time welding vertical, any advice? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-08 20:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-06 04:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try magnesium supplements! Helped me with jaw clenching side effects from various meds and wont hurt anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>