<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7039</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 03:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for clarifying! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 19:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Antoni 3

ETA Antoni is bisexual :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 04:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is breathtaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 20:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad got pulled over while I was in the car as a kid. Later, dad was trying to explain to my mom why he had his licence suspended. He wasnt telling her the whole truth, so I helpfully added that it was because he had been doing 90 in a 50 zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 07:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw Aqua a few weeks ago and they KILLED it. They still have so much energy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 07:58:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, Tali, but thank you. Keelah selai. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 04:05:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go ask in /r/makeupaddiction  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-22 19:45:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My office is doing karaoke - get a couple private rooms at Fantacity :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-22 03:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Im* Phoebe Judge; *this* is Criminal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 16:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heres [one](https://www.akc.org/expert-advice/lifestyle/laser-pointers-more-frustration-than-fun/), but you can just google ocd dogs lasers and look at all the results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 04:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read the original posts, and much later I listened to that episode with my heart in my throat, but I only realized the connection to Reddit after I looked up the case. Fucking heartbreaking when the operator asks the mom if her daughter really killed the kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 21:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm, took our dog to Seattle and stayed at La Quinta. She made herself at home on the couch immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> KJ admiring his freshly dyed hair </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 05:10:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 03:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> B12 from American Dad is iconic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-13 05:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because I stopped working there after two years :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-13 02:01:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to work at a college. This comic hung on my wall for two years. Students almost never noticed, but when they did they usually chuckled nervously... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-06 09:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> British Columbia, Canada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-06 08:25:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. In fact in my experience if someone asks if you smoke, 99% of the time they mean weed, unless they specify cigarettes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-06 08:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Born and raised in BC. My grade 12 English teacher was talking about smoking and asked me if I smoked - I said smoke what? without even thinking.

I dont even smoke anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-02 20:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just bought me and my friend tickets to Aqua and Prozzak! Thank you so much for making this post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 23:37:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its been years since I watched it, and I dont remember anything about the plot, but I still think of John Henry from time to time. What an incredible show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 00:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally just did this ten minutes ago! Cashier said he liked my sweater and I told him it was on sale for $5 at H M. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 04:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 950sqft duplex, 2 bed 1 bath, husband and two 48lb dogs in Vancouver between Riley Park and Sunset.

Moved here last year from a 500sqft 1 bed 1 bath garden suite with husband and no dogs further in east van where the landlord didnt raise our rent for three years  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-28 06:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I worked at a restaurant for a bit. One day I was walking down the back stairs while a coworker was jogging up them with a jug of milk in each hand.

I told him nice jugs

He didnt hear me :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 07:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres a brand new one at Sunset Park (like Prince Edward and 51st) but its not open yet. We take the dogs there every couple days to check since its close to our house. I also emailed them asking when it would be done but no answer yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 22:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Out of curiosity, who is paying best-in-city compensation rates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 09:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both of our dogs are rescues from Thailand and our first one got to see snow for the first time last year here in Canada. She was completely baffled by it! I cant wait for our second dog to see snow this winter :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 04:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have two dogs and we love it. We signed up when there was a promo for a free extra toy in every box, so we get three toys, two treat bags and one special treat every month. The pups love the toys and the treats last until the next box usually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 21:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tablespoon, teaspoon, fork, bread knife, tongs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-18 01:20:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the fuck? He died in a Vancouver hospital in 2015. Im ashamed that I never heard about this. Stick RPG was a truly amazing game.

[Article](https://www.google.ca/amp/s/www.cbc.ca/amp/1.4229140) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 05:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My gym teacher in high school named his son Jack, middle name Daniel (after himself). He didnt appreciate us laughing at that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 06:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is exactly what happened with our dogs! My husband would growl when playing tug with our first dog. Now when she plays tug with our second dog, she growls the whole time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 02:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Used rover, thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 00:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, you're not alone. My husband does this too due to crippling anxiety. It's no fault of the employer - at his last job, they were super understanding and gave him a few days off to take care of himself. It didn't really help. My husband was amazing at his job, everyone loved him - it just comes out of nowhere. I'm usually the one communicating with his managers (which they just love) to let them know that he's having a panic attack, no, he won't be coming in, no, he can't talk to you on the phone, yes, that's fine, you can fire him.

They called nonemergency once to do a welfare check on him. I was grateful for that.

Hope you're doing a bit better today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 23:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seconding this - my husband got his suit for our wedding during a sale at RW Co - jacket, pants and shirt. Cost another ~$30 to have it tailored elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 17:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It can happen if they become too playful I think. It happened in my game, except it was the bride that died at her own wedding. I had my founder bring her back to life, and about ten seconds later my founder died of old age! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-28 08:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anecdotal but my dogs didnt. They both came to Vancouver from Thailand, spent 20+ hours travelling, and had no problem falling asleep when we made it clear that it was bedtime (lights off, in bed, quiet). But dogs generally like to sleep/nap whenever anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-24 01:07:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy SHIT! As a Vancouverite who has followed Jacob Hoggard since he was on Canadian Idol, this is nuts. Cant say I didnt see it coming but wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-23 16:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One of the eggs in the carton was elongated </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-23 16:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-23 06:52:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just finished the finale after binging the series and I gotta say, the last four episodes made me cry. Wasnt expecting it to get so heavy. Cant wait for season two, this totally blew me away. Youve done an amazing job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 22:00:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, in Vancouver the mountains are north. Never had a problem with directions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 19:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Message some dog walkers/sitters on Rover.com and explain your situation; someone with a car might be happy to help for a fee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-14 19:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always ask what are some things I could do in my first couple days that would immediately make a difference? and what is something that a person in this position could do for you specifically that would make your job easier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 20:12:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im pretty sure Mount Pleasant Optometry has a box in the reception area for used prescription glasses. I think they donate them but you can call and ask! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 06:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went to follow you and realized I already do! Theyre so beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-03 22:42:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-30 02:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, and then she killed herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-29 05:10:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I should have added that back-hook is preferred :) he steps over his leash all the time because hes blind in one eye so a hook on the back would help prevent that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-29 04:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have a shampoo from the vet and were working on getting his skin better, but weve only had him for about a week and a half so its slow going :) Ill look into the goats milk stuff though, havent heard of that for dogs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Help] Harness recommendation for large-chested dog with sensitive skin? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-29 03:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our second dog Dozer has a chest girth of 27 and bad skin. Were using an Easy Walk harness right now but it rubs under his armpits and is really irritating the skin there.

Any recommendations for a harness that will fit his chest and also not rub his armpits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-28 02:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im guessing this is in Yaletown?

I also work in Vancouver and my former colleague was high school buddies with the girl Idris Elba is now engaged to. I also served Tom Felton when I was working at the Scotiabank theatre. Its funny how normal it becomes when you live here haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-17 02:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You cant take nursing at Langara if youre not a Canadian citizen or PR. If you are, send an email to advisor@langara.ca for advice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-16 00:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Baby carrots! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-12 23:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one I kept getting was how do you stay organized? Meaning, what apps/software/strategies do you use. Have a list of 3-4 ways you keep track of things - to-do lists, apps, calendars, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 19:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard to answer because my dad swore all the time but I didnt hear my mom swear until I was in my 20s, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 07:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like it might be this guy: Missing Golden Retreiver
https://vancouver.craigslist.ca/van/laf/d/missing-golden-retreiver/6612921446.html

I sent them this post and PMd OP - hope they can be reunited quickly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-06 01:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre thinking of a panel interview (multiple interviewers at once, one interviewee). OP is asking about group interviews (multiple interviewees at once, one or multiple interviewers). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 20:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was pretty neat, and I found the results to be accurate. The problems I ran across were the image of the guy yelling at the other guy who's on his knees crying - the two images I was given were identical as far as I could tell. Also the image of the woman talking to the boy in the baseball cap, both of those were identical I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 19:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres a younger guy at work who says this to me sometimes. One time, an older male coworker was nearby and overheard - he told me you dont have to smile for anybody! haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-02 07:55:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine was upset that I left my contacts in for a one-hour nap. I cant imagine leaving them in overnight, let alone an entire year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-31 00:35:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I physically cringed to this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-18 21:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brown sauce?

...Gravy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-17 09:32:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seconding Charles Mansons Hollywood. Wish I could find another series thats as long, informative and engaging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-17 08:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn, I go there all the time. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 17:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/OldSchoolCool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 02:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My landlord originally only allowed one small dog or cat. I told her the whole reason we were interested in her place was that the ad said it was pet friendly, and we were adopting a medium sized dog. So she raised the size limit. About 7 months later we found out the dog we adopted has a best friend at the shelter, so I asked the landlord to allow us to adopt him as well. Weve been good tenants so she said yes. We basically won the landlord lottery; I cant imagine moving anywhere in the same location, with the same square footage, for the same price point, that would allow two dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lost keys along Prince Edward </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-14 18:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband lost his keys this morning on a bike ride along Prince Edward from 41st to about 14th. We retraced his steps but didnt find them, so if anyone happened to pick them up, please let me know!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 04:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My coworker passed out while walking her beagle. He immediately ran across the street to beg someone at a cafe for food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-11 05:46:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup. I had the exact same face during my wedding. My husbands cousin had the exact same face during her wedding. Like youre sucking on a lemon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-11 03:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And to think they only met at the audition! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 06:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [TIL theres a real life animal called a dugong](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dugong) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 02:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mother in law did this. Luckily it was only a few minutes on low and the cat survived - although my husband swears it came out a few shades lighter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-01 20:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw this exhibit many years ago at the Royal BC Museum in Victoria. Its absolutely worth the trip, its an incredible experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-24 00:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Three so far today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-19 02:09:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry for your loss. I understand what you mean about people asking what's new. One of my managers asked me that a few days after my father in law committed suicide.  

"What's new and exciting?"  

"My father in law killed himself."  

"... Fuck." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-09 06:43:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boring update, I told my husband it was probably an Amway scam and he said we dont have to go after all :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-09 06:43:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, boring update, I told my husband I thought it was an Amway scam and he said we dont have to go after all. Alls well that ends well :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-09 06:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boring update! I gently told my husband I thought it was an Amway recruitment scam and he said we dont have to go. Crisis avoided. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-09 06:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, were not cancelling and also not showing up :) Luckily my husband didnt take much convincing since I was already pretty uncomfortable with the whole thing. This guy can have fun wasting his time waiting for us to show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-08 06:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its good. Switched from Shaw to Teksavvy two years ago, exact same service for half the price. I think theyre a Shaw reseller so they use Shaws lines - if youre on Shaw already its an easy switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-08 01:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha thank you! My dad is a conspiracy theorist so Ive been extremely sceptical my entire life. I will definitely be posting an update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 22:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats disgusting. What is it about MLMs that remove peoples ability to feel shame or realize that harassing someone who is literally working at their job, to try to sell them another job, is not okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 21:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Planning on doing this as well since I have the guys contact info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 21:55:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre absolutely spot on. Nothing about it sounds legit. I really hope I can talk my husband out of it - Im more scared of him going alone and being convinced to sign up and waste money. Hes bad at saying no. Luckily, Im great at saying no! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 20:47:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I searched around and found [this site](http://lallouslab.net/2015/03/25/7-tips-to-help-you-spot-amway-wwdb-recruiters-in-coffeeshops/) which sounds exactly like what happened to my husband (he works at Starbucks). Hopefully if I show this to him, hell agree to cancel the meeting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Am I walking into an MLM trap? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 20:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband met some guy at work. This guy asked my husband to bring me to meet with him and his wife on Tuesday to talk about being an entrepreneur or something. I really dont know. He gave my husband homework which was to talk with me about what wed do if we won $300 million in a lottery. The calendar invite for our meeting is titled follow up on homework.

Im 99% sure this is some kind of scam but I cant find anything about it online. I also told my husband in no uncertain terms that I am not going to be polite about it if it is a scam, and I have no problem literally walking away if I get uncomfortable.  

Anyway, any ideas?

Edit: Thanks yall. Im convinced that its Amway - they met at Starbucks and the meeting is at another Starbucks. Plan A is to explain MLMs to my husband and cancel the meeting, but I also have plan B which is to go with him and call this guy out on his bullshit. Well see what happens!

Update: Anticlimactic. I gently approached my husband saying About this guy were meeting - I did some research and it looks like hes just going to be selling us Amway. My husband said Okay, we dont have to go. And that was that. I dont think Ill notify this guy that were not showing up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-06 21:00:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was it the one at Simply Wellness? I had her before she moved, she was great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-06 03:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries :) enjoy your movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-06 03:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesnt look like its even on that website. Go here and scroll down to the bottom for official prices: [Cineplex website](https://www.cineplex.com/Theatre/cineplex-cinemas-marine-gateway-and-vip) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-06 03:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3D is $16.25, regular is $13.25 - as in, not 3D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-02 02:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like sprinting and then hitting the crouch button to slide? My husband has this glitch, we just tried it and it didnt work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-30 01:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dog ate my passport right before I went on a trip. I was able to get another one in time, but damn was it pricey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-29 19:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> went from links to scramble on the battlefield

*Oh my god.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-27 21:43:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just say great, Ill be there, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-23 03:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the positivity! I keep thinking that Sofie's changed since she got here, they only knew each other for 3 months, etc... But I'm sure you're right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Help] Reintroducing our dog to her best friend from the shelter, whom we are adopting </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-23 02:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We adopted Sofie in July from a shelter in Thailand; we live in Canada on the west coast. Recently we found out that she had a best friend at the shelter, a male named Dozer. Long story short, weve decided to adopt him.

Here are some details:

-	Sofie is almost 4, Dozer is about 2.5
-	Theyre about the same size 
-	Theyre both spayed/neutered
-	Dozer was born blind but had surgery to restore partial vision in one eye
-	They were inseparable for the 3 months Sofie was at the clinic; Dozer has been there almost his whole life

Our question is, how can we safely reintroduce them once he arrives in Canada? I dont want to assume that theyll immediately recognize each other, though it would make it a lot easier if they do.

Like, should we immediately take Dozer to a park upon arrival and have Sofie meet him there first? Or should we have Sofie crated in a closed room and let Dozer explore the house when he arrives? Maybe both? I just want them to be safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-20 05:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Research the CEO so you have an idea of what hes like, how long hes been with the company, his education/job background, etc. Use the info to help you relate to him, dont just bring it up to bring it up. Stuff like Ive read that your vision for this company is x. What could I do in this position to contribute to that vision? Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-19 21:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While youre under 25, you can access youth clinics in Vancouver. They have doctors and counsellors for free. I can recommend Ravensong (on Broadway and Ontario, open late) or the East Van Youth Clinic (Broadway and Commercial). Theres also a few downtown - you can google search Youth Clinics in Vancouver. Theyre a fantastic starting point. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-17 01:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol yeah it was definitely a shock waking up to this thread today. No worries! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-16 19:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahh I see. Not UBC, but good guess. My schools partnership with Queens isnt being advertised yet though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-16 19:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a small one in BC. I sat in on a presentation with a rep and afterwards we chatted alone and he brought up Elon. I argued for a good 10 minutes that prospective students would LOVE to hear about that but he insisted that the higher-ups wont allow it because he dropped out and it would send the wrong message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-16 19:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, Im fully aware that Reddit is public and Im conscious of what I post. Doesnt bother me! I upvoted him :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-16 19:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol good job! Where did you get the Ontario part from? Ive never been there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-16 06:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work for a Canadian college that partners with Queen's and spoke to one of their reps a few weeks ago. Apparently they're not allowed to advertise the fact that Elon attended their school because he didn't actually graduate, and only chose Queen's because the girls were more attractive there than at Waterloo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 07:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol! Thats true. I have no illusions about her name being unique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 07:31:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dogs name is Sofie :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fun fact: Shadow Lake, where the Lodge's lake house is located, is named after Shadow Lake Films, the Vancouver company that produces Riverdale </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 03:29:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being from the area where they film the show, the name jumped out at me immediately! I'm surprised no one else noticed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 08:12:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our dog Sofie has that platypus toy too! https://i.imgur.com/g7SXqW0.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-09 03:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just came here to ask the same thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 01:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a complicated question... Most, if not all of us, learn some French in school, either through immersion (all classes are in French all the time) or as a second-language class (kind of like Spanish classes in the US I imagine). Whether they retain any of what they learn is another matter. I'd bet that the average Canadian knows more French than the average American. However, unless you're in Quebec, French doesn't really come up on a daily basis. Still, I'd guess that the majority of Canadians would at least know the basics like hello, goodbye, thank you, please, etc., and would likely be able to guess French words based on context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-07 17:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got married in Leavenworth last year :) such a beautiful place everywhere you look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 00:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh... that sucks, Im sorry :( best of luck then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-28 23:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a gyno, try to get a referral to Dr Yuen at Crossroads OB/GYN clinic, hes amazing and does a very thorough job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 22:04:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it, we used to have a membership and its our go-to place to bring out-of-towners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-24 20:46:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hah, they approached me at Metrotown when I was around that age. The guy complimented my runners, asked if I played sports (I dont) and tried to transition into how Id be great at doing yard work. I humoured him for a few minutes before telling him my hobbies were playing WoW and sleeping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-23 21:49:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Langaras closed now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-22 21:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazon, seriously. I got one for my wedding for about $15 and it was gorgeous and very well made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-22 01:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For when you're craving New Town but don't want to go all the way to Chinatown. Bao Bakery is *so* good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-21 20:57:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice! Its such a gorgeous place for weddings. Before I started working there I had only been there once, and it was for a wedding reception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-21 17:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its just my iPhone SE, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-21 07:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats dope, I didnt know about that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-21 05:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Foods good, but Im biased because I work there lol. Its a bit overpriced, although not entirely out of place in this city, but I suggest going at least once for a romantic date or to show off the city to some out-of-towners because the view is truly spectacular. Try the sablefish! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-21 02:53:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Inside Seasons in the Park restaurant :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Took this a few days ago from Queen Elizabeth Park </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-21 01:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 08:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah man I live near John Oliver (where they film exterior school shots) and the best Ive gotten is a wave from KJ as he drove away. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-14 00:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Serious question: is it not ok to say your worst boss was the one who broke a bunch of labour laws?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 01:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're friends with Daniel Ingram? That's awesome! I met him once years ago and I was very awkward about it but he was very nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 04:14:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We adopted our dog through Rescue Paws as well and the Rescue Paws family facebook group are all worried sick about her. Cant believe shes gotten that far from Coquitlam. Poor girl :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 03:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/BotsRights  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 23:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just found this out a few weeks ago when I saw the music video for Stayin Alive for the first time. Blew my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-01 04:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Went shopping at Uniqlo yesterday and saw a familiar face on the wall </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-31 23:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 03:10:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At the college I work at, our managers actively encourage us to apply for better roles... I think it depends what department youre applying to; if it has anything to do with your department, or if your supervisor is friends with the hiring manager for the other department, they might find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 17:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats an adorable name! I might start using it as a nickname haha. Her name is Sofie but we call her Birdie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 06:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/g4AAg5H.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 06:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you heard of Rover? You can sign up to offer dog walking/boarding/etc services. My husband started doing it on the side a few days ago, he walks a ladys dog for an hour and makes $25. Maybe itd be good for you to start out with? Ill add that my husband also has big gaps in his resume due to mental health issues and he really enjoys being able to make money dog walking when he feels like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 00:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there a way you can just say you were going through some big changes in your personal life and had to make the difficult decision of getting another job to support yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-25 21:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah thats exactly the point of doing reality checks. Make yourself do the checks frequently in real life, like every couple minutes. Eventually itll be just a habit you do when youre awake. So when youre dreaming, youll automatically do the checks because youll think youre awake, and then youll realize youre dreaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-25 07:44:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To fly during a lucid dream, imagine the ground pulling itself away from your feet instead of yourself lifting off the ground.

To prolong a dream, spin in circles with your arms outstretched.

To meet someone in a lucid dream, imagine that theyre just around the corner and youll walk into them - you cant just will them into existence.

To wake yourself up, focus on wiggling your toes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-25 07:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, theyre called reality checks. Easy ones:

-	read a clock, look away, read it again. In a dream the time will change
-	look at your hands, in a dream you wont have five fingers
-	read some text, look away, read it again; in a dream the words will change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-23 10:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.govolunteer.ca/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-23 04:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Phoneme chart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-19 04:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was the podcast? Ive been looking for something to listen to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-19 02:02:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Were PM_ME_ANIME_THIGHS_1 through 6 taken?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 05:02:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband does this bullshit too! Hell have a movie on Netflix while music is playing while hes playing a video game and talking in Xbox party chat. And he thinks Im the weird one because it physically hurts to have to hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 03:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband did this when his anxiety was at its worst. He had no problem applying and making phone calls but when it came time to leave for the interview hed have a panic attack. Hes doing better now - he just had an interview today actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 07:10:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same, but subtract the kids and add a dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 06:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldnt think so. Theyre really busy and it might just annoy them. Plus, at least in my theatre, we had like 7 managers and only 2 were responsible for hiring so if you got any of the other ones on the phone they wouldnt care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 03:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use In Out, its perfectly fine. Just make sure to declare everything at the border. They can also forward your packages but its a pain in the ass if you need it quickly - paid $50 for a rushed delivery and it went to a distribution centre in San Francisco before getting to my house 3 days after I needed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 23:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in my mid 20s and I cant drive. I walk to work and have always lived near bus and skytrain lines so its never been a problem. My husband drives so we use car shares when we need a vehicle.  

That being said, I want to learn to drive this year so I can be an active participant on long car trips and drive to work in crappy weather. The only thing stopping me is the price of lessons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 08:47:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, there was an individual interview that they called us back for a few days after the group interview. Forgot that part.  

Its definitely a great first job and it has tons of transferable skills: cash register, customer service, food prep, cleaning.  

Some of the group stuff was: 1- partner with the person beside you and tell them a little about yourself such as favourite movie, why you want to work here, etc. Then your partner presents you to the group and vice versa. 2- break into teams of 4-5. As a team discuss and write down your experiences with stuff like excellent customer service, bad service, etc. 3- also as a team, discuss why we call them guests and not customers, list important skills to have for customer service, etc. 4- then one person presents what you discussed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 08:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I worked at one for about half a year. It was extremely busy and popular with tourists for some reason. I did concessions, which was popcorn, soda, nachos, hot dogs, candy, and sometimes promotional stuff like special movie-themed popcorn buckets or kids toys.  

It was really really easy. All the positions were equally easy, from the floor (ripping tickets, cleaning theatres and washrooms, sweeping the floor and changing trash bags), to the frozen yogurt and Starbucks combination stand, to box office (selling tickets), to the hot food stand (burgers, pizza and fries), to the specialty popcorn stand. I was one of the oldest and I was 23. Everyone else was around 16-19 years old, some younger.  

The job itself was super easy to learn. Make popcorn, bag it, serve it. Ring up candy and toys. Put a container of queso cheese in the nacho trays. Memorize the available combos. Id make it fun by trying to memorize huge orders.  

There were some annoying parts. You had to always ask if they had a membership card, and ask if they wanted a combo. This was annoying because someone buying a $5 bag of candy most likely doesnt want a $25 popcorn, drink and candy combo, but you had to suggest it anyway.  

You do have to smile and be nice but at a job like that, you get a lot of guests that you can fuck around with. I had a lot of fun bantering with guests and I even served some famous people. If you have a sour mood no one will like you. Find something that makes the job fun. Luckily I had amazing coworkers and managers.  

Getting the job itself was easy too. There was a group interview, which was all of us seated around a table and broken into groups for team building activities. Really just wanted to see how you functioned in a team. About half of us got hired (6 out of 12 or so). Turnover was high because it was high school kids who needed to focus on school at various points, and it was minimum wage. The benefits were actually great for what they were - 50% off food, free popcorn and soda, and free movie tickets. I could get chicken strips and fries for like $4 along with a small bag of popcorn and a drink.  

If you have any questions just ask! It wasnt worth building a career off of - managers made like $12/hr - but as a side gig it was awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 07:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 06:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/RhEHx4T.jpg Hey FYI, this is what comes up when I try to sign in with Facebook.

Edit: oh, I cant add my dog because theres no option for her breed - shes part Korean Jindo but itd be very useful to have a Mix / Mutt option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 06:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hah! I was skeptical at first because these kinds of apps never include Canada, but Im actually in Vancouver so this is awesome! Ill definitely be downloading it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 05:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look into Neverland Tea! I go for high tea once a year and its totally worth it. Huge selection of teas and the sandwiches and desserts are amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 23:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. When my father in law passed away my first reaction on the phone was are you fucking kidding me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 23:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband did it. Super easy. You just need to go to a VPD office that does fingerprinting first (easily googleable) and tell them its for a name change. Then fill out and file the name change paperwork at a Service Canada office. Takes over a month to get the certificate in the mail though and then youll need to order a new birth certificate separately if you want a new passport.

Edit: heres a link to the fingerprinting: [link](http://vancouver.ca/police/organization/records-checks-fingerprinting/fingerprinting-service.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-25 01:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And buttholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-18 04:18:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol I had to force myself not to. I love that album so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 22:32:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1.	Waking Up in Vegas
2.	Thinking of You
3.	The One That Got Away
4.	One of the Boys
5.	Fingerprints
6.	If You Can Afford Me
7.	Self Inflicted
8.	Not Like the Movies
9.	By the Grace of God
10. Roar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-02 23:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was walking to work this morning through a foresty kind of park and saw what I seriously thought was a small bear sniffing around the forest floor. Froze in my damn tracks until I realized it was an off leash GSD and its owner was just out of sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-01 23:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn! That was my favorite when I used to commute by train. The crossword made me feel smart because it was so easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 21:10:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt notice at first but the entire back half of the passport is shredded. Anyway, Im at the passport office and they told me I need to apply for a new one. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 21:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope :( its faster to pick it up but it costs the same, unfortunately. Luckily I live relatively nearby the passport office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 18:30:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in Canada and it wont be a problem to get it before Sunday, Im more upset that I just paid good money for it and now Ill have to pay the same money plus  expediting fees for no reason :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 18:29:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, that does make me feel a little better. Thanks for sharing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 18:28:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds terrifying! Im glad you didnt lose her. I am trying my best to remember that shes just a dog and she probably doesnt even remember doing it at this point. She certainly didnt mean anything by it. Im more upset with myself for leaving it within reach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 10:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope so! My friend is joking that she just doesnt want me to leave for the trip. Im sure itll be a funny story one day but right now Im stressed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Vent][Discussion] I literally just paid for a new passport and my dog ate it. I fly out in one week. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 09:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so upset. I JUST got a new passport. It arrived in the mail less than a week ago. I had it on the coffee table in the living room. My husband just woke me up to show me that she had chewed through the corner of it. The corner of the page that they swipe at customs is destroyed. Were flying out next Sunday. It cost $120 to get the passport and itll cost at least $250 to get another one rushed to me before Sunday. I cant sleep. Ill need to take the day off work tomorrow to deal with this. FML!

Update: just left the passport office. It was $110 for a new passport plus $50 to have it ready by the weekend, so, not bad all in all. I still love my dog. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-24 21:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in Canada and the trainer I use suggests an umbrella, as the top commenter said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-23 02:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I'm curious, if this was a real case, what was the actual outcome? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-23 02:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe contact your home country's embassy? But as long as you're a minor I don't think there's much you can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-12 21:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was really interesting. Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-12 05:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Used to work there and I asked a manager this once. He said that people originally complained about the reserved seating when it first came out (dont recall why though - probably confusion lol). But there are plans to make it all reserved seating eventually - this was almost a year ago though; no idea when those plans will come to fruition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-09 20:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you looked into therapy or counselling? In my area there are organizations that pair people with mental illnesses with therapists who specialize in finding them a job that accommodates their needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Would someone who died in their sleep still have died if they were awake at the time? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-09 20:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-05 01:35:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And in the choir I saw our sad messiah, he was bored and tired of my laments, said I died for you one time, but never again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-04 17:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wisdom Panel 4.0, purchased directly from the Wisdom Panel site. Its a doggy DNA test! It was less than $100 and took about two weeks from ordering it to getting the results. There are other companies that do the DNA test, one thats more thorough but also more expensive is called Embark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-04 04:24:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The before pic looks exactly like my dog right now! Shes 1/4 Jindo, 1/4 chow chow, 1/8 sharpei, and 3/8 mixed asian/terrier breeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-28 07:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah... I tried that and ended up destroying the phone, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-28 07:06:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They offered to replace the battery for $100, but it was an older phone so I just ended up upgrading it in the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-28 01:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its either not measuring the charge properly or your batterys max charge has decreased. My old iPhone 4 would die at 40%, brought it to Apple and they ran a diagnostic which showed that the max capacity was only like 56%. Worth bringing it into an Apple store for a check up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-27 05:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Well try that. She already kind of knows go potty for pee and do your business for poo, so Ill try to incorporate it with treats in the yard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Help] Is there a way to teach our housetrained dog that it's okay to go in the yard? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-27 01:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sofie is completely housetrained; never had an accident inside the house. But when she needs to pee, we'll take her on a walk and she won't try to pee until maybe 5-10 minutes into the walk, far from our house. Is there a way to teach her to pee/poo in our small, unfenced, but grassy-and-surrounded-by-bushes yard? 
 
 It would be helpful for those midnight walks in the winter where it would be easier on all of us if she could just pop out for a minute (leashed) to pee, and come back inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 06:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love Lab is super underrated and hilarious! Its about some girls who make a club where they basically brainstorm ideas to get themselves a boyfriend. Really cute and relatable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-23 21:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last night I was out walking the dog past the graveyard by my house. The graveyard has absolutely no lighting so its pitch black at night. My immediate thought was I gotta put some torches down. Then I asked my husband for a glow ring, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-23 04:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Help] My dog is always hungry. What else can I add to her food? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-21 20:55:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dog is a 41 lb Jindo mix. When we got her in July we were feeding her Blue Buffalo, about 2 or 2.5 cups a day for weight loss (she was 44 lbs when we got her and the vet said she was overweight). We live near a raw food supply shop, so when the Blue Buffalo ran out in September we switched her to raw dehydrated food, called Grand Cru. The recommended serving for her with this stuff is 1.5 cups a day with water to reconstitute it.  

So she gets 3/4 cup for breakfast around 10 am, and 3/4 for dinner around 6:30 pm. We also add a spoonful of plain organic yogurt to the bowl. She also usually has a big braided rawhide bone to chew on after meals.  

But she acts like shes starving all the time! And I dont blame her; 1.5 cups of food a day doesnt feel like that much. I was having a granola bar the other day and she tried to eat it out of my hand, wrapper and all. Whenever we have dinner she sits beside us and stares at our food like she thinks well give her some.  

What should we be doing? Should we switch her back to something more filling? Can I add brown rice or an egg or something to her meals? The worker at the raw food store said to give her the bone to chew on after meals, and its somewhat working, but she gets bored of it eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-20 09:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, he ordered popcorn from me and I had to ask him if he had a Scene Card. I definitely fangirled after he left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-20 03:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tom Felton came into my theatre a few times when I was working there. The girl ripping tickets had a Harry Potter movie on her name tag as her favorite film, and Tom told her good choice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-18 06:14:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same! Working on my bachelors right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-12 18:03:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was a kid, my dad was that guy. If I had a computer problem, just telling him about it would magically fix it. I guess its genetic because now Im that person at work, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 09:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can also use a tensor bandage/elastic bandage (the wide stretchy kind you would wrap around a sore muscle) in the same way, you should be able to google some instructions. The dog trainer we go to recommended it as a cheap alternative to a Thundershirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 09:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use iKibble Free on iOS for that :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-09 00:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some patients can't be saved. That burden's not on you. Don't ever let anyone tell you you deserve that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Discussion] Our dog loves to chase foam bullets shot out of a toy gun, any safer alternatives? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-30 02:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have a crappy toy gun from a dollar store that shoots foam bullets with a suction cup on the end. For whatever reason, Sofie goes nuts for this and will come sprinting if she hears it being fired, and will try to chase/track down the bullet. Obviously, we don't want her eating or swallowing the bullets because they're pretty small and she could easily choke. Are there any alternatives that made a clear, loud noise and fire a projectile that's safe for her to put in her mouth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-29 03:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't get used to their behaviour, good or bad. We've had our dog for two months and she's different every day. She was a nightmare when we picked her up from the airport but calmed down once she was at home. She used to be calm when playing - now she nips at me and bites when she's excited. She would sleep on the floor and wake up throughout the night and whine, now she sleeps on the bed with us all night long. She would try to sniff every person we passed, now she only tries with every 10th person or so. She used to sit and freeze if she saw a dog, now she looks but keeps moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-21 04:50:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hah! I live in Vancouver and found out yesterday that my unknown-mix rescue also hates the rain. I tried to take her out and she just sat down by the door and pouted at me. I'm looking at getting a rain coat with a hood for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-19 23:12:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Out is great. Two tips: Have receipts with you, printed out, for everything you're picking up. And don't lie to the border guards about the value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dog won't stop scratching her face </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-16 00:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dog, 3 years old, spayed female, mix breed, 40lbs, rescued from Thailand on July 28, was perfectly healthy. 

She's had what I can only describe as an itchy area on the right side of her muzzle. When we got her, she had a couple itchy spots, but the muzzle was the worst. The first time we took her to the vet for a check up, we were given a medical shampoo to wash her with twice a week. But she hates water, so trying to get her in the bath just traumatized her and we ended up paying a groomer almost $100 just to bathe her. So that's only happened once.  

She would scratch it until it bled. One day she was getting blood everywhere. We took her to the vet and got a cone and some antibiotic ointment (canaural eardrops). She could smell the ointment so she would snap/bite if you got too close with it, or just lick it off her face.  

Then she managed to get the cone off and scratched even more - [picture](https://imgur.com/wwhaeeX). We took her back to the vet, got a better cone and some oral antibiotics.

We did the course of antibiotics but she's still itchy. We bought Burts Bees anti itch spray with apple cider vinegar but she just licks it off. We've been taking her cone off before walks the last 3-4 days because she's distracted enough by the world to not scratch, and she's much more stressed and reactive with the cone on. But today when we got home, she scratched while I was getting her cone.  

[Picture](https://imgur.com/yoEIxUx).  

This is after cleaning the blood with a wet paper towel, saline and hydrogen peroxide. I also put a thin layer of antibiotic ointment (not one for dogs, just a generic brand from my medicine cabinet) on it and got her cone back on right away.  

I don't really want to have to bring her back to the vet. But she's had the cone on for a month and obviously just made it worse - and we have a training class coming up in a week and a half, and it'll be harder to get her to pay attention and see visual cues with the cone on.  

Any advice? Her name is Sofie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-11 18:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I literally just did the math on this because we're going to switch our dog to raw dehydrated soon. Note that this is in Canada. For the brand CaniSource, red meat version (slightly cheaper than the other proteins), 10kg bag (22lbs), for our dog who is 22kg (44lbs) = approx $2.07/day. This is the cheapest I can find so far. For comparison, we had a 24lb bag of Blue Buffalo kibble that was about $1.67/day, feeding her within the weight management guide instead of the recommended guide, so it stretched it out by about an extra 1/3rd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-09 21:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our dog has something similar where she has wounds on her face that can't heal because of the scratching. We got her a cone, which she somehow took off and scratched her face so hard it got infected. So, got a better cone, oral antibiotics, and some anti itch spray. The infection is gone but she's still itchy and the spray doesn't really help because she just licks it off. I think we just have to wait until it's completely healed before taking the cone off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-04 02:38:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to learn how to do this, [this](http://gmmentalgym.blogspot.ca/2011/03/day-of-week-for-any-date-revised.html?m=1#ndatebasics) is a super in depth tutorial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Casual] How many weeks are in a month? One question. Open to everyone. Settle a bet. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-25 22:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-15 05:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry! She's 40lbs and about 18" tall. She does look a lot like your dog! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Breeds] What's my rescue dog crossed with? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-15 04:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's three and from Thailand. She's part Australian Kelpie (the rescue agency thinks), but she's definitely crossed with something else - the ears are a giveaway. Any ideas? We're planning to get a DNA test in the future out of curiosity anyway.  

[Album](http://imgur.com/a/JCxhb) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-13 21:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you considered sedation dentistry? I don't have any experience with it but I'm sure you could find it on google. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 02:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I know her! I'll send her an email.

Edit: Told her it's at the VPD, thanks for posting!

Edit2: she's going to get it, thanks again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 05:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, that's something I haven't considered. I tried feeding her and giving her water in her crate today and she didn't seem to mind, so it's a start. You're right that it would be a safety issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 05:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you thank you thank you. This is all so helpful. You've mentioned a lot of things that I would have never even thought about, like taking her collar off and letting our landlord know she might be noisy. I fed her and gave her water and a treat in her crate today and she went in all by herself. I've frozen some kibble with beef broth in her Kong as well - I'll see if she likes it. I'll definitely keep everything here in mind and start working on it ASAP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Help] We have to leave our new rescue alone at home for six hours on Saturday. It'll be the first time she's alone at home and she has separation anxiety. What can we start doing right now to make it easier? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 00:23:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband and I work opposite schedules so there's always someone home with our 3 y/o Kelpie cross, Sofie. However, he just got scheduled for an extra shift on Saturday morning. We'll both be at work from 6:30am-12pm. The longest Sofie's been alone at home is about five minutes, and in that time she managed to destroy our blinds. She whimpers and whines if one of us even leaves her sight, let alone leaves the house. When my husband left for work the other night, she whined by her doggie gate until she fell asleep, even as I was calling to her from the bedroom.  

We usually keep her in the kitchen with the gate to the living room/front door area closed, the front door out of sight. She has a crate, which she's investigated a couple times, but hasn't shown interest in entering. She has a Kong toy but isn't interested even when there's treats in it. There aren't any daycares open early enough on the weekend to take her before we go to work, and she doesn't seem to get along with other dogs right now anyway.  

I was thinking to start trying to crate train her, or at least distract her with food and toys in the crate long enough for us to go to work. Would it be better to keep the crate in the kitchen, do you think? Or put it by the front door where she could see us leave and enter? I was also thinking of putting her food in the Kong with some broth and freezing it, as well as leaving some talk radio on. I also don't know if this new shift will be a permanent change to my husband's schedule.  

Ideas please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-05 06:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We got married there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-03 18:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a ticket to the Vancouver show but had to sell it cuz I needed rent money. Apparently the concert was amazing. Feels bad. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-02 20:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't thought about that yet, but that sounds like an idea to try. We're trying to get her used to the sound of the shower running and she's come in the bathroom once or twice now to investigate, so maybe she'd be open to it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-02 20:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We got her Friday and went to the vet on Saturday. I didn't want to try bathing her right away but I thought it would be important to use the medicated stuff as soon as possible because she spends a lot of time scratching and biting at her skin. You're right that it's probably traumatizing. We'll definitely try to find a groomer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-02 20:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't even know that was a thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-02 20:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! That's all great info. I didn't consider wearing a swimsuit. We do have a shower head but it's not the kind with a hose, so that's something else to consider. I'm worried how she'll react to rain because we live in Vancouver and it'll be rainy season in about a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-02 20:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, that's a great idea. I can see a couple in my area so I'll reach out to them. The only thing is that we're supposed to use the shampoo 1-2 times a week and it's a bit expensive to pay $20+ for a bath every time, but it's definitely something to consider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Help] How do I give our dog a bath when she's terrified of baths? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-01 23:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband and I just adopted a 40lb, three-year-old mixed breed named Sofie. She has some scabs and rashes, so the vet prescribed a medical shampoo for her. The problem is she's absolutely terrified of the bath.  

We spent a few hours trying to get her into the tub to no avail. We put about an inch of warm water in the tub. We tried to coerce her with treats but she doesn't really like any of the ones we have, and certainly not enough to get in the tub. She also doesn't really play with her toys so we can't just put them in the bath and expect her to have a good ol' time.  

My husband picked her up to put her in the tub a few times. Every time she would pull her legs and tail up as far as she could, and the second she touched the water she would leap out of the tub and bolt away. We managed to block her escape once but I accidentally splashed some water, which scared her, and she managed to jump out again. Now she won't even enter the bathroom.  

We do have a hose outside but our yard is tiny, there's no fence, and it's next to a main road. I guess we could keep her on a leash and hose her down but I'm afraid of her trying to run away again. She's also afraid of the sprinklers that we pass on our walks.  

Is it normal for people to literally hold their dogs in place and force them to be washed? I think Sofie would have a heart attack if we did that.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it normal to be hired on the spot for grocery/restaurant/hospitality jobs? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 02:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Settle a debate between me and my husband.  

Every job he's ever had has gone like this: submit resume; get a call back the next day asking him to come in for an interview with void checks; go to the "interview" where they just tell him what he'll be doing, give them the checks for direct deposit, and sign some hiring paperwork; leave the interview; have first day of work the same week.  

He's worked multiple hospitality/tourism, restaurant, and grocery store jobs in two countries over seven years and it's been the exact same every single time. It happened again today and I pointed out that he's never gone through a formal interview process of submitting references, waiting to get a call back, second interviews, etc. Meanwhile I've only worked office jobs and I've definitely had to go through the entire nerve wracking process.  

Anyway, is this about standard for those types of jobs? Or is he just really lucky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-23 21:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I worked in a theatre. Get [these](https://m.payless.com/mens/work-safety-shoes/77456.html?dwvar_77456_color=black). They're SO comfy. They have them in men and women's. I actually wore them outside of work for a long time because they were so comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just moved into a house that smells like the previous tenants' cat and has cat hair still in the rug. If I got a dog who didn't like cats, would it bother him/her? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-04 20:23:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-02 07:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try posting on /r/weddingplanning :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-22 22:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waterfront has them, stood in line for about 15 mins to get one. Compass card dispenser by the main entrance.

ETA: Vancouver City Centre has them too. Shorter line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-17 09:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> www.icheckmovies.com has a ton of lists, including a Reddit one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-12 04:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Icicle Village Resort! They have a gorgeous arbor on the grounds that has a mountain backdrop. It was stunning and my party was small enough that everyone just stood up with us, so they let us use the grounds for free (we paid for our hotel suite obviously). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-12 04:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-12 04:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To the dress? It's [this](http://www.aritzia.com/en/product/belgravia-dress/49407.html), but in the colour Oak which I don't think they sell anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-12 04:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We didn't! We wanted to do so much and just didn't have time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-11 09:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup! Thank you! :) My friend said I looked like a doily, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-11 06:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Couldn't have done it without /r/weddingplanning :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> None of it felt real until he was saying "I do." Married today, 6/10/2017, in Leavenworth WA 3 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-11 06:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-08 03:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw, that would be sweet. I'll see if it's doable. Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-08 03:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a good idea. I'll see if she's feeling up to it. Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My MOH can't come to my wedding [sad rant] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-08 02:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're leaving tomorrow for our destination elopement, getting married on Saturday. For a year and a half, my dream wedding has been to elope to this particular town with only my best friend and my FH's best friend. She has been super excited about the wedding since I invited her in January. We've talked so much about it, and I was so excited to have basically my one and only girlfriend with me.

A few minutes ago she let me know that the new medication she's been taking is making her really sick and her doctor advised her not to travel. Now, I completely understand - FH has health/med problems and I totally sympathize and understand that her health comes first. And she's made it clear that she's disappointed and didn't want to have to make this call. I have nothing but love for her.

But I'm still really disappointed! Now it'll just be me, FH, his best friend, and another close mutual guy friend. Three guys and me for four days. I love all of them but now I'll have to get my hair done alone and do my makeup alone. I guess I can have one of the guys stand on my side during the ceremony but it's not the same. I wanted her in my pictures, I wanted to visit all the kitschy shops in town that I know she would love, I wanted her to smell my bouquet...

I'm still excited to get married, but I'm just sad, you guys. :(

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-21 21:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leavenworth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-21 02:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're eloping in three weeks! The basic gist is that we're driving ourselves and three friends up to a small touristy mountain town in Washington for a four-day vacation, and getting married on the Saturday. I've reserved one huge hotel room for all of us to sleep in, got a real photographer (for one hour), an officiant, and a wedding cake (cheesecake). I got a white lace dress ($40, on sale from Aritzia), he got a grey suit, we have our shoes and his tie and pocket square. He still has to write his vows, I still need to make the cake toppers (the DIY clay kit got lost in the mail), and we still need to get alterations. My wedding band may or may not be ready before the wedding (they'll lend me the sample ring if it's not). But everything else is on track and I'm excited!  

Oh, except that I still haven't told my family. Probably should get that done soon lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-21 02:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're called sample spoons or tasting spoons, maybe try those keywords? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-19 23:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes I read it as earring and get confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:28:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes it's marked as delivered but will actually be delivered the next day/in a few days. Sometimes it's marked as delivered but was actually lost in transit (this just happened to me, god bless Amazon customer service   refunds).

I live in Canada and order from the US a lot. I'd say 2/10 packages never show up, or get delivered to the wrong address lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We tend to call waiters "servers" where I live. I feel like that's more neutral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-16 08:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, I got it myself. I looked at rings online for a long time and showed him a couple I liked. He happened to like the one I liked the most. At the last minute I decided to customize the stones. Contacted the company and paid for the whole thing with money I've been saving since we started dating. He proposed with a ring pop a month or two after we already booked an officiant and photographer, a few months before I got the ring in the mail. No regrets - we have different tastes and I don't know that I would have 100% loved it if he chose a ring by himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:25:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might want to post on /r/weddingplanning as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We just got his paperwork in so we should have time to get everything done! There is a rush passport option and it's a little pricey but it's really our only option at this point. Thanks for the kind words! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god oh god.  

So, the wedding part of my wedding is mostly done. I still need to get my wedding band and alterations for my dress/his suit. He still needs to write his vows. I have to make the cake toppers and figure out my DIY makeup.  

What's stressing me out is that FH is in the middle of legally changing his name before we get married. He put in the paperwork at the end of March and we still haven't heard back. As soon as we get the paperwork back in the mail he needs to rush order a new birth certificate, wait for that, then rush order a new drivers licence and passport so that when we go to get our marriage licence (in the US, we're in Canada) his name is correct on everything. It's supposed to take 6 weeks at the most and it's been almost 8!  

I'm so excited to be married but I wish we had more time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:25:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took it a few years ago. It's harder than you think. I type 100+ WPM and I failed the first two attempts. You can't backspace and you have to put two spaces after a period/punctuation. They give you a couple paragraphs from a textbook and you have to copy it into the computer exactly. I think they cover your hands but I don't remember. Don't remember if homerow matters either. Go slow on your first attempt to get a feel for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad was the best dressed person at my high school graduation. I thought it was sweet. It showed everyone how proud he was. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG are you getting married in Leavenworth too?! We're getting married there on June 10! :)  

Ninja edit: or is that just a default address? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm actually going to a wedding later this year where everyone but the bride will be wearing white, so I'm probably in the only possible situation where this is appropriate, lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 12th grade (last year of high school) chemistry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:00:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol I read the title as "wedding snapbacks" and was like oh cool like custom hats?  

Beautiful picture! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:47:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds awful. I'm sorry you have to deal with that.  

I'd like to point out though that fiance = female and fianc = male! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always wanted to share my FH's last name since I was a kid, so it wasn't a decision at all for me. But I'll tell you that when I was in seventh grade, my teacher got married. She told us when she got engaged and we had lots of discussion about her new last name (she was going from Ms. Z to Mrs. B, which is a big deal when you're a student and everything is done in last-name alphabetical order). We even threw her a surprise party when she came back from her honeymoon! It was super fun and no one had difficulty remembering her new name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ordered mine in February for delivery May 10 and I just got a call today confirming they'd be shipped very soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRW the best man proclaims to FH that "everyone's getting laid" at his bachelor party next month </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> June 10, date twins! We're eloping so there's not all that much left to do, but I've been putting it off:  

- Buy my wedding band 
- Get dress and suit altered  
- Figure out what I'll do for makeup (DIY)  
- Have FH write his vows  
- Tell my family (lol)  
- Get the marriage licence  
- Make our DIY cake topper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:51:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry this is happening. I don't have much advice except maybe let FSIL (or let FH let FSIL) know what was going on in case she's been feeling offended or worried what you said around her child?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Heres a recipe you could follow](https://www.mccormick.com/recipes/main-dishes/easy-meatloaf), it would probably taste really plain without seasoning though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for making this thread, we're going to Universal (and Disneyworld!!) as part of our honeymoon too so this is super helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:42:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't see "no gifts" anywhere but that's definitely something I should check. We'll ask FH's aunt, thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks :) Just wanted to be sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wedding gift for a destination wedding with no registry? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FH and I are going to his cousin's destination wedding in Costa Rica later this year. I just looked at their website again and realized they don't have a registry.  

They're older than us, have been together a long time, and are quite well-off financially. Would giving them cash and a card still be the best thing to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My ring is from BE. I customized a setting, not by much though, just switched the side diamonds for different gems. They were fantastic, got back to me very promptly, had everything set up faster than I expected, confirmed every detail with me. And the first week I wore the ring, I was experiencing irritation that I thought was an allergic reaction, and the customer service rep I had been dealing with was so patient with me about it. I asked a million questions about alternative metals for the wedding band, and she gave me so much information and said to keep her posted if it got any worse. My ring is moissanite so I don't have a dog in the fight re: diamonds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might also want to ask /r/weddingplanning, there's tons of Vancouver brides there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:50:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:25:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, it's fine. Also don't capitalize the following word. Such as:  

"Oh no!" he exclaimed. "What is it?" she asked. "I stubbed my toe," he replied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you signed a contract, there's gotta be some kind of legal repercussions, right? If your wedding date comes and goes without hearing back from this guy, I'd lawyer up (if you think it's worth it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:50:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [You and Elaine are kindred spirits now!](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/6b/2d/9f/6b2d9f913c883215a3d1eb62d1e7f7e0.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love those! Like "Curiosity killed the cat - but satisfaction brought it back" and "Great minds think alike - but fools seldom differ." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The full saying is "the blood of the covenant is thicker than the water of the womb"! The friends you choose are closer than family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:46:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess you're looking for ideas for the wedding ceremony? [A Practical Wedding](https://apracticalwedding.com/sub-main-page/writing-a-wedding-ceremony/) is a good place to start.  

Specifically, [Writing a Non-Traditional Ceremony](https://apracticalwedding.com/writing-a-non-traditional-wedding-ceremony/)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone suggested a silicone ring and I second that. My FH insisted he hates jewelry and would have to wear a wedding ring on a necklace at the most. Got him a silicone ring in a colour he loves, he put it on without me prompting him, and never takes it off. Best part is that it's cheap so if he wears it out by spinning it, we can just buy a new one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try ASOS and Modcloth! Tons of dresses under $100. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome! I'm up in Vancouver BC (west coast = best coast indeed) and now I'll have to see if we have anything like that here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:55:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Sorry, I don't speak German!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:56:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where did you grow up that has Japanese immersion schools? That sounds awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Canadian this is a bit hard, haha. We measure long distances in KM but measure ourselves in feet and inches and pounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit has always hated diamonds. Mention diamonds anywhere on this site at any time and you'll immediately get a lecture about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When my coworkers go to Starbucks, they'll usually ask if anyone wants anything.  

If you say yes, you give them your order. I try not to be too complicated out of politeness.  

When they come back, they hand me the food/drink and I either hand them a $5 (if I know that's about what it costs), or I ask "how much do I owe you?"  

Most of the time my coworkers will say "don't worry about it, my treat", and I'll say "thank you" and do the same for them at some point in return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:04:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have pierced ears either. I was looking at clip on earrings though - there are some beautiful ones on etsy, but they're pricey! I might still try to find some though because I'm wearing my hair up and I like the look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I've seen all the shitty reviews so I'm not putting a lot of stock into getting my flowers. Thankfully it's not that big a deal to me because I'm eloping and the bouquet (or lack thereof) isn't going to matter at all, but I'll definitely strengthen my Plan B. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry! I had to call Eco Flower today to change the shipping address on my order. To their credit, the lady from their wedding department that was helping me on the phone was extremely sweet and helpful. But I ordered the flowers for May 1st and I'm pretty sure they're not going to arrive on time - which is fine, the wedding isn't until June 10th. Still... My backup plan is to stop at a Trader Joes on the way to the wedding and take whatever bouquet I can get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:54:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4 8 15 16 23 42 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:32:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as I know, it's perfectly fine to invite people to the bachelor party and not the wedding! I've never seen any etiquette dictating otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you considered lab created diamonds (cheaper) or moissanite (much much cheaper)?  

In your shoes, I wouldn't trust them to make another ring if this one is already loose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:05:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not 100% sure what a toonie bar is either, but I'm guessing it's where every drink costs $2! In Canada our $2 coins are called toonies. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:06:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, thanks again for your advice. I had a long talk with FH about it and in the end he sent BM a message explaining everything and being completely honest. He does want to go the party, but his anxiety is making him think of all the reasons why he shouldn't. So having those out in the open was a good idea. BM was understanding about it! They're talking about ideas for a bachelor party now and FH isn't anxious at all because he doesn't have to hide anything now. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, that's a good way of going about it, although he is very persistent, haha. I'll bring that up with FH as an alternative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I agree that we can't keep beating around the bush. I'm going to offer a baseball game as an alternative and talk to FH about me at least letting BM what's going on. Thanks - it's helpful to talk to someone about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for your input! We've brought up a simple game night but I don't think he took it seriously.  

I'm starting to think the only solution is to have a talk with FH about telling BM about all this stuff he's been going through. I'd love to just say "Hey BM, calm down about this bachelor party stuff please, FH is going through some shit right now" but I feel like that's not my call. You're right that we need to have a discussion about it and come up with an alternative that works for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to tactfully tell the best man that FH doesn't want a bachelor party? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're having a tiny wedding. The best man/FH's best friend wants to throw him a "bachelor party" which means taking him for a weekend trip in another country shortly before the wedding.

The problem is that FH struggles with mental health issues and recently stopped working because of it. He's working on getting better but he hasn't really told anyone about it because he's embarrassed. Our friend is offering to pay for everything for this bachelor party, but frankly FH is dealing with a lot of anxiety right now (not to mention lack of income) and just doesn't want to deal with it.

We love the best man and we both know it's coming from a good place, but he's not taking no for an answer. FH has tried explaining that he doesn't have the time or money, and tried redirecting towards less stressful activities, but our friend has himself so hyped up about having a party.

What else can we do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's the post :)](https://reddit.com/r/weddingplanning/comments/65aqn5/just_booked_my_dream_honeymoon/dg8yyy9)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's the post :)](https://reddit.com/r/weddingplanning/comments/65aqn5/just_booked_my_dream_honeymoon/dg8yyy9)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's the post :)](https://reddit.com/r/weddingplanning/comments/65aqn5/just_booked_my_dream_honeymoon/dg8yyy9) I had it saved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh good lord. I'm so sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair, I don't know anyone IRL whose parents are still together... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not OP, but I'm getting married in June and having our honeymoon in December. We have to go to a relative's wedding in Costa Rica so we're doubling it as a honeymoon :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you tried non fish sushi like California rolls (crab meat and avocado and/or cucumber) or tamago nigiri (egg)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a customer ask if our prices were in Canadian dollars. What I wanted to say was "what the fuck else would they be?" but what I said was "we're in Canada, so..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha thanks! I'm so stoked. We went from "well, we're not big on cake but we want to respect the tradition of having a wedding cake" to "fuck it, it's our day, let's have the best cheesecake ever!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Date twins! I love the enhancers, what's the centre stone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't lose hope! A lot of people apparently consider the RSVP-by date to be the mail-by date.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MRW I ask for a cheesecake with brownie base, ganache and strawberries as my wedding cake and I actually get it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably depends if it's being run manually by someone sitting at a projector, or if it's being run digitally and automatically.  

I worked at a theatre where all the movies and ads and trailers were automatically run off a computer at a certain time. It didn't matter if no one showed up; it would still run.  

If it's being run by a guy in a booth moving reels in and out of a projector, he probably won't play the movie, but I don't know for sure. My dad used to tell me that he once was the only person in a theatre and the projectionist stopped the reel while my dad used the bathroom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was under the impression that it was customary, but here's what our officiant quoted me:

While the $175 does cover my services, it is customary for the Groom or Best Man to tip the officiate for the services rendered, normally $20-$50.

He's non-denominational and not affiliated with any churches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the quick answer!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can you send a letter to a grocery store? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not a resume. I need to mail something to a particular manager at a local store. Can I just make it out to:

Ms. Manager  
c/o Meat Dept  
Grocery Store  
123 Street  
Etc, Etc  

?  

I imagine they do get mail every day but I want to make sure before I send it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:24:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same! Ours is $175 plus tip, but I'm pretty sure he's literally the only officiant in the town we're marrying in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 09:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Liquor licensing is equally dumb in BC so I feel ya. I used to work for a catering company whose owner refused to get a liquor licence because it wasn't worth the hassle and liability.  

As for being a June bride, the only thing I'm worried about at this point is how many people are actually coming! Out of five people invited, one still needs to get a passport and two (a couple) haven't responded to my invite (that I sent over fb message, so they've seen it).  

Luckily I've planned out enough that even if no one shows up, we'll be fine and we'll just end up saving a lot of money. But it's still frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, thanks for the link. I spent a good hour looking at Pulitzer winners. The same guy also won in 2015 for photographing the Ebola crisis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haven't eloped yet, but here's the plan for now:

Before 2 - Hanging out with FH and our friends  
2:00 p.m. - Hair appointment (no trial)  
3:15 p.m. - Doing my own makeup, put on the dress  
4:45 p.m. - Meeting the officiant and photographer  
5:00 p.m. - Ceremony (photo taking begins)  
5:15 p.m. - Taking photos at a nearby park for 45 mins  
6:15 p.m. - Dinner at the hotel restaurant  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For issue 2, how long have they been dating? Could you say "long term couples only" or "the venue is too small and we can't accommodate everyone" or something? It looks like you've already cut people; personally I'd be finding every excuse not to invite a girl friend of my FH's who doesn't like me, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband just made himself this for dinner, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:35:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These are GORGEOUS, oh my god! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I may have found it [here](http://budgetbridalworld.com/products/wedding-dress/567/weddingdress-new/) - looks like the designer is Pronovias </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:58:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A [chevron band](https://www.etsy.com/search?ref=auto-1 as_prefix=chevron+wedding q=chevron+wedding+band order=most_relevant view_type=gallery) would be perfect for that ring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> matradee  

Sorry, it's maitre d', short for matre d'htel which means master of the hotel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:49:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was about 10 years old I went to the Philippines for a month. My cousin and I bought two dyed chicks that were being sold on our street. We kept them in a shoebox with air holes, a small bowl for water, and food (rice, probably). We only had them for a week before they escaped and got eaten by a neighbourhood cat.  

Looking back, yeah, that's fucked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was working three part time jobs, 7 days a week until recently. My longest streak was 36 days of working before I got a day off. Now I'm working one job full time, M-F. But I like working, and I need the money, so I'm looking for a part time job again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Their customer service is so good! The lady I worked with is amazing, she answered all my questions very promptly and double-checked everything with me. And I love the ethical sourcing, my sapphire is lab-created :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It gets way more expensive for med school and stuff like that - med school is more like $17k per year. But for a plain ol' Arts degree it's pretty reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the tuition breakdown for a first-year Bachelor of Arts student at UBC (University of British Columbia), one of the top universities in Canada/the world:

(First year course load - 30) credits | Tuition $5,189.70  
Student fees $996.00  
Books / supplies $2,060.00  
Educational costs subtotal $8,245.70

I work at a community college in the same area where the cost per year is literally half that, though.

That's all in Canadian $$ too, so in USD it's about $6146 per year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I'm honestly lost as to what kind of band I want. I was thinking just a plain thin white gold band so it doesn't overpower the colours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Moissanite centre stone, pink sapphire and aquamarine, custom from Brilliant Earth. It's so *me* and I'm in love with it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My cotton candy ring :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:31:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm having a similarly small wedding with max five guests and a photographer. I'm wearing [this](http://www.aritzia.com/en/product/belgravia-dress/49407.html) in white!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.gameofthronesconcert.com/

It looks like their last show was on the 2nd. I was lucky enough to see them in Vancouver last weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was weird that even though I answered no to "have you been to Exit before", it still asked me if I would recommend it to others and why not. I finished it though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hah, the same thing happened to me several years ago, also in the food court at Metrotown. A man approached me and commented on my running shoes. Then he started asking if I was an athlete (nope), then about my hobbies (World of Warcraft at the time), then said that I'd be a good fit to do some office work over the summer. Canadian Property Stars. I filled out the form on his tablet and regretted it immediately afterwards. Ended up having to block their number and emails for a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:51:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom, who had somehow never seen or heard Star Wars spoilers, assumed that Vader was lying when I finally had her watch the original trilogy a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 11% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waiting for FH's custom ring to be shipped, and my wedding shoes. Gonna pick up my e-ring next week, it's already waiting for me at my PO box but I just don't have time to get it. Still need dress and suit alterations. Gotta follow up about my wedding cake because the lady hasn't replied in over a month - trying to get cheesecake with brownie base, ganache and strawberries on top; fingers crossed they actually do it for me! Waiting for FH's name change docs to be finalized so he can update his drivers licence so I can rent the car in his new name for our trip. And I gotta send the one couple we're inviting to the ceremony an actual invitation. Oh, and I'll have to find a wedding band to match my e-ring.  

Apart from the ring stuff, I'm super chill about everything else and I'm sure I can get it all done by June. I feel like I've already conquered a mountain of to-dos and I just have the little things left! I'm not stressed about anything at all, which is weird because I'm a planner and a worrier!  

Oh right I almost forgot that we still have to write our vows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:41:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope! The last Arby's standing is in Coquitlam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seconding the copper Enso ring! I bought one for FH and even though he's said for years that he hates jewelry and would never wear a ring, he LOVES it. I even had to get him a smaller size so he would stop spinning it. He loves anything copper so it's perfect for him.

The only caveat I would add is that they run pretty big; he's a 7.5 and I found that the 6 fit him best (and was still a tiny big large). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:31:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Carrot Rewards: Earn points just for walking (Canada) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:04:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, that sounds great. I'll shoot you a PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would be awesome, thank you so much!! Paper coupons I'm guessing? Maybe I could PM you closer to June? Unless you want to mail them to Canada, haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Eat based on what's on sale, not what you feel like"

100% this. I've literally never bought meat in this city that wasn't on sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:34:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha I was waiting for someone to catch that - yeah, Leavenworth! We live in Vancouver BC and my FH grew up in Bellingham. For our first vacation he took me to Leavenworth so it holds a special place in our hearts. :) It's beautiful and kitschy and I love it! We're getting married at the Icicle Village Resort, but the first time we went we stayed at a B B. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:26:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm getting my hair done at a salon because I'm completely hopeless at doing anything more complicated than a ponytail. We're having a 12 minute ceremony with five guests, but what matters to me most is that we're hiring a photographer and I want to be beautiful in my wedding pictures.  

Makeup, I'm decent at, and I have my own products, so I'll be doing that myself.  

Hair is $90 plus tip. Makeup by an MUA would have been $110. (I'm getting married in a remote town with literally one MUA that I can find!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is exactly why my FH has zero wedding-related responsibilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh, a question I can answer!  

We're eloping to a small tourist town in eastern Washington state. We're bringing three friends with us for the whole weekend, and inviting a couple who lives nearby-ish for just the ceremony.  

No wedding planner, but what I did was contact the hotel and ask them if they provide elopement packages. They didn't, but the guest services lady I was emailing gave me SO many ideas and so much help. I asked her all my dumb questions about where to get an officiant, marriage licence, etc etc and she was extremely patient and full of answers and recommendations. In the end we're getting married on the hotel grounds, outdoors under an arbor, for free :)  

I'm renting one big room to accommodate us and our three friends that are staying the weekend. I'm also renting a car to pick everyone up on the way and make the five hour drive up the mountain. We're paying for everything with no expectations of repayment because it's the wedding we've always wanted, and we don't really want our friends (who are young and probably broke) to spend their money on something like this.  

For the photographer I spoke on the phone with a lady from Seattle who offered me a great deal including her travel up to our location. Cake and "reception" are just gonna be a sit-down dinner in the hotel's restaurant with us and our five friends. Flowers I bought online from ecoflower (haven't arrived yet so that remains to be seen). Officiant is a local who probably does all the weddings in town, since the population is tiny. Hair will be done by a local stylist who does lots of wedding hair. Deposits have all been paid through PayPal, communication has all been through email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotcha, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:31:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a second question! Again, my fianc and I are Canadian living in Canada but he has a US green card. He is in the process of legally changing his name through the Canadian govt.

He will first update his drivers licence to the new name, but will probably wait to update his passport until after the wedding.  

When we cross the border into the US, will it cause any problems that his Canadian passport + US green card + re-entry permit show one name, but his drivers licence shows another?  

(He's just dropping his current surname and making his middle name his new surname.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the AMA!

My fianc and I are Canadian, but he has a US green card. He's been living in Canada for a few years on a re-entry permit, which will be expiring shortly after our wedding. However, he has no intention of moving back to the US. We're getting married in the US in June. 

My question is, is it safe to go to the border with the intention of surrendering his green card and re-entry permit if the border agent requests it? Or should he surrender it before then so we don't get denied entry on our way to our wedding ceremony? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:50:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The hotel and overall wedding weekend! We're treating our closest friends to a 4-day vacation where we're getting married on the Saturday, so I splurged and got us a big, two bedroom condo-style suite for $1600 (after converting $1200 US to Canadian ;_;). We're treating them to all their meals, whitewater rafting (about $100 a head), and hopefully horseback riding! I'm not asking or expecting our friends to pay us for anything, but knowing them they probably will, haha.  

The other thing is my e-ring, which I've been saving up for for years, and customized myself (with FH's approval). It was actually less of a splurge than it should have been, because it was originally $4500, but I got it down to $4000 after switching some of the diamonds to an aquamarine, a sapphire, and moissanite! It's arriving in the mail tomorrow and I'm so excited :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:54:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 67% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 89% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 74% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 39% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want something cheap and non-traditional, you can easily find pretty white dresses at any clothing store at the mall. I got my dress (knee length, fit-and-flare, lacy, ivory color) for $40 at Aritzia. My friend bought her wedding dress years ago at H M for about the same. I'm dressing mine up with a hair piece and cute shoes, but we're having a really casual/non-traditional wedding so it's not that big a deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:57:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fianc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We bought an Enso ring, they're fairly cheap, shipping is fast, come in a variety of colours and their customer service is awesome - I ordered a size too big and they shipped me a better size as soon as I contacted them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We always wanted to propose with a ring pop. Initially we said that I would do it, because I was the one who wanted to get married more. Anyway that never happened and we talked about getting married for a long time (I recently found my original wedding plans from Oct 2015). Then we had to solidify those plans this year when we found out his best friend is deploying soon. So a few weeks ago, after the venue, photographer, officiant etc have been booked, we went out for dinner by the water to celebrate something unrelated. After dinner he walked me down the nearby pier (in the rain and pitch black), got down on one knee and pulled a ring pop out of his pocket. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're attending a relative's destination wedding in Costa Rica in December so we're making that our honeymoon! We're planning on spending a few days in Cuba first and then flying over to Costa Rica for a few more days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm selling something on eBay for the first time. The buy it now price is $400, and someone with a new account/no feedback offered $425. My immediate assumption is that it's a scam, am I wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I wouldn't have thought of that. I'll make sure to check with them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotcha. It doesn't seem to be an RRSP, TFSA or DPSP. From what I'm reading it says it's a "taxable trust". It's a Trust Agreement governed by various representatives/organizations, and any income and capital gains are taxable and will be issued a T3. I assume that changes things?

Yes, Vancouver. I'd be interested in purchasing a condo (around 300k) in the next 5-7 years, but I feel like I don't have a solid enough plan to justify building a savings plan around that goal, if you know what I mean? I'd rather save for the long-term now and see if the market's changed at all in a couple years - unless you think it's smarter to save for the short-term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right on both counts.  

It looks like I can withdraw once per calendar year for a $12 fee, but have to maintain a $500 minimum in the plan. I can change the allocation of existing contributions for a fee, or change future allocations for free. I don't see the MER fees on the paperwork they gave me so I'll have to find that one out.  

I took a look at the PDF and I see what you're talking about. And moving funds to a different account every couple years sounds like a good plan. Thank you so much for your advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help allocating my contributions to an employee savings plan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm filling out benefits paperwork for a new-ish job, and one of the benefits is an employee savings plan. I'm in BC if it matters.  

I think it contributes 1.5% of my salary and my employer matches 2%.  I need some guidance in figuring out how to allocate the contributions between the four funds that they offer. I'm not asking for an exact breakdown (though that would be helpful), just a general idea. Mainly I'd like to play it safe, and I won't be withdrawing anything in the foreseeable future.  

Descriptions below:  

Equity Fund - This fund seeks long-term growth through both capital gains and investment income, by investing in a diversified portfolio of quality Canadian and US common stocks. Due to the nature of the stock market, the unit value can be expected to fluctuate more widely than the unit values of the Income and Savings Funds.  

Income Fund - This fund consists of government and corporate bonds and other fixed income securities. While investment income tends to exceed that of the Equity Fund, the unit value will vary depending on prevailing trends in both long- and short-term interest rates.  

Savings Fund - This fund is invested in government or government-guaranteed treasury bills and high-grade corporate short-term securities. The income earned will fluctuate according to prevailing short-term interest rates. This fund normally will maintain a fixed unit value of $10.00 and income received will be allocated to members by means of additional units.  

Ethical Growth Fund - This is a mutual fund which includes stringent economic, environmental and social criteria in its investment policies. The fund seeks long-term growth through capital gains and investment income by investing in a diversified portfolio of Canadian, and some US and international, common stocks. Due to the nature of the investment, unit values will fluctuate proportionally to the performance of the underlying stocks.  

Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:22:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally gasped when I opened the picture. Gorgeous :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I'm reading Reddit at the doctor's office right now because I think I might have tonsillitis! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha yeah... We're eloping specifically so that our families don't/can't get involved, and if I tell them too soon, they might try to come along or convince us to have a big wedding. He's told his family because they all live far away, I'm just waiting to tell my family (who are all local) much closer to the wedding date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We made that decision mutually maybe a year and a half into our relationship, long before marriage was a serious concept for us. The tipping point was the fact that his mother is completely estranged from not only his father, but her own family, whom we are very close to. We both have broken families but that was the big "there's no way" point. A big wedding was never even a twinkle in our eyes.

ETA we're having it at a destination so none of our family invites themselves along/asks why they weren't invited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you using anything from Mass Effect as readings? FH and I initially bonded over ME so I've been trying to find something to fit into the ceremony! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh shit, I'm a June 10 bride, when did my 100 day marker pass?? 

Stuff I still need to do:

- Send the jeweller FH's ring size so they can make his custom ring, but the sizer hasn't arrived yet  
- Call the other jeweller tomorrow to finalize my own custom e-ring (he proposed with a ring pop; I'm designing my ring)  
- Receive his backup silicone ring, tie, pocket square, watch, ring sizers, and bouquet in the mail - I check tracking info every day and it seems like nothing's moving!  
- Find a wedding band that suits the ring, prob need to be contoured  
- Rent the car for our trip  
- Get my dress and his suit altered  
- Get wedding shoes for both of us  
- Get wedding eyeglasses for myself  because my typical ones are too bulky for wedding pictures
- Get the marriage certificate (within 60 days of wedding)  
- Confirm my wedding cake (cheesecake!) because the food coordinator hasn't replied to me in a month  
- Send an invite to some last minute invitees
- Tell my family  

Oh god there's so much to do and 50% of it involves waiting for the mail... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, and it's:

At Emerald Lake Lodge in Yoho National Park in Canada. It is the prettiest place I've ever been! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:59:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Found it!](https://www.reddit.com/r/weddingplanning/comments/4wm1nv/we_did_it_we_had_our_dream_wedding_in_canada_and/?ref=search_posts) It's one of the few things I've seen in r/weddingplanning that's really stuck with me. Weirdly enough I just searched the sub for "perfect" and it was the first thing that came up, haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 02:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will! Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:43:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's starting at the ceremony, which is about 12 minutes long, and then about 40~ minutes of photography at a nearby forest/river.  We're eloping so there's not much to take pictures of! Just the two of us and about five of our friends.  

I think, because I was set on only having an hour of photography, I was in a better position to "splurge" on a great photographer. I'm sure if I was having eight hours of photos, first look, family portraits, getting ready, etc etc, I'd be a lot more budget conscious, which is hard because great photographers are very pricey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:31:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On the opposite end of things, I'm paying $400 for one hour, which includes a $50 travel fee for 2.5 hours of driving each way. Comes with digital, edited photos, which is all I want. I had another offer for $225 for the same thing with two photographers, but I ended up going with the first lady because her work is magazine-quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like there should be a question about whether the respondent has taken ballet lessons/has ballet experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This](http://www.aritzia.com/en/product/belgravia-dress/49407.html) in white! It was on sale for $40 in my size and I bought it on a whim at like 2 am. My first wedding purchase, too. It arrived three days later and fits perfectly!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:09:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're good at typing, Microsoft Office, spelling/grammar, and organizing, consider taking an administrative assistant or office administration program. I did an admin assistant certificate at a community college straight after high school. Took eight months, aced every class, and got a well paying job before I even graduated. I'm now full time with benefits in a government job two years after graduating, with plenty of room to move up. It's also a great job to get your foot in the door of various industries - I've had interviews/jobs with the catering industry, mobile games industry, managed IT industry, real estate...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:35:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Randomly came across this post and thought I'd answer your question, if you haven't watched the show since :)

Left side context: The main character (Rick)   his group find a survivor in the Center for Disease Control. The survivor wants to die and reveals that the CDC is rigged to explode/destroy itself. The survivor at first refuses to let Rick   Co. leave the building, saying it's better to die this way than to the zombies outside. Rick convinces him at the last minute to let them leave and decide their own fate. He is grateful, but the survivor says "the day will come when you won't be."

Right side context: Rick   Co. get captured by a bigger, more violent group. The leader, Negan, kills two of the main cast and then forces Rick to chop his own son's arm off with an axe. Rick struggles with doing it while his son Carl encourages him to just get it over with. At the last minute Negan stops Rick and reminds him that he is in charge of Rick   Co.'s lives now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seconding PinPin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome! Congratulations friend :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats! I'm sure you'll do fine, but listen, even if you don't get this job, your new resume clearly stood out and was worth noticing. They saw something impressive in you, and are taking valuable time out of their day to evaluate you. If this company noticed it immediately, others will too, so don't be discouraged if it doesn't work out this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:44:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same! Our broken families barely get along within themselves (my mom + stepdad vs my dad + stepmom, and then FH's dad + stepmom vs FH's mom vs FH's mom's family, whom she is estranged from), let alone would get along as one big group. We have 0 interest in bringing any of them together. Plus, his family is white, rich and well-traveled, while a large chunk of my family are middle-class immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, we're kind of doing the same thing. Our ceremony includes only my best friend, his best friend, and a very close mutual friend. My best friend has a boyfriend of about two years who isn't invited. Our mutual friend might be getting back with his ex, who is also not invited. But the reason is that we're taking them on a four-day vacation and paying for everything ourselves, so I don't really want to spend extra on people we're not close with. I also don't want them at my ceremony - my parents aren't even invited, why would I invite someone I don't even know?  

I'd be open to them bringing their SO if they paid for it, but that's an awkward thing to ask of them, and it's also awkward to then not include them in the ceremony. Luckily my best friend is totally down to come without her boyfriend.

If you were having a bigger wedding I'd say invite them, but the whole point of having tiny weddings like ours is that you don't want those extra people there. If you invited them you might as well invite your families and have a big wedding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ring maker and the cake maker haven't responded to my emails and it's been a week and a half! I'm ordering a custom wedding band for my FH and a certain type of cake as my wedding cake and neither has replied to my latest email. I'll probably just send them another email tomorrow but I feel bad because the exact same thing happened a few weeks ago with the same two companies where I had to ask them to please respond. And they were nice and apologetic about it, but come on, I'm trying to buy things from you, at least give me a status update! I don't want to feel like I'm bothering you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:44:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. He doesn't hate it, per se, but he gets visibly antsy when I talk about it for more than a minute. He's 0% involved in planning, other than the colour of his suit and tie and the design of his custom wedding ring (which he doesn't want to wear anyway). Luckily we're eloping and there's not much to plan anyway.  

I was stressed out about planning one day because no one was responding to my emails and everything was so expensive, and it just made him too anxious to hear about it all. So now I save the details for my BFF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PSA: Ecoflower is having a 33% off sale on wedding flowers until Monday (2/27/15) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:00:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Using the code BRIDE33 at [Ecoflower.com](https://www.ecoflower.com/)

I already bought mine at 25% off at Valentine's Day, but hopefully some of you can make use of this sale! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They didn't have the listings yet because Monday was a holiday in Ontario, where corporate HQ is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup! I grew up going there with my dad. Glad it got so much love in the latest episode, made me nostalgic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vancity on commercial and first should have one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit, glad I saw this post! I'm at the end of season 5 and was taking my sweet time finishing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:18:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're eloping! My FH also hates attention and gifts and being celebrated (to my chagrin - I love that shit). But mainly we both have big, broken-up families with multiple sides that don't talk to each other and I am not about to deal with that drama. We're taking a short vacation with our two closest friends and marrying while we're there. Plus it's so much cheaper - we're staying at a hotel for $800 for the four of us and they're letting us get married on the property for free. The photographer is barely charging $400. My dress was $40. The only thing we're splurging on is my e-ring and his wedding band.

If you're not comfortable with a big wedding, elope! I would hate to be anxious on my wedding day. Do what makes you comfortable. Your heart's gotta be in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My FH is doing the same thing! He wants to change his last name to his middle name. I'm down for it, but I don't really know what to do about contracts and such. Right now I'm explaining that "his surname is currently X, but he'll be changing it to Y before the wedding."   

Not to mention my anxiety about telling his dad (whom we're fairly close to) that he's changing his name, and all the $$ it costs to get a new passport, drivers' licence, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're going on a road trip for our elopement! We'll be taking two of our closest friends (as witnesses) for a 3 or 4 day trip to the first place my FH ever took me. I have a huge hotel suite booked for the four of us. We'll have a photographer but that's about it. Cheap dress, fake flowers, dinner and a tiny wedding cake. No idea what we'll do with our families afterwards - the whole reason we're eloping is that we don't want to involve them or have them pressure us to have a big wedding. Probably just take small chunks of our families out for a nice dinner individually, and be like "by the way we got married last week!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://mobile.twitter.com/TransLink/status/825836097716494337 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was so intense. Thanks for the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The free butter flavouring is margarine. The stuff you pay for is real butter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Legion, the answer to your question... was *yes*."

"I know, Tali, but thank you. Keelah se'lai." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:19:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ThisIsCriminal.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The dollar tree on commercial and east 10th has a bunch, just bought one the other day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:45:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was this: [here](https://m.reddit.com/r/Assistance/comments/hax0t/my_friend_just_died_i_dont_know_what_to_do/c1u0rx2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-02 09:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you haven't gotten one yet I just saw one today at the London drugs on Kingsway near Joyce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-03 00:02:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I finally got IT to install the manufacturer's driver and everything works fine now. Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:26:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll have to get IT to do that; unfortunately I need the admin password to do anything more than poke around on this particular machine.

You're probably right - the driver on the PC that works is different from the driver I was able to switch the PC that doesn't work to.

(Sorry for taking a while to respond - still busy working lol) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:05:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks like it's shared and the port is an IP.

I did manage to make it half work though - I changed the driver it was using and now it will "print" a blank sheet of paper with nothing on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it did - my computer was only connected to the printer yesterday (it wasn't recognizing any printers before that). Looking in Device Manager under Print Queues it says the driver date is 6/21/2006.

I tried to check the driver date on a computer that does work with said printer, but there's no Print Queues menu in this one's Device Manager. Is that weird?

Edit: Looking into it further, it looks like it's indicated as a network printer on the PC where it works, but not on the PC where it doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Windows 8, recognizes but won't print to one specific network printer; prints to other ones just fine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> New computer at work.

OS is Windows 8. Network printer is a Canon ImageRunner 1025iF.

Printing anything from any program (notepad, PDFs, IE, Chrome) yields the same result. The computer says it printed successfully. The printer itself will turn on the "processing data" light for a second or two, then nothing happens. Nothing in the printing queue on the computer side nor the printer side of things.

The printer in question prints fine from every other computer.

The IT dept "fixed" this for me by connecting my PC to a different printer, which does print successfully, but is located in a completely different part of the building.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-28 08:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Isosine - Radioactive Swimming Pools](https://isosine.bandcamp.com/track/radioactive-swimming-pools) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From an askreddit [thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/57x7t5/hiring_managers_of_reddit_what_is_the_most/d8w2d6y) yesterday:

I used to work at a fortune 500 corporate firm in a high rise in New York city. We would hire about 10 out of the 1000 applicants we received for a straight out of college entry position (base starting salary being 100k) each year.

We would have the candidates go through three rounds of interviews and during the last round, we would do panel group interviews - ie, you would sit next to four other candidates for the same position while facing a panel of five current company employees and answer the interview questions one at a time.
The very last question we would ask was, "out of all of you sitting there, who would you say is the weakest candidate? That is, if you were in our position, who would you not hire?"

It was a cutthroat question to say the least, but it weeded a lot of people out. A great majority of them were more than willing to throw another candidate under the bus, citing lack of experience, education credentials, answers to previous interview questions, basically every answer under the sun.

Those candidates were immediately eliminated in our minds.
The candidates that did indeed make it to the final 10 were the ones who answered something along the lines of "I believe that in order to make it this far in the interview process, we are all qualified candidates. At this point in the game, it is just a matter of who is the best fit for the company culture and environment."

We were a cutthroat and sometimes cold company, but we protected our own. We wanted to make sure that anyone who joined us would do the same.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://www.riverdistrict.ca/events/drive-in-movies/

South Vancouver, around Boundary and Marine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-18 03:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's one in the river district that's showing movies for the next month or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 02:07:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the explanation, I couldn't understand the idea before this. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Signing up for a new credit card. This question had me confused for a good minute. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 02:10:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much for the advice. We'll definitely try all that and see what we can work out. I was just feeling overwhelmed and unsure where to even begin, so this helps a ton! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently because my husband mentioned that it had been sustained at work. So the hospital expected WorkSafe to pay, and when they didn't, they sent the bill to us. We've been to the ER many times before and never had to pay. 

At this point I don't know if I can just call the hospital and ask why it can't be covered under provincial health care, since the bill has moved to collections already. But I'll try calling tomorrow when the billing office is open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Canada] Spouse went to the hospital over a year ago for a small injury sustained at work. We got sent a bill which then went to collections. Tried reporting it with WorkSafe BC to have them pay this bill, but they apparently can't because it's over a year old. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:26:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're in Vancouver, BC. My ultimate question is, where do we go from here and is there any way of getting out of this short of paying the bill?

Here's a timeline:

March 1, 2015: spouse is at work and hits his head hard on a metal countertop. Because he had hit his head at home a few days earlier, his work tells him to go to the hospital down the street. The ER asks about his injury and he explains what I said above. He waits in ER for a few hours before a doctor brings him in, shines a light in his eyes, tells him to take it easy, and leaves within three minutes. Not once was it mentioned to my SO that he would be charged or that he should be filing a WorkSafe claim.

August 2015: spouse quits his job with that company.

December 2015: we get a bill in the mail from the hospital for the first time for about $300 for this hospital visit. We get a bill in January and then February informing us to send the hospital the WorkSafe claim number to have the charge dropped. Otherwise, the bill will be sent to collections. 

Why didn't we just file with WorkSafe then? My SO was diagnosed with suicidal depression at the same time and had just started medication. I was working a terrible job and he was unemployed. I'm kicking myself now for not just filing back then, but it just wasn't the biggest priority at the time. I think I had tried to file the claim online around this time but was unsure of how to complete the claim since my SO had quit that job months ago, so I stopped and forgot about it. Yes, this was really stupid. I don't have a time machine, unfortunately.

July 2016: we get a bill from the collections agency saying that if we don't call them within 10 days, it will be recorded as a black mark on my SO's credit.

At this point we were both in a better place emotionally and were able to focus on this problem. I emailed WorkSafe asking if they could still handle this if we filed at this point. They responded telling me to just file it.

So we filed the claim. Called the collections agency and gave them the claim ID. 

August 17, 2016: we got a letter in the mail from WorkSafe. They needed confirmation of the date of injury. Apparently, according to the Workers Compensation Act, workers have one year to file injury claims. Barring extenuating circumstances, WorkSafe can't pay for claims over a year old (as I understand it).

Why don't we just pay the damn bill? That is the easiest solution, but I'm only working part time and he's still unemployed. We just can't afford it. I'd really really rather not pay $300 for a minute of having a light shined in his eyes and a "you're fine, just take it easy". If there is any way at all to eliminate or reduce the bill, I want to try that first.

*TL;DR*: Husband hits his head at work last year, goes to ER, they send us a bill which goes to collections, tried to claim the injury with WorkSafe 17 months after the fact but it's looking like they can't do anything about it. 

My questions: Is there anything we can do about this, and who should we be talking to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot! That's all great advice and I'll definitely keep it in mind. I'll see if I can use an empty room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it ok to do a Skype interview using the iPhone app? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-17 01:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never done a Skype interview before and currently have one scheduled for Friday for a potential second job. The recruiter knows it'll be on my main job's lunch break. My idea was that I'd just do it in a quiet spot using headphones and my iPhone. Frankly I've never used Skype on my phone before either so I'll have to test that out before the interview date.

I could possibly bring my laptop to work and use that but it's excruciatingly slow and old.

Update for anyone reading later on: the interviewer's skype wasn't working so we had a regular phone interview. But I had found a quiet spot outdoors at a picnic table where I could wedge my phone between the slats of the table and have it steady. I made sure I was in reach of wifi and tested my headphones/mic a few times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck. I've been reading your stories for years, since you posted the first one on NoSleep. I haven't read NoSleep for months now but yesterday I was binge-reading some of the top stories of the year. I got to one of yours today and wondered if you've posted anything new, so I checked your history and found this.

This sucks man. I don't know you but as someone who's gotten excited every time I've seen your username for the past 3+ years, this bums me out.  I really hope you beat this thing. Just do the best you can; I'm sure you are. This stranger is keeping you in her thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-01 02:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Necessary has one C and two S's - like a shirt, you can think of it as one collar and two sleeves. Or the mnemonic "never eat cheese, eat salad sandwiches and remain young"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-10 06:13:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've read it three times over the past four years and I'm not even ashamed of it.  

*This wall needs a mural.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-21 09:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 17 hearts later and I've caught Shellder and Tranquill, and seen Pidove about 5 times without catching it, and nothing else.  

Meanwhile, my husband plays it once and catches Unfezant.


Off to a great start! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-20 07:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone know how to get mascara stains out of a white tshirt? It's already been through the laundry and it's 92% polyester, 8% spandex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-18 00:42:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eighth grade science class. First day. Got a handout that covered safety in the lab. Immediately gave myself a paper cut on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Way too many people. Got there at 11:30, waited for an hour to get inside. By the time we got in, all the time slots to try the big ticket stuff were full. Tried a couple smaller games that were being run on Android phones, and those were alright but I own a Google Cardboard already so it wasn't anything I couldn't have tried at home.  

Stood in line for over half an hour to try the Futuretown booth - it should have been a cool experience but when I put the headset on, the screen was so foggy with sweat it looked like someone had smeared Vaseline on it. But the line had been so long and I was feeling overwhelmed already, so I didn't want to waste everyone's time by asking for it to be cleaned. I should have, though, because I could barely see what I was supposed to be shooting at and my experience ended in about 30 seconds.

Another thing I got to try was just playing Battlefront in a virtual theatre, which I honestly don't see the point of, but the booth runner made sure everyone used it for 60 seconds only so the line moved quickly at least.  

The one thing I really did enjoy was the 360 video of "natural wonders" which was really just aurora borealis. The headset was snug and blocked out all light, which made it so much easier to be immersed.  

We also bought 50/50 tickets and were told the draw would be at 5. We left at 4 to wander Gastown and came back for the draw, at which point we were told it had been moved to 7:15 but we could keep an eye on social media for the winning number. The number never got posted so I assume the winner was still present at the event, but that was a letdown.  

All in all, I'm glad I didn't pay full price (had 40% off student tickets) but I wouldn't go again. The ambiance kind of sucked too - less smoke machines next time, please.  

Editing to add that only 2 out of the 6 or so things I tried actually felt like VR. Either due to shitty focus that made seeing it in 3D very difficult, non-snug headsets that let light in, or headsets that covered part of the screen, for the most part it just felt like I was watching a video game on a small screen near my face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try Simply Wellness around Kingsway and Victoria - www.wellnessmadesimple.ca - if you call them, choose the Medical part, not the Dental part, obviously. Should be covered by MSP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-12 19:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-12 19:29:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the explanation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-12 19:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, thanks! Never would have guessed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Got a bunch of kitchen equipment from my grandma when I moved out two years ago. Just noticed this at the bottom of my baking equipment shelf - what is it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-12 05:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-22 22:36:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Similarly, [Putting the Dog to Sleep](https://youtube.com/watch?v=Xg8Ckamh8Gw).  

*You said I can't prove to you you're not gonna die alone, but trust me to take you home to clean up that blood all over your paws. You can't keep running out, kicking yourself off the bed, kicking yourself in the head, because you're kicking me, too.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-19 20:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god I've never met anyone else who feels as strongly about this as I do. President's Choice white cheddar is the greatest. The grocery store by my house stopped selling it individually, now they only sell them by the dozen - no complaints here, that stuff is legit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [XB1] LF1M NF, we're at last boss </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-12 22:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Post GT here or message nocturnaaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-05 00:56:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll send you an invite whenever we get it up and running, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [XB1][LFS] King's Fall, Warpriest cp - two of us looking for a Sherpa for 4pm PST/7pm EST! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-04 22:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Need a Sherpa for 4pm today, and then we can figure out the rest of the fireteam. 294 hunter and 296 warlock, haven't done KF before but we get the Warpriest mechanics.

Message me GT nocturnaaa or leave a message here!

Update: Beat Oryx in about 3.5 hours. Thanks chiIIr!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-04 04:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Invite Nocturnaaa and Ender Wiggin 12 please! 294 hunter and 297 lock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-24 05:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it doesn't work after trying everything, you can always go to the Compass customer service walk in at Stadium station and ask for a new one. You should be able to sync the new one with your upass/school account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 03:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't done the raids so I'd love to join at least NM - my GT is nocturnaaa and I'll be on until around midnight pacific. Would like to do it on my 34 hunter. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 09:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is, but the flag specifically says "get head." I thought it said "go head" at first, though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-28 08:32:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Get down girl, get head, get down." It's a Kanye lyric </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 20:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Legion, the answer to your question... was yes."

"I know, Tali. Thank you. ...Keelah se'lai."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 18:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Matador 64, because that range tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-17 04:15:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just wanted to share since I didn't know anyone else went through shit like this. In elementary school I made a club and all my friends joined. An older girl, who was my bully and a huge bitch, made a club called "Kill (my name)'s Club". A bunch of the older kids joined, including some people I thought were my friends. It really didn't bother me much at the time, just because I had my own club-running shit to deal with. But looking back, it was awful shitty of her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-12 08:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time I have an edible, even when I consciously limit myself to a very small dose, I cease to function. No video games, no reddit, no eating, no thoughts in my head. Just curled up on the bathroom floor, in my own personal hell, trying not to throw up.

Nothing against edibles; I'm well aware of their benefits to those who can't/don't smoke. Just not for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-15 05:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I picked up Haikyuu!! on a whim since I don't typically watch sports anime, but holy shit what a show. The OP gets me so pumped up, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-28 19:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read it for a second time last year, exactly a year after my first read-through. Here are some thoughts I remember having:

1. So much foreshadowing.  
2. Knowing what happens to Steelhooves makes every scene with him precious. Probably because he's my favorite. 
3. Velvet Remedy came off as a supermassive bitch in the first couple chapters, something I didn't notice the first time reading.  
4. Velvet and Calamity betraying Littlepip re: the PTMs was hard to read. I was angry at them on Littlepip's behalf. But at the same time Pinkie Pie's parallel addiction, heavy-handed as it was, made it easier to sympathize with everyone involved. Dunno if I felt this way the first time around.
5. It bothered me that Littlepip had somehow never heard of the Ministries. I guess her stable didn't teach that or something? But it felt a bit contrived to have that super-important detail missing from her education, as though its purpose was to allow for the reader to learn about the Ministries via exposition dumps. I don't remember if that was ever explained.
6. Lastly, knowing who Watcher is makes his visits more precious as well, and it's fun to read his dialogue in his voice.

I should also add that when I read FoE for the first time I hadn't yet played any of the Fallouts. By the time I reread it, I'd logged a couple hundred hours in both Fallout 3 and New Vegas, so I was able to pick up on so much more detail - parallels between certain cities, characters, abilities, quests, enemies, buildings. And because of it I was able to much better appreciate the things that Kkat added to the story, like the memory orbs. However, I don't feel that I missed out on anything the first time around. I just think that having played the games really enhanced my appreciation of the story.

Speaking of rereading, I want to read it again soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-05 22:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get shivers when he sings the words "deafening pleasure." It's beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-03 08:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as I know, the crossover was cancelled because FimFlamFilosophy made some sexist jokes and Sherclop got really offended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-08-02 09:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I spent the last few hours listening to the entirety of Deja Entendu and The Devil and God Are Raging Inside Me for the first time. So many of those brilliant lyrics are stuck in my brain.

"And I wish for one more day to give my love and repay debts /
But the morning finds our bodies washed up thirty miles west" - *Play Crack the Sky*

"Love is just God on a good day" - *You Won't Know*

"Is this the way a toy feels when its batteries run dry? / I am the watch you always wear but you forget to wind." - *Guernica*

"You are the smell before rain / You are the blood in my veins" - *The Boy Who Blocked His Own Shot*

"Hope you come down with something / They can't diagnose, don't have the cure for" - *Okay I Believe You But My Tommy Gun Don't*

"And in the choir I saw a sad messiah, / He was bored and tired of my laments, / said 'I died for you one time but never again.'" - *Limousine*

"I'd drown all these crying babies / If I knew that their mothers wouldn't cry / I'd hold them down and I'd squeeze real soft / And let a piece of myself die" - *Handcuffs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-23 00:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did, too. After about twenty minutes I was feeling terribly motion-sick and had to stop. Minecraft and Proteus have the same effect on me. It's a shame, because I really wanted to like Antichamber and the first puzzle I tried seemed very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-22 13:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometime last year I was walking around downtown and a man at a bus stop said, "Excuse me, miss, but have you been told today that you're beautiful?" 

I was in a hurry to get someplace, so I kept walking, but my brain processed it in time to say "Thank you" as I passed him. If he had followed me or attempted to make more conversation with me it might have creeped me out, but that's all he had to say to me and it completely made my day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-16 18:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one I've heard is Never Eat Cheese, Eat Salad Sandwiches And Remain Young. I think your version makes more sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-11 03:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haru is supposed to be the MC, but it seems like more of an ensemble cast (not sure if there's a word for that when you're talking about anime, but that's what it'd be if it were a movie). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-07 02:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for linking this. I just placed my order. $7 for 12 samples, AND it's free shipping? Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-07-06 22:31:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was already really popular before the show even aired. Hell, it was popular before it was even announced that it would be a show.

There've been daily threads on /a/ for weeks, not to mention the tumblr fandom (under the tags "Free!" and "swimming anime") and all the art on Pixiv. And this has all been going on since the first "Sexy Swimming" PV.

To a straight guy it's probably standard, but to a lot of girls, this anime is a dream come true - it's a show about attractive boys who are constantly shirtless and dripping wet. The fact that the animation is solid and the soundtrack is great is just icing on the cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-24 09:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The music in this show is so beautiful. That bit that played when Kasuga was talking about how you could call him and Nakamura friends was great. And I especially love this version of the OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-22 05:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Hentai Ouji to Warawanai Neko" is the Japanese name. "The Hentai Prince and the Stony Cat" (or "The Pervert Prince and the Stony Cat") is the English name. "HenNeko" is the shortened version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-21 07:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't want this show to end. I want another season with 8man and Yukino acknowledging each other as friends.

Then again, I also want a Saika ending, so I probably shouldn't hold my breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-20 08:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wept over Legion. I'd assumed that I'd done everything right and would be able to [make the geth and the Quarians work together, saving both Legion and Tali.](/spoiler) Noooope. ["Legion, the answer to your question is *yes*." "I know, Tali. But thank you. ...Keelah se'lai."](/spoiler) Fucking tears everywhere, every single time I remember that moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-19 06:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly cried during every single episode. Shit, I managed to cry during the ED of episode one and the OP of episode two (that's when I realized that I should probably skip them). I marathoned it in one night and I think something inside me broke. Randomly remembered the ending while on the bus the other day and it was all I could do not to break down sobbing. I just shed a tear while typing this.

The "found you" scene is as bad as the field scene in Clannad AS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-19 06:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hataraku Maou-Sama! is my personal AOTS; it's about the Devil lord from another universe taking a portal to Japan and becoming a human. So he rents an apartment with his demon general (who becomes essentially a housewife) and gets a part-time job at MgRonald's, where he meets his cute coworker who has massive jugs. It's really funny.

Shingeki no Kyojin (Attack on Titan) is pretty good since it's an exciting shounen action show, but the animation quality varies from week to week and the plot is really slowing down. Worth watching, anyway. The most hyped show of the season.

Hentai Ouji to Warawanai Neko (also known as HenNeko) is about... I don't even know. It's a comedy harem-ish show with a perverted teenage MC, a girl who is almost unbearably moe despite the fact that she has no emotions, a blonde tsundere girl who is also super moe, and the first girl's older sister who is hilariously stupid. There's also a cat god and they make wishes... it's gotten kind of weird these last few episodes, but it's worth watching for the emotionless girl alone.

Aku no Hana is really polarizing, so you'll either fall in love with it or hate it and wonder why anybody likes it at all. It's rotoscoped, and the first two-three episodes aren't very pretty (though the art gets a lot better), so it's offputting to a lot of people. It's about a guy who steals his crush's gym clothes, and the person who sees him do it blackmails him because of it. It's really fucked up and depressing and intense. If you have time, give it until the end of episode seven, which is just fucking crazy beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-16 04:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so glad that this episode was funny. The first two episodes of HenNeko had me crying from laughing so hard, but then the humor really started to slow down. This episode was a return to form, in that way, since it had me laughing the whole way through.

I'm pretty sure that the Tsutsukakushi sisters being mistaken about living with their mom is the result of another catgod wish. And I'm starting to think that Tsukiko is the result of a wish as well. I really hate how much of a dick the catgod is though, since it's granting wishes seemingly arbitrarily for its own amusement. Curious to see how the series ends, since we're down to two last episodes.

There's a theory on /a/ that Tsukiko and Yokodera go back in time and are actually Steel King's parents. This is now what I believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-14 07:41:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not disappointing at all! I completely forgot that the LN still has a bunch of volumes. I don't want him to choose yet; I just assumed that if the series was ending with one season, it would end with him choosing someone. But I think episode 13 is an anime original ending? So I'm not sure how that's gonna play out. Either way, I'd love to see more seasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-14 06:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ["But why do you want the sheep to eat the baobabs?"](http://i.imgur.com/BIIHAnw.jpg) ["Oh, come, come!"](http://i.imgur.com/woVoS3F.jpg)

*Hnnnnnnnnnnnng*

"I'll show them how to *really* change the world."  

Damn, that's ominous. What's he got planned?

Yukinon laughing behind her paper when 8man calls out the chairman

Oh god, I had to pause the show because I was laughing so much. I love that she couldn't hold in that laugh, but she immediately went straight-faced when she pulled the paper away.

Yukinon's awkward wave and "See you tomorrow"

God, I love her so much. Nothing else to say about that except that she's adorable.

Dat scheming Haruno

I still don't like her much, but she's fun to watch.

"Are you lot culturing?!"

What? Assuming this is a weird choice of words by the fansubbers, this is why I don't watch Commie subs unless I have to.

The Chairman fucking up the intro speech

As much of an awful bitch as she is, I can't help but feel bad for her... She really shouldn't have taken the position in the first place.

dat play

This is probably the cutest thing I've ever seen in my life. I can't stop grinning. Goddamn. And now I'm trying to imagine 8man in the place of Totsuka and hahahahaha

"Saged, reported, called the cops."

Thanks for that, Commie.

Yui and 8man going on a date, maybe

I really don't know who I'm rooting for anymore. Yui is a really great character, but I feel like 8man would get along with Yukinon much better (as evidenced by her laughing during the meeting). At this point, I'm guessing the season will end with 8man definitively choosing someone, and I'm pretty sure it'll be Yui. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-12 07:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a small selection of NYX at the new Target stores that are taking over Zellers, at least in BC. Mostly eye stuff. But you can look here for locations - http://www.nyxcosmetics.ca/index.php?pageId=15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-10 14:26:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What eyelash curler do you use? Also, your bottom lashes are ridiculously perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-09 12:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit, I love how intense this show is. I love that nearly the entire episode took place in one place, at one time. I love how batshit crazy Saeki's turning out to be, and how the more this goes on, the more I'm sympathizing with Nakamura. Kasuga's speech hit so close to home and was so honest and heartbreaking. And Nakamura crying and throwing Flowers of Evil in his face. And the way Saeki and Kasuga just stood in the police car's headlights and stared as Nakamura ran away. And her scream at the end.

Fuuuuuuuuuck. Seriously, this show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-09 00:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a really fantastic show. The art is fine, and in fact it really serves to enhance the uncomfortable mood and general wrongness of the show. It's also genuinely beautiful at times (the end of episode 7 is a masterpiece). I really can't imagine Aku no Hana being animated in a typical anime fashion. The rotoscoping, like the music and the dialogue, is an incredibly important part of the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-08 17:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've read the article. Sucking tequila off Salma Hayek's toes in *From Dusk Till Dawn* must have been the goddamn highlight of his life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-06 03:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It could be, but I'd gotten it from the small selection of books available in my elementary school classroom so I doubt it was a) a biography with b) a high reading level. Thanks though, I'll definitely look into books written about or inspired by those two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-05 15:30:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries. Thanks a bunch, I've been trying to find a good nighttime ab routine for a while and yours sounds awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [TOMT][Book] Children's/YA fiction novel about a phone phreak </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-05 12:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read this sometime in the early 2000s. It was definitely a fiction book, not a comic or a movie.

As best as I can remember: it was about a kid who lived in his parents' basement and learned how to hack phones (called phone phreaking). He had a nickname and made friends with other phone phreaks on the phone, I think, but he didn't leave his room. I believe he also lied about his age and managed to get a girlfriend over the phone.

I'm not even sure if any of that is right beyond him being a kid who was a phone phreak. I know for sure that this book was where I learned about phone phreaking and how it worked, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-03 16:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd really like to know your night time routine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-03 05:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I played Dear Esther long before I got this bundle, but I still remember it well. I absolutely loved it, but I'm a sucker for games that are more story than gameplay. I fell in love with its stunningly beautiful scenery and it's vague story-that's-also-a-metaphor-for-like-twenty-different-things which is well-narrated. I liked being able to explore, and I didn't mind the slow walk at all. The cave "level" is probably the most beautiful thing I've ever seen in a video game. I loved putting the story together as I went along, and after I was finished I really enjoyed reading other people's interpretations of the game. I didn't find it pretentious at all; then again, I didn't find Braid pretentious, either. I appreciated the prose. To me, it was an experience that was well worth my time.

I can understand why other people wouldn't like it, though - it's sort of false advertising to market it as a video game when it's more of an interactive story, and I can see how people would feel betrayed by it, especially if they don't enjoy that type of thing in the first place. The people who find it pretentious and boring are the kind of people who wouldn't have picked it up in the first place if it had been upfront about what it was. The lack of interaction, the slow walking and exploration, the metaphorical narrative - these aren't flaws, they're just things that some people don't enjoy and other people do.

Proteus, on the other hand, gave me motion sickness, which is a shame because I think I would have enjoyed it otherwise. Minecraft gives me motion sickness, too - I think it's because of the cartoony graphics... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-02 01:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rainmeter. [Download here](http://rainmeter.net/cms/), find skins you like [here](http://browse.deviantart.com/customization/skins/sysmonitor/rainmeter/).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-31 15:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did hardcore raiding and serious PvP in WoW for years, and now I find it immensely difficult to get into any other multiplayer games, and just games that are harder to win in general. It's frustrating to lose after becoming accustomed to being good at that sort of thing. It's also really disheartening to realize that you'll probably have to invest dozens of hours into watching videos, reading wikis, and practicing before you're at the skill level/win:lose ratio you're used to being at.

I jumped into SC2 right after quitting WoW and it killed me that I was losing game after game because I didn't know the tactics/forgot the build order/couldn't macro and micro at the same time. Back in WoW, I'd be the one that my friends and guildies would go to for advice. On a few occasions, I was even the one carrying the group to victory. To suddenly not be that person anymore completely sucked.

It's a silly problem to have, and I feel like an entitled brat for even complaining about it. Generic advice is "play games to have fun, don't take it so seriously, it's just a game, if you're not enjoying it, stop", but it's hard for me to take that to heart when, to me, 90% of the fun is winning. I don't get angry when I lose, I just get disappointed in myself for not being better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 06:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try to give Larry CPR? Nope. I hated him. I'd been friends with Kenny since the beginning and really, really hated both Larry and Lily, so I was glad to help him die.

Spare any or both of the St. John brothers? Killed the first; saw how Clem reacted; spared the second.

Leave Lily or bring her along? Left her. That bitch killed Carly.

Let Kenny shoot Duck or the boy up in the attic? Like I said, Kenny and I had been best bros since episode one, so I offered to kill Duck and the boy in the attic. I couldn't make him kill his own son; that's fucked up.

Bring Clementine to Crawford with you? Yeah. She was so excited to go; I would've felt bad saying no.

Where did you tell Clementine to go at the end? I told her to find Omid and Christa. Figured it was the best chance for her to survive.

Show the group your bite? I actually hid it the first time around and ended up with just Kenny at the end of episode four, but episode five fucked up my saves so I decided to go back and showed them the bite and ended up with Kenny/Omid/Christa.

Did you cut your arm off? Yeah. Not because of the show, though. I figured it would buy us more time to find Clem.

Did you save Ben? Nope. Kenny hated him, I ended up hating him for what he did to Kenny and for leaving Clem, and he was pretty adamant about leaving him to die so that we'd have more time to get away.

Other stuff: I took the food from the station wagon; figured we'd need it. I told Clem not to eat the human-meat. I saved Omid first because of his leg. I tried to save Hershel's son because Kenny was nearby to save Duck. I cut off David's leg to try to save him. I talked Kenny down on the train rather than fight him. I didn't let Clem kill Lee because I didn't want her to be traumatized by it; in retrospect she was probably traumatized by having to leave him behind, but I think she loved Lee too much to force her to do something unbearably difficult like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-30 04:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a visual novel that's been in development for a long time. You can read about it [on its official website](http://www.zap-apple.com/). Personally, I've been looking forward to it since I heard they were making it because it looks awesome and the character design and artwork are gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-29 13:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In addition to what the others said, it lasts a really long time. A single stick or tube of something won't run out for months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-27 02:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The scene where Joker tries to make her laugh and she snaps at him for not being more serious was painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-26 11:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, [Glaze's (WoodenToaster) remix](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t_6JKO_l9l8) is *awesome*. Kenny's version is nice and slow while Glaze's is super upbeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-25 04:46:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, fake designer handbags (and fake designer anything, really) tend to be of worse quality than the real thing. The materials used are less sturdy, the stitching tends to fall apart faster - things like that. The Coach handbag I've been using for years doesn't have a scratch on it or a loose thread anywhere, whereas the fake one I don't use all that often is beginning to fade, has a hole in the pocket, and is creased in several places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-25 03:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gravity Falls is a new-ish Disney cartoon about two kids, their crazy great-uncle, and a bunch of supernatural stuff. Kirsten Schaal does the voice of the main girl. The show is just completely fantastic and hilarious even though it's technically a kid's show - [here, have a clip](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uAvaThHyZ6s). Oh, and there's a bunch of stuff in it for the grown-up fans - the overarching plot is a mystery and there's a ton of cyphers and hidden clues in the show. /r/gravityfalls

Also, Regular Show. It's sort of on the same wavelength as Adventure Time in that it's a kid show with adult overtones. Supernatural stuff happens in it, too. [Have a clip!](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b5Kk7-uLGyc) /r/regularshow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-25 02:46:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here you go.](http://i.imgur.com/wAVCEL1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-23 12:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The Spirit of Redemption](http://www.fanfiction.net/s/6735812/1/The-Spirit-of-Redemption) is 162 chapters and 3,404,854 words long. For comparison, the Lord of the Rings books are approximately 474k words, and the A Song of Ice and Fire (Game of Thrones) books are approximately 1.77m words.

*That* is the longest fanfiction I have ever seen. I'm almost tempted to read it, but I feel like it'd take me an entire year... Granted, it is four stories (Redemption, Hunt, Unity, Victory) in one - but still. Goddamn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-23 02:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My computer was fucked the other day and (though I fixed it eventually) for a moment I had to seriously consider reformatting my hard drive - losing all my music and tv shows and movies and all the art I've made and pictures I've saved and things I've written? I could live with that.

Losing my Mass Effect save games? *Fuuuuck. That.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-20 08:48:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It helps a lot when you're searching for a particular comic and can only remember some dialogue. XKCD does the same thing with its search function, as does A Softer World. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-18 06:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The entire trilogy took me 80+ hours on my first playthrough; that includes a few hours of reading the Codex, hours of non-essential dialogue, and all the DLC (multiple playthroughs of Citadel). I'm sure you could finish it faster if you really tried, but I don't think ME is something that should be rushed through unless you've already done it once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-18 06:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't go Renegade/bad karma/asshole mode in any game with moral dialogue options - ME, Fallout series, and Telltale's The Walking Dead, specifically. Unless they've done something to deserve it, I just can't be a dick to people or risk their lives unnecessarily. I guess it's because I like to choose the things I'd say or do in real life to become more invested and immersed in everything. The game just wouldn't feel the same, and I wouldn't care as much about my choices, if I didn't do that.

That being said, I really want to do a Renegade playthrough. I figure I'll compromise with myself by being nice to my squaddies and being a dick to everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-17 06:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [How's this?](http://i.imgur.com/9tSBIdO.png) It's Bebas Neue and Adobe Caslon OsF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-15 22:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got my mom to watch the original trilogy for the first time last year. When this scene happened, she turned to me and went, sincerely surprised, "No way! Really?!" 

I have no idea how she didn't know, seeing as how my dad was a huge Star Wars fan, but I was pretty overjoyed to see her be surprised by the reveal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-15 01:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The funniest part about Garrus making fun of Femshep's dancing during the party is that [he's using the exact same dance animation](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=eXt9kVfLgjQ#t=32s). I took him to the casino the first time I played the DLC, and the second I saw him dance I actually had to pause the game for awhile because I was crying due to laughing so hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-12 11:20:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really did have to choose Destroy, because I needed Shepard to live so Garrus wouldn't be alone forever. :'(

Before I began the final mission, I spent a very long time trying to figure out which choice I'd make. I thought about it hard and decided that synthesis was the best option because Jeff deserved EDI and the geth deserved to live.

And then Garrus was evac'd during the run to the Conduit and *holy fucking shit* the emotion in Femshep's voice when she says ["No matter what happens here, you know I love you. I always will"](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=jTooTyDyXqI#t=138s)... There was absolutely no fucking way in hell I'd be picking anything but destroy. Shepard lives and they find out if turians and humans can have babies together, goddamnit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-06 10:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go to the [index](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1D6PJA5lrE0OzzS-ZC2kbf-4piyyuUdF-zniVqUs79uM/edit?pli=1#), scroll to the bottom, and click on the chapters you want. For each chapter you'll have to go to File  Download as  PDF Document. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-05 11:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't finished all the DLC yet, but I completely agree with what you said about Kasumi's mission and LotSB. Kasumi's seemed like it was going to be so awesome - sort of like that one mission in Dishonored with the party and the masks, where you sneak around trying to figure out who you're supposed to kill - but then I realized that Mass Effect isn't a stealth game. I was disappointed when I started [shooting enemies and breaking windows and no one cared or came to check what was going on.](/spoiler)

Lair of the Shadow Broker was just so much fun all the way through. Investigating Liara's disappearance, the plot twist (which I actually saw coming but enjoyed anyway), the chase scene ("Truck!" "I know." "Truck!" "I KNOW!"), the first battle - but the most fun I had was on top of the Shadow Broker's ship, using Slam on everyone and watching as they were blown away in the wind only to be disintegrated by the lightning capacitors. Then the final confrontation which changed things up a bit, and how the whole plot was resolved (which I also saw coming, but it was so satisfying, especially since I romanced Liara in ME1 and was really proud of how her character had grown). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-04 19:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A few months before Mass Effect 3 came out, I tried picking up **Mass Effect** for the first time. Unfortunately, it was at a time when I was the absolute worst at shooters and did not have the time to listen to hours of dialogue and lore, so I gave up as soon as I got to the Citadel. Three days ago, I woke up with the overwhelming urge to play something immersive, so I picked it up again. And holy shit did I ever get immersed.

After installing a hires texture mod, I played ME1 that entire day, stopping only to sleep, and played until I finished it the next day. I spent a long time listening to every entry in the codex, doing all the side missions, and talking to every crew member after every mission. And it was unbelievably fun. I got so caught up in the story. I loved how it was a linear game while still being relatively open-world. I loved watching my Femshep's relationships with the other crew members grow. I loved the Citadel. I loved the Normandy. I loved being forced to make tough decisions, or making Renegade decisions because I thought it was the right thing to do. I loved how my choices affected everyone and everything, even if the effect was as minor as a change in dialogue.

But there was a lot that I didn't love. The combat-pausing mechanic was awkward and interrupted the flow. The menus were obviously made for consoles - no rearranging of equipment; the dialogue wheel. There were a couple glitches like my weapons not cooling down and being stuck in elevators (I later found out how to fix these, though). Elevators! Talk about Elevator Simulator 2007, although the long rides were redeemed by the conversation between my companions and the news bulletins. Also, the main quest was way too short and there were a few instances where I continued on without realizing that I couldn't go back and accomplish things that I'd missed. The Mako segments weren't *that* bad, but the Mako itself handled badly. The equipment screen was badly organized and it took me a long time to sort through everyone's equipment after every few missions. Lastly, the final boss fight was a bit of a let-down. Oh, and it felt a lot like KotOR minus the lightsabers, but that's neither here nor there.

So after finishing ME1 (although I definitely plan on returning to it later on), I immediately started **Mass Effect 2**. And as fantastic as it is, I feel like for everything it does better than ME1, it does something worse. Let's list everything it does well: varied camera angles during dialogue; less annoying combat; no need to sort through equipment all day long; better Normandy; more companion options; more romance options (^I've ^always ^loved ^Joker ^but ^Garrus ^will ^do); quick load times; no long-ass elevator rides; more interesting and varied settings; frequent autosaves (although this has bitten me in the ass a few times); Joker's commentary on new members.

The worst thing about ME2 is that so much of it was badly ported to PC. There are no hotkeys for your journal/codex/squad. The keybindings in menus are completely arbitrary - why can't I double click something or hit enter, and why can't I use WASD to navigate menus? The planet scanning takes forever, but it's not so bad with the scan upgrade. Apart from this - the Citadel is broken up rather than being one big space to explore, which bums me out. The story is not nearly as engaging as ME1's. Shep's reunions with everyone (except for one) were a letdown. The Paragon/Renegade QTEs are pretty annoying since I usually reach for a drink during cutscenes/dialogue. Also, the ability to dance at clubs is completely ridiculous... but I appreciate it nonetheless.

So all in all, I really don't know which game I like better. I love the story and world of ME1, but I feel like the gameplay and overall darker tone of ME2 is better (the fact that people actually say *fuck* is wonderful). I'm tentatively looking forward to playing ME3 since I heard that the DLC makes up for a lot of the issues people had with it, as well as provides a lot of fanservice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-02 15:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It immediately reminded me of the "Do or Deer" fanmade episode that /mlp/ is working on in response to Double Rainboom. (You can google "do or deer mlp", but there's not much in the way of archives - there's usually a thread about it on /mlp/ though.) Can't really tell you what it's about since, last I checked, they hadn't decided on a storyline more specific than "something about deer." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-01 01:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was brilliant; my mom thought it was okay. Apart from that, though, I'll agree that it is incredibly polarizing - sort of like Napoleon Dynamite, where either you understand and appreciate and enjoy the overall style of the movie, or you don't and thus hate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-27 19:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [](/ajhappy) Petirep *is* the guy who does Rainbow Dash Presents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-27 19:05:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since you edited a misspelling, I thought I'd point out that it's actually spelled "eerily". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-27 15:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neil Cicierega soundtrack

What?!  

Ninja edit: oh, found it. I used to be a big fan of his, but I gotta say the current soundtrack is awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-24 01:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for doing this. As someone who doesn't own a PS3, your Uncharted movies made me feel less left out of console exclusivity. I can't wait to watch your AC movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-23 09:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try this fic - [The Vinyl Scratch Tapes](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/06/story-vinyl-scratch-tapes.html). Octavia and Vinyl have a radio show; it's hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-17 07:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GODDAMNIT! You can't put a spoiler alert after the damn spoiler! I've been trying to avoid finding out the twist of that episode for years. :(

Granted, in that time I could have watched the entire series, but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-13 09:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm on the other side of the country, but I get mine waxed at a nearby Vietnamese salon every few weeks and it only costs $6 (but I tip her another dollar). Also, maybe I'm just lucky, but the lady who does my brows just knows what kind of shape they should be in and does it perfectly. I never have to give her any input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-13 02:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These days, photos taken digitally have built-in data called EXIF data that includes things like when it was taken, what kind of camera was used, and approximately where it was taken (GPS data). The OP didn't bother deleting that data before he uploaded the photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 13:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shizune's route is definitely different, yeah. It's also great as a sort of "cool-down period" between more emotional routes because it's a lot more casual and relaxed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-10 12:41:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Save Lilly's for last, I think. Hanako's character growth is better in it than in Hanako's own route, so it would be bad to play both of them back-to-back. But I suggest this mainly because Lilly's good ending is very fitting as the end to the game as a whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 06:01:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've played Spec Ops: the Line and I do agree with you that it's a good contrast to PH. There are only two things about your post I want to touch on, but other than that I can see where you're coming from and you do make some very good points.

She's been through more trauma than virtually anyone can imagine over the span of a handful of weeks and somehow manages to keep going

I read through it from chapter 1 to 54 pacing myself for maximum value over the past 2 months

I think this is the crux of my issue with PH - that despite the story being over a handful of weeks, I've been reading since somewhere in the 30s and (though initially Somber did update every two weeks or so) it just kills me that, after waiting a month or two for a new chapter, the exact same shit happens with BJ every single time. Maybe if I waited til the story was complete and read the entire thing over the course of a few weeks, it wouldn't feel so dragged out - but the fact that a) the story is lengthy, b) the wait between chapters is even lengthier, and c) so little time passes in the story itself amplifies the "dragged out" feeling I get from PH. So I guess that's ultimately a complaint I have with the medium and not the story itself.

The moment there was a conflict over it and she figured out what the problem was, she tried to rectify it immediately

The problem is that Rampage and everyone else spent *ages* playing the "I know something Blackjack doesn't know" game and no one bothered explaining it to her (which is understandable given their personalities, but it was still annoying). The suspense of waiting for the whole thing to blow up in BJ's face just took so long that it wasn't even suspenseful anymore, and I think it would have been better had it been resolved sooner, though I understand that this wasn't possible due to where they were and what they were doing at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 03:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What I like so much about FoE is that it feels like it knows where it's going the entire time. The story is the perfect length, and things clearly move from A to B to C, so to speak. I don't think anything is dwelled on for too long. The pacing is absolutely spot on, character development takes just the right amount of time... Everything happens when it needs to, and takes as long as it needs to, then goes away when it should.

PH does the exact opposite. The first volume feels like it knows where it's going, and then it just goes on and on and on for the sake of being long. Things move from A to B to A to Z to K and back again and it just feels tedious. Plots get rehashed, character development either takes way too long or happens too quickly and then the character is stagnant the rest of the time, things that should have been wrapped up ages ago are still going on...

That being said, my favorite thing about PH is how and how much it expands the pre-war lore. Goldenblood is a fascinating character and it's incredibly interesting to see how much he had a hoof in. Psalm is an interesting character, and what happened with Doof and Twist was crazy. The Marauders mostly have recognizable personalities, and the fact that a lot of them are present in BJ's gang is made all the more awesome because they're so fleshed out.

I can't really speak about how FoE fleshed out the pre-war lore, because it built the foundation for it, but I really enjoy that it leaves things unsaid - although not having a name for the Zebra empire, while understandable from the author's perspective, is stupid considering they were Equestria's main enemy. One of the best things about FoE while I was reading it for the first time was finding out what happened to the Mane 6 and other notable background characters.

One of the things I hate the most about PH is Blackjack, strangely enough. I hated Velvet for the better part of FoE because she was incredibly unreasonable, but at least she eventually mellowed out and became likeable. I feel like BJ has gone in the opposite direction - while she was relatable enough in the beginning, her growth as a character feels stunted and the more it drags on, the more grating she gets. 

I get that it's nice to have a hero who feels conflicted about killing, but hearing "I know you [raped me and cut off all my limbs](/spoiler) but you said you're sorry and you'll never do it again so that's okay because I'm not an executioner" gets exponentially annoying every time some variant of it occurs. It's also annoying to hear her beat herself up about her stable, that filly from the beginning, etc. as well as her continued ignorance on how sex/relationships work outside Stable 101. I know that she's barely been out of the stable for a few weeks and that she's stupid (which is another thing I hate - her being stupid feels incredibly contrived, like her saying "I'm stupid plz explain like I'm 5" is a cop-out for Somber to not have to explain anything in great detail) but due to the length of the story it just feels like it's taking so much longer than it should.

Something that bothered me about FoE was the fact that Littlepip had never heard of the Ministries but had been taught about the war. What she was and was not educated about feels contrived for the sake of suspense/having exposition dumps placed conveniently throughout the story. I understand how no one had heard of the OIA in PH, but the Ministries literally ran everything during the war. Why didn't LP learn about them?

Lastly, I actually really enjoy PH's homages to anime because they break up the monotony a bit. Although I'll admit that my eyes glaze over during particularly long battle/action scenes...

Wooooo this is way too long. Okay, **TL;DR FoE is the perfect length; PH is too long. PH's pre-war lore is awesome. I hate Blackjack. Why didn't LP know about the Ministries? FoE  PH** but I still like PH and read every new chapter, but I just want it to end already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-08 02:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My first time in Minecraft (sometime in Alpha, I think), I didn't realize I could break blocks by holding down the mouse (I just clicked over and over...) so I ran around exploring and got blown up by a creeper. Called the game stupid and didn't play it until I discovered Minecraft LPs much later, then realized that *I* had been the stupid one *all along*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-07 02:07:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently this is a dissenting opinion in this thread, but I love the .mov series. I think they're entertaining and funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 10:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup! [At 16:40 in Neigh, Soul Sister](http://www.sherclop.com/v/neigh-soul-sister) Twilight says "Today, in a separate adventure, the Brohoof Bash, I learned the importance of loving your brother! Even if you don't always get along." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 10:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just rewatched it to find out -

[At 16:40 in Neigh, Soul Sister](http://www.sherclop.com/v/neigh-soul-sister) Twilight says "Today, in a separate adventure, the Brohoof Bash, I learned the importance of loving your brother! Even if you don't always get along." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 05:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tropico 4 was so funny. The mission where everyone starts turning into Penultimo was hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 03:13:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! They're so upbeat and bouncy. And I love how he sings this part in Song Against Sex -

*And all the drugs that I don't have the guts to take to soothe my mind*  
*So I'm always soooooober*  
*Always aaaaachiiiiing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 02:25:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone else likes On Avery Island! Last summer, the night before I saw Jeff Mangum live, I realized that I'd never heard NMH's previous stuff so I listened to On Avery Island all day and fell in love. At the concert he played Gardenhead (which is my favorite song), Naomi (which apparently no one else knew the words to), Little Birds and A Baby for Pree. During a lull I shouted for him to play Song Against Sex but he didn't. :(

Where You'll Find Me Now and Engine are some of my favorite NMH songs, and he did play Engine and I was happy. Sorry for gushing, I've just never met anyone who's heard (let alone loved) On Avery Island. Not even at the concert, which was the best concert of my life, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 11:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Classics, you say? *(for reference, "grimdark" generally means dark and violent; shipping is romantic relationship-building between two characters. oh, and most if not all of these were written during the first and second seasons, so a lot of it conflicts with what is canon in the show. just keep that in mind!)*

[Past Sins](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/07/story-past-sins.html) - crazy cult may or may not have brought Nightmare Moon back as a filly; Twilight takes care of her. I personally didn't like it all that much, but it *is* a classic.

[Progress](http://www.fanfiction.net/s/6982210/1/Progress) - pretty much shaped Luna's character in the fandom's eyes before she was fleshed out on the show itself. Don't read *Luna versus Ponyville* and beyond because the quality drops a lot.

[Fallout Equestria](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/04/story-fallout-equestria.html) - grimdark-ish adventure in post-apocalyptic Equestria. So good it spawned its own fandom-within-a-fandom with a myriad of spinoff fics. 600k words long. Absolutely brilliant (I've read it twice and plan on reading it again). Beginning is a little rough but after the first few chapters it's nearly perfect. You don't need to know anything about Fallout to read it.

[It's a Dangerous Business, Going Out Your Door](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/04/its-dangerous-business-going-out-your.html) - Tolkein meets ponies: Rarity, Applejack and Rainbow Dash go on a quest. A bit formulaic, but the characterization is completely spot-on.

[Somewhere Only We Know](http://www.fanfiction.net/s/7051532/1/Somewhere-Only-We-Know) - depressing as hell, but wonderful. If you want something sad, just read this.

[Simply Rarity](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/06/story-simply-rarity.html) - this one's really sad too, but it's one of my favorites. Coming into the show, I didn't really like Rarity - and then I read this (and *Dangerous Business*) and fell in love with her character.

[Bubbles](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/03/story-bubbles.html) - I've always been on the fence about liking this one. It's about Derpy's backstory and it's sad and it's a classic.

There are a lot I'm missing, but these are the good "classics" I can recall off the top of my head. Now, onto the **bad classics**...

[Rainbow Factory](http://www.fimfiction.net/story/5381/rainbow-factory) - grimdark tale about Scootaloo and how the pegasi make rainbows. Honestly pretty silly, but a classic nonetheless.

[Cupcakes](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1qTTzMqlRTHeHIarZZhwQhADc-1aff9fkHKWx-kn0wMk/edit) - grimdark tale about Pinkie Pie cutting up Rainbow Dash. Ridiculous and awful, but arguably the most well-known MLP fanfic next to

[My Little Dashie](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/10/story-my-little-dashie.html) - sad yet heartwarming story about a brony who discovers Rainbow Dash in real life and raises her. It'll either make you cry or laugh, depending on how ridiculous you find it. 

[Spiderses](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/08/story-spiderses.html) - Twilight gets turned into a spider and has spider sex with Big Macintosh. So terrible it's hilarious.

And now, fics that I never see anyone talk about but are **my absolute favorites** out of any fic I've ever read. And I've been reading fanfics for over a decade.

[Black and White](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/07/story-black-and-white.html) - a beautiful story about Octavia, written as a letter from her to Lyra. I recommend listening to the audiobook because the narrator has the perfect voice for it.

[Allegrezza](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/08/story-allegrezza.html) - great Octavia/Vinyl Scratch shipfic. Beautifully written.

[The Vinyl Scratch Tapes](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/06/story-vinyl-scratch-tapes.html) - finally, a story that's both great *and* funny! Vinyl and Octavia host a radio show; the story is presented in the form of a transcript. I cannot overstate how absolutely hilarious this fic is. Every chapter has me rolling.

[Forever](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/04/story-forever.html) and [Beyond Forever](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/05/story-beyond-forever.html) - aaand back to sadfics. This one's about Photo Finish's backstory. Beyond Forever is the sequel. Pretty sad, but it's worth a read if you like expanding minor characters' personalities and stories.

[Anthropology](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/12/story-anthropology.html) - okay, this one's sort of a classic. It's a funny story about Lyra and her obsession with humans.

[Tales](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/06/story-tales.html) - next to Fallout Equestria, this is my absolute absolute absolute favorite fanfic of all time and NO ONE talks about it! It's about Twilight in an alternate universe where she's the royal librarian, looking back on her life. It's kind of sad but it's just so incredibly brilliant that if you only read one fic on this list, you should read this.

[Yours Truly](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/02/story-yours-truly.html) - letters from everypony to everypony. Really beautiful story with lovely shipping and sad bits and funny bits and it's just a great, great story.

[White Box](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/02/story-white-box.html) - I can't tell you anything about this story without ruining it. It's relatively short and refreshingly unique. Also sad. I like sad stories, what can I say?

[Five's Company](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2011/07/story-fives-company.html) - everyone decides to confess their feelings to Rainbow Dash. Turns out she's the only one who's straight. This one is really, really funny.

[Pinkie Pie Watches Paint Dry](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/04/story-pinkie-watches-paint-dry.html) - let's end this on a happy note! This one is hilarious. Exactly what it says on the tin - Pinkie watches paint dry and contemplates her existence. It was also written long before *Too Many Pinkie Pies* came out.

...Holy shit, apparently I've read a lot more fics than I thought. And I actually had to cut down on the list. Welp. Sorry. Hope it was helpful, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 07:48:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit, your Dishonored album is beyond gorgeous. Dishonored has the most beautiful art style I've ever seen in a game and your screenshots left me in absolute awe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-05 06:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first time I heard In the Aeroplane Over the Sea, I turned it off 30 seconds into the song and declared that it was the most hipster bullshit I'd ever heard in my life.

Almost a year later, I decided to give it a chance again, and now it's my favorite album of all time.

I don't understand it either. I guess it depends on where you're at in life as well as, obviously, what kind of music you enjoy in general. It's a weird and unique sound, is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-04 09:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so pumped for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-03 09:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you break through the clouds at the very beginning of the game - when the music changes from suspenseful to welcoming, the parachute pops, and Booker sort of gasps. I actually leaned back in my chair and went "Holy shit" because it was probably the most beautiful thing I'd ever seen in a video game.

Sort of the polar opposite of leaving the vault for the first time in Fallout 3 - both moments were shocking and memorable, for completely different reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 08:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's both; "that feel when" or "their face when", depending on the context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 08:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There've been articles/stories on Everfree Radio about them before, but I can't find mirrors of them. All I got are the [Equestria Daily](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/friendship-is-magic-from-japanese.html) posts [from last year](http://www.equestriadaily.com/2012/03/friendship-is-magic-from-japanese_29.html) - I'm sure someone could find mirrors of the articles themselves, but they seem to have been lost when Everfree Radio renovated their site.

Anyway, from the EqD post:  
Fluttershy for example is apparently battling the top three positions with Cheerilee and Big Mac as best ponies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-02 06:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guest starring Lance Bass

My 8-year-old self just squealed in delight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 08:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't wait to watch other people play this on Youtube.

Damn console exclusivity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-01 03:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [](/wahaha) But Dark Willow was freaking *awesome*!

[](/sp)[](/ra20 "Bored now.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-31 14:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TTGL vibe from P-21

I wasn't going to read the revision, but now I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-30 14:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to play Minesweeper in class all the time. About once a week, without fail, someone would comment about how confusing the game looks and how they just click random squares. 

Learning how to play that game was one of the best things I've ever done. It's so goddamn fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-30 10:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disney releases episodes a week early online if you pay for the service; I can't remember what it's called.

Anyway, [episode is here](http://megafiles.se/v7hs52v9r3f4), just uncheck the box that says "Download with megafiles accelerator" if you're going to download it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-30 07:09:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I sat staring at the screen through the entire ending, and through the credits, and I only cried once they started singing *Will the Circle be Unbroken* in the video because it was so beautiful and it brought everything together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-30 03:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In addition to Kkat's "official" one, [this is the one](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AmdxxHLawBxTdGNOZDlCMVFBeDVrdGFOT2YzSEdUTXc#gid=0) I've been using for my playthroughs. It's a fan version, but it has the in-game equivalents for all the traits and some other things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-29 08:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Using "that" is optional; people will understand what you mean whether or not you use it, the meaning of the sentence stays the same - you'd really only have to use it to clarify what you mean, I guess.

"Sorry I hit you by accident," "Sorry I bumped into you," "Sorry your aunt died," mean the exact same thing as "Sorry that I hit you by accident," "Sorry that I bumped into you," and "Sorry that your aunt died."

"Sorry I ate all the grapes" is the same as "*I'm* sorry *that* I ate all the grapes" - "I'm" and "that" are implied in the first sentence.

Maybe it's not 100% proper if you're a grammar expert, but generally speaking everyone will understand what you mean to say either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-28 01:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not announcing your late arrival, you're apologizing for being late. "Sorry I'm late," not "Sorry, I'm late."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-19 03:38:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took the liberty of uploading everything to imgur [right here](http://eclipsedharmony.imgur.com/), but this particular chapter can be [found here](http://imgur.com/a/6qBrp). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-18 10:30:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's more or less my headcanon, too. AJ is muscular because she works on a farm. Dash is slightly less muscular because even though she's just as athletic, her job requires her to be aerodynamic. Pinkie spends all day in a bakery eating sweets, so naturally she'd be somewhat chubby. Rarity takes a lot of pride in her appearance, so it makes sense that she'd be slender. Twi spends a lot of time reading and not doing much, so she'd be average. And although Fluttershy is a pegasus who should be skinny and athletic like Dash, she spends all her time on the ground and eating healthy foods, so she'd just be skinny-to-average. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-18 08:06:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I'm in the minority here, but watching *without* subtitles tends to degrade my viewing experience. With subtitles, it's easier for me to catch things like character names and locations, as well as understand what's happening in general. It isn't distracting for me at all since I only need to spend about half a second reading the current subtitles before returning my attention to what's going on onscreen. 

Edit: Apparently I'm not in as big of a minority as I thought I was! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-17 03:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was really close to one of my teachers in my senior year. One day I did pretty poorly on an important exam and tried to brush it off as just having a bad day, but he pushed and I admitted to him that I'd been really hungover (I was the legal drinking age already, though). He just laughed, told me I could take the exam again, and then we hung out after school and talked about times our friends had gotten us way too drunk the night before important events.

Being friends with teachers is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-15 05:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's very similar to the original fic (FO:E) in that it features a female unicorn protagonist who lives in a Stable and can only really do one spell. But it takes place in a different part of the Equestrian Wasteland, called Hoofington, which is a really dangerous place to live. Blackjack, the protagonist/pony in this picture, leaves her Stable because these bad guys raid it in search of a program called EC-1101, and she manages to escape with the program on her Pipbuck. Throughout the story she's trying to figure out what the program does and how it's connected to everything.

The whole story is really dark (in comparison to FO:E and just in general), with more detailed violence and lots of really fucked up scenes. It's also really really really long (over 1 million words, and it's only like 75% complete). But it expands on the Fallout Equestria lore by introducing a shady character who ran things sort of behind-the-scenes during the war, before the balefire bombs. It also expands on the lore by telling the story of Macintosh's Marauders, Big Macintosh's unit during the war.

The characters are all fantastic and unique and memorable, as are the locations. Due to its length, it kind of loses steam after the first volume in that it feels like Somber (the author) wasn't sure where the story was going and so you start seeing a lot of the same themes over and over. Also it only updates about once a month, but lately chapters have been really long so it's okay. But that also means that you tend to forget things that have happened around the middle of the story because it's been so long since you read it...

Anyway, it's definitely worth reading if you were a fan of Fallout Equestria. It's not *suuuper* grimdark, but it's darker than FO:E. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-12 02:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know about anyone else, but most automatic emoticons (the kind that automatically replace :) or :(, etc) were pretty obnoxious and ugly back in the day. To avoid them, we'd type the smilies backwards instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-28 13:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it is, and I've read *I Have No Mouth*. I only meant that the words used and the way the sentences were constructed were something I'd expect from a novel, not a fanfiction. The story itself didn't blow me away, but the way it was written certainly did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-28 11:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy fuck thank you for bringing this to my attention. That was brilliantly written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-28 08:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres something you should know about me, I told him sadly.  Im not the Bearer of Honesty.  But I know her.  And I love her.  

also

"You are my message." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-27 08:45:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've probably read the Wikipedia page, but I'll just copy/paste what's there:

He also said that his film deals with the problem of people trying to live a decent existence in an essentially junk-obsessed contemporary culture without selling out, admitting that he himself could conceive of giving away all of "[his] possessions to charity and living in much more modest circumstances", continuing, "I've rationalized my way out of it so far, but I could conceive of doing it".  
According to actress Stacey Nelkin, Manhattan was based on her romantic relationship with Woody Allen. Her bit part in Annie Hall ended up on the cutting room floor, and their relationship, though never publicly acknowledged by Allen, began when she was 17 years old and a student at New Yorks Stuyvesant High School.

I can't really comment on it otherwise because I haven't seen it in years, but that should explain the "why?" of it, at least. Although something that has stayed with me is the fact that when Woody and the girl are with Woody's friends, the girl doesn't speak at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-25 08:18:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're fantastic. The main series is an adventure full of references and fan shout-outs (surprisingly not obnoxious or annoying) where Chysalis captures the CMC and the Mane 6 go on an adventure to save them. The art is really great to look at, to boot.

The mini-series is alright. It's about Twilight alone. It's predictable and more cutesy, but I enjoyed it.

You can read them all here: http://yp1.pony.pp.ua/book.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-24 03:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, when I watch FiW and then go back to FiM the voices sound all wrong. Her Rarity is perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-24 01:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god, the song. The fucking song. It was hilarious throughout, but I completely lost it when she ended it with I Dreamed a Dream. This is going to need multiple rewatchings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-21 09:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The tumblr story was fantastic. I love how serious and mature he made her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-21 00:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loved this so much. Two things, though:

~~Was that Scootaloo scene a reference to that scene in the Digimon movie where the kid is telling the Digimon to get up a few minutes into the movie? Or am I remembering that scene wrong?~~ I'm remembering that scene wrong.

And why the hell didn't Max include a scene where Applejack finds out that Apple Bloom is alive? That was a hugely important part of the jappleack tumblr storyline and even though the "Nobody cares, Applejack" part was great, it's really disappointing that he wouldn't touch on Jappleack's arc at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-20 09:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Melatonin always either knocks me out for 14 straight hours or wakes me up after 4 and doesn't let me fall back asleep. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-13 23:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's kinda what I've been thinking since we've only seen the one copy of the Toy Fair magazine, but this could have been easily debunked by Hasbro or anyone else who was at Toy Fair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-13 08:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [PonyPokey](http://youtube.com/user/ponypokey), creators of FiM: The Ultimate Abridged Series, have some games on their channel. The majority of them are crappy old MLP games, which are hilarious, but there are some non-pony games as well. They also have commentary for previous MLP generations' movies and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-13 06:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just in case y'all haven't seen it:

[Hi-res scan of the magazine page](http://i.imgur.com/6oJka8O.jpg) / [Video of the page](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RGid7Moeu6k feature=youtu.be)

I think that these tweets just mean that the crew working on EqG is going to be completely separate from the FiM crew, which is a shame but understandable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-10 02:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. It really should have, since that was a really important part of the book, but it didn't, and it skipped a lot of other things as well (like that part with Marconi where there's a wall of monsters that they defeat with music, I think? It's been ages since I read JDATE). Regardless, I liked it a lot. The dude who plays David is fantastic, and John is spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-02-02 03:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [I felt like it needed inverting.](http://i.imgur.com/FwsFIkE.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-29 02:14:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "My girlfriend sucked 37 dicks!"

"In a row?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-28 06:49:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god, the bathroom scene was so classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-27 05:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finding Dad in my first playthrough of Fallout 3. It genuinely made me so happy that I just stayed there going through dialogue options over and over just to be able to talk to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-27 05:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take your time. It took me 8 months to pick it up again after Hanako's route. Remember to save Lilly's for last, and please know that every ending, good and bad, is worth playing (although you might want to wait awhile before trying for the bad/neutral routes since most of them are really heartbreaking). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-25 07:44:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I genuinely started laughing so hard at her face that I cried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-01-23 12:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was stuck in that phase for a long time, and then 2013 started and shit hit the fan all at once. It's absolute hell. I'd give anything to have my "nothing is happening" back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>