<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject436</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hospital or no? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-09 05:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> D* on a 12 hour road trip...suggestions? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 14:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm traveling halfway across the country by car today with my fiance's family, returning home from a family reunion. One of the kids we're traveling with woke up v*ing this morning, so I rode in the car he wasn't in, hoping fhat'd help the fear. BUT. Right before we left, I had d*, and now that I'm in the car I'm feeling like I need to again, and I'm terrified that the entire trip will be me needing to stop every exit to d*, or worse, more of the adults start v*ing as well. I need suggestions or help to get me through this. Thanks in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-18 03:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-18 03:51:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you ate it yesterday, chances are that food poisoningnwoukd have kicked in by no and you'd be feeling something by now. If you haven't thrown up or had diarrhea at this point, you're probably in the clear. It might have been just an odd Indian spice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-20 07:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the tremor during attacks as well. My body convulses so much that it looks like I'm seizing. Klonopin has helped significantly, but the tremors still worsen when I'm anxious. I can't really comment on a consistent coping mechanism because I haven't found one yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-27 20:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wasn't really a fan. If Green was going to write about OCD, I wish he would have mentioned that it was specifically OCD, which he never did. I did appreciate the detail he took in describing Aza's obsessions, but I probably wouldn't read it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Alternatives? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-02 06:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have unbelievably severe pure O OCD. I'm on 200 mg of luvox, 2 mg of klonopin as needed (taken most days), and 75 mg of wellbutrin, and I'm still having crippling panic attacks daily, enough for people to notice and enough to hinder my normal activities. I have tried every coping mechanism/therapeutic tactic I know. I'm frustrated by the severity. I only have one trigger - throwing up, and whether or not it's going to happen to me or someone around me. I can't control it...or I don't know how. Suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exactly what happens to me! It's not necessarily a bad thing....it makes the weed last longer, but it's a fine line between being relaxed and being really anxious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That actually makes a lot of sense. I hadn't thought about that. Thanks so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ocd exacerbated by weed? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:19:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have severe ocd, and it seems like weed only helps if I'm barely high. Anything more than that causes me to worry, and often escalates into panic attacks. I've smoked several types of weed, and it all seems to have to same outcome. I enjoy smoking, but every time I smoke, I worry I'll panic. Has anyone had similar issues? Or, can anyone help shed some light on the problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> OCD exacerbated by weed? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have severe ocd, and it seems like weed only helps if I'm barely high. Anything more than that causes me to worry, and often escalates into panic attacks. I've smoked several types of weed, and it all seems to have to same outcome. I enjoy smoking, but every time I smoke, I worry I'll panic. Has anyone had similar issues? Or, can anyone help shed some light on the problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pure O. It gives a 4 step plan for combating the obsessions. It takes work, but it can be helpful. It's a good read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Brainlock." I can't remember the name of the author. It's fantastic.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:40:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same! Birth control really helped me out too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel your pain. My audition was almost 3 years ago. First off, it's not about perfection, it's more about how you react to your mistakes...be confident. You should be very, very familiar with the pieces, and you should put a significant amount of effort into them. Confidence is a big thing. Don't let one mistake shake you, and don't make any indication that you made the mistake. I'm sure you'll do fine....I was nervous in much the same way before my audition. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad you've found something that works! I take 75mg, and I have found that it does cause a bit of drowsiness, so I take it before bed, and that takes care of the problem for me. I do usually feel a little off for the first couple weeks after an adjustment, so that might have something to do with it. 
  I agree that it makes a huge difference. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-05 04:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I looked at the 148 page version on Scribd, but none of them include Two Little Words. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-05 04:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scribd is great. I looked, but didn't see that one. I'll try looking again. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In search of Steel Pier sheet music </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-05 01:01:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am in search of a copy of the song Two Little Words from Steel Pier. I have looked most everywhere, and I can't seem to find it. I'm hoping someone here might know. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-05 00:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't currently have the link, but Scribd has it under the piano book "Best Theme Songs." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> OCD/Anxiety Causing Migraines? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-02 23:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have pretty severe OCD, and one of my biggest obsessions is about getting migraines. I got my first one around the time I was 9, and from the time I was 9 until I was around 12, I got them fairly frequently... probably around three to four times per year. The OCD comes into play because I started obsessing over the fact that I thought they'd only happen every third month on the 27th day at a specific time. I know, it sounds insane. However, they started happening like that. I got braces around the time I was 13, and the migraines stopped for about 3-4 years. I had another one in December of 2010, then one in March of 2011, and I didn't have another one until December of 2014. I think about getting them all the time, and I'm wondering if the constant obsessing can cause migraines. Also, I get this strange dizzy feeling around the month before I actually get the migraine. It makes me feel like I'm moving when I'm not. I don't know if that's something I'm just imagining or if it's something that actually happens. I freak out pretty badly about these, and any advice will help. Thanks so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> OCD causing Migraines? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-02 23:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have pretty severe OCD, and one of my biggest obsessions is about getting migraines. I got my first one around the time I was 9, and from the time I was 9 until I was around 12, I got them fairly frequently... probably around three to four times per year. 
   The OCD comes into play because I started obsessing over the fact that I thought they'd only happen every third month on the 27th day at a specific time. I know, it sounds insane. However, they started happening like that. 
  I got braces around the time I was 13, and the migraines stopped for about 3-4 years. I had another one in December of 2010, then one in March of 2011, and I didn't have another one until December of 2014. 
  I think about getting them all the time, and I'm wondering if the constant obsessing can cause migraines. 
  Also, I get this strange dizzy feeling around the month before I actually get the migraine. It makes me feel like I'm moving when I'm not. I don't know if that's something I'm just imagining or if it's something that actually happens. 
  I freak out pretty badly about these, and any advice will help. Thanks so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 20:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would cause me so much joy, but she's only about 4 weeks old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 20:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The mods suggested that the title of this post needed to be changed. Both are true. The kitten was found in a dumpster after being abandoned by the mother in a fire. The cat was not purchased.  Thank you so much for the personal appearance evaluation, seeing as this is a modeling site.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found after her mother disappeared. Reddit, meet Blaze </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 18:08:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apologies. I'm very new to posting and am not familiar with the rules. I'll remove it as soon as I find the edit button.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rescued after being thrown in a dumpster. Reddit, meet Blaze. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 16:40:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> the Latest Nursery Rhyme </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 19:58:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>