<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9218</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 21:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed but the same would be true for hollowed bones I imagine, you may float better but people will likely still drown occasionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 20:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But star wars is dumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 20:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But our bones would be weaker (I think) and we would probably still drown, people can float they just freak out or get caught in a wave or whatever and end up downing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 19:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk where you live but the military can usually get people motivated if you need a purpose, even if you just go to boot camp or something. I'm not exactly sure how it all works and I actually hate the military but it's just a thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 19:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They already are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 19:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And texting while driving causes SO many deaths </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 19:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok maybe in a sense but when 2 morons meet then havoc can occur, aggressive drivers may run into the morons, the morons might cause a rear end collision, the morons might swerve into the other lane, they could crash by not using their turn signal... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 19:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, eww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 19:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 02:02:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok sure but a science based in chances, while useful, is not what I would call accurate even if by definition it isn't ever wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You said it, not me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:11:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe it but why is there a patch of tree missing, it's at,the bottom where the V of trees intersect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Easy solution, don't eat out and or don't eat meat and or don't order food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No but it's good, I assume we have more advanced sciences like measurements or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes, I've done that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They do but I'm just going to say that they dont </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suspect this is fake cause I didn't know dunes drop off like that and there's a weird box along the trees. It might not be, idk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:42:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doubtful, I imagine if we start running low on natural clean water we will just fabricate it or filter ocean water. However I highly doubt we would run out of water to the point where stores won't sell it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone does besides the dead and unborn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I say you're a nigger if I don't think I'm superior to you? Is that still racist? I'm a nigger, you're a nigger we're all fucking niggers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id like the freedom to say whatever the fuck I want. The one place where people will tell you there God honest opinion is the internet, why take that away? So the sensitive snowflakes don't grow up to face the cold truth that people are assholes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the tip system in America is stupid, even if I have a bad waiter or waitress I've still got to tip 20% or else I'm the asshole but I'm not rich so when I get a good waiter why the fuck would I tip above 20% that's already pretty high... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 00:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk why, maybe it's in your head maybe it's not, I couldn't say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Burn the money, all the money. But seriously that's fucked up, I've been in that kind of situation before where someone else gets treated like a king and I'm treated like shit. It feels horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But why do they like eachother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've run into similar issues, you can find your own psyciotrist although you've gotta pay more but you won't have to wait around. Just schedule an appointment. My mom handled all of this so I only know the basics, sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I know, I've taken astronomy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 22:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe try a theripist, I haven't personally tried one but I've heard good things. Although make sure it's the right one for you.

Personally I hate that people smoke and self medicate but maybe it's just what you need. If you don't want to do it anymore then you can totally quit but an alternative it just using it less or only in high stress situations. I'm not reccomending it, as I said I hate those drugs, but it might be what you need until you're in a better place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 22:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a good person to give advice on this subject, the last time I had a friend that I could actually trust was 11ish years ago, about a year ago they tried to contact me but I couldn't bring myself to reply. I do hope you find someone, good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 22:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uhhhhh Idk, I just persuade myself that they were shit friends and I'm better off alone. 

\_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 22:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit... Maybe u rite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 22:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, you didn't mention athletes like in the NFL. Spending hundreds of dollars to watch people hit a ball or tackle eachother just doesn't make any fucking sense to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 22:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you misunderstand, people are dumb. Also you can look at the sun when the moon completely covers it but I don't think your talking about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 22:05:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I doubt anything will make you feel as good as the weed does (idk I haven't used any) it releases dopamine. Exercise is a great way to get dopamine but as you said you want another option. Find a hobby, join a club, go to a psyciotrist for a better method of coping... there are lots of things you can do but it will take a good deal of motivation and will power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 21:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> U high </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 21:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A week is between Sunday to Saturday, atleast that's what I've heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 21:48:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I know, I was implying that the elephant didn't make a tool. It's using a fucking stick Idk what's so hard to understand. The title says "elephant creates tool" but that's not true at all. I do realize my phrasing was bad in my original comment. Also no, it's not a lever it's not being used to lift anything, it could be but it's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 21:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Higher than average in the animal kingdom although not nearly as good as human intelligence. Some birds, monkeys (apes idk), and even some kinds of ocean life I think have all been seen using tools and advanced problem solving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 20:01:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sexism at it's finest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 19:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All mammals produce milk, atleast most of them do I think. It's not like we go around and milk dogs or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 19:42:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it's so small you can't even comprehend it sooooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 19:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it's a lever, that would be like a crowbar or a seesaw. The elephant is using the stick as a tool but it didn't make it, a tree did... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 19:31:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell her you need it, if money's the problem you can get help for cheap  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 19:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah Idk either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 19:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not a lie if it's half a truth and if it's not hurting anyone I don't see a problem with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get this fortnite shit off of here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it's not really a tool, it's just a stick but it's still cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. Is This really needed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think your just beating yourself up, it will be better tomorrow. I'd wish you a happy birthday but I guess it wasn't too happy so I hope you find happiness soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well stop watching them to start with, after that seek mental help. this may sound like I'm criticizing you or joking but I'm not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe this is a Facebook post? Well it's retarded and just a shitty way to farm likes that equates to nothing besides a false sense of accomplishment, pathetic. But this is just a repost so no worries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it doesn't matter what it could mean if it doesn't mean that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about instead of specifically looking for bpd treatment you could try to just say depression or social anxiety or some other common mental condition. If mentioning bpd makes people uneasy about you then just lie to get the help you need. Dont imply your condition just accept the diagnoses they give you. 

P.s. I'm not saying you don't have bpd, I know it might sound like it tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 18:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well good luck, I hope they catch the drug addicted pricks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 17:57:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sound fucking mad but I'll ignore his appearance for now. I looked him up and he sounds like a fucking asshole and a thug, there's probably a reason his music was banned from spotify  (I don't know the details) they said he contributed to hate, that doesn't sound like love. 

Apparently he beat his pregnant girlfriend, id be willing to find the police report if you don't believe me. His death is thought to be a robbery and i don't know many of the details but it sounds to me like it was premeditated so I'd assume he was involved in some heavy gang activity. You really shouldn't support cunts like him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He looks like a phyco, I don't know much about him and Idk how he died but if you look like that then you've got some serious issues. Plz enlighten me about who he was thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 11:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sit outside for an hour and just think about anything. If it's serious then I recommend anti depressants and or a therapist. If you would like to elaborate a little more I'd be happy to have a conversation but I'm about to fall asleep so I'll get back to you tomorrow :) atleast if you want to go into more detail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 10:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try to make a change, maybe you've got siblings you could move in with or visit, maybe you could go outside and just sit without any electronics for a few minutes. Exercise can help, a hobby can help... Idk just do something I guess.

Edit: if you are literally feeling like you are reliving the same day again and again then you've got a brain problem and should see a doctor, although I assume you mean figuratively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 10:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If one of the main causes for your depression is loneliness then it might be better to just accept it. It sucks but it can make you feel better. that doesn't mean give up on making friends but just accepting the fact that you are alone and may continue to be alone could help. Atleast in my experience. I fucking pity myself and hate myself but those feelings are better that feeling empty and emotionless, sometimes just crying can make you feel 10 times better. 

This may not be good advice, im just a guy on Reddit so what do I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 10:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Testosterone is not a good way to face your problems. Find a friend, a new hobby, talk to a therapist (they can be cheap depending on your finances) if the root of your depression is just living then you should definitely talk to someone. Also what level of school, college? If so then maybe move in with your parents and explain everything to them. Stressing about school will only make your depression worse so don't worry about it for the time being. Drop out if you need to, I know it's not smart but if it makes you feel better then do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 10:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 06:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't spell dabbing backwards on rainbow 6 siege either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 02:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I meant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 02:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bad shower thought. Caves are close to the surface so the earth heat doesn't reach them Nd the sun can't heat it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 02:08:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo, that's fucked up. People are some real assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 02:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really want it but I really don't want it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 02:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you sure you didn't just drop it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 01:57:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are some nice puppys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 01:55:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a bad shower thought  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 18:42:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 18:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know you, so it goes without saying that I didn't hear you complain. And it's not just the thanos memes. Also it's the internet so why the hell shouldn't I complain on it????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 12:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too \_()_/

 try to set a goal 

 Find a hobby

Life is a blessing and a curse but once it's over it's over

Play video games

Travel somewhere

Talk to someone

Work out/ go for a walk or run

Help others to make your life feel more meaningful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 12:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. The group could be flat doesn't have to be curved

2. a building could be leaning slightly (they do that)

3. the earth is actually surrounding the universe so the opposite is true. (Hollow earth) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just tell myself "if i cant live for myself find someone else to live for" it becomes a quest to find something worth living for and thus you keep on living.

Also it would make your family feel bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cause real life SUCKS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I read it as dyslexia, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do love spiders but I'm also extremely afraid of them. The very very small ones are fine tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate, I've got dyslexia too and have experienced all the same things. I only feel stupid when I'm around other people because I start comparing myself to them. Although I don't actually think I'm stupid, I think I'm quite smart. But I've definitely embarrassed myself more that enough times to know I'm not an average thinker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why don't we all just bomb syria, it would fix everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh! I'm not the only one. How surprising :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe speech could make you feel more significant like quotes or something. Something philosophical. It sounds like you feel insignificant, correct me if I'm wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to feel like people could read my mind or I was psychotic and would say everything I was thinking without realizing it. It was horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:27:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As you wish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 10:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not familiar with the drug but I'd assume you would stop gaining weight shortly after. I can't say anything for loosing weight, also be weary of withdrawal, but again I am not familiar with the drug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:55:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's possible. it might go away in time, sometimes your body just needs some time to get accustomed to the drug. Heads up the withdrawal of zoloft is quite miserable, atleast for me. Be sure to take it everyday or it can loose it's effects quickly (according to my psyciotrist) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except that they arent butt plugs cause they don't go into their anus -_- 

have you seen an animal before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's interesting but I doubt it will lead to anything substantial. Language is dependent on education and social groups, for instance I am pretty articulate when typing but in reality I can hardly finish a sentence without stumbling over my own thoughts. I would be willing to participate however I've had depression for awile and only recently started posting to Reddit so I would probably just cause problems with the data :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 06:35:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. You have no say in this. All anyone ever talks about is "did you see the new superhero movie" blah blah blah and those shitty fucking memes that cover the internet for months, it's fucking stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 03:50:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People tend to be very caring around me, that stigma doesn't exist here. Although we do joke about it like about school shooters or something
P.s. I know its fucked up that I would joke about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 03:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really, if anything people seem to open up about themselves. It has caused people to worried about me though but no one has ever looked down on me afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 03:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not being spoiled, You've got a right to feel happy. sadly I don't know how to make you feel happy about your life, maybe whenever you feel sad try to do a hobby like drawing or jogging. Good luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 03:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please don't kill yourself. I don't know you but it makes me tear up thinking about it. Call someone, find someone that can help you. There are suicide hotlines that I highly recommend if you are contemplating suicide, atleast try it before you choose to end your life. Call a family member like your mom or a sibling. Just hug someone and try not to worry about what people expect of you  I can't say that things will get better but please just try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 03:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be willing to talk but I don't know what to say. What I can recommend is a depression hotline or something like that. A therapist could also help and they can be pretty cheap depending on your financial situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 03:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There has been lots of reasurch into depression, it's just not as common of a topic because people didn't always feel so open to talk about it. Many anti depressants exist and while they may not be a cure they can relive you of some of the hardships in life. I don't believe you can really cure depression as it's not an illness, It's part of the human body. While it is certainly an epidemic I think we can blame that on the governments and society in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 03:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's truly remarkable that they were able to accomplish it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bomb. Obama. Wall. Plane. Stolen. Trump. Whitehouse. Suicide. Sniper. Accident.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have absolutely no idea how people meet eachother, it's usually something like "we work together" or "my friend introduced us" or "we met at a bar" besides all of those I've got no idea how to make friends.

You could try to join some sort of community although I don't really know anything about those. Find people with similar interests I guess.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's hard to admit it to people. I feel that it's better just not to cause trouble for people but it's good to find atleast one person you can confide in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely relate to this. I think it's definitely because you know for sure that this is yourself and find comfort in that. Rather than acting happy or different to fit in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forgotten by all, friends, family, father. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was excluded in activities by my previous "friends" there were a few times where we would all hang out but a few times they would all go hang out with eachother and post stories to Snapchat about it. They never even invited me and would ask why I didn't come. I'd explain that they never told me and then they would make up an excuse.

My siblings too. Sometimes we all go out somewhere or make plans to go out somewhere but a lot of the time they just forget about me and go by themselves. My sister was going to pick me up recently so we could go look for a pet bird together. But she just didn't and I always feel guilty for bringing stuff like that up cause then she might feel guilty. Why the fuck do I have to feel bad when it's everyone else who just seemingly doesn't want me around.

My dad used to call me every day for years ever since my parents got divorced. Within the last 3ish years he started calling me once every week, I was okay with that. Then he started calling me ever few months and in the last 6 or more months he absent called at all. I've texted him a few times (like 3 or 4) just saying happy birthday or happy fathersday... he responds and asks if he can call me, ofcorse he can it's not like I ignore him. And then he just doesn't. It makes me think something happened or there is some sort of reason so I feel bad. Honestly I just don't even want to talk to him anymore, if he can't remember his own child then fine, im glad he left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 11:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I disagree." - myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 11:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anytime I'm asked to do a drug I always end up saying sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 11:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are 4 elements my friend. It all changed when the fire nation attacked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 11:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Also when your educated on a topic but to stupid to articulate it, maybe that's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 11:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has no will so how is that even possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 11:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't believe him, now I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 02:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's cuz an extra 2 months were added later on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 00:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on the individual also there is a pause in every buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see he found a fresh wire and decided to destroy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What fucking school do you go to where dogs are allowed!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fortnite is gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you normal, no. What people mean when they say "i don't think there is such a thing as normal" is talking about any single individual because everyone is different and thus not normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't trust those suction cups  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:22:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scientificly we might be able to.  Light doesn't travel on the axis of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Back" would mean undo in a sense, so yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:17:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you may be stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If we had no moisture on our body's it wouldn't do anything, if there was no oxygen in the air the fire would just go out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't seem to understand how it works, it's not a human construct, it's a byproduct of currency. You can print lots of money but the reprecutions of that would only lead to more misery, poverty, and starvation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, that is a horrible idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 11:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ikr, people are fucking disgusting smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you don't recall them. I once saw someone at Costco and made mental note cuz they were tall and the next time I went to Costco THEY WERE THERE, p.s. they don't work there, they were like 13 or something and with their mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:48:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do y'all close the toilet lid (the actual lid not the poop seat) when you finish?!? Cuz it pisses me off so much when people don't do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No girls allowed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't help you, no one can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:40:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If anything that just looks like more work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By that I mean just 2 of those things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have a few of those thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So much floof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It probably is stuck, it can most definitely get out but it may not know how/ to much of a pussy (get it :3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't believe you would creampie a child, smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, and I hate the fact that retards in the porn industry decided to call it that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've got a neck beard sorry to say, thats not nessisarily bad but it depends on who's looking. If weight loss is out of the question then Idk, your hair doesn't really suit you. Btw I'm not trying to be an ass, you look pretty average in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It ain't fire, nigga, it's plasma (fire is made of plasma tho) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You, sir, are being smart ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope world records aren't going to be around when that time comes. It's really stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A little bit of weight loss, a new hair cut, maybe lose the beard maybe not and ur looking good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HA GAYYYYYYYYYYY!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "When?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't you just left with the same exact string? Why go through all the trouble of getting more or less string? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a good thing I'd imagine, it means I don't have to feel ashamed when i cry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:12:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does unpair mean  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 10:33:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A person is smart but people are dumb

A person is weak but people are strong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 05:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think that's luck, evolutionarily I doubt that would allow their species to survive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 03:59:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It hurts me too when I look back at it, auto correct did not save me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What am I worth </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 01:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 01:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 01:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends who you are I think, some people can get by without it and live happy lives but a lot of drop outs end up regretting it in the future. If you cant decide what to do then maybe dont go for awhile until you know youre ready </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 00:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deleted posts of his show a lot of incosnisticys and out right lies according to a now deleted comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 22:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glurple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 22:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buy a trail cam, unfortunately they can be expensive but if you can catch her in the act then you should have all the proof you need. And tell you parents that you should be allowed locks, give them a key if it makes them feel better. She has no right to steal your money and your parents should support that, id hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 22:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 22:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it's called consciousness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 22:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't pin down a widely agreed upon definition but it seems anywhere from 8 to 12 hours would be considered fasting according to wiki. Basicly just a long period of time without food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 22:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would make it hard to believe if you post shit like that and then try to start up hate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 22:08:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love in America so I can't really comment of this but I'm going to anyways. First of all you shouldn't throw them all into one group classified by rape, robbery, and murder. Idk what the gun laws are in your part of the world but it might be helpful to get your girlfriend to carry one around or at the very least a taser. I am also unaware of the amount of police in your country but that is an option depending on the situation. Other than that blame the retarded people in charge and the ignorance of religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 22:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Live as moths do... also fire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I kind of can but it's hard to comprehend so you can't actively visualize it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can do it if you really try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While we can't see through eachother eyes we can compare eyes surgically. So no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's how time zones work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now my ears hurt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is suctioned to the roof of my mouth, it is resting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell her to stop or youll kick her ass, make her pay you back and lock your door. If you can't then get a different handle. If your parents won't solve the problem then you should be able to do what you want without punishment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's called consciousness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Snapchat has more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, daytime is just half the earth being lit up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 21:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trees don't feel sadness or anger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 19:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 19:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you're saying I'm a God, I agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 19:09:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google says it varies depending on lots of factors but anywhere from 10% to 90% and fiber is passed through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 19:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get it and I agree to an extent but in recent times it takes a lot of testing and regulations to get drugs into the market. It's not perfect and the drugs are far from risk free but it certainly has minimized the risks. I doubt anything too substantial as severe memory loss will occur due to these drugs however I do see your point and we should tread lightly. (Sorry if I sound pretentious, it's just a habit from writing in school) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:14:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> New borns are ugly but they grow up to be decent and then cute and then possibly hot or handsome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not if you're dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:08:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not an animal or a rock so what now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you even buy a single brick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:05:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not if you're tied up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No u </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I'm not the strongest if there is another player who is stronger than me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:58:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huhh??? You mean anti-depressants? And with whay proof do you base these claims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about an mmo, I get my ass kicked all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rotting things get sweeter then gross so maybe (like an apple) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wut? Side note why the hell did God put the Apple there if he didn't want them to eat it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A fast is 12 or more hours so that is incorrect. You've made me realize that it's called breakfast because people sleep for 8ish hours and prob haven't eaten for 12 therefore break fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Butterflies eat dead people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got about a 75% success rate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:42:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, you may be more vigilant but you don't retain any knowledge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not true, some went into my body to be stored as fat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:37:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a puffle from club penguin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think so, I think most murders occur out of anger and a disregard for the consequences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 03:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know so many geniuses lived in California </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 00:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 20:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 20:07:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Humans BUT who taught you how to do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:50:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never take an oath unless you mean it* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure if tattoos were a common thought it would happen? I can't recall ever seeing any but I don't really know anyone with big tattoos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:48:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't relate, all I've got to do is masturbate on a daily basis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:46:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ikr, let's do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:45:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Context is key, it could go either way I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An ass with nips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some apes can put underwear on tho, atleast I think they can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Time will heal but there will always be scars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What of you only have a knife? Is it worth possibly stabbing you brain O_O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe but I don't think the question is really looking for that answer xD also I'm no expert but it may be like blood type so the 1 person could be comparable with everyone else (o-) but everyone else could be each other blood type and thus non-compatible. I said that poorly but hopefully you understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the actual fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait wait wait... You want money?!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a good deal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exposure ain't worth shit (depending on what it Is but most of the time it ain't worth shit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, I've got the same dishwasher as you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it prob was to begin with and then the fag in the truck got mad and started doing that stupid shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, that isn't art. The nose could be art but the action the nose it taking is not art smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Breaks my heart, wasn't even mad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:00:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a dot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 06:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think they are, but okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 05:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rem is disabled, Emilia is best girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 05:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this porn??? Reported </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 04:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I see 2 dicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 23:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is this a screen shot and not a picture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 22:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trump is just the byproduct of the problem, not the problem itself. But yeah I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 22:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, it's ridiculous that instead of helping people with addiction we are throwing them in the same places as murders and rapists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 22:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just repeated everything, I am well aware of the situation. What I'm saying is that he should not have ordered that pizza or a pepperoni, he should have just gotten a cheese so that everyone can enjoy it -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 21:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 21:24:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Why on earth wouldn't he just get a damned pepperoni pizza" that sounds like complaining to me. Just because it's the most popular pizza doesnt mean everyone likes it, however everyone does like cheese. guess your reading comprehension isn't so good... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 21:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe your standards for men are just to fucking high or you've got a shitty personality. I'm a guy and I instantly judge hot/ pretty women for trying to hard and I associate them with sluts. Every woman I've fallen for was purely do to their personality and yet they never show those same feelings towards me. Also don't kys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 21:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vegans get the same treatment... also u are upside down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 21:06:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just do what you want to him. If he fuck with you then fuck with him till he stops messing with you. You can't just say "he looks like a school shooter" that's not how it works -_- he's probably just an asshole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 21:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pepperoni is disgusting, don't complain about him not getting meat dumbass. Not everyone will enjoy that or even eat it. You could complain about him not getting a plain cheese if you're that upset about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 20:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (I do eat a lot of sugar) it's kind of hard not to cuz everything has it in it and I hate cooking for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 20:56:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I disagree somewhat. I hate addicts of all kinds. I've never done any illegal drugs either (I'm 18) and I hate people that drink, smoke, use weed ect. I've never drank alcohol or smoked/ vaped, I think it's pathetic that people reply on those shitty ass poisons to get by in life. I'm extremely depressed and anxious all the time but you don't see me using that as an excuse for doing drugs. Side note I don't drink coffee but I don't really care if people do, everyone does it so I guess that I'm just desensitized to it although I am well aware of the side effects and I will look down on those who drink it like it's water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 20:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely agree, absolutely no effort was put into that and yet it's a famous painting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 20:46:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a thing as terrible art. Basic uggly shit is bad but I'd say that some abstract art can look cool. (If that's what you're referring too) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 20:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It already is hell, the government is so fucking shitty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 20:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Life can be hard, don't get so mad at him ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 20:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then switch, dumbass. Apple is the epitome of greed and people that buy it are the retarded sheep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 20:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love man eggs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 11:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bloo me by the zone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 11:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm getting mixed signals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 11:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That woman is like 80 years old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 11:01:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's your grandma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 11:00:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A girl has never looked at me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 10:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get your dog fixed, there's enough puppys in this world ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 10:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Level that shit up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play video games \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's always been shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you married him then I assume you like him xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you post to Reddit expect random people to reply :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brown eyes are like red hair. Red haired people have no soul and brown eyed people have no feelings. True fact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need to go to the poilce, I know you don't want to. Nobody does but it should be done. The girl is a lunatic and if she wants to be raped and maybe killed then it will be her own damn fault. If you are truly worried about them and you have proof then the police can and will (hopefully) help. You've got the right to feel safe. The longer you wait the harder things will get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 07:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe not but it makes you a retard for buying a worthless piece of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 07:55:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Headphones! but I agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 00:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 23:54:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 23 may be a legal adult but your still a kid, it doesn't matter if it's illegal or not. It's a family issue and while 23 may seem like you've got life all figured out I guarantee your still as stupid as you were at 17. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 22:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I too find this annoying, I just ignore it. It's mostly just retarded kids anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 22:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man up, cunt. I'm just kidding I cry like a baby every other month after remembering a pet that died or wallowing in my own depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 22:25:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, the guys fucked up. Make sure he didn't damage anything, not that he would be able to pay you back... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 22:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's a video that articulates your thoughts very well https://youtu.be/5bHimOJb-Xw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 22:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you just don't evacuate and burn to death??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 22:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are definitely smarter than the retards in that building.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 21:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not saying anyone has a right to look through your phone but you kind of asked for it. You've done hardcore drugs in the past so I'm sorry to say but you forfeited the right to trust and privacy. Two years isn't enough to earn back that trust. Your father definitely sounds like he has some trust issues but getting upset about it will only make things worse. I think you should apologize for accusing him, if he did do it then the guilt will do far more good in the long run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 21:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister's are in a similar situation. One of them is doing really well for themselves right now. I talked to her about her life and she definitely recommends online classes. You can go at your own pace for the most part and the work isn't absolutely exhausting. She managed to get a job she really likes recently. The company she worked at went under but she demenstraited her skills while working there and someone recommended her to her boss at this new job. She didn't have a degree but because of how well she interviewed she got the job. Confidence is key. Her boyfriend kept telling her that the squeaky wheel gets the grease. So she kept checking in with them about the job and was eventually was hired. You should avoid giving money to the church but that's just my experience with them. Job hunting is always hard but if you find one that you think you'd like then decently keep following up with that company to see if they've got anyone in that unfilled position yet. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 08:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Just be yourself" doing that may very well end in me being in a far worse situation in the social higharchy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:13:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All mine does is ask me how I feel, weigh me, and proscribe me more and more drugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you need a video for that??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 07:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Make friends" I've tried, it's hard to talk to people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 06:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> End it before it's to late. I'm just kidding don't do that  happy birthday!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 06:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in the same boat but every girl that I've taken an interest in ends up running away with one of my other friends. You sound like you need some anti depressants or better friends. If your younger then ask your parents to take you to a psychiatrist. If you want better friends then you probably need to open up to people more, that's how trust is built and how bonds are made. All you need is one person, a girlfriend is a good place to start but that's up to you. Maybe you could start things slow and try to be good friends before restarting a relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 06:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like you started the fight but that doesn't give him the right to be a dick. Depending on what you did you can apologize and he will likely do the same. If your really unhappy with him then leave. Although If you're constantly getting drunk and going to party's I think he's got some right to be pissed/ if you're a lunatic but Idk you so I couldn't say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 06:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it's hard. Honestly I would just tell your dad to fuck off, get your mom to divorce him and buy a new home where you can live happily. Life is cruel, it gives you so much but takes even more away. Make sure your brother knows you love him, depending on your age that's about all you can do. It would mean a lot to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 06:26:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (I only read the title). No, you can feel bad, I think it's completely reasonable as long as you don't highly dislike your cousin for it. Maybe your cousin is being an ass but just try to get over it, weddings are dumb in my opinion anyways. No point beating yourself up about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 06:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate gay people that brag about being gay, it's like they think of it as a personality trait. I don't go around telling people I'm strait so why the fuck does everyone need to know you're gay??? I also hate the whole pronoun situation, im willing to call you him or her if you ask me but I'm not going to call you they, if you tell me that you don't want to identify with a gender then I'm going to call you what I think you are, deal with it. I don't say this to be mean, love who ever you want I'm all for it but don't inconvineice me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 06:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like a dirty slut and you sound like a gay faggot who vapes every 5 minutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 00:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People in first world country's don't seem to know how to barter, sometimes they try to scam you but end up making themselves look like idiots and sometimes they are so stupid that they can't understand prices if they aren't clearly laid out on a price tag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 23:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know how old you are but you can definitely learn what not to do by looking at her, never even start on drugs and there is no problem. Your sister is a fucking idiot for continuing down the road of addiction.

I'm sorry to say but it seems like your family has done all they could for her, the only one who can change her is herself. I knew someone who was a heroin addict, he was my sister's boyfriend and ended up having a kid with her. He just recently cheated on her and left her all alone. We paid for treatment and tried for years to get him off the drugs but it ended up not working in the end. From what I've seen those who are addicted to hardcore drugs can only think about those drugs and will resort to all sorts of manipulation and crime to get their fix. If the baby couldn't wake her up then I doubt there is anything else that could help her. I know this is very pessimistic but I wish you and your family the best of luck, I hope things turn out well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 23:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 23:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What they don't show you is the mother swallowing the child whole... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 23:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if you roll the cart into the corral from a few yards away? Cuz that's what I do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 20:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pride is a deadly sin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 20:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Natural selection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 20:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Electric bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 20:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did somebody say vAulT tEcH? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 20:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One night I looked out my window (3 storys up including basement which opens up to ground level) and there was a tree frog chilling on my window, from that day on I would see it almost every night until my mom put my screen back on  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 19:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's toxic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 19:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glad to hear it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 19:51:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Next you'll probably tell me that if i like a trap then im gay, smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll definitely start trying it out. anything could help, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:37:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Side note, I don't really care if someone's had sex but I don't like hearing about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't agree more, I wouldnt want used goods but for some reason some people can't get enough of it -_- as soon as I hear a girl talk about her sex life or a guy who brags about some chick he banged I immediately hold that person in such low regard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One way to start a apocolips is create a disease or virus by modifying DNA in am existing strain. Even if it's very basic you could probably wipe out a city. Just give me a warning before you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:28:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hose them down if you can, the cops can't really do anything about it if they were fucking with you and if they're acting like little shits then I doubt their parents care about them so they aren't going to come after you. You could also get sprinklers or something to turn on if they come around again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:20:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1-800-273-8255 that's the suicide hotline, I don't know what I can say to make thing better so there ya go :/ atleast try it out, maybe they can help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The problem is that there are so many differnt groups fighing eachother, it's fucking chaos and it has been for many years. I don't see it stopping anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:12:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Atheism is by far the easiest thing to debate to a religious beliver. they cant hold a candle to logic when all they've got to go on is faith. If they want to try and convince you then just be rude and shoot down any argument they have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 12:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can either resist those feelings with all your might and eventually they will drown or you can let them run loose and possibly have an amazing, stressful, embarrassing, fun time until they fade away in a year or so. Or you could do something else but who the fuck would want to confess their feelings, that's scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your boyfriend sounds like a fucking asshole, if he's only in it for sex then dump him. Girls are so fucking dumb about relationships, Idk the whole situation but love should always come first and it sounds like he doesn't give a shit about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister is very similar, she's over weight, smart, and pretty but she drinks and smokes a ton and has a cheating heroin addict "boyfriend". In my case my sister is just really stressed out and has an unhealthy relationship, I've talked to her about it and our mom has been a big help to her. Just let her know you care and try to be a bit more forceful about what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you find out how to solve this issue, I'd love to know. I'm on anti depressants that are meant to help with but I still have to force myself to do things even the things that I want to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I reserve the right to call someone a piece of shit if they're a strait up asshole or take advantage of other people.

If you are depressed and want to kill yourself, I've been there. Things will eventually get better although you may still hate yourself but what can you do \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking chads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wax? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it should be fucking mandatory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:25:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think because they're beautiful people treat them like gods so they stop caring about anyone or anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a tern, they live around water. They're very cool looking and cute as they fly 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just tell them ur gay, they might stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 10:55:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I complain about being single and Idk if I have above average looks \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 10:52:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lolis are hot, children are not. I ain't no pedo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 10:50:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Breeders are bad
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 10:49:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Facebook is a shit site, don't use anything touched by Mark fuckaberg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 10:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something so cute ruined by "like a boss" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 06:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to cry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 05:15:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not if you can play video games and go to the gym :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 00:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's a jealous fucking bitch, lock her out of your phone and tell her to fuck off. you can be friends with who ever you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 00:02:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get a job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 00:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This reminds me of how some gay people constantly tell you that they are gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-22 23:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are also those nice few who decide to just shit and piss on the floor... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Stolen art? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-22 08:39:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A few years ago I had painted a beautiful turtle, atleast I think it was beautiful I have very little recollection of what it looked like and I never took a picture. Near the end of the year I went to go and get all my art to take home but I couldn't find the turtle so I just figured the art teacher misplaced it or something and I decided I wouldn't make a big deal about it. I didn't really care but just today I was thinking about it and I think SOME ASSHOLE STOLE IT I wasn't even mad about losing it until I realised this possibility and now I'm upset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 02:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's fix one race at a time please
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Traps are not gay! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-17 18:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>