<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5791</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 17:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great, thanks a ton! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The search button gives me a 404 error </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 17:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just downloaded GBA4ios 2.1 and when I go to the search button in the top right (trying to download Pokmon Gaia, if that matters) I get a 404 error and it says site not found. This is my first time using any emulators so I have no idea if there is a fix for this. Any thoughts? I'm running iOS 10.3.1 if that matters. 

Thanks for the help, and sorry if this isn't the right place or is a dumb question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 14:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remindme! 1 week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 18:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 18:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any chance you can pm me what this spoiler is? I can't see it in mobile and can't hit Reddit on my work computer. But I'm super curious judging by everyone's reactions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 17:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes she did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 16:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 12 years ago today we experienced the greatest elation, and then the greatest heartbreak we have ever, and will ever experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 18:56:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like the one sentence off screen death is really what made it hurt so bad though. And really summed up the stakes of the Last Battle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 22:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I coped your mom. 

Nailed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 05:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AND IT MOVES US ALL!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 21:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Technically all life we know of revolves around the sun, so good point on it not revolving around women. Either way, good luck with the job, hope it's brings some joy to all those harsh harsh realities you're so big on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 21:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big yikes here, I tried too. He told me I'm delusional and need help . Keep fighting the good fight, friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 21:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Too old to realize" I'm 24 bro. You gotta get some nuance in there and see some good in the world, I feel bad for you. But you do you man. I'll take my 5'5", 125 lbs soft-ass, allegedly-one-time-cried-in-a-kids-movie, not totally miserable self and... you know, go talk to some real women or whatever. Hope things work out for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 20:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aight yeah that's fair. Stereotype has British people as being traditionally more stoic and most of my family are Italian Americans who stereotypically are one step away from crazy people. I'd guess in your situation it's a bit cultural, a lot your own perception, and a healthy dose of just being a really emotionally confusing day. Stay frosty, homie.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 19:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So for one, sorry for you loss homie. But can I also ask where you're from, because I've been to more funerals and other such events than I care to admit in my relatively short like (24 years) and I have never, not once, seen anyone look down on a man for being emotional there. Nor have I ever heard any one of my friends saying that they've seen it. In my humble experience, it seems to me any negative feelings in that all come from within, not from anyone else. Obviously this is anecdotal, but that just seems unrealistic to me. 

Obviously there are for sure problems with how men are perceived when they are emotional vs. stoic, but this just seems to be a bit ridiculous to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 19:34:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buddy, you sound like you've been hurt, and I get that. If you need help, feel free to talk to this rando internet guy. That being said, the shit you're saying is so wildly out of proportion. 

Are men traditionally supposed to be more stoic, yes. Are there SOME women out there who'll see you as less of a man if you cry, yeah sure, just like there are some men that just see women as sex objects. But that's just a loud minority, and they're not the ones you want to be around anyway. You see these things and they tickle your confirmation bias, but the vast majority of people just don't think like that. You speak about our animal instincts but that's kinda the whole thing that separates humans from animals is that we can see nuance and are not beholden to our baser ways. For example, we can diet, despite our bodies telling us we need food. A dog cannot do that. 

Saying opening up is risky is only true in that vulnerability is inherently risky. I can promise you, the vast majority of women on the planet would prefer someone with a healthy emotional range, who can feel empathy, who occasionally gets nervous or embarrassed, who cries at the end of Marley and Me, as opposed to a statue with the emotional range of a brick. What women don't want is someone who's constantly whining, who's crying every day but doing nothing to fix their problems, who expects their SO to shoulder 100% of their emotional burdens, and who is constantly playing victim. But here's the thing, that's not just women. Fucking no one wants that. 

I'm not trying to be a dick and sorry for being long winded, but just take a step back and realize that we're all basically the same, just trying to find some happiness and meaning in life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-06 05:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd pay infinite money to have 1% of this optimism. Good on you, friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-12 15:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm going to spread it out a bit. Plus, I want to give myself some time to just appreciate the post WoT thoughts. Keep my brain in that fantasy world for a while  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-12 15:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clearly the taint hit this guy hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-12 00:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love any books/movies that can make you cry. That just means they're well done and were worth the time invested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-12 00:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo so true. Couldn't agree more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 15:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *laughs furiously in hand talk* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 01:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clearly this user can channel the one power because he/she is ancient. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 01:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's the baddest bitch in the business at that moment. It was so incredibly satisfying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I've never actually dabbled with audiobooks before, but it's something I may try with this series when I'm ready to revisit it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know he's too pretty, but that doesn't change that fact that her and Aviendha are my two WoT crushes and I think Birgitte and Mat have/could have such a great dynamic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was such a culmination for me. The black tower and ashaman were some of my favorite characters/storylines in the series. My friends kept making fun of me because I was getting frustrated that Rand wasn't dealing with Taim and the problems there and I kept asking when that storyline was going to come to the forefront. I was so excited when it finally did and Logain's arc, though it could have had more to it, was awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:50:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Strongly recommend giving it a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:49:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There should be a warning not to listen to some of those parts while driving. Seems like a safety hazard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Feel like that came back to bite her in the ass this time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Totally agree. Loved the sequence but a Rand v Moridin battle for the ages would have been tight. 

3. That's fair, there definitely could have been more top tier character deaths, but I thought it did a really good job of making even some of the second tier deaths really hurt (i.e. Birgitte or Siuan/Bryne). 

6. I've actually been mostly a fan of Nynavae for a solid 80-90% of the series so I totally agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I remember correctly I'd say she has a pretty big impact. Especially during the darkest days she was really the only one whose head he wouldn't bite off instantly. I'd say that calming presence probably saved a chodean kal aided nuclear extravaganza once or twice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope it's better than Aiel humor. I shall never understand Aiel humor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 14:38:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I remember all that now. Wild how far these characters have come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 06:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly, you get it. That moment definitely makes a running for the single most heartbreaking moment in the series. I'm not quite certain that it takes that top spot, but I wouldn't count it out. I almost lost it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 06:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have fun in the nursing home you geezer! 

But in all actuality if it makes you feel slightly better I was like, pretty close to being born in 92? Kinda? I don't know, trying my best here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 06:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right, didn't he like, call lightning or something at one point? That sounds familiar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 06:07:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lowkey thought it was fantastic. It was so chaotic and anti-climactic for such a dynamic character. While it sucked, it really shows how unpredictable and shitty war is, and I can genuinely say it upset me enough that I felt mildly sick to the stomach, which I think is probably the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 06:05:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is great advice and much appreciated. I've read New Spring, I read it before AMoL because I just didnt think it would be the same after knowing the conclusion. I'm also a huge kingkiller fan. 

I've heard fantastic things about Malazan, and that'll probably be my next dive into another big fantasy series, but I think I'm going to shift genres for a bit. I'm a huge fantasy and sci-fi guy, so for the longest time I always made sure in between every one of those I'd read something else, either non-fiction, sports, classic lit etc. Just something to get a different perspective. But then I started the Eye of the World and instead read 15 straight WoT books (NS included obviously), so I think I'll go back and fill in some of my other genre holes. Nevertheless, the advice is sincerely appreciated. There are so many great stories out there I'd hate to miss any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 04:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Egwene's death by itself actually didn't get me sad at all. I gasped, but she went out with such a bang that I was into it. Rand reacting to her death, however, was absolutely gut wrenching. I almost felt physically sick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 04:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm definitely excited for a reread, but it won't happen for a while. I have a lot of other books on my list. I was thinking of making a post in the next few days asking for any cool foreshadowing/tidbits/Easter eggs I missed in the first read since I won't get around to another one for a while. Feel free to hit me with some of your favorites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 03:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We'll get through it together, friend. But only just </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 03:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're less grim than I am haha. I thought Rand was going to have to watch Mat die so everyone else could get saved. I don't know if I could have taken that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 03:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the perfect description. I'm simultaneously full and empty. Buncha words on some pieces of paper have done irreparable things to my psyche. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 03:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's actually probably true but I shan't believe it and that is that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 03:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fine but don't come crying to me when I burn you out of the pattern so far back you wouldn't have even been around to issue this challenge, thus creating a time paradox and ending all existence. 

Also, fuck the Sea Folk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 03:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yer mum wears snug brocaded breeches!
Nah, jokes aside though, I'd respectfully disagree with your point. I feel like min actually had the least reason to fall in love with Rand. She briefly met him once, then all the sudden she was in love? I don't buy it. Contrast that to Rand and Avi in the waste, all the time they spent together, their fights but also slowly growing respect, Avi's growing internal conflict over being Elayne's friend but knowing her feelings for Rand, and Rand growing fond of her because she sees him as Rand (who she still hates at the time), not as the car'a'carn I feel like the way their relationship grew was the most natural and most in character. Also come on, after her maiden and wise one training she's gotta have the body of an absolute smokeshow. Sorry I can go on about this forever.

I will give Min credit where it is due though. She may not have fallen in love in any reasonable fashion, however, her companionship during the Darth Rand days was huge and shan't be forgotten.

Also also, in regards to your controversial opinion, I am not actually sure what I believe. If that brings about the vision Rand saw with no strife but also no choice, that's kinda dark too. It's a hard conundrum and I have yet to fully decide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 03:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right?! I like to think I'm the kind of guy who's nicely in touch with my emotions, and I've shed a tear or 2 during a book before, but I can't think of another one that had the sheer number of moments that made me get a bit soft. Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 03:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn dude I wasn't even born in '92, that's wild. But yeah it really was. I feel like a changed man now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 02:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That part scared me, I couldn't see how he was going to get out of that, and then Rand started focusing on Mat and I thought Mat was going to have to get sacrificed so Olvar could call the heroes. Scared the tits off me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 02:28:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit how could I forget Birgitte in my write up?! Her death might have been the one that hit me the hardest, between the fact that it came out of nowhere, the brutality, and what it meant for Elayne and the twins. Absolutely gut wrenching, followed by one of the most badass revenge moments in the biz. 

There is a reason I still say her and Mat are meant to be together, and that's because they're both fucking awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 02:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't you soil her name like that! She's not dead she was just taking a strategic nap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 02:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's one way to look at it! It's definitely in character, but obviously we don't know and won't know. I can't decide what I want my headcanon to be yet. There's still so much to process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 01:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loved this moment. I had kinda pictured him looking like my younger brother when he had been described earlier so when he went mad that kinda hit me hard. Definitely think this is an underrated moment in the series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Spoilers AMoL] I just finished a memory of light for the first time. My soul is in shambles. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 01:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have so many thoughts. I've been reading this series basically nonstop for over a year and the journey is finally over. My brain is scrambled. I don't know what to do with my hands. This parting hurts more than any breakup I've ever had. I have so many thoughts.

1. Rand vs the DO. My Lord what a sequence, every bit of it was just a treat to read. All the different possible future scenarios, Rand almost breaking. Just wow.

2. Egwene going out like an absolute rock star. Taking out M'Hael using just nuclear amounts of the power. We will miss you dearly, Eggy, you lovable annoying stubborn queen.

3. So much death. We went through 13 books with almost no major deaths, then in the span of a few hundred pages my heart gets ripped out time after time. When Rand is sitting there watching all the threads wink out - Bashere, Egwene, Jori Congar, Hurin, Lan (thankfully not actually dead) - That scene was heart shattering.

4. Bit surprised Moghedein was effectively the last foresaken standing. I thought it would be Demandred or maybe Lanfear as they have much more of a "final boss" vibe. Though this fits Moggy's character.

5. Aviendha vs. Graendal was FLAAAMES! If you don't think she's the best one of Rand's harem of heroines, we will never see eye to eye. 

6. Lan's ride at the beginning into what he thought was certain death. Straight up sacrifice of farimir from LotR vibes there. I re-read the scene while listening to Pippin's edge of night song and boy was it exquiusite. 

7. That end. I'm so conflicted. It was beautiful and exceptional and also so sad that Perrin and Mat and Nynevae and poor Tam have to think Rand is dead. Tam lighting the pyre made me cry, and as a mid-20s adult man I am not ashamed to admit that.

All of this and so much more. Sorry for the long text, I am just trying to unscramble my brain. Hit me with some reactions and discussions and some therapy so I can get over this separation and put my life back together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-02 16:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Strong yes. Maybe I'm biased since I'm currently right in the middle of the last book, but I can honestly say that I'm on a different planet right now. There are definitely some things that might get annoying depending on what you do or don't like, but holy crap is the payoff worth it. The magic system is great, the bad guys are super fun, and there are without a doubt some of the most epic moments I've ever seen in a fantasy series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-20 02:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are  a wonderful person, a true gem. Thanks a ton, I'll give it a try sometime this week/weekend and let you know if I fuck it up somehow and end up with more questions. 

As for streaming/recording, I'm not much of a twitch guy. I've never recorded but I'd be more than happy to give it a shot if you're particularly interested. Though I'm not sure how exciting my play style will be. I rarely play past king or emperor difficulty and usually play with some sort of roleplay in mind as opposed to straight min/maxing which often leads to more peaceful games, or sometimes seemingly nonsensical decisions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-20 02:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No he's on third </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-18 20:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have a question about mods for civ vi. I'm assuming this is pretty common but I've never played with mods before, so figured I'd ask. I'm looking to play a larger earth map than the default one (I know this exists as I hear people talk about it a lot). Preferably a map that lets me have more than the standard 8 civs. The ability to do a true-start location would be an added bonus. 

Can anyone tell me how/where to get this? I'm on steam but have no experience at all with mods and don't want to fuck it up. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-11 21:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So kind of oblivion-esque then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 16:32:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo what is this a reference to?! This was the first thing I thought when someone said "local yokel" and I can't for the life of me remember why I know it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 00:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah wow I didn't even think of it like that. Good looks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 04:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm super late to this but I just finished COT and was looking up old threads on it... can you briefly elaborate on this? I won't have WH available to me for a few days and I'm curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 16:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was a good joke  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 16:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is great! Do you know if this has spoilers through each individual book, or just up to each one?

So for example I'm currently on chapter 6 of crossroads of twilight, so can I read the character descriptions for CoT on this site, or will it spoil the end of the book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 15:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neal Peart stands alone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-14 15:38:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, but you (or at least we as a society) do, I assume, know artists entertainers like Shakespeare, Chekov, or Homer. Obviously many of our celebrities are just pop culture icons not nearly on the same level as those above, but plenty of actors/entertainers/other pop culture personalities of today might be remembered on a similar level. And for good reason, their cultural contribution is just as important a part of the human story as the contributions of great scientists, just in a different way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-05 22:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the Mets, they won't be. Don't worry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-02 02:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We are totally in agreement, friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 19:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah when Rand starts working with the crazy voice in his head, everyone else better watch out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 19:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was when I knew this was gonna be one hell of a fight. So bad ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 19:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds kinda hot to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 17:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Ashaman kill" had me feeling all sorts of ways. 

In terms of faile I just think it's ridiculous that she gives him the cold shoulder for weeks when Perrin is clearly trying to do anything he can to avoid stalker-y berelain. Also my choice of Rand's ladies I think has to be Aviendha so far. To each his own  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 16:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it can't be. Adding that onto the already rough combo inevitable taint madness and Rand having a disembodied loony toon sharing his head and we have a nice conception of craziness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Spoilers LoC] I just finished LoC, please help untangle my brain. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 15:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy moly the end of this book. From when the Salidar Aes sedai try to intimidate Rand all through the end was one hell of a ride. I have so many thoughts

1. Aes Sedai SUCK. I used to think they were cool but they are so disgustingly arrogant and manipulative. You'll never get anything done if you're always trying to outmaneuver people. Like did we forget that the end of the world is coming, maybe let's try to work as a team with the only hope of defeating it. 

2. Perrin is far too good for Faile. Also his armies of wolves are just so bad ass. 

3. The ashaman are scary af. Really want to see more of them. 

4. I forgot about Demandred in the prologue until he showed up again in the epilogue and was getting congratulated, so that makes me think he was right under my nose the whole time. Still trying to figure out who. My top guess is Taim, but he also could be one of the random nobles, or someone else I'm missing entirely. 

5. We've been building up to Rand's master plan against sammael for like 1800 pages now. Can't tell if the payoff is going to be absolutely amazing, or a giant case of never ending blue balls

Sorry for the long post. My brain is all in a pretzel after that ending. Cheers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-23 20:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey guys, I saw last week that espn was adding new keeper functionality, but it seems that that was a false hope. Does anyone have any advice on the best way to draft for a keeper league, for reference our rules are 3 keepers, kept the round they were drafted. You can't keep anyone from the first 3 rounds and if they were picked up mid season theyre an auto 10th round pick. I know this is kinda complicated so if anyone has any ideas please let me know. Also if it would be better to ask this as it's own post, let me know too. Please help out this commissioner who has no idea what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-09 02:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it's the equivalent of a nuke then thank god Rand doesn't live his life the way I play civ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 23:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you bot friend. I needed that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 23:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank god I was in meetings all day and didn't get to see this until the spoilers were removed. Would have been quite miffed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 23:32:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That makes sense. You really didn't get that perspective from Rahvin at the time but I've just read a few of the chapters from Lord of Chaos from the perspective of Sammael, Semirhage etc. and you get a better sense of how they're for sure wary of him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 23:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also slaps on the bottom. I don't want to miss out on all of those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 23:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pointing out that that is a healthy response is probably exactly why that never even occurred to me. \_()_/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 23:28:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it basically is described as a drug whenever they talk about the effects. Rand's got that good good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 23:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair I was mainly asking why he didn't use it when fighting Rahvin/Lanfear, so in those cases overkill is probably a good thing. But regardless I get your point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 16:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being a god does sound like it involves a lot of unnecessary responsibility... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 16:55:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair, my tea consumption has gone way up since I started this series so RJ clearly had untapped marketing potential. 

But yeah all good points. Makes sense to me, I just wanted to make sure there wasn't some clearly expressed reason I was forgetting. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 16:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's true, I figured that fat little guy was enough for most things but I was just kinda confused why he doesn't bring the big guns to fight the forsaken. But maybe I'm underestimating the power of a regular angreal or rand's cockiness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 16:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That makes sense, I think I remember that. I've blown through books 3-5 super quickly so things are kinda getting blurred/lost in my head. Thanks! I'll keep reading and see where it goes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [ Spoilers LoC] Confused on why Rand doesn't.... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 16:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Use that super powerful Ter'angreal/ sa'angreal?

I'm on my first readthrough (7 chapters into LoC right now) and I've become kind of obsessed, but I'm confused as to why Rand doesn't use the super powerful statue sa'angreal that he gets from Rhuidean. I can understand why maybe he doesn't use it on a day to day basis but for example when he goes to fight Rahvin, he knows he's going into battle with an incredibly strong opponent with hundreds of years of practice and knowledge, why does he risk failing? Am I missing something?

Also if anyone wants to discuss anything up to LoC please hit me up, I'm kind of obsessed and don't have anyone to talk to. (Also hope I tagged the spoilers right. If not my bad).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 18:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 17:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't Mat described as being kind of short? Or is that just in comparison to the others/Aiel men? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 17:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a 23 year old male, hearing that even most of the women in this story are taller than me is a real killer. Ouch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 17:10:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm, I'm only 5 books in but just looking up characters/fan art definitely gave me some solid spoilers before I learned my lesson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 17:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow super happy I found this, I just finished Fires of Heaven yesterday and needed someone to vent my shock to. My roommates were laughing at me because apparently I was reading open mouthed at the Moirane/Lanfear scene. It's funny because I was planning on texting a buddy of mine after I finished the book discussing how much I like the series but the lack of any major deaths like 4000 pages in is kinda crazy and then Moirane took the need straight away from me. What a doozy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 17:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow wait what? I just finished TDR like, a month ago and don't remember this at all. Is the madness coming for me already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 15:51:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every morning when I drive this I wonder if I died in my sleep and woke up in hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-29 16:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I wish I had done this. I'm currently 3/4 of the way through fires of heaven right now and I've had so many things unfortunately spoiled by trying to look up people/names/ideas that I wasn't sure had been mentioned before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-22 19:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RIP in peace to the wolves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-22 17:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also people generally get paid per episode not per hour. With 6 episodes you can pay people less and use that money for other things like more special effects or still not having direwolves.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-09 17:00:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The perfect murder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 16:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love to discuss with you guys, or anyone else! Only thing is I'm only on the Dragon Reborn (probably going to finish it this evening, I have about 60 pages left) so I'm pretty far behind you guys. Still let me know if you're up for some no-spoilers discussions of the first 3 books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-19 01:49:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank God we're all birds. Not being able to fly would be such a god damned drag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-14 22:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats on the sex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 18:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spelled Capisci wrong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-11 01:24:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wrong zip code for Hackettstown you faker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-06 20:36:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 big components IMO:

1. "Practice". Not saying that you should just let people walk all over you, but in many places in life, the strongest relationships are built through some healthy ribbing. Get good at dishing it out in a way that is funny, a little bit insulting, but not crossing the line. If you can dish it as well as laughing at yourself, the whole process will be easier.

2. Know context. In many groups of guys, especially the way I grew up on sports teams and other really "masculine" groups, the guy who isn't taking a little shit is usually not well liked. If you know the context is good natured, it makes it easier, and if you know it's not good natured, then you learn that those people kinda suck anyway and aren't worth your time.

3. Set boundaries. even among close friends, everyone has a boundary and that's ok. I'm a pretty small guy and my friends will shit on me mercilessly for my height, but that's fine because I can laugh at it. Conversely, they knew that a few years ago after a bad relationship that that was a topic we avoided for a long time because I simply said "guys, I'm not ready to joke around about this one yet, please respect it." And good friends will do that. Because I set that boundary, they knew not to go there until I was ready. Now, that I'm cool with it, they'll every once in a while give me shit for it and it is FUNNY, because we have a mutual respect and understanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 20:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.google.com/amp/www.foxsports.com/mlb/story/chicago-white-sox-mark-buehrle-closed-world-series-game-while-drunk-122816%3famp=true

That's the best link I could find with a quick search, though I'm like 80% sure (I have no idea where I'd hear it so that's why I can't say 100%) I heard an interview with him where he basically said since he pitched the night before their inactive pitchers had been known to drink during the game, and during the 8th when it was tied he went and asked the manager if he should stop at his 2nd beer or if he was cool to keep going and he was told he wouldn't be needed. So... I feel like it's not ridiculous to say he was at least several beers deep 6 innings later in the 14tg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 18:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun fact, he was drunk when he got that save </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-17 15:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair point. I definitely wish we could have seen both Whent and Hightower. Definitely not saying it's perfect, just that in the face of many questionable decision in adapting the books to the screen, to me the changes in this scene are pretty reasonable and fairly well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-15 05:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, it obviously would have been amazing to see one guy wreaking havoc with Dawn, but there are limitations. The fact that they found a way to work around those to get the point across while still giving us an exceptionally dope scene really speaks volumes IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-15 00:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I remember reading that the Dual wielding was done not necessarily to make him more bad ass, but for choreography reasons. They didn't want to make it look like a lot of action movies where the bad guys stand in a circle around the hero and attack him one at a time like idiots. They couldn't find a realistic choreography for the fight with Ned's posse all attacking at the same time if he just had one sword, so they had to switch it to 2. Just limitations of the screen vs. a book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-14 21:28:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Benigni just looks like the happiest, most fun dude to hang around with  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-13 06:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah I'll make them feel as bad as I want. I've been there, I have the same grievances. I've been shit on and rejected and insulted and shut down. But demonizing 50% of the population just because they have different genitals? Fuck off with that. 

I stand by what I said. If someone needs help, shoot me a DM and I'll talk you through it if it takes all night, because I've been there, and everyone could use a hand in a time of need. 

But some guy who's gonna rant on feminazis and women trying to sap men of their power? Nah. I'm just an internet stranger I have no obligation to entertain that sort of abject illogical trash. Sue me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 15:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough, I totally agree that insulting people who don't agree with you never helps. My comment was mainly aimed at the OP the give her some encouragement in the face of the asinine responses to her very reasonable post. 

If you take a look at my next post on that thread you'll see that I mention wanting to just make fun of those responses, but instead doing my best offering whatever wisdom and positivity I can as a random Internet stranger who doesn't know shit. 

If people need someone to talk to, I'm all ears and they can pm me, because I get the frustration. But quite honestly I don't have the time or the patience to deal with the bullshit immature "feminists are trying to kill men and the world is out to get me" defeatist sort of talk. Anyone with an ounce of logic, self awareness, or life experience can tell you that that's silly, and though I'll occasionally try to help, I will treat it as such.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 05:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got a really good compass. 

Also we live in a time with more social openness and acceptance than any other time in history. 

Also even if we don't, just chill, take a deep breath, and keep moving. Things will be just fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 02:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, good old Sparta New Jersey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 22:18:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ALTUVE IS THE FUCKING GOAT  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 22:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo stay frosty friend those super negative haters got nothin on you, and just know there's a whole metric ass ton of us who appreciate you here!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 18:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wasn't gonna comment because I don't have a ton to add, but I saw all the aggressive negativity down here and just wanted to say that you are an intelligent and insightful woman with some good points. 

Society's bogus expectations of women are just as much a part of the problem as society's bogus expectations of men, and it's harmful to both. Luckily, despite what the grumpy guys on the internet echo chambers want to say, things are getting better, slowly but surely. There's a ways to go, and things will probably never be totally perfect for short guys, tall women, or really anyone because life isn't perfect. But we're getting there, and we can all take solace in knowing that these broad societal "truths" don't really mean much on an individual level, because we're all individuals who can make our own decisions, not some savage hive mind who all hate people that don't fit our ideal match. 

Keep fighting the good fight and don't let the negativity stop you. It's only a small but vocal minority.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 02:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Triggered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 02:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-08 08:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's Doug Dimmadome, owner of the Dimmsdale Dimmadome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-28 00:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-22 21:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's pretty funky. I'm also mildly disappointed he didn't respond. My boss was all up my ass this morning, I shamefully would have loved a bit of a pointless reddit argument  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-22 16:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The optimistic part of me says I hope this guy gets his shit together as he sounds genuinely kinda sad, and that stinks. 

The rest of me kinda likes seeing t because no matter how badly I fuck up, at least I'm not that delusional dingbat. 

Ah the duality of man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-22 15:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The two aren't mutually exclusive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-22 15:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to be a dick, but you sound like you spend a lot of time on some very unsavory, misogynistic, and defeatist types of internet communities. If the advice of this internet stranger means anything, get off that shit because your comment is so  disgustingly untrue I can't even laugh at it. Also, if you think women are that bad, maybe your worldview is contributing to that. Let's cool it with that "women will suck your soul out" and "we need more control over women" nonsense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-20 21:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your bathing suit is dank and I want it. 

Also cool pic and stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-18 19:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tough is one way to describe it. Heart-rending, or soul-crushing, or alcoholism-inducing are others  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 06:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not pretty, but I've done it. I did all 30 pages of my senior thesis in one sitting (Though I did have most of my data compiled and my research done, and more than half my regressions run.) Started at noon on sunday, finished it at 6:30 AM monday. Slept for 90 minutes, looked it over and revised it, submitted it by 11, and made it to work by noon. But then once I got home I was so exhausted I ran face first into an open door which my roomate had a good laugh about. All part of the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-06 17:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Jerry Callo. The judge already got his name wrong once, don't you do it too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 22:10:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is great info, thanks so much! I just screen shotted that and saved it so I can find it once we get there. I appreciate the help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 21:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a ton! We're still looking around right now to see where we can get reasonable prices, but by the sound of it we'll probably be taking our chances with SLC/ Park City. Hopefully it works out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 20:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome, thanks. Much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 19:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! I looked into them and they look great. Only thing is we're coming from the east coast so we're looking to get a real "out west" ski experience. I see that Arapaho is a good deal smaller than things like Park City or others along those lines. Would you still say it's some authentic West skiing? Just so I know what I'm looking at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 19:26:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My life is basically a series of poor decisions that somehow work out better than I deserve. I think we're gonna do it haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 18:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's what I'm hearing as well. Unfortunately there's only 1 week in December that we can make work so we might have to just chance it, but good to know we're hearing similar things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 17:46:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That'd be dope. Any info is appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 17:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damnit I got so excited when you replied. Thought someone had some options for me. 

Appreciate the support though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Best early December skiing in the Western US? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 16:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A buddy and I are trying to hit the slopes second week of December. I know it's a little early in the season so anyone have any recommendations for good mountains/areas at that time of year? Also just recommendations in general of your favorites. We're most likely looking around Colorado, Utah, or Wyoming, but can be convinced of other areas as well. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 19:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Pretty much all girls care about is height"

You ever actually like... talked to a girl, dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-01 19:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now THIS is pod racing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-21 23:29:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or that. Gotta get some variety in the diet am I right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-21 17:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Them Swedes gonna be eating salted venison for ETERNITY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 16:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, what else are you gonna snack on when you're playing board games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 16:00:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When losing, become an anarchist. I like you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 04:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sound like the kinda guy who always loses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 04:56:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Out Loud by Dispatch gets me every damn time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 04:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's usually what happens when you stick your dick in crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 04:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In any board game, no matter which one it is, never make a deal with Aaron. He has thought farther ahead than you, and his deal WILL help him more than it will help you. Fuck you, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-13 15:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I love it as well. To be fair I lived there for 4 years in college so I should have said I'm moving BACK. Fully aware of what I'm getting into and I could not be happier about it haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-13 05:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you DIDN'T dip in Norther NJ, I question your actual existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-13 05:25:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Moving to DC in 2 weeks. This makes me feel awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-07 02:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wooooweeee! This is some exceptionally heavy handed satire. Or just actual craziness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-05 22:45:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that Conforto is 2nd in WAR for outfielders and isn't even on the ballot is absolutely bananas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In aggregate maybe, but in my current spot in life not at all. In the past 5 years I've needed antibiotics once and an inhaler for bronchitis once, and that's it. The increase in taxes would definitely lose me more than the cheaper healthcare would gain in that situation. I'm not even big on the ACA mandating I have insurance because right now, it just costs me way more than I use it. Will I need it at some point? Yeah probably. But I don't now, and I'm willing to take that gamble because I'd rather use my own money that I work for to get my feet under me and deal with student loans and other such things one has to deal with at this age. Is this specific to my own personal situation and not at all reflective? Yeah for sure, but I said in my original post my thoughts are partially selfishly motivated, just like everyone else's political views. Overall, it basically comes down to being committed to wanting to make my own decision, good or bad, instead of having some old guy in Washington from Texas or somewhere I've never been tell me where I should spend my money and what's best for my health. How the hell does he know what works for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That may be the case, I don't know and it sounds like you know better than I do. Also I work for a large health insurance company and I know that they are for sure a huge part of the problem. All I'm saying is that as with anything in life, there is a finite amount of resources, and they have to be allocated somehow. And when the government is in charge, I know that they do not have MY best interests at heart. I'm not some crazy conspiracy theorist, the government probably has the best interests of the population as a whole in mind (actually executing that is a different matter), but me as an individual person? They don't give a damn, so I'd like to keep as many of the decisions in my own hands, and with my own money as possible, instead of just throwing it in there in taxes and expecting to always be taken care of and to not have a choice because I'm not the one directly footing the bill. (Also I'm aware that that is an oversimplification of how it works, please don't jump down my throat for that.) Add this to the other reasons I mentioned and it's just not something I really trust, but what do I know, I'm young and dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean I think this is a pretty good point that you make in terms of "every single issue in healthcare." It's a MASSIVE industry effecting hundreds of millions of people (and due to the global influence of the US, the rest of the world) and people so often think they have the solutions. Like, just OBVIOUSLY pay more taxes and have the government give it to everybody. But even at its most basic level, economics, politics, industry etc. are not nearly that simple. I know I don't have all the right answers, I'm barely qualified to tie my own shoes, but it really peeves me off when people scoff at not having socialized healthcare like its the most simple thing, because it's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You also forget just how much lawyers drive up costs. Doctors and hospitals need massive malpractice insurance policies, because suing people is like a sport in America. On average, a doctor in the US gets sued every 7 years for malpractice. Obviously those suits exist for a reason, sometimes malpractice is a legit problem, more often than not, however, it's a blatant money grab that the doctors have to be protected against. They need to build the costs of those policies, suits, and the resulting impacts on their businesses into their operating costs, which then drives up insurance and screws the whole system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Little late to the party, but as someone who is in the middle on this I can at least throw out some of my reasons to be against:

1. Scale- it does work fairly well in some other countries, but very few of those have a population of over 300 million spread through every geographical and sociopolitical background imaginable. It's highly unlikely that something that is good for a poor coal miner in WV will also work for a CA school teacher or an NYC ad executive or a nebraska store owner. What benefits one will be a detriment to others. Also again on scale, any time there is an endeavor that massive, there is a huge amount of beaurocratic inefficiency and waste. Not that there isn't already, but if I'm going to pay for it it, I'd rather keep it smaller and more privatized where it is in the private company's best interest to minimize waste and inefficiency.

2. When the government controls your healthcare, they have the right to make the ultimate decision on what that entails, and rightfully so since they're paying for it. At some point they'll have to make the economic decision that your problem can wait, or that it is not in the budget to perform X or Y procedure on you. I'd prefer to be able to make that decision myself, even if I'll have to deal with the monetary consequences later.

3. There's definitely a selfish aspect, why should I be in charge of paying for someone else's health? My taxes are already pretty damn high, even more so considering I'm 23 and dealing with student loans and getting my own life off the ground. Add to that I work pretty damn hard to eat healthy and take care of my body, why should I have to pay for some straw man on the other side of the country who though KFC every night for a year was a good idea. Fuck that guy.

4. There's some worry about oversight. When the government pays for it, they have the authority to tell medical professionals how to do their job at times. As we've all seen, lawmakers are hilariously nosy in fields they have no qualifications to be in (see the head of the EPA not believing in climate change, or a room full of dudes legislating women's reproductive rights.) I don't want those same ignorant people having power over my doctors to tell them how to treat me, which already kinda happens to an extent, as the ACA for sure allows a lot more government intervention into how doctors and other professionals run their businesses.

5. I'm a big individulist/free market guy, things will always be better when you'll lose your revenue if they stink. The government won't have that incentive.

Tl;dr - I'm kinda jaded about the government and might be kinda selfish? Idk, sue me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first time I played that final fight I didn't realize you had to manually activate the guns, so I was just trying to survive til they activated. I think I died about 20 times over a 2 hour period because I figured it out. So god damned frustrating but one of my favorite video game memories of all time because of the intensity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exceptionally worth it. It nearly doubles the size and scale of the game for a relatively low cost. It adds a whole new dimension to the game with the addition of religions, completely revamps the cultural victory to make it waaaay more interesting than in the original, pretty much doubles the Humber of Civs, as well as several other improvements. Basically the number 1 DLC of almost any game. Do it, you won't regret it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stupid isn't unique to the wealthy. It's the most abundant element on the planet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last thing I bought was a gin and tonic at the bar last night so.... now I have a MEGA GIN AND TONIC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too real man, too real. I feel this so hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:16:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this is your response then there's your problem right there buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo screw you man just cuz you found some girl you like you're ok with subjecting your sons to that torture?! For shame!

Nah I'm kidding. Being short has its disadvantages but like, it's not that bad. You just gotta teach the kids how to be personable and fun to be around and they'll be totally fine. My buddies give me shit for it all the time but I'm pretty sure they think Europe is a country so I think we all know who the real winner is here. Your kids will be just dandy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:24:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I respect your dilemma, but I shame you for your overall choice. Thane 4 lyfe, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thane Krios getting no love here is straight up bulllll shittttt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No education is useless, but it is expensive. While learning those skills that aren't traditionally useful may be nice for the individual, someone's gotta foot that bill, and that money comes at the expense of something or things in their lives. In an ideal world everyone should totally be able to be able to be educated on whatever they want, but we don't live in an ideal world. Everything comes at the expense of something else.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm, I grew up in NJ and worked for a car dealership in DC for a while. Now I live in CT and nothing has prepared me for the hellscape that is driving in this crazy fucking state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fucking true. Bergen county contains every road to, from, and in hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you're a bit drunk? I don't know man, have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-13 03:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We'll make Rock Ridge think that it's a chicken that got caught in a tractor's nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-12 05:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know, man, I'd probably stay away if the entire University of Alabama football team was there. Who knows what kinda crazy shit they're getting up to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-05 03:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FINALLY SOMEONE ELSE WHO UNDERSTANDS ME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:09:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because all of the rest of your clocks move too fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any time, friend! There's a lot more inter league play now, so if you watch a Giants game where they are playing an American League team at an American League park, you should be able to see this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the 70s there were worries that fans were losing interest due to low scoring games. To try to increase offense, the American League instituted a rule where a "designated hitter" was inserted into the lineup for another player, almost always the pitcher since pitchers tend to be weak hitters. The DH wouln't play the field, so they didn't really need any glove skills, just the ability to hit some dingers, and the pitchers would never get to bat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe I'm wrong on this one, but I feel like that's just an excuse. In my experience, I have almost never seen that happen. You don't become the "creepy guy" unless you react badly to rejection. Getting hit on isn't creepy, if after a rejection the person doing the hitting on goes "my bad, thought I got a vibe there but I guess I was wrong, this'll be awkward for a few hours/days/weeks and then we'll get over it so let's not worry about it." It only becomes creepy if you can't take a hint, deal with rejection like a spurned child, or never make a move but sit there and creepily leer and get mad when she hooks up with someone else. That's my experience anyway, but like, I'm not that old and have been wrong on a lot of things before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If she was really committed she would have put it under the stairs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best: Graduating from college

Worst: Graduating from college

....The real world is weird, man. Not sure how I feel about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flying Dutchman: Arooooooo
Spongebob: ahahahaaha
Patrick: Ladleladleladlela.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 on the username, just sayin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any time man, trust me positivity beats negativity every damn day, even when it's hard to keep up sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasn't gonna comment because I'm pretty late to the party, but holy balls there was a lot of negativity here, so I'll give you the other side- you're totally fine. The best part about college is that there are an absurd amount of single women all around your age all in the same area. Are there some who won't be about you because of your height? Yeah maybe. But there are also some who won't be about mr. Tall guy because his facial hair is patchy and we can all see it, or won't be about Mr. Athlete because he thinks Europe is a country. Don't listen to the negativity man, be funny like you said You are, do well in classes, be good at a hobby in extra curriculars (I did theatre and Greek life, weird combination I know) and meet people. Sometimes height might put you at a disadvantage, but trust me, as a short guy who graduated last May, you know what makes that disadvantage go away? Being fun to be around. If you're a good time, then no one will give 2 fucks about your height because, shocker, girls are people too, and everyone is just here to have a good time and to learn something. Chin up homie, get out there and slay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it was straight up bull shit. Definitely not the peak of my college career, but you live and you learn. It all turned out alright. Blows my mind that DC spends money on a whole squad of detectives trolling liquor stores in the super safe northwest part for college kids while there are serious problems in other parts of the city though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait why is the umpire on reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-03 04:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah it was undercover cops outside a liquor store because I'm a fucking dunce and my buddy who I was with is certified the worst person on the planet at getting away with anything outside the rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-03 04:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a fake CT ID and used it in DC for a while. Worked great... then I got caught and got arrested... Now I live in CT. Funny how that works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-27 03:38:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jyggallag's forces are gathering in my fringe... and I HATE IT when people gather forces, in my fringe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-26 03:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> huh... looking back it seems I did. Whoops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dude same. It's great we can communicate with nearly anyone on the planet with an internet connection while on reddit, and we still gravitate to the same shitty people from our area! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-07 03:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a friendly cunt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had an AL team, then they singled the Mets do death in the world series and now I hate everything about them. Eat a dick, Kansas City. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's honestly fair. I was drunk ranting. I change my perspective to the fact that the royals broke him. He now can't hit the postseason without ptsd, last year against the cubs and LA he was golden but pitchers are headcases and they broke him. I'm also just still super salty. I'll probably get over it in a day or two and be right back on the familia train next year. But until then... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:46:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least there's that. Don't feel me too hard though, douche lord shit bag Hosmer is on the list with bum too. That guy gives me ptsd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 15:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Just bury me in a deep dark place where I can never hear the name bumgarner again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 15:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God this thread is just full of all my least favorite teams. Someone just find me a dark hole to crawl into </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 07:01:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> those cubs games weren't exactly the highest pressure situations though. 8-3, 5-2 4-1. Dude is fine when he has breathing room, he just can't do pressure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:57:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just fuck baseball in general. It's bad for my heart and my psyche at this rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair, we said we were going to be in contention for a long time in 06/07 too. I know it's not the same, but this team never ceases to find ways to utterly crush all chances of optimism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bumgarner is incredible in the postseason and everyone says he's the best playoff performer there is. Familia is trash in the postseason and everyone says you can't count that. How does that make sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 06:12:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn. wish I had seen this sooner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:37:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man, think what you want, that's your prerogative, but can we try not to spread the negativity to others. Some mild bitching and ranting every now and then is all well and good, but this defeatist talk does no good for anyone. Life isn't some formula, weirder shit has happened than a dude getting with a girl 6 inches taller than him. Shit happens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah man. If she's gonna be taller than you, she's gonna be taller than you. Lifts are the exact opposite of owning it. If you get a nice pair of boots (I usually wear redwings, but I'm old and boring with disposable income, they may be out of the price range for a high schooler) they can add an inch or two which is dope, and in the case of prom your dress shoes may have a small heel. Overall though, stressing and obsessing about an inch or two here or there is just going to make you look silly and make you feel worse inside than you should. We're short man, some chicks aren't going to be into that, that's life. But it could be worse, you could be dumb, or have BO, or be an Eagles fan. Now those are real problems. Just remember, if this chick is into you, she's going to be into you with or without lifts. And if she's not, an extra inch isn't going to change that. Just relax and have a good time, nothing is more attractive, to chicks or dudes, than someone who is exceptionally fun to be around. Life is too short (pun semi-intended) to worry so much, brother. Now go out there and make future you more proud than I am of high school me. 

Edit: Spelling. Also changed "no way" to "nah" because tone and shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-04 03:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fucking go for it. Own that shit. If she says she's embarrassed to wear heels, ask her why she would be embarrassed about being the prettiest girl in the room. If it's awkward when you dance, acknowledge it, laugh at it, make jokes, be the life of the party. If the angles are weird when you kiss, own it, laugh, and suggest you sit down because then you're all the same height. Or just do it anyway, and flip off your friends who will undoubtedly give you shit because that's what good friends do and if they have time to laugh at you while you're making out, then clearly you're winning this one. It's easy to be confident when you're 6'2", But if you've got the balls to mess around with a girl 6 inches taller than you, you-are-the-man. Own that shit and fucking enjoy it. Also, you're eye level with her boobs, and that is, as the kids say these days #lit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-04 03:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe with that mentality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-01 00:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *your (times like....8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-30 23:53:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Back in college I joked that I wanted her to set me up with one of her friends so I could get into her sorority's formal. She had just been dumped so she said I should just go with her. We got rip roaring drunk, danced like maniacs, hooked up, then woke up and never spoke of it again. We're still great friends, and years later I realized I was totally just her rebound bang.... Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it's way better to get a boner over trump/clinton or the shit Kim kardashian does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:25:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His whole story is a hell of a ride, definitely worth getting it all if you have the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Mets fan, watching him make my team look silly was hard, but as a baseball fan, not having someone like this around anymore is a fat load of shit. I was really looking forward to an NL east That Featured Fernandez, Scherzer, Strasburg, Tehran, Syndergaard, and DeGrom to have some of the best interdivisional pitching matchups in history. This is heart breaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is one of the best Gifs of all time. This kid embodied the way baseball should make us all feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know what the sub is called? Now I'm curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 00:04:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm like 80% sure this was in the benchwarmers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *boxed lentils, you were close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait a minute.... Why does your girlfriend have a mother-in-law? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:26:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not so much a joke as it is a dialectal thing. In some southern Italian dialects (where most of the immigrants to America were from) it's common in speech to drop some final vowels, so capisci (meaning "you understand" or "do you understand") becomes pronounced as "capiche." It's the same way you'll sometimes hear "mozzarell" instead of "mozzarella" and other such things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're looking for an actual answer, in my mind it has to do with a natural propensity to dislike being told what to do. In my case, I just started my first really full time post grad job, and it's tedious and soul sucking and consumes 60 hours of my week, but it pays well. To then see 30, 40, 50% of that taken away in taxes is a really shitty feeling, especially because I know that as someone who's only 22 I'll probably never see that come back in social security. In a socialist system just by its nature those taxes would need to be even higher, and it's honestly really unappealing to spend 60 hours a week of my time working to then have the government take it away and give it to someone else/tell me what to do with it. I recognize that there are some benefits to this system, but on a personal level it's really unappealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-09 04:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Nice" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never thought 2 Bartolos could make me sad, but you found a way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus, do you even have a liver? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh so it's your fault? Damnit, WaywardWriter!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't get your hopes up, buddy. It's going to be a long year
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let me know if you find the proper beer-to-loss ratio needed to survive being a Mets fan. Haven't found the sweet spot yet.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-20 06:29:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No fear not, it's still all hopeless bullshit. They just like to extend my hope so it hurts more when they inevitably crush it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Why Do My Legs Always Hurt When I'm Hungover?: A Memoir" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-02 01:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I put on the Disney pandora station. I'm a straight, 22 year old, college educated male who spent 4 years as a frat guy. I don't regret any of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey /u/NDLPT have you gotten any answers to your questions? I just committed this morning to working in Hartford and have a lot of the same concerns. I'm in a pretty similar situation as you, just graduated college and I don't really know anyone in CT, I went to school in DC so I'm used to a city with a lot of people and things to do, trying to find an area with young people and stuff. Any info you've found would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-26 08:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Syndergod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-20 18:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That I'm considering not voting for a Republican. He'd flip a shit if I ever "became a liberal." Though admittedly he hates Trump too so there's that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-18 22:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yeah, I didn't hear that part of the story. That's pretty unprofessional. My guess is they had to check what car it was and then they forgot, I know things can get insane back in the service bay. That being said who knows, maybe it was just a joyride. Either way in my time there I never saw anything but professionalism when handling the cars for the most part. Who knows though I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-18 21:17:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a former employee at a Tesla store (store, not dealer) a lot of times it is necessary to take the car for a little ride after servicing it. Would you rather someone take your car for an experimental trip around the block (someone whose job it is to responsibly deal with the cars, I might add) and get your car back fixed, or have no one drive it then potentially have the problem not be taken care of when you get the car back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A sitting US senator/the commencement speaker at my college graduation yesterday said that I had "grit and gumption." I tweeted at him that I liked his speech but the focus of it was wrong. He replied to my criticism then I asked him if he was hiring. His compliment was one of the coolest things to happen to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-05 03:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not only is it important, but it's just plain fun. Never again in your life will you be in a place surrounded by 10, 20, 30 of your closest friends with no responsibilities for an extended period of time. I had some of the best times of my life, and you get incredibly close to all the guys, which really helps whenever you're in trouble or need help. There were always guys who didn't want to live in the house, but I never really understood it and I know a lot who regretted it. Strongly recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-07 22:15:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lack of open container laws. There was nothing better when I was studying in Europe than being able to take my beer with me while walking to the bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-29 01:38:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Day after his birthday." The dude isn't sick, he's just aggressively hung over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-26 04:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> chimpfuckers, not motherfuckers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-26 04:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Veeeeeeery carefully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-23 04:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because when faced with the dark creepy hallway one of my jackass friends would pull out the "do it, you won't.... pussy." And then I'd quickly end up with a chainsaw halfway up my bum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-18 23:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Read a lot. It strengthens the brain, you learn new words and ways to use words, and overall just makes you quicker. 2. Practice. It's a skill like any other, just shoot the shit with your friends and build a rapport. 3. Be shameless. Just say the first thing that pops to your mind. Sometimes the joke will land, sometimes it won't. If it doesn't that's cool, you tried, no one really cares. When's the last time you remember someone else's bad joke? I guarantee you your wittiest friends have also had the most bad jokes, it's just how it works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-25 20:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My roomate and I have some Music posters and some cool artwork. I have a Mets flag and some sports jerseys. The best part though? I have a giant ass Bowie Knife mounted on the wall across from my bed. It was a family heirloom and that thing is bad fucking ass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-16 03:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I strongly recommend it, with the caveat that you're in it for the right reasons. I'm currently in my last semester in college, and I know I am going to miss my time in my fraternity immensely. The important things to remember though, are that you will only get out of it what you put in, and that you have to be in it for more than the parties. Don't get me wrong, the parties are great, but there's a lot more to it, and there's also a lot of work involved. Personally, I've gotten 2 jobs from some of my brothers, I was encouraged to take up theatre which I always had an interest in, I've become more confident when talking to everyone from girls to employers to professors, and I've learned the value of having a very close support group. The main thing to do is to go to rush and hang around with some brothers. If you are feeling it, I think it is a great decision for a lot of people, and it definitely made me into the man I am today. If you aren't feeling it, however, that's totally fine. There are plenty of other student organizations out there to fulfill your social, professional, and developmental needs. Go with your gut and you will be fine, and whatever you decide, cherish the hell out of it because it goes really fast.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-12 00:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dispatch and the Foo Fighters. Both fantastic from A-Z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-11 18:08:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I watched Field of Dreams last night. I hadn't seen it in a few years but damn if that last scene doesn't make you emotional you're inhuman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-29 20:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man! Just tryna spread some positivity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-29 19:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adding to this, just say like "take it as a compliment then" or "take it as flattery." Rejection sucks for the person getting rejected, but no one likes to be the rejector either, it's awkward and most people don't like hurting others. Telling them to take it as a compliment shows that you're a mature, well adjusted person who isn't going to be too bothered. Plus if they feel flattered and a little good about themselves then you just did a nice thing for your crush, as shitty as it feels for you right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-29 19:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm assuming you mean when asking a girl out, and in my experience, no I don't expect/demand/want one for a few reasons:

1. 9/10 times, it has nothing to do with you. She has a boyfriend, she's knows she's leaving the city in a few days, she's really stressed out with her job, or any other internal reason that really doesn't effect you or concern you at all.

2. She just isn't into you, whether it's your looks, your interests, your style etc. Sucks. But hey, you tried. Move on, someone will be, and as painful as it is, at the end of the day it wouldn't have worked anyway if she doesn't have that attraction to you, or you have nothing in common. 

3. She actually does have a mean hurtful or unpleasant reason to reject you. In this case, she will either lie to you if she is a nice person, and it won't accomplish anything, or she will tell you, and then you'll just feel bad. Plus if she is going to reject you and be mean about it, then once again, that's not really the type of person you want to be with anyway, even if you do find her attractive.

In any of these scenarios, especially number 1. which in my experience is the most common, is hearing an explanation really going to do anything for you other than maybe make you a little more upset for a longer time? Probably not, it's really not worth it.

In my experience the best way to deal with rejection is just to take it in stride, tell her to take it as a compliment, and even though it kind of sucks a little bit, you can move on knowing it wouldn't have worked anyway and know you aren't wasting your valuable time on what would ultimately be a dead end. Just my thoughts, but I've noticed that since I've started thinking like this I've cared a lot less about rejection and have been more happy and successful because of it.

If you were just talking about rejection in general (jobs, colleges, etc.) then... an explanation couldn't hurt, but you may not always get one, or you may not always get an honest one, so be aware of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-27 07:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tl;Dr Blacked out on a pub crawl, made out with a lesbian, won 900 Czech crowns at a casino (turns out that's about $35)

Edit: can't spell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-24 08:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that note is the single most haunting musical note I've ever heard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-24 06:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was at that game also. I've never heard that much venom before. Sitting with the 7 line must have been amazing though. That game is another moment I'll never forget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-24 06:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah it was the year before they instituted the instant replay and it probably would have been overturned. Interestingly enough, the very next game R.A. Dicky would have had a no hitter also, except this time the umpires blew a call in favor of the other team, which instant replay would have also would have overturned. Just funny how that stuff works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-23 18:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a die hard Mets fan. One friday night when I was a senior in high school, my dad my friend his dad and I all had tickets to go to the game that night. Now in 2012, the Mets weren't particularly good, and since we usually go to a bunch of games per year, I wanted to go to a party that night instead of the game. My dad convinced me to go, however, and I was there to witness Johan Santana throw the first no-hitter in Mets history after 50 years of trying. It was even cooler because my dad had been at 2 previous games where no-hitters had been taken into the 8th and the 9th innings and been broken up, so getting to see his face light up like a child when they finally did it was really cool. And that was how an ordinary game became extraordinary.

Also, I was able to go to the World Series game 5 in NY last fall, which was the only game they won. I've never heard a stadium so loud in my life. The energy was something I will never forget. In a lifetime of the Mets being disappointing, lovable losers, these moments were absolutely surreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-12 06:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm playing as saxons right now and doing pretty well. I found it really useful to get rid of the Franks asap. After that I built up my economy, and made it a point to try to ally with the Gaets and/or the Jutes. Both factions always tend to do well, and once all the barbarian tribes start to form barbarian nato, your alliances with them will bump up your standing with a lot of others, making it easier to trade with them. Then either go to Britain (fairly doable, but not particularly wealthy or fertile provinces), or do what I did and expand in a big glob south and east. The only problem there is it eventually runs you right into the huns, but I got lucky enough to liberate one or two small factions to act as a buffer. Either way, main things I would focus on are getting rid of the Franks, raiding and sacking some of the WRE so everyone else likes you, and not angering the Gaets unless you do it early because they tend to grow really fast in my experience. Also, you want to build a warlord's hold (I think that's what it is) as soon as you can so you can get hearth guards, which are way better than any other early units you can get with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-10 21:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All it takes is one good book or series to open the door. I tend to like fiction/ fantasy so for me it was Harry Potter and the Bartimaeous trilogy when I was younger. They're still great, but for someone Older maybe try A Song of Ice and Fire, Ender's Game, The Kingkiller Chronicles, or anything by Kurt Vonnegut (Slaughterhouse five is his most famous, but he's very bizzarre and not for everyone so I'd suggest taking 15 minutes to read his short story "Harrison Bergeron" to see if you like his style.)
If you're more into non-fiction then it really depends what you're into. If you like sports, pick something to do with your favorite sport. For example I'm a baseball guy so Moneyball is one of my favorite books. If you like history maybe find a biography of someone you find particularly interesting, or try some historical fiction. 

It really all depends what you like, and if you have an idea maybe I/we can be more specific. Really all it takes is one thing you find compelling though and you'll be surprised how far that carries you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-09 08:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you're right. Maybe you're not. All I'm saying is that coming from someone who has spent a lot of time in the wrestling locker room, someone who hasn't may not realize how pretty much every conversation is punctuated with references to size or weight. It's an integral part of the sport, and on everyone's mind. I was simply telling the OP to take his buddy's compliment at face value, because it sounded awesome to me, and I've been in that position. If not resting until no one ever mentions your height is your goal, and that works for you, then by all means, keep rocking. Conversely, if that's not how you roll, then that's cool for you. In my experience, it's pointless to find disrespect in every little statement, but if it motivates you, then go for it. I don't know OP or his friend, but to me it seems like he's smart enough to decide for himself. It's nothing to get worked up over or to make someone question their friends or teammates' intentions over. Just tryna spread a little positivity to a fellow low weight wrestler.

Edit: grammar N shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-09 07:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ....... Wut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-09 07:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna disagree man. I don't know if you've ever been on a wrestling team, but size is always on everyones' minds because of how integral it is to the sport. In some situations it might be right, but in regards to wrestling, mentioning someone's size is just part of the rhetoric. It has nothing to do with a lack of respect, and it's not a qualifier or anything like that. It sounds to me like his teammate was just genuinely giving a compliment on skill, nothing else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-09 07:21:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to wrestle a few years ago when I was in high school. I wrestled 103 for 2 years, then 113 the next 2, so I know what it's like to be small. Just wanted to say congrats, especially if this kid was as good as he sounds. Those low middle weights that you compete at tend to have some of the most skilled wrestlers in the sport, so being good at those weights is a hell of an accomplishment. What your buddy said should be taken as nothing more than a compliment, and a pretty damn good one. Plus, chicks dig wrestlers, regardless of size. You gotta have some serious balls do that sport. Keep rocking buddy, and have fun wrestling, you'll start to miss it after you graduate and move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-06 02:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Starbucks -- Starducks. Send some ducks to Mars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-06 01:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 22 Jump Street. It was very self aware and absolutely hysterical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-06 01:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How often do you remember when other people do something awkward or embarrassing? Probably not very often. If you fuck up or do something awkward, no one is going to remember it, because there is a 99% chance that that other person is also too busy worrying about whatever they are self conscious about. Once you realize that everybody is too busy worrying about him or herself to worry about you, you'll be free to do/say whatever the hell you want. Within reason of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-30 02:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Replace Tom Hanks in Castaway with Heath Ledger. Watching two hours of a dead guy on an island would be a real drag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-29 01:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately I don't have NTW, but I've always thought doing a hotseat would be cool. Definitely better than dealing with the AI. Maybe one day in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-29 01:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These were actually the types of things I was wondering myself. Care to post once you find out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-24 00:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> -Moneyball, if you are into economics and/or baseball
-Slaughterhouse five or Cat's Cradle by Vonnegut if you like some bizarre sci-fi
-A Song of Ice and Fire or Kingkiller Chronicles if you like big long high fantasy books
-World War Z, because zombies are dope and the socio-economic and political happenings are actually really interesting
-The life of PI if you like books that have a meaning that's very up for interpretation
-The art of War if you're looking for something historical
-Fahrenheit 451 for anything dystopian and awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aksum campaign help. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-21 22:26:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in a bit of a predicament in my Aksum campaign. I've basically taken about half of the Arabian peninsula as well as the East African provinces you start out with. At this point, I'm trapped. There's the Sassanids to my North and East, and the ERE to my North and West. My original plan was to wait for them to fight each other, however, they both have very high opinions of the other one making it unlikely. I'm pretty sure that as soon as I enter war with one, I'll get attacked by the other. I'm fairly confident I can take on one, but not both. Any tips for what to do here, or how to fight both, since that seems like my only option?

Background, I'm hovering between number 4 and 5 on strength ranking, Sassanids are 3, ERE is 1. ERE is at war with WRE which helps, but that's the other side of the map. They're both fighting some small insignificant nations, I think Judea and the White Huns and maybe one or two others, but they're all 40+ in strength ranking so not enough to keep the big empires busy. I have a full stack, and 2 other half stacks, and a half stack navy. Economically I can probably maintain 2.5 full stacks and my Navy right now. Any ideas would be appreciated. Also difficulty is Hard for both campaign and battle maps. Thanks in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-15 15:49:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's funny I'm the opposite, I always like the Mediterranean/desert/warmer climate factions in these games. But yeah, I may be able to get both, just not sure. I'll totally check it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-15 15:45:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know Mass Effect 3's soundtrack is on spotify, not sure about the rest. Look it up there or on youtube next time you are trying to do some work or are looking for some music without lyrics. It's definitely worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-15 00:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try re-reading it now. I loved it as a kid but I went back and re-read it summer after my freshman year of college and found that I understood so many references that went right over my head when I was younger. Very fulfilling re-read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-14 23:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm no lawyer but I'm pretty sure that's grounds to claim workplace discrimination against anyone Macedonian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-14 22:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dope thanks, I'll look into it and pick one as soon as I'm done with finals... or before if I just decide to give up and hope my professors are impressed by a sick virtual empire. One of the two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Attila- Which culture pack should I download? I'll probably only do one. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-14 21:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Money is a little tight, but I want to download one of the culture packs and/or Charlemagne. I was thinking going with the Viking forefathers or Empires of Sand, but honestly I don't know much about any. Any recommendations on which ones are good and which ones aren't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:19:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mass Effect's soundtrack is epic as all hell. Especially if you're trying to study or get work done, that soundtrack makes even doing calculus feel interesting.

Edit: For clarification, I personally mean the soundtrack for Mass Effect 3, however, I'm pretty sure they're all great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-12 02:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did it to my dad a year or so ago. He was not a happy camper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get one of those timers people put on their lights when they go on vacation and set it up all around his room/on his stereo if that'll work. Cue a different light to go on every like hour or so, just enough so that he can never get into a deep sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-09 20:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not so bad yourself.... wanna meet my parents now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-09 07:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Generally very little, I'm not a big social media guy. The one exception is if there are constant posts about politics or social/political/current issues all up there. For one, I really hate politics. More importantly, at least IMO, someone who thinks that complex world issues are clear cut enough to be posted and solved on facebook is just someone I am going to nope the hell away from. Plus, in general the people who tend to do that are people who tend to be the least open to constructive dialogue and debate. It's also a sign of a desperation to be validated, but honestly aren't we all just trying to get people to tell us we are awesome? Same thing with selfies, which is why I really don't mind those too much. 

Edit: Can't spell, am dumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough, can't argue with that. To each his own I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-07 06:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? Just out of curiosity how come? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-07 05:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Book the Life of Pi. Completely blew my mind and really made me think about the relativity of truth. Plus it shows how regardless of what you believe, whether you are religious or not, that ultimately we all started from and are going to the same places, and are all just trying to make sense of the world we live in and to live the most fulfilling lives posssible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-01 19:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My family watches The Godfather, and if you're going to tell me that isn't a Christmas movie I will totally go all Michael Corleone on your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say go for it. Just be honest, and like someone else said, just very specifically ask her on a date. If it works, then dope, well played man. If not, then so what? It'll be awkward for the first couple of days and weeks, and if that is the case, then you just have to act like it was no big deal. It's going to hurt, but if you care for her as a friend the way you say you do, then shake it off, still hang out with her like normal, and commit yourself to moving on. The biggest mistake that people make with getting rejected by friends is then acting weird after words. If it doesn't work it doesn't work, awkwardness only lasts for a little while, so power through and have some fun.

Source: I have a serial habit of developing feelings for friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:04:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah exactly. If they're just bringing you in for doing something then they don't have to say jack shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-30 22:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just so you know, even when you're arrested you don't have to be read your miranda rights. It's only in specific circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-30 04:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Mets fan, all I do is create expectations then spectacularly disappoint everyone involved... I don't think about baseball during sex any more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-25 21:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. He's a Jedi Master for a reason, people trust his wisdom, and he knows how bad it could be if he didn't kill Palpatine. That being said, killing an unarmed man would still be illegal, and so he would have to face the consequences. Nevertheless, as a Jedi, it is his duty to serve first and worry about himself later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-17 18:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before getting involved in one of those arguments, you have to ask yourself "is the type of person who believes that sort of ridiculousness, and uses facebook as their #1 source of 'intellectual' discourse, the type of person that will listen to my logical argument about why they are wrong and possibly change their mind?" In my experience, 99/100 times, the answer to that is obviously no, and as much as you want to put them in their place, all you end up doing is wasting your own precious time stooping to their level and arguing with an idiot about something idiotic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is this everywhere I look?! Just let me grieve in peace :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not our fault. A lifetime of being comically awful makes you a paranoid, jaded, angry person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just end it so I can go be miserable in peace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Murphy probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Classic Philly fan, kicking em while they're down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-02 06:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mets shitty defense is the Royals real MVP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-02 05:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except the Mets breaking my heart
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-16 19:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CLEARLY YOU'VE NEVER WATCHED BARTOLO COLON TRY TO HIT A BASEBALL. THERE IS NOTHING IN THIS WORLD MORE MAGICAL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-01 19:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So true. Harrison Bergeron is arguably the best short story I've ever read. Strongly recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-04 19:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Give yourself some sort of mental challenge. For instance I try to name all of the MLB teams by division. Fucking AL central always messes me up, but I'll find that while I'm sitting there trying to remember the Cleveland Indians I get a few extra minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This.... this is a joke right? You're making no sense dude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I have, it's fairly reputable. Plus from my standpoint he was coming into the store to spend $95k on a whim so he has to be doing at least fairly well for himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-21 00:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I am very aware that it might just be conversation. But as someone who is going to be graduating in a year, it can't hurt to try, especially with the job market the way it is for recent grads. Definitely didn't have my hopes up, I just figure something is better than nothing
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A customer at work today asked for my resume, I am not sure how to proceed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 23:53:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A little background, I am 21 years old, I am a college student about to enter my Senior year. I will be graduating with a degree in economics in May of 2016, and I currently work in sales at a pretty reputable tech company.

Anyway today at work a customer came in and while I was taking him through the product he asked if I owned one, which I replied I did not as they are too expensive for your average college student to afford. He then asked where I went to school and what I was majoring in, and told me he worked at an investment management firm in the area, and if I was interested in that type of thing for when I graduate I should send him my resume. 

I'm pretty excited about it since even though I work in sales right now, finance/investment management is more along the lines of what I want to do for a career. I have to email him tomorrow with questions about the product he is looking to buy, and although I want to follow up on his offer, I am not sure how exactly to do it. For instance, it seems unprofessional to put some questions about another company in a work related email, but I also do not want to spam this guy by sending him one email that is work related and another one from my personal email asking about his company 5 minutes later. Also should I just straight up send him the resume, or should I be more subtle and ask about his company etc. and wait for him to respond with "send me you resume if interested". Thanks for all the help in advance.

Also sorry if this is not the right place for this or if this is done wrong, first reddit post here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>