<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6900</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 17:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It just seems so minor for a dealbreaker  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 13:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not all welcome if ppl under 18 can't take it lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ew definitely not thx for the nightmare fuel tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never understood why guys like high pitched voices so much. 

I like your username btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you weren't related to your parents/siblings and randomly met them somewhere one day, how would you get along with them? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:44:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Username checks out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me I just started asking myself what do I have to lose when asking someone out? Worst thing that happens is they say no, I'm disappointed for a few days, and I move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:36:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Male giraffes can cum in only a few seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever I make a female avatar I get hit on almost immediately, usually in the first five minutes. Which I think is kinda funny cause I'm pretty sure a lot of dudes make female avatars as well so they could be hitting on any creep. But still it's annoying when I'm trying to quest or explore or just learn the roles of the game and there's someone asking me where I live irl and if I'm alone rn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spending too much time talking to their friends. I understand they'd rather talk to their friends than me but if we're on a time constraint we don't have time for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dyed hair. I know it's artificial but I don't ever see myself going back to normal colored hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Use a computer mouse. My mom taught me to use a computer young before she knew I was left handed, so she taught me the right handed way. I have to say I'm happy it turned out that way because I use public computers at the library and at my college pretty often and they're all right handed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not during, but right before. She had cancelled the previous lecture and apologized for it. Then she explained that she had cancelled it because her family had an outbreak of head lice and she had to take her daughter to the doctor. Then she announced she still had head lice but she didn't think it was a problem to come and teach anyway. I've never seen an entire class look so disgusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you find yourself getting upset and worry there's going to be a fight, inform your partner you need to cool off and then talk about it in the morning. Don't let anything progress to a screaming match- talk it out when you've had a chance to settle down and think things through.

Congrats, btw!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mostly my phone and money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a ride operator, and it is nothing like Final Destination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:07:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn, look at your grandma using modern cauliflower grain! She's truly in the 21st century now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the thought that counts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is Jacko typing inappropriate thing into Amazon tho?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:01:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great idea I'm going to go get a spiderweb on my ass tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 11:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful cat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 11:29:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If men are going their own way then why are the even worrying about what those women are doing lmao 

Someone sounds bitter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 11:18:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine walking into a tattoo shop and describing this to an artist. I'd be mortified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 09:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys who are passive aggressive or keep things from me to spare my feelings. If they have a problem with me it pisses me off to no end if they prefer to keep it in until they explode or smtg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 09:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually "I hope they don't leave me a guest complaint." Or in a couple of instances, "I hope they don't hurt me." Some people get really pissed when their kid is too short to ride the roller coaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 09:22:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually I just keep everything in my purse. When I'm at work I have to keep my purse in a locker so I take my debit card, work ID, glasses cloth, and cell phone in my pockets. That's really all the space I need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 09:19:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely wouldn't go down without a fight. I'd try to go for either the hands or eyes first. If I could break their hands they wouldn't be able to strangle me or use a weapon very well, and if I got their eyes I'd be able to get away and run and they'd have a very hard time following me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 09:13:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really wanted to teach myself how to lucid dream when I was younger, so I read a lot of articles about it. Unfortunately one of the articles mentioned that lucid dreaming increases the chance of sleep paralysis and that terrified me. That night I had my first and only lucid dream. I was standing in a white empty room and realized I was lucid dreaming. For a moment I was elated that I had done it. Then I remembered the sleep paralysis and freaked out and woke myself up. I never had another lucid dream again. But now I get sleep paralysis anyway cause of a medication I'm on so I'm considering trying to learn again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 09:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on where I'm located in the house while s/he is trying to break in. I'd definitely try and grab my cell phone and something that can be used as a weapon, then run if I had a big enough head start. I'd break my window, climb the fence, and get out of the neighborhood. Once I was in an area with a lot of people, s/he would be a lot less likely to try and hurt me. There's a McDonald's not too far from my house so I'd probably try to go there before calling 911.

If I didn't have that big of a head start then I'd hide. I'm small so i can fit into a lot of unusual places. Obviously they'd find me eventually but hope I'd have my phone and would be calling 911 while they looked. 

And if they found me before the police came, the last resort would be to get out and fight. Again, I'm small, so the attacker would have a good chance of beating me, so I wouldn't focus on taking out the attacker, I'd focus on taking over their weapon or rendering them unable to use it effectively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 09:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats on your first Liv doll- you're going to love her. They're so pretty. Sadly I've stopped using mine as much because they don't look good next to my smaller headed dolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 09:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still not thrilled about Anu but this was my favorite episode this season. I liked Howard's impressions of Sheldon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 13:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tried to take it but said I don't have permission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 12:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome. How long did it take you to pack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 12:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pra.yers . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 11:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sooo necking is something entirely different in the giraffe world lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 10:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would definitely mention that if I were you. And there's nothing wrong with insisting on the benadryl. When I get my premeds I insist on no benadryl and nothing in its place cause all that stuff makes me sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 10:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 10:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the facial expressions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 10:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much that really helps. I'm feeling better about what I'm doing now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 07:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work as a ride operator at an amusement park. My most embarrassing situation was when I was giving the spiel for a ride. When the ride stops we're supposed to say "have the best day at \[name of park\]." While I was saying that, I felt a yawn coming on and tried to yawn quietly while talking at the same time. Instead, I had the worst voice crack of my life. Kinda killed my professional vibe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 07:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww I was expecting to see a bunch of horrible answers but this made me smile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 03:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really tiny and have two chronic illnesses that prevent physical activity of any kind and also make me really sick when I eat if I'm not on my meds. So I wouldn't stand a chance in the arena. I'd probably just jump off my plate at the beginning to avoid being hacked to pieces by a career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 14:27:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a professional, but I've worked in haunted houses before and these are the things I've done.

The three tactics I've used are jumpscares, staring, and being gross.

For jumpscares you'll need a scary costume obviously. The more shocking/gory, the better. Perfect your scream- if you're good you'll be able to terrify everyone, if not you're going to sound like you're in a comedy. Then pick a good hiding spot. Walk through the house and try not to pick an obvious spot where you'd expect someone to jump out of. Pick an unusual spot that people might not look twice at. Then, when groups of people start coming through, jump out and scream. Make sure you get your timing right. If you do it too early or late it won't make as big of an impression. After you jump out you can hide again or chase the people- just make sure you don't touch them.

For staring (this is my favorite), put on a more dramatic costume- still scary though, obviously. Last time I did a vampire with thick eyeliner and blood running down my face. Find a spot to stand or sit. As people walk by and look at you, make direct eye contact and follow them slowly with your eyes. Turn only your head as needed. Try not to blink and don't let anyone break eye contact. This won't make them scream, but the dread of what you might or might not do will definitely make them nervous. And occasionally if they don't seem to think you're real, a quick swipe at them can be even more terrifying than a jumpscare.

For being gross (I'm sure this has a better name)- this is an ongoing performance. Maybe you can crawl on your hands and knees as a possessed demon or lay flailing on a table as a torture victim. Your purpose is to horrify the viewers rather than outright scare them. It can be a physical performance and require stamina and more advanced acting skills. Think of yourself as a living piece of decor.

So yea that's what I've done. I'm sure there's more tactics but this is just from my experience. I hope I could help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Questions About College And Living </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 14:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a three part question as I'm going to be done with my lower division work soon and need to start thinking about where to move on.

1. Is a BFA necessary or would I be alright with an AA degree? I'm trying to decide whether it would be a better option to get my AA and then start auditioning full time and continue my training through private lessons and master classes, or to stick it out an extra two years and earn my BFA. 

2. Is California a good place to stay in to start my career? I don't feel established enough yet to move across the country.

3. Do you guys attend classes outside of college, and if so, which ones have helped you the most in furthering your career?

If you have any other advice I'd be happy to hear it. I'm honestly terrified getting ready to jump in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 13:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I thought it was weird they never even mentioned Anu (or if they did I missed it). I feel like the episodes this season aren't connected very well just trying hard to tie up all the loose ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 07:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thx for the advice. I don't want to put anything that wouldn't look good on there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can I add non paid work to my resume? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 07:31:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This weekend I'm going to be working as a scare actor in a haunted house but it's a non paid thing. Would it still be acceptable to add to my resume? I don't have a professional career yet, I'm still in school and just doing minor acting jobs at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 09:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it wasn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 09:26:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 09:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had a fever of 104 and was completely out of my head. I became convinced that NASA had put a chip in my brain so they could turn me into a gorilla or horse. My evidence for that was my head hurt (from the chip obviously) and they gave me a banana for lunch. My poor nurse had to deal with me demanding not to be turned into a gorilla/horse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 09:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy had been into me for about a year. One time I was hanging out with him and I let him finger me except he he was really horrible at it like he was actually hurting me. So I told him he was hurting me and then he got really mad and the next day complained in a group chat we were both in that I was the worst girl he'd ever played with and he hated my small tits. Then later he announced to the chat I had scars from cutting myself. So yea fun times lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 09:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks I will :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 16:19:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Water. I don't technically hate milk but I'm lactose intolerant. I honestly don't even remember what it tastes like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 16:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a big fan of facial hair. The guy I'm into is completely bare faced and I think he's hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 16:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmmm I'll have to ask my mom and find out. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 16:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just don't mention you have it and you're good lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 12:36:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BURNING PEOPLE AT THE STAKE IS MURDER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 12:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt exactly the same way after getting my nipple piercings. They made me feel way more confident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 12:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/oldpeoplefacebook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 11:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't wine considered the blood of jesus tho? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 11:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The black and white look really good together :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 11:39:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm assuming this is after an alien race, animal species that has managed to take over, or dominant group of cannibals. Anyways. Women would be used for procreating. Only the strongest and healthiest women would be bred with the strongest and healthiest men. Then they'd be forced to breastfeed the babies ( cause breast milk fed meat would be worth more). After the babies are weaned they'd be taken away and the woman would be impregnated again.

After women reach menopause they'd be slaughtered along with the sick, elderly, and those too small to have any good meat on them. The meat from those humans would be used for pet food for the master species/ cheap human beef jerky/ human hotdogs. 

The babies and kids grow up encouraged to play and work out and are fed a ton of veggies and protein shakes so they grow big and strong. Almost all of the women are then used to procreate and a few fertile men are selected because you only need a couple men to keep a group of women pregnant. The rest of the men, who are ideally strong and muscular are slaughtered and that's where the best cuts of meat come from.

Disclaimer I don't condone cannibalism in any way I just wrote this for fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 11:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy birthday Loki :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 11:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only right way to do it. Congrats :)) Stanley looks happy for you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 10:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful doll! How's the Obitsu body? I've been wanting to get one but don't know much about them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 10:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 10:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 10:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw poor fishie. At least she lived her last few days in comfort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 09:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has content that could upset a lot of ppl so it doesn't appear in r/all and you can't search it and if you do access it there's a warning before you can continue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 09:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just checked and it's not shut down just quarantined </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 09:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom and I set up traps in the neighborhood to catch feral cats so we can spay and release them, but we've also gotten skunks, raccoons, and opossums. The worst was the skunk cause we had to go close and let it out and then it sprayed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 09:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just did it. I think it's a really good idea actually and I'm interested in doing one myself now- did you get a template or make the whole thing yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 14:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now I'm wondering why he'd assume you wanted the drinks when there's an easier way lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 14:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine just felt like a hard pinch. My septum was worse imo. I'd say my nipples were equivalent or maybe a tiny bit worse than my navel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 14:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I assume it's a horseshoe ring you're talking about? Just unscrew the ball and pull it out. If it's stuck try having someone else do it or go to your piercer for help. I ended up having to take mine out right before an MRI and the nurse had me use pliars but idk how safe that is.

The hole isn't going to close up immediately. It'll stay open at least a few hours or even a few days depending on the person. It'll be fine if you take it out, clean it, and put it back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 13:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg that sounds a million times better than that chlorine tasting shit. I wanted to throw up with every drink of that golitely I took. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 13:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "It's just a life sentence for attempted murder" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 11:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That'd be really awesome- I'd definitely take part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 11:19:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I have a flare my safety foods are scrambled eggs, applesauce, smoothies, plain mashed potatoes, plain popcorn, and plain gluten free pasta. It's not much but it's something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 11:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can do it as a tablet? I drank a gallon of Golitely for nothing?? Omfg I feel enlightened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 10:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not quite sure but I think she just sent you a sticker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 09:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as he showers and dresses appropriately I'm cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 09:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd rather get hit and sue the crap out of someone than have it be the other way around  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 09:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really. The only difference is ppl don't worry about being caught. But like I said it's California and ppl aren't as uptight abt it as some places so the fear of being caught wasn't rly that big in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 09:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Toilet paper  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 08:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Cali and everyone smoked weed before anyways so legalizing it just meant ppl just do it in public more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 02:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's true- I didn't think of the possibility of a woman outright admitting she lied. That's not fair for the man who was accused that they get away without repercussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 00:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I'm saying is it's hard to prove someone is lying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 15:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes a false accusation should be punished. That's despicable to do to the accused and makes actual victims lose credibility as well. However it would be very hard to prove something didn't happen and it wouldn't be good if they were locking up real rape victims who hadn't provided enough proof. 

My marine bio teacher made a good analogy once talking about falsifiable claims. The claim "there are no mermaids in the ocean" can be falsified by finding a mermaid. But the claim "there are mermaids in the ocean" can never be falsified because you can only falsify that by proving there are no mermaids in the ocean, and you can't do that because there's always the possibility you just haven't found one yet.

Similarly the claim "s/he was not raped" can be falsified by finding proof of the rape. But "s/he was raped" can never be falsified because there's no way to prove nothing happened.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 15:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I like it. It's a topping some ppl like and some don't... I don't see why it's such a big deal lol 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 15:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> News like this pisses me off. I'm immunocompromised so once an epidemic of preventable disease starts I'm basically guaranteed a horrible and possibly life threatening version of it immediately.

 I always wonder are anti vaxxers just totally ok with killing kids, the elderly, and ppl with health issues by enabling the return of all these preventable diseases? Or do they just not get it? If I end up dying because someone else didn't get their fucking shots I'll rise from my grave and haunt them for the rest of their lives  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 15:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is it with anti vaxxers and colloidal silver? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 15:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn't sound like you are from the post. I assume if there was an epidemic or you started getting the flu every year you'd start vaccinating? Or if you had a kid who really wanted the flu shot for some reason you'd let them get it? Not wanting to get the shot cause it's a hassle and not wanting to get the shot because you believe it's poisonous and will give you autism are different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 15:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What other people are saying, it's all in game stuff. Totally random. Usually it ends up being a piece of furniture. I've gotten a lot of lamps and chairs.

The supernatural one sends an elixir your Sim can use and once you get supernatural you can make and send any elixir you want.

Basic, luxury, and surprise are all just random shit tho lol

Also if you want more gifts lmk your username. I send a lot of gifts to give my sims the moodlets lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 15:07:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow... and I thought my mods were cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 15:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's how crusties look. If it's infected it'll be painful, hot to the touch, oozing pus, stuff like that. If it does get infected, see a doctor or your piercer before taking it out. Otherwise the wound could heal and seal the infection inside. But for now it looks ok. If the crusties bug you then do a warm saline soak to soften them. Don't pick at them tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 14:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like spam posts just clutter up the sub and there's nothing wrong with banning them. 

I like looking at pictures of other people's dolls and it's nice knowing I'm not alone in my love for doll collecting.

It'd be cool to see more discussions- maybe about our collections, what we're working on, underrated dolls we might not know about, ect. I've noticed the sub isn't very vocal and I'd love to have more opportunities to talk with other doll collectors. 

I'm sorry this is so badly written i just pulled an all nighter and now I'm tired lol 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 14:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find that when I'm having a flare, the more "raw" the vegetable the more it makes me sick. So during that time I eat either cooked, processed, or broken down veggies- for example grilling onions before eating them, tomato sauce instead of whole tomatoes, and drinking soups and smoothies instead of trying to eat them raw.

As for not liking them- there's no recipe that's gonna magically make you like vegetables. If there's a couple you like, start there. Try eating veggies you don't like in combination with other things. For example I learned to like pickles by putting them in my burgers. At first I thought they were horrible, then I found them tolerable enough to keep on, then I started enjoying the taste, now I like them.

If you really just don't like the taste of vegetables another way you can get a dose of vegetables is in a smoothie along with fruits. I blend my own so I know exactly what's going in and that there's no extra sugar or anything. Obviously it won't work for every vegetable but ik kale is a really common one. If you blend it with some pineapple and yogurt or whatever combo you like you won't even taste the kale- it just adds a sweetness and a slight difference in texture.

A recipe book I use for smoothies is the Big Book of Juices- it has over 300 recipes and you can look up smoothies by ingredient. If you get a small portable blender and get in the habit of grinding up a smoothie for breakfast each morning you're already on your way to getting more veggies (and fruits)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 13:14:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The question was a little confusing- I assume the guy wants to be friends with the girl cause he's not into her? 

Just don't flirt with her or lead her on or anything. And if she indicates she's interested in you say you only see her as a friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 13:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day and also anything with sour cream and salsa is amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 13:09:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "This is getting awkward I'm gonna go now." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 13:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to be a theatre major and I'm gonna suffer by giving up financial stability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 13:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not speaking for all women. But personally I don't get mad easily and I love it when guys don't sugarcoat stuff to avoid hurting my feelings or whatever. I've seen a lot of guys talk about sucking things up for girls or going over the top with flattery and complaining about things girls do that they don't like and it annoys me cause that makes communication so much harder.

I was friends with a guy who would just straight up tell me if I was annoying him or I didn't like something I was doing (and vice versa too). And it was so much easier than us dancing around each other. I never had to read into anything or worry that I was annoying him or anything cause if i was he'd just let me know.

Again not speaking for all women and not saying all men are like this. And I know some girls just want to hear what they want to hear. These are my experiences and what I like. Not trying to offend anyone here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-13 10:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They used one of those on me too. I like it so much better than doing it by feel. They left it in there after and I spent the whole infusion weirding out my mom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-13 08:40:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom is Democrat and my dad is Republican. They got divorced for other reasons. But when they were married they'd joke about it but now that they're divorced they just fight about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-13 08:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom made me a homemade stylus where you covered the end of a q tip with aluminum foil and then got the end wet. It worked pretty well actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-13 08:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations I'm really happy for you! Good luck I hope you do great :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the biggest inconvenience you've put up with for a significant other? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-13 08:13:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-13 05:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They wouldn't charge the relatives for something they had no knowledge or involvement with unless they could prove they helped out somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 12:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a big fan of Disney so I'm impartial. From watching the trailers I do feel like it takes away a bit of the charm from the animations tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 12:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made a small mistake at work three months ago- like a tiny misunderstanding that took five minutes to resolve. Ever since then, she shit talks me to everyone, spread rumors about me to not only my department but to at least two others, told a guy I was friends with that I was into him, thus ruining our friendship, and yells at me every time I do something she doesn't like. It's getting exhausting and a lot of coworkers are taking her side and have stopped talking to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 12:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work as a ride operator at an amusement park and they don't care as long as the colors aren't too bright, my hair is still well groomed and styled, and I don't shave designs into my hair. It's the first year they allow it so I'm glad I didn't apply last year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 12:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It makes them feel powerful and exclusive. And if they really hate the group they're discriminating against it'll keep them away. I don't discriminate myself and I don't think it's ok but I mean those are the good things that happen to those who do discriminate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 12:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have one myself and it's fucking annoying when ppl park in the handicapped spots they don't need. Usually it just annoys me cause it means the walk is gonna hurt me a lot more. But last month I had to go to the hospital and all the handicapped spots were taken and like 3 cars didn't have placards. We had to park like 3 parking lots away and not only was I not wearing my braces, I was dizzy, weak from not eating and had a fever of 104. I could barely make it in and I was so furious at those ppl who found it inconvenient to park farther away. The hospital has a fucking free valet service and everything too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 11:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now I'm just imaging him waking up and being like "holy shit! I'm earning way too much money!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 11:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that's it. Other than that ways to get lifetime happiness faster are accepting larger wishes, sending and receiving gifts, playing the little game on the loading screen, completing wishes as soon as your sim gets them, and cancelling out wishes you feel won't be fulfilled anytime soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 11:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a person who used to self harm I'd say this is manipulative behavior. I self harmed as a coping mechanism and I absolutely did not want people to know. I didn't threaten people with it and when I ended up doing it I was ashamed and tried to hide it.  I was convinced no one would care if I was hurting myself or even if I killed myself so I didn't see a point in talking about it. 

Now I'm just one person out of many, many self harmers so I'm not saying my experiences cover everyone's. But it sounds like your wife is trying to make you feel guilty rather than actually feeling like she needs to self harm.

About the breaking the skin thing, some self harmers don't do that so you can't really tell by that alone. Some people scratch, some people use tools that make it hard to break the skin, and some people love breaking the skin - it really depends on the person.

It sounds like your wife could still benefit from therapy as it sounds like she does have some issues- self harming issues might not be what she's dealing with exactly, it could be attention seeking or abandonment issues also.

And as a disclaimer in case this advice is completely wrong- I'm not a professional in any way so this is just my personal opinion. Good luck with whatever happens tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 10:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How are they going to punish the woman if she actually kills herself tho? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 10:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I love the bright colors what polish brand did you use?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 10:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oooh I have the same tools I never thought of the bubble design before tho. Looks great I'm trying to resist the urge to steal your idea now lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 10:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't really punish a person who is dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 10:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooooooh a "yeah I'm fine???" I'm literally shaking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 10:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like him to shut the fuck up... does that mean I can kill him now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 09:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I enjoyed seeing some of the older scenes and it was hilarious with Tam in them. Although I think Tam's appearance itself was a weak attempt to connect Young Sheldon and BBT. I would've enjoyed it more if Tam stuck around but with his brief appearance it just seemed like they were tryna connect the two shows real quick and get it over with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 08:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crumple cause I don't have time to sit and fold it I got better things to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 08:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Np- good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 08:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep in mind that it'll be up there forever and anyone will be able to find it. So be careful what you say. No inflammatory political jokes, no racism, sexism, ect, no shit talking people you might work with in the future. Basically, imagine every single future casting director you audition for is going to see this and don't say anything that would piss them off. Otherwise I don't see how it could negatively impact your career. If it turns out great you could even use clips of it in a video reel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 13:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With their last thoughts being "damn I should have got a job instead" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 10:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It could be extreme procrastination or denial of the work it's going to take. You can't make him study tho. He might just have to find out the hard way what happens when he doesn't study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 10:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Prob cause no one cares enough. Also you'd need to know the person's username also and most ppl don't just give out their bank info. 

Thanks for the great idea tho there's a couple ppl I'm hella pissed at rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 10:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends if you had adequate food and water or not. If you didn't you'd be focused on that not her. If you did have that then eventually your desire for sex an human contact might lead you to find her attractive, or maybe after getting to know her you'd be into her personality. 

Or on the other hand maybe you'd get sick of each other and fight to the death lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 10:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always thought about how one would kill themself in a situation like that. Haven't come up with anything yet tho... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 10:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So pretty!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awww this made me smile  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So what happens when he orders a pizza? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [SPOILER ALERT]

In Mockingjay it talked about him raising geese, so maybe it was something he liked to do when younger? Like maybe cooking or raising animals. In my opinion Snow definitely would have made him pick a talent. There would be a lot of attention on him- not only did he win the second quarter quell he did it as an underdog from district 12 and he was handsome and charming at the same time. He'd be getting a lot of media attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn I need a husband who does that xD

Seriously tho awesome hair I love dyeing my hair bright colors the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The IV didn't hurt cause they numbed my hand beforehand. Then they knocked me out and I woke up after it was done. My throat hurt but other than that I wasn't in any pain. I was more confused that loopy, I just asked the same questions over and over which were "is it done already," "did it go ok," and "did I clean out good enough". You'd be more likely to say smtg stupid if you were drunk or high. Then they wheeled me out and I got jamba juice for my throat and then I slept for the rest of the day. 

Tbh the worst part is the cleaning out before hand- after that everything is easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only know the steps in the rides department, there's associate, trainer, supervisor, area supervisor, and rides head. After that I think you get into park wide stuff such as scheduling and finances and after that assistant CEO and then CEO I think? During training they told us all these inspirational stories about ppl rising to the top after only 3 yrs of working there but in reality each step takes forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who got to get certified at the new roller coaster at the park I work at. I won but they decided to certify her anyways cause she's over 18. I'm still pissed abt that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bought a necklace my freshman year of high school after going through a rough time with the comedy tragedy marks to remind me of my passion for theatre. It's been on me during some pretty awful times and whenever I see it I remember that no matter how horrible things get or how alone I feel there's always the theatre. Great thing about it is that it's always on me so I never have to worry abt losing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 09:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Technically CEO if you wanted to stay and work hard enough at it, but that would take forever and I have other plans for my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 14:16:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No area is immune to either natural disasters or extreme weather. So why bother trying to get away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 14:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm extremely immunosuppressed and catch stuff really easily so the flu shot is a must for me. And if you're not gonna get the shot that's chill just lmk so I can stay away from you when the symptoms start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 13:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I assume you mean sore throat? Gargle with warm salt water, suck on cough drops, drink a lot of water. Spoonfuls of honey also help coat the back of your throat and soothe it a bit. If you feel like you're coming down with something just take it easy for a few days and it could go away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 12:17:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Consider the fact, also, that she could be making up the story that her mom went through her phone at all and was just too cowardly to say she wanted to end things. I'm really sorry you're not able to reach her and best of luck whatever happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 11:21:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work at an amusement park. We haven't had any huge accidents for awhile but occasionally someone does something hazardous on a coaster or the lift stops or something. In which case we have to climb the lift and evacuate. Which is why not being afraid of heights is a prerequisite for the job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 11:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in California where weed is legal but when applying for a ride operator job we need to be clean anyways. Then every year we want to stay we get another test that we can't fail. They said they'd be giving us random tests throughout the year as well to make sure we stay clean but I haven't seen it happen yet.

They say they don't care what we do outside of work but ofc weed stays in the system for a long time so if you do end up getting a random test you're done. I mean on the one hand I get it, can't have a bunch of drugged up ride operators in the park. On the other it's hella annoying planning exactly when and how much I smoke in order to pass our annual test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 11:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He told me he loved me right after I said I wasn't looking for commitment or a relationship at that time. Then every time we talked he ended it with I love you and talked about the things he wanted to do to me. He was 14 at this time so I doubt he knew what love meant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 10:34:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was awesome. I love how smooth it was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 10:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, that's beautiful. How long did it take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 09:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn if that's what he expects in a woman then I think a sex doll is the only thing that's gonna please him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 09:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinking a 7.5 inch sandwich... preferably with onions and mustard. Now I'm getting hungry... 

Also fr idk why guys think monster dick size is impressive 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 09:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the dark colors and the spiderweb!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 09:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "What do you want, peasant human?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 09:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great reason to fight someone... being left on read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 09:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 279? That's all? I have an IQ of 450. This person needs to get on my level. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 09:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woah beautiful colors. I'd love to try that on myself eventually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 09:06:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It always makes me sad when moms come up to cuss me out at work with their kids in tow. Great to know that parents are teaching the next generation of kids how to be a complete asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 08:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel indifferent to them and I'm not married to one cause I'm straight and underage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 08:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My first kiss was with a guy I was into and the only thing I could think was "shit he kissed me I'm the luckiest girl ever."

I feel like that's not sweet enough after seeing other peoples responses but that's what I thought lol


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 08:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be really upset because it shows he doesn't care about me enough to make sure I felt good too. I mean guys would be pissed if we stopped mid fuck and left so I don't see why girls can't be pissed also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 08:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make sure you're not over cleaning it- the piercing needs to dry out between washes. Also make sure the salt to water ratio is correct and finally I'd recommend switching to implant grade titanium as you may have a nickel allergy and nickel can be found in some stainless steel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 08:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Highly unlikely. It's probably just irritated- it's easy to irritate a piercing when they're new. Don't touch it or sleep on it or anything and you should be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 08:11:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depending on how bad it is you might want to get stitches. If not just keep a close eye on it to make sure the wound doesn't get infected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 00:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty much sums it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 23:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anything physical. I have the instinct to punch or throw things but I try to channel it into more positive physical activity such as skateboarding and weightlifting. When I put 100% of my effort into my workout it decreases my anger significantly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 23:54:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean you jumped out of a fucking plane that's braver than most people lol

How was it btw? I've always wanted to go skydiving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 23:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know why people still mistake me as a guy because I have pink hair that goes to my chin and wear dangly earrings, but I get mistaken for a guy at work all the time. Could be because I have a lower voice for a girl and our uniforms make everyone look hella flat chested. Anyways I was talking to this dad who was asking me questions on how I operated the ride I was currently at and then I asked him to step back cause I was going to close the gates. He kinda saluted me and was like "yes sir," and I didn't correct him cause I didn't want to risk making a guest unhappy.

However I am able to make my voice really high when I want to (think retail voice/camp counselor voice) so I just started doing that. Suddenly he goes quiet and stops talking to me and I figure he got it. Then he gets on the ride and I check his seat belt and he makes a big point of going "Thank you *ma'am*". Honestly it was hilarious to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 23:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you get over your fear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 23:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $300, I was doing some editing work for my mom and she paid me for it and this was before I had a bank account so I got it all in cash. Holding a shit ton of cash is satisfying but once I got a card I never went back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 23:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You got time then lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stepped on a nest of wasps while we were searching for a cache near an apartment complex. I was about 8 yrs old at that time. They started going for my head and my mom took her GPS (it was an old fashioned bulky grey thing) and started hitting my head trying to kill them. I was screaming and crying and my mom was terrified someone was gonna think  she was beating me with a rock so she tried to drag me to the car with wasps still in my hair. Long story short I couldn't lay down for a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An ex friend of mine told me I was into him and he started acting super weird around me. I thought it was so stupid that he was making a bigger deal about it than I was (I wasn't going to pursue him so I acted normal around him.) I realized he wasn't mature enough to either talk to me about it or get over it, so I got over him instead lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's strange, it used to happen to me too but it was sporadic so I didn't really do anything about it. If you email customer support earlier in the day they have ppl who are actually helpful or at least they did last time I tried. Or maybe other ppl have better advice- sorry I couldn't be more helpfut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exercise, either weightlifting or skateboarding. I used to throw things but doing a non destructive physical activity is better. And then once I get tired out I'm more focused on getting in the shower and eating than my problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:06:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one will ever know which statements were true or false tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm ready sorry you lost your job. Your boss sounds like an asshole for doing that. Also I'm really sorry that your pregnancy took such a toll on your body. I'm glad you were able to have a healthy baby like you wanted and that you're doing better now, but I agree that it's important to think of the woman too. It would be horrible for someone to force you to go through that knowing what would happen to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 09:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks :) I can't wait to listen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Best Version of And Eve Was Weak? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 09:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://youtu.be/vd6CcDZBN_o

https://youtu.be/p-6Vw5BZgFM

https://youtu.be/zUHtXy46Vdk

Personally my favorite was Alice Ripley and Keaton Whittaker but I'm curious to know if you guys have favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 09:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you go days without restarting your computer or play without saving for long periods of time? Those are the only reasons I can think of for the game crashing like that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 08:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great idea I'll start looking for a dragon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 08:56:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The heal time is 4-8 weeks and you should wait that long to have sex too or at least until you can pull on it  gently without hurting it. Not sure about the blowjob part cause I've never sucked off a guy with a piercing before but I'm sure it can be done. I'm pretty sure no one would get a piercing down there if it meant no blowjobs ever again lol

If you ask these questions in r/piercing you'll be able to get advice from ppl who've had it done already also :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 08:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbh you should go for it. The initial pain isn't that long and it looks great once it's done. Make sure you see an experienced piercer tho... don't trust anyone to put a piece of metal in your dick lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 08:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow what are your secrets to such a long life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 08:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have my nipples and navel pierced tho I never really considered that a sexual piercing. I love both of them especially the nipples cause I feel hella insecure about my breasts and they make me feel better about them. Neither of them hurt that bad when I got them done. It was kinda just like a hard pinch.

I know I want a VCH (clitoral hood) piercing later on and I'm considering a tounge piercing eventually too. Those make me nervous tho because facial piercings make me dizzy and VCH just sounds painful, but I'll get it done eventually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 08:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depending on your age and gender you might still be growing. If not there's some kind of surgery you can get where they put metal in your legs to extend them if you have the money and are that desper to grow. Or wear high heels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 05:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can't get it out you can always go back to your piercer and ask them to change the jewelry for you. 

 #x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 05:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most piercing parlors will give the option of piercing with titanium initially and you can go back to buy more jewelry if you want. I buy most of my titanium earrings on Etsy and with dangly earrings I buy titanium wire at craft stores and just rewire them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 20:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course that's rape. He was too drunk to consent. Had the roles been reversed everyone should be pissed. Male rape is a thing. That monologue was appalling to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 20:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ordered a lava lamp shape desk lamp with fairy lights wrapped around it. It was supposed to be a birthday present for my mom. When it arrived it was the size of my thumb and the "fairy lights" were a piece of wire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 10:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Performed an original monologue in the Orpheum theatre as part of the EduHam program. I was pretty proud of myself for that. I mean compared to some of these ppl it's not as impressive but I haven't been alive long enough to build some amazing career or anything yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 10:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ohhhhhhhh so that's why girls don't poop  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 10:19:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I already posted this story in answer to another question but it applies here too so ima say it again.

Basically I tried to kill myself and ended up in the psych ward, which I hated cause it was hella boring all we were supposed to do was sit around and think about getting better. We had half a deck of cards, a cloth puzzle in one piece, and a TV with all the shitty channels. So we were bored to tears most of the time and that wasn't making me feel better at all.

Night 3 I was in the community room after dinner and they played the Hunger Games movie for us which has always been my favorite movie and book. Anyways they reached the scene where Katniss was trapped in a tree by the careers and I was marvelling at her acting job.

That reminded me of my own passion for acting and how much I loved it and all the roles I'd dreamed of playing and the things I wanted to do. I mean it wasn't an instant cure but it slowly gave my life purpose again. After I got out of the psych ward I started acting again and then singing a little and now I'm in college to become a theatre major (slash waitress, I know). But I like to think that movie stopped me from ending it all.

I have a ton of nightmares now days where I'm dying slowly and all I do in those dreams is cry and talk about how I'll never perform again. I mean it sucks but at least I know I don't wanna die now.

So yea sorry for rambling so much but retelling the story helps me too sometimes lol

Also I just want to add that they stopped the movie halfway through and made us go to bed and I'm still pissed about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 08:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always wondered what would happen if you shaved a maine coon- thank you for satisfying my curiosity. Your kitty is adorable btw especially the tail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 08:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever someone says tattoos are gonna look bad when I get older ima show them this pic. She looks badass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [NSFW] Bump on Nipple Piercing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 08:11:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's a pic idk how to make it link 

http://imgur.com/a/IVwwxYO

Anyways I keep getting this bump on the right side of my left nipple only. It's tender and after a few days it starts peeling and once it peels it burns if contact is made with the bump. Usually all I do is ignore it and it goes away. Then after a few days it's back. And the cycle starts again. It's really annoying and not very attractive- any advice on how to make it go away?

EDIT: The piercing is eleven months old, the jewelry is externally threaded titanium and I haven't changed it since I got it pierced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 06:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea it is lmao 

Someday I'll find out for real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 06:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbh I'd try to put as many in my mouth as possible cause I've always wanted to know how many I could fit. I'd eat them later tho. And share the ones I didn't put in my mouth lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 06:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I subscribed to that awhile ago when I was considering killing myself. Seeing post after post about why everyone else wanted to kill themselves just made things so much worse for me. No judgement to anyone who the community helps but idk how anyone could get anything out of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Way too much work. Also after an 8 hour day at work you get sweaty and that doesn't look great. And if I accidentally rub my eye or wipe my nose- big mess everywhere. But mostly I just prefer using those thirty minutes in the morning to sleep in rather than put on makeup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Comedy or Errors was the first Shakespeare I was in so it holds a special place in my heart. We  did ours with a circus theme and I was Dromio of Ephesus. I love the idea to set it during the 60's as well. I  wish I was close enough to see that production- it looks amazing. Loved the cast pictures! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It takes about a year for it to heal fully. I was able to do everything normal after about two months tho. And yea clean it, especially if it gets irritated, change your bra/shirt every day, and don't bump your nipples too much. Other than that you're good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry :( I hope you're able to get everything worked out with your meds soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:25:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what happiness looks like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww it looks so happy! I know where I want to go on vacation now lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful doll and beautiful outfit too. She looks stunning in it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 05:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I can I take the day off, if not I just grin and bear it. If anyone asks why I'm in the bathroom so much I just say I ate something funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasn't me but a coworker came to work high. He told me he was bored and he didn't see any reason not to. We're ride operators so that could be a huge safety hazard. He took the control of the ride we were operating and I was exit (basically he controlled the ride, I watched and alerted him if anything seemed off). After about two cycles I realized he had no idea what he was doing, called our supervisor, and informed him I'd be taking control. I mean don't get me wrong I smoke weed too but not when I'm working. That's just stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A ride operator at an amusement park. It's pretty great I'm still there actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually what I do to ensure I don't fuck up is I imagine what would happen if I were in that situation and what I would and would not want someone to say to me. I mean obviously we're all different but it helps me get some general ideas.

 #x200B;

Often my friends just want to talk or vent so all I need to do is listen. 

 #x200B;

And if all else fails buy them ice cream and/or alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does it not break a guy's nose when a girl sits on his face?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 04:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does relationship status change the quality of the ride at all? Do they get a negative moodlet when around enemy bikes?  I'm intrigued here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 22:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And now Bernadette shames Penny for not wanting kids. A full transformation... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 10:48:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once it heals blowing your nose is no problem. I could blow it gently after a few weeks and after about 2 months I was fine. I'd reccomend getting it just get it done at  a time where you don't get as many allergies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 10:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually I have a fetish for being treated like a literal piece of trash so he's right! :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 10:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll definitely keep that in mind when I make the move to LA or NY- thanks so much for the great advice.

I don't know how long it'll be till I can do that since I didn't start out as a child actor, but hopefully college will do some good lol

I didn't realize networking could be so powerful- I suppose you get somewhat of a reputation in the community? I heard that once you get labeled as difficult to work with it's a lot harder to get cast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok but I wouldn't be laughing if a kid shredded all my money like that. Especially if all I knew is /maybe/ I'd get /some of it/ back but not for two years. 

"Ahahahaha classic Leo, shredding all the money we've saved for a year. Such a cutie!"

I mean not that it's all the kid's fault, they shouldn't have left out the money and shredder. But still I'd be hella pissed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just hope the finale isn't that Leonard manages to change Penny's mind and she gets pregnant and a that shit.

It annoys me when the end of romance novels/comedies/whatever always end happily ever after with the girl pregnant. Even if she didn't want to get pregnant in story somehow her family always convinces her and that's the happy end. 

My point is it would piss me off if that happened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for your response, that really helps. Good luck with your acting career- being able to support yourself is a great thing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd reccomend FLuffeeTalks- he's not totally unknown but he's still got a small channel. He posts hilarious shit tho I could spend all day watching his channel 

https://www.youtube.com/user/FLuffeeTalks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:31:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in the psych ward and they played the Hunger Games for us and at that moment I remembered my dream of becoming an actor and my passion for theatre and film and all things acting really. I mean it wasn't like boom I'm cured but it got me thinking. Now days I have terrible nightmares about dying cause I'm scared of how close I got but it's better than the alternative  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was 15 I gave myself a stick and poke treble clef. I'm 16 now and still don't regret it although I'm gonna wait before adding anything else lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:28:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sit back and watch the next person come and try and get them off while laughing?

I hate it when ppl don't unrack the machines cause usually I'm too small to get the weights off which leads to some embarrassing situations lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's this girl who was in my biology class who just turned 15 so there were 6 months until she could get her permit. So she asked her mom to get her a car, her mom asked what she wanted, she said a brand new Corvette, and that's what she got.

About a week later she's posting on her sc "omg I hate my mom I can't wait till I move out" and all that shit, turns out she was upset cause the wifi went down for two days and she thought her mom was a cheapskate for not getting it fixed?? Idk but the next day her mom have her 200 dollars for makeup and all is forgiven. 

Currently she's mad at her mom again for being cheap we'll see how long that lasts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To add onto the sneezing stories, I was operating a chairswing ride and sitting on a stool looking up at the ride in case I needed to E-stop it. Some dude on the ride sneezes and a huge glob of snot goes flying over my head. 

Other things that have gone flying over my head include cell phones, vomit, and spit. I guess that's why they provided a hat with our uniform... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a hard one but maybe tickets to RENT when it went on tour in my city. It's hard to beat live theatre imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:06:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How fascinated I am with the acting choices the actors in horror movies make right before their deaths... whenever someone gets me started I ramble until I realize no one's listening lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 08:58:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How long did it take for you to make the jump? My drama teacher said it might never happen which scared me a bit so I'd love to hear your experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do you Balance Auditions and a Day Job? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 08:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm still in school so I don't have to worry about this quite yet but I want to be ready when the time comes. How are you guys able to work a day job and make it to auditions at the same time? Do you leave work whenever you have an audition or work a job with weird hours or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 08:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awww. You tried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 00:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How would they even know what you're doing in the bathroom tho? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Meet Red Boy- I love him so much </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 13:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 13:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What country do you live in? I've never heard of that before. 

Also I'm sorry to hear that- I hope your job is ok  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 13:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never been pregnant and never plan to be so I can't compare to that. 

My period cramps are pretty bad to the point where I want to do nothing but lay down when they happen. But that doesn't compare at all to my Crohn's cramping.

Everyone prob thought I was having a baby with the way I was screaming and crying lmao 

At least with labor pains you get a new baby at the end and with your period you get the wonderful news that you won't be having a baby. With Crohn's cramps all you get is a colonoscopy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 13:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happened to me too during my very first flare about a year ago. I lost a bunch of weight and I'm already really small so I looked unhealthy af. 

So my doctor said I needed to drink three cans of Ensure a day which was fine in the beginning but after about a week I got sick of the taste. It didn't make me gain weight but it made me lose weight slower.

I also tried to make myself eat a little bit of solid food every day even though it was usually only a couple bites. Rice, mashed potatoes, plain popcorn, plain scrambled eggs, and applesauce were about the only four things I could tolerate.

Really my savior was jamba juice. That stuff is amazing. That's just a personal preference but I tell it to everyone. 

Good luck getting through this flare- you got this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 12:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I let a guy who'd been into me for a while finger me. He really hurt me and I told him that. Next day he goes on a group chat we're both in and says I have small tits and I'm the worst girl he's ever played with. And now that I think about it that's prob where my insecurities started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 12:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found twenty five bucks on my way to work one time. I used the five to buy lunch and I think the twenty is still in my purse cause I use my card way more than cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 12:24:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really enjoying Hot Dog Bush right now. I had to pay 2 dollars for it but it's really addicting. It's probably not the best of the best, but that's all subjective anyways :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 12:21:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I really enjoyed watching your stop motion- I wish cooking were that easy irl

Out of curiosity, how many fps was it? I'm struggling to get my stop motions to be as smooth as yours are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 12:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh maybe that's why I always feel sick after drinking coffee. I've actually laid off it entirely except for when I volunteer at science camp because at that point I need it. I always thought it was the coffee making me sick, maybe not tho... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 12:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awww it's nice the guy stuck around after knocking her up tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 11:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awww that's so nice. It really makes things so much easier when there's someone to look after you.

Also holy shit you're still going to work? Last time I was sick I basically spent two weeks on the couch. You're a trooper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Giraffe Spots </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 10:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 10:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awww so cute! I love the big eyes and the rose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 10:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Winning a Tony award. I know it's not realistic but it would make me proud of myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 09:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbh I just do. It was harder when I was younger but now I just tap their name and say hey.

Ik that doesn't really help- a tactic that helps me is imagining the best and worst outcomes. The best thing that could happen is you have a nice conversation. The worst thing is that she leaves you on read. And then you move on. It's not a life altering action. Unless you're gonna confess to murder. But I doubt you are.

Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 17:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's weird. If all your sims die at uni then usually the game just takes you back. You could try going to edit town mode and switching households or just starting a new game. How does your game even work with no sims? Are you able to click anything to interact with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 10:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then, my mom called 911 and they took me in for a psychiatric evaluation! They said I had "serious issues" and it's "against the law to assault people" and now I'm going to jail for a few years. But it was all worth it to protect my Tumblr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 09:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After the last Sim in your house dies you'll be taken to the map again and be prompted to choose or create a new household. If you want your new Sims to grab your old Sim's tombstone then a ghost will come out every so often and of course the Sim can always be resurrected with ambrosia or the Oh My Ghost! opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 09:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds like a really interesting concept- do you know if there's a cast album out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 09:29:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I've been called ugly before, mostly by people who get mad at me and once by a guy I rejected. It makes me really self conscious cause I'm a really small person pretty much everywhere and I hear nothing but negative stuff about that. But what can you do besides ignore it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 09:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ew the maggot one scarred me for life. I should've listened to your warning lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 09:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kleenex is a brand and tissue is the generic name. So when people say can I have a Kleenex they're only right if it's Kleenex brand tissue. I mean it doesn't matter but it still bugs me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 08:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand. When I'm upset I also demonstrate totally rational human emotions such as murdering people. It's just the way we express ourselves! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 23:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now I feel left out I might have to do some research... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 23:56:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a basic dick lmao

I didn't know dick drawings could be cute with a smiling face  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 13:37:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sadly I've never gone a day without encountering parents like that. The "please check ten billion times to make sure my kid is strapped in" question is the most annoying of all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 13:08:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I've always wondered too. They willingly put their kid on the ride and then freak out like I'm gonna make the ride self destruct or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 13:05:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the coat and your foal is super cute. Also I love the name Ziggy! I can just imagine him running around  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 13:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all I'd definitely recommend getting your hair done at a salon- it's 100% worth the extra money. I tried to dye my friend's hair but we ran out of dye and also I didn't leave the bleach in long enough so she ended up with half normal hair and half greenish brown hair. So salon all the way if you're not experienced.

They'll bleach your hair if they think it's too dark to take the color or if your hair is blonde enough they'll put it straight in. 

Of course your natural hair is going to come back because you always have more hair growing in. The more of your hair you dye the longer it'll take- for example if you only do your tips you can cut them off if you get sick of it but if you do your whole head you're going to have to wait a while if you want to grow a whole new head of natural hair.

If you want to change your hair a whole new color permanently then I'd reccomend getting it touched up every few months- either when it fades too much or when your roots start showing too much- i.e, when your natural hair grows back and you feel like it's showing too much.

If you only want to do it one time, then just dye it once and either wait for it to grow out or wait till you get sick of it and dye it back. 

If you want to do tons of different colors just go in to change it whenever you feel like it. That's what I do- every few months when my current color fades, I go back, pick a new color, and cut the dry ends off. 

If you're worried you're gonna hate it I'd reccomend chalking your hair or using a temporary dye to see what it'll look like before fully committing. But if it turns out a complete disaster, you can always just dye it back.

There's not really much else to do for upkeep. If you want to preserve the color longer you're gonna have to take cold showers and stay out of the sun for long periods of time, and I'd reccomend washing your hair with a lot of conditioner specifically meant for dyed hair in order to keep it soft.

Good luck and let me know if you have any other questions :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 12:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For my endoscopy they knocked me out and I woke up with a sore throat. Then I got jamba juice and went home and slept all day. It's really not bad at all. The sore throat is the worst part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm Sick of People Saying They're Jealous of Me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 12:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A surprising amount of people love to vent to me about how jealous they are of me. Everyone at my school, after finding out my PE class was waived, would respond with "luckyyyy" or "I wish I was you" or "you're so lucky to be sick, you have no idea how awful it was running the mile today"

That stings, especially cause I'd give anything to be able to take PE class.

I even have people tell me they wish they had broken legs like me so that people will feel sorry for them, or that they wish they could trade bodies with me so they can have my "robot legs" (KAFOs).

I know I shouldn't get mad and these ppl are just trying to be friendly. But I'd give anything to be healthy and be able to walk and run and jump and not be in pain as much as them and all they want is "robot legs" and for people to feel sorry for them.

Do any of you guys get these comments and if so how do you respond?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 12:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was really sick and couldn't keep any solid foods down I drank a lot of Jamba Juice and Ensure. It didn't help me gain weight but it prevented me from losing weight until I was good enough to eat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 12:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meeting my dad's side of the family in Vietnam. The meds I'm on make me so immunosupressed there's no way I'd be able to do any kind of international traveling, especially to rural Vietnam. Not to mention finding food and water that wouldn't make me have a flare (idk if I spelled that right sorry). It sucks cause I'm half Viet and I've always wanted to meet the rest of my family and see where my dad was born. But it's not something I'm gonna risk my life to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Q A for the Helicopter Parents at my Workplace </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 12:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dear Parents,

To save you the hassle of asking me these questions when you bring your kids to an amusement park, I've prepared a short Q A answering all of your burning questions! Feel free to share this with any parent who is considering bringing their child to an amusement park!

Note: I'm certified at a chairswing style ride but these answers apply to any ride you're wondering about :)


Q: Are you going to double check my kid?

A: Don't worry. We check everyone.


Q: But what about my kid? She's the one in the pink sweater!

A: I checked her. She's fine.


Q: But what if she's not?

A: She is.


Q: But what if she falls out?

A: She won't unless she decides to jump out. 


Q: But the seatbelt looks wrong!

A: Come back and criticize me after you get certified at this ride :)


Q: What are you doing now??

A: Pressing the button that makes it start.


Q: What is it doing??

A: Starting.


Q: Now what is it doing??

A: Going up.


Q: Is it supposed to make that noise??

A: Yup.


Q: Why is your hand over the red button?

A: In case there's an emergency.


Q: There's gonna be an emergency???

A: I said IN CASE.


Q: Now what are you doing?

A: Watching the ride.


Q: Don't you think that's creepy?

A: You're right. I'll close my eyes and plug my ears instead.


Q: WHERE'S MY KID?? SAY HI TO THE CAMERA! DON'T JUMP OUT! IT'S OKAY! JUST STAY PUT. EVERYTHING IS GOING TO BE ALRIGHT.

A: Please stop screaming in my ear while I operate a piece of heavy machinery with your kid on it. 


Q: What about that noise? 

A: We're trained to bring the ride down at any sign of abnormality. Don't worry.


Q: Why is the ride coming down??

A: Because it's over...


Q: What if my kid jumps out?

A: It'll probably hurt.


Q: CAN YOU GO LET MY KID OUT?

A:  I'm not allowed to leave the control pannel...  but you can go let your own kid out!

Don't get me wrong, I love my job! But don't worry parents- your kids are more safe on the ride than I am in the control booth. Relax and stop screaming in my ear :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 11:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drew a dick on her sweater. In their defense she was a dick. I still felt bad for her though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 11:32:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well my mom spent all year talking about how great she felt after going off a antidepressants and what horrible side effects they gave her.

Then I get prescribed antidepressants and suddenly she's on my ass every day making me take them and forcing me to go to my therapy group even though they made me tired as fuck.

I mean I'm not mad at her, they did make me feel better and I know she was just concerned for me. Still hypocritical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 11:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mentioned my birthday in passing to a classmate and the the day of she made me three adorable cards and a drawing of me. I still have them in my drawer. Not even my close friends remember my birthday so that was a huge deal to me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 11:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk if you're familiar with the EduHam program but my school had the opportunity to participate in it. We had to write a project about one of the historical figures in Hamilton's time and then we'd get a ticket to go. 

My project was actually chosen to perform on the Hamilton stage which was cool cause I got to see backstage and meet some of the actors and then perform which was a dream come true for me. The performers got orchestra seating as well which I never would've been able to afford but the view was great. And as a bonus after there was an ice cream truck and I happened to have two bucks. So yea that was the best trip I've been on.

As a side note this wasn't Broadway it was the Orpheum Theatre in San Fransisco. The performance  wasn't any less impressive (I'm talking about the Hamilton one not mine lol) just specifying where I'm at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 10:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm thinking post explosion Veronica from Heathers. I'm a musical theatre nerd but also it's
Halloween and I wanna use my fake blood. So I came to a compromise lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 10:18:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here it pissed me off so much. And my first phone was a flip phone and my sister got a smartphone. 

BUT now that I'm 16 I was able to get a job and my sister can't get one now no matter what she does. And I just treated myself to an S9+ so I feel like I got my revenge lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 10:13:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My most precious thing is a necklace that cost 20 bucks and the thing I've always dreamt of is a billion dollars. Let me know who's up to make the trade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 09:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Hey did you finish your part of the group project? By the way, I wanted to let you know I'm not interested in you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 08:56:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks great! I love the blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 08:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The dramatic last words and head tilt when someone's about to die. No one's head tilts like that and death isn't beautiful. It pisses me off so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 08:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a ride operator and I'm certified at a roller coaster with a loop so all I gotta do is check restraints and press the dispatch button  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 03:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woah that's beautiful. I know what I'm going to be putting on my backpack next! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 03:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a lot thinner and just feels like a piece of thin skin and when you pinch it it hurts a lot less than the cartilage. Another way I tell she got it is sometimes I feel for it again and it's hard to find because there's a piece of metal through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 03:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.bodyjewelry.com/tibeburiwila5.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 03:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea those ones! My school had a book fair and I couldn't resist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember when I was younger they were categorized as near threatened- didn't realize so much had changed now. Poor giraffes...

On a happier note, the calf is adorable. I can't wait to see what they name her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you use semi permanent dye or something more temporary? If it's permanent or semi permanent it's going to be there for awhile. The only way to really make it go away would be lighten it with bleach or totally bleach and redo it, but you'd want to be careful with overdoing the bleach and damaging your hair. 

You could also try to fade it by taking hot showers and spending a lot of time out in the sun, which you're supposed to avoid if you want to preserve the color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New navel jewelry! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I inhaled my ball the other day. If you blow your nose really hard it might come back. If not I don't think there's anywhere it could really go. If you ate it, there's nothing really you can do about it. I'd reccomend keeping a few extra septum rings on hand for situations like these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 11:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's mad at me for a small mistake I made two months ago and is spreading rumors about me that not only everyone I work with has heard but all of the other areas of my workplace have heard as well. She turned a lot of people against me and it's really awkward during break and lunch now. Not only is she spreading rumors about me, she complains about me to my coworkers- my appearance, personality, habits, everything. Whenever I do something she doesn't like, even if it's not against the rules, she yells at me and then goes to the guest and tells them everything I said was wrong, thus making them mad at me and usually getting me cussed out. But when the manager is around she's the nicest person ever. 

I really don't even care if she has a bone to pick with me, but I lost a lot of friends at work and that really hurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm an introvert and I'm not afraid to talk to people or anything, sometimes I just need someone else to initiate a conversation. And I do get tired of socializing after awhile and it's annoying when people take it personal. That's pretty much it. If I really want to get to know someone better then I'll reach out myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well now I know what to make for my uncle's birthday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't wait. I have the pop art version which is my favorite right now but I'm super stoked for the new content and just to have the 10th anniversary edition in my collection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-28 10:28:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My piercer definitely got my sweet spot (she showed me where it was and let me feel it before she pierced it) and it was still my most painful piercing. I think it's different for everyone but I'm surprised how many people didn't feel any pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:46:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never thought about it that way- that's a really good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard that before... not very reassuring... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried it for years and it didn't help me at all. I literally can't build muscle and I was dislocating my ankles and knees every day. I'd reccomend asking a doctor familiar with EDS before trying. 

And I'm just gonna put a disclaimer down here: I'm not a doctor myself. If my advice ruins your life... well I warned you lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:30:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oof you have my deepest sympathies. I definitely got the anxiety with the Prednisone- I had random panic attacks out of nowhere for months. It also caused me to gain about 20 pounds (I think it was water cause I lost it right after I went off.) And I was either always sleeping or wide awake. 

The worst thing it did for me was magnify my depression and just send me spiraling down- I had a bit of mild depression at the time and the prednisone just enhanced it.

The way I dealt with it is not a method I'd reccomend- I decided I was going to kill myself, my mom found out, and I ended up in the psych ward.

As soon as I got out my doctor took me off and put me on Mercaptopurine instead.

So what I'd reccomend is don't do what I did, if your anxiety gets too bad or if you feel the urge to hurt yourself, tell your doctor you need to get off immediately, and having a therapist to help you get through this time isn't a bad idea either. 

Otherwise what I did was try and go to events and do hobbies that interested me- which was hard when I was feeling depressed but I tried to do something that excited me each day.

Good luck-- you can get through this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get most of my doll furniture and accessories on Etsy. 1:8 isn't a super common scale but I see it around, and a lot of shops take custom orders as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Giver. The main characters were supposed to be like twelve and they made them teenagers having a dumb forbidden romance... as if there wasn't enough of that.

Also I'm a diehard Hunger Games fan so of course I noticed every dialogue and detail change and would love nothing more than an 8 hour R rated version detailing each and every line of dialogue and death and everything. But of course that would be expensive and probably really unpopular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 10:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually I walk all the way to the back looking for empty seats cause I hate sitting next to people. Then if there's no empty seats I panic and sit next to the smallest person I see to reduce the chance of touching them.

By small person I mean small adult obviously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 09:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me, I get into a totally different mindset when I walk onstage for an audition. I think to myself, "I look great, I'm doing great, and everyone wants to see me." Then if we have time to practice or they give us space I'll go to the middle and do my thing. Not trying to butt other people out or be pushy- just to be unapologetically there and put the entirety of my effort into my dancing/acting/whatever without a care about what other people think. For an audition, it's essential to stop worrying about what other people are thinking about you or it WILL hold you back.

And in real life I'm a pretty reserved person, so I just treat my audition self as another character- "this is Audition Emma and she knows she looks sexy doing this dance and she's going to stand right here and practice".

You don't have to stay in that character mindset after you get the part. You don't even need to do what I do. I'm not a professional, just a fellow actor sharing my own method. 

Basically just forget about everyone else and do your thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I feel heartless for not wanting kids </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 09:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stupid rant but I can't really post this anywhere else without being patronized- I mean maybe I'll get patronized here too I'll find out.

So I'm only sixteen and work with people ages 15-20, so I was surprised with how much kids were brought up in our conversations when I first started my job. Literally all of the girls and even a couple of the guys are suffering with baby fever. 

Recently one of my coworkers found out he's gonna be a dad and when his friend was telling me about it I was expressing my condolences and saying maybe if he was lucky the baby wouldn't be his. She was shocked and told me he was elated.

This was news to me- he's still in high school and elated to be a father? 

A few days later I mentioned it to one of my other co-workers- something like "all the babies that come here are adorable but honestly I don't understand how a parent could love a child so much when all it does is bring pain and exhaustion."

She actually yelled at me, calling me selfish for not wanting kids and said we were born to raise kids and she couldn't believe how selfish I was being by not wanting to bring life into the world. She said she couldn't wait to have kids and she already felt love for her future children and couldn't believe I couldn't.

Now I feel confused- like I was born lacking a certain empathy or feeling I need to love a child or whatever.   But I do know how to feel love because I care about other people a lot. I just don't think I could ever love a child if I got pregnant.

So yeah. I don't know how to conclude this post. Thanks for reading my whole rant I guess if you actually did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 10:32:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was a guy in high school who said he liked girls under five feet so he could pretend they were little children. He wasn't joking either. Then he started hitting on me... hahaha no thanks. 

I'm gonna assume this isn't the case for most men tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pink and blue- I was worried how it would turn out but it reminds me of cotton candy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 10:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 10:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful placement and jewelry and I can tell the piercer knew what they were doing. I love the opals. I can't wait to get dermals myself, just got to make sure there aren't any MRI scans in my near future... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Questions About Buying New Jewelry? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had my nipples pierced for almost a year now so I'm very excited to change them. However I'm having a hard time finding implant grade titanium pieces. So I guess my question has two parts.

1. Is there a place online that sells titanium nipple jewelry? Most of the stores I've been to have had very sparse selections.

2. There are piercing shops near my house I could go to, but are you allowed to just walk into one and buy jewelry? And if so would I need an ID to do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:50:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well obviously wear the bandages and clean the piercing three times a day with either piercing spray or salt water. Other than that all you can really do is make sure it doesn't get bumped or irritated too much. 

Some ways to tell if a piercing is rejecting or migrating is if the hole seems bigger, you start to see the bar through your skin, or it seems irritated all the time. In that case you should see your piercer and have it removed before it tears through the skin.

I don't mean to alarm you with that tho. You'll see the bar pushing the skin long before that happens. Congrats on your new piercing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks nice :) 

Have you ever considered the same piece but in gold? I think that would look really good on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful. I'd never have the patience to spend that long on a painting but kudos to you for doing so. I love how clean you were able to make the lines- I was never able to figure that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My grandma used to make rose hip tea when I was a little kid and I became fascinated and made all my friends eat rose petals. Totally forgot about it until now though... thanks for reminding me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad it's finally happening... too bad it's taken so long. The more diversity we get with actors, producers, basically everyone, the more new ideas and different takes on characters we get... basically what I'm trying to say is that if everyone is the same it's gonna get boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely go in with a monologue prepared from the style of the show- but not a monologue from the actual show. What happens after largely depends on the director. Sometimes they'll have you just go. The last audition I was at the director kept me and had me read a monologue from the show (with script) and then had me cold read two scenes with other actors. So basically go in with a monologue ready but be prepared for anything. 

Make sure you understand the play too. Reading the whole thing before the audition is a good idea. My high school drama teacher was a former director and told me that when she cast shakespeare plays she always had the actors cold read a monologue or scene and then made her casting decisions based on who was actually able to understand and portray the language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:09:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started out with Romeo and Juliet, but that's just because they made us watch it in school. The first one I read on my own was The Tempest- it was funny, fast moving, and easy to understand, and afterwards I went on Sparknotes to decode the jokes I didn't get the first time. It was a lot of fun and I ended up using one of the monologues as an audition piece later on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 09:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Is that a banana in your pants or are you just happy to see me?"

"Nah, it's literally a banana in my pants. Sorry." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 11:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually have both of the same problems you do and was able to get my nipples pierced just fine and love them so much.

The key here is finding a great piercer. Make sure he or she is certified, sterile, and, of course, makes you feel comfortable.

My piercer had three sizes of nipple bar and when I told her that my nipples were really small, she just pierced them with a small bar. If your nipples really are too small, though, a good piercer will tell you that- they won't do a piercing that you aren't anatomically suited for.

As for the second part of your question- I'm also immunocompromised with sensitive skin and my piercings were able to heal fine. I know I said this already but find a good piercer who will do it correctly. For the initial jewelry I'd reccomend titanium in order to prevent an allergic reaction.

Then it's up to you to take care of them. They are high maintenance piercings. You need to clean them three times a day with piercing spray or warm saltwater. And at least for the first few months make sure you change your bra or shirt every day to avoid buildup of bacteria. And make sure you don't bump or pull at your chest as that will irritate them.

As for how much it'll hurt- I mean obviously it's gonna hurt some but I honestly didn't find it very bad at all. I thought my septum was worse. My piercer iced my nipples first to make them hard and I think that numbed them up a bit. Then I got really nervous and she played some music and I just focused on that and then it was just like a hard pinch.

About thirty minutes after my nipples started burning really bad so I took off my shirt and iced them but that also went away after about an hour. And it was smooth sailing from there.

Let me know if you have any other questions- as you can see from my essay, I love talking about my piercings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rematch Question </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 11:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>