<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2341</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 17:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you need to talk to someone, it's not a bad thing. Everyone does, and I'm sure at least some of them would understand if you need to just talk things out. If they aren't giving you the time you need, though, then you need to make it clear that you have needs like this, like everyone else. And of they don't take it seriously, then there's someone else who will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 02:13:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not really about "fate" or anything like that. What I mean is, your life is exactly the same as before you learned about determinism. It doesn't matter in the end whether we control our actions or not, because the world we live in is the same one as it was yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 01:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I beleive in determinism, but i think of it a little differently than just you have no control. Basically, if determinism is true, it still doesn't mean that there's a set future or that the future you think you're destined for is what you'll get. What I mean is, even if there is no free will, we still don't know what the future is. We still feel the effects of our actions and those effects can be good and bad. There's no reason to be afraid of a lack of free will, because its out of our hands whether there is or isnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 15:56:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just need to explain to her that too much advice and help stresses you out, and that you'll help yourself more when your ready. 

She might also be putting this on you if she's going through a tough time too to kind of forget about her own stuff going on. Does she talk about what's going on with her a lot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 02:19:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A covalent bond is when 2 or more orbitals overlap, but electrons tend to stay in the orbitals of carbon slightly more because they are at a lower energy state in the carbon orbital which is more stable. This means carbon has a slightly negative average charge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 02:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fallout New Vegas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 01:53:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In organic chemistry, reduction is when you gain something that increases charge density with the carbons, so when you ad a hydrogen, with a lower electronegativity than carbon, the carbon gets slightly more electron dense than before. Oxidation in organic chemistry reduces carbon's charge density, like oxygen or chlorine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 03:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It shouldn't ruin your friendship with either of them. This could be a really good thong honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 02:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, I'm not sure what you need help with? Is this necessarily a bad thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 18:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't do that, I know it's hard to keep going, but cutting your life short isn't the answer. If your parent's really don't like you, that isn't your fault, it's not a reflection of you in any way. If your friends don't like you, then that's their loss, not yours. Scree them, there are people out there who will care about you and love you, even if people around you right now don't give you what you need. Happiness is hard, but over time, we make it. Don't give up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 23:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had a lot of friends who talked to therapists, most of them said that it helped them. It's good to talk about how you feel with someone. I'm sorry about how you're feeling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 23:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Btw, what do you mean "making yourself useful"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 23:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you talked to your parents or doctor? Or a close friend? Although, I'd be a little careful of what you tell your friends at your age, sometimes some people you think you can trust can't really be trusted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 23:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 23:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, at least once a week. I think it's fine as long as it doesn't completely take over your life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 21:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean nice of you to not just scroll by and pretend you didn't see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 21:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good work dude, honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 19:10:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya, they will trust you less, i think it goes down by 10 points. They won't wanna be your ally as much and their opinion of you will go down. Anyone else in the war on your side that isn't your client state will lose trust in you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 03:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I can tell you is that my friend, who I'm very close with and I believe is a good person, made his choice. He doesn't regret it, and he's made the lives of the people around him better. He is a good person, and you are too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 02:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You aren't a burden on your parents, they're taking care of you because they love you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 02:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't give up either, it's gonna be hard for a bit, but it makes you stronger, and you will be wiser and happier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 02:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend went through something similar. His girlfriend cheated on hin at 16 and told him the baby was his, he didn't know he was cheated on. He found out after it was born and thought it was his for i think a few months, left her and hasn't spoken to her since. He doing much much better now because he "got out of there" 

She betrayed you, you don't owe her anything. Take care of yourself so you can save your energy and life for someone who appreciates you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, we're here to help, whenever you need it. I hope you feel better soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:36:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> None of us are born with rational thoughts, we have emotions and desires getting in the way. Some of us just get depression to add to it. 

I know those thoughts, honestly I do. Don't listen to them. It won't make things better, its just a flaw in our biology that we sometimes think that way. 

I'm sorry if none of this is making you feel any better. We all know what it's like to have people tell us to stay strong or something when we're down. I don't blame you if you don't wanna read any of this, but if there's one thing you should listen to out of any of our comments, its that you shouldn't go through with your plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 04:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thoughts going through your head about this aren't thoughts you should listen to. Depression sucks, it makes you want to die, and you'll think of ways to justify that, but it can't be justified because there's no logic or reason behind them. 

Don't listen to those thoughts, they aren't worth it. Who cares if you moved back home? We all hit a shitstorm at least a couple times in our lives, it's nothing to be ashamed about. 

If your deoression isn't getting better, you need to talk to someone about it, your doctor or a counselor, and if you've told your friends explicitly and they still don't understand, then either sit them down and make it clear or find people that do care. 

You are worth being alive, you aren't a failure and you are good enough for a career and a relationship. Sure there's a couple things you need to fix but we're all a little screwed up. Nothing wrong with being human. Don't give up, not because you owe it to anyone, but because these thoughts aren't yours, the "decision" to kill yourself isn't yours. It isn't worth all the pain it will cause, and it isn't going to make anything better for you or anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 14:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you don't take care of yourself too, you won't be able to help them for too long. They won't mind either, they would prefer you take care of yourself more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 00:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya my friends don't know alot about my depression, just that I have it. If you really aren't doing well, you might wanna tell them though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-13 22:21:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I understand what you mean. I can't imagine life without depression, I'm just so used to it that sometimes I wanna make myself as depressed as I used to be. It makes no sense but I don't want it to leave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-10 23:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand. People who don't have any sort of personal experience with it sometimes have a hard time understanding it. There are people everywhere with depression though, dont worry, you aren't alone irl. It can be hard to find friends who have dealt with it too, because alot of people who go through it are sort of less sociable, or try to put on a brave face for every one to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-10 23:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem! You never alone as long as you have reddit lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-10 23:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Always been every month for me. I think you can change it in the settings on the opening screen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-10 23:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didn't you play the battlefront games? They turn frickin invisible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-10 23:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Studies usually helped me take my mind of things which almost nothing else does in my daily life. It was easier for me to focus on things I understood and could learn more about than the things that made me sad, so ya it helped me. Hope it helps you too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 01:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to school for chemistry, and right now, it's one of my only priorities. I've always liked science, but going to school to be a scientist is different than just thinking about being a scientist. I can see myself improving in the field, and I've started working at a research lab on campus. It's wicked exciting. 

Alot of what you said sounds like something I would say, especially about family, I feel like a shitty son. Once you find something you love to do, something that makes you want to get up every morning, you will put yourself into it like you've never thought you could. Keep trying to find your purpose dude, and don't let people like your landlady keep you down. Screw psychopaths and sociopaths.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-06 19:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry. I know it's hard. There's no good reason for pain to be in our lives, but it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-06 18:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I ask what you can't bear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 23:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry. I can't imagine what its like to lose a home like that or have your family in danger like that. I don't know what kind of person just gets up and leaves like that, too. He's scum if he can't help you and your family in a hard time. 

All I can really say is, things could have gone much worse, and they didn't. Not that they went well either. If you can take it day by day and you and your family can move past this, you'll all be stronger for it. 

Sorry if this wasn't any help or if it made you feel worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 20:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 19:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn, that's tough. Portugal's stolen so much land that I wanted to colonize in just about every game, they're real dicks lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 19:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We all get down sometimes, just gotta pick ourselves back up. You sound like you're not doing that bad though, living in New york isn't easy after all. I mean, debt isn't fun at all, obviously, but most people have debt I think. You can get through this, don't worry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 19:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did the Portuguese really steal the East coast from you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 08:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you kill yourself, what are you going to put your friends and family through? Especially if you do it while you're hanging out with them, they'll blame themselves. If you die tomorrow, you'll be gone, but they will have to live with it. There's a good chance they'll get depressed, too.

I know what its like to want to kill yourself. It sucks. This world sucks. But is it really worth devastating your friends? I promise you people care more than you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 19:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course you deserve help, you didn't choose to be depressed or anxious. I guess I don't really have to tell you not to kill yourself because it would be hell to your family and friends, since you already said that, but it's still true. All I can really say is that those thoughts aren't worth listening to. The world isn't going to get better if you leave, and you won't be happier if you die, you'll just be gone. 

I don't know how to fix depression or anxiety, but I do know suicidal thoughts aren't logical thoughts, they have no reason behind them, they just sorta pop into existance if you have depression. Your friends and family are real, they're a logical reason to not commit suicide. I understand if this wasn't very helpful, but I hope you feel better soon.

By the way, I wouldn't really worry about not being productive too much, honestly our whole species is barely productive at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 18:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't worry, we all feel like this at least sometimes. I understand what you mean exactly, life just seems tedious at some point, like there isn't a reason to keep going but we just do, cuz its easiest to just go with the flow. Or maybe it's different for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 11:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it would be a good idea to talk to your doctor about this. There's nothing wrong with you, but if you think you should get help, don't hesitate to talk to someone. Take care of yourself buddy, sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 09:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry to hear that. If your medicine isn't helping that much, you should let your doctor know. I don't really have a lot of advice, don't have all this figured out for myself, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-17 19:57:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think doctors say depression is sadness that lasts for more than 6 months. I've heard that it can be genetic or caused by an event. Probably more causes too. Sounds like you came to the right place. Sorry buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-17 19:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. Sorry you feel like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-09 19:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get what you're saying, no reason to make good console and pc games if a company makes way more money marketing to the average person on mobile platforms and with microtransactions. The only thing i think we can do is support good game development and try to boycott assy games. Still, who knows where games will go in the future, could be totally different than what I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 01:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this all the time, I'm just mad jealous of other people having fun. I'm a freshamn in college and didn't got to prom, honestly I don't regret it at all, would've been a waste of a night (I probably wasted that night anyway, but whatever I did I was happier than at a dance) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-31 22:06:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crushes come and go, it's not the end if the world if your crush is taken. I wouldn't try to "win her over" though, people usually don't take it well when someone comes on to someone else in a relationship. Still, it's not like you can't be friends with her or anything, I mean, if they break up on their own, it's not a big deal to try then. Just be respectful of others and their circumstances, and put yourself out there whenever you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-22 14:56:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This definitely sounds like something to talk to a counselor or therapist about. I'm sorry you feel this way. Me and alot of people I know think like this, and none of us consider the others to be attention seeking or self pittying. It's a complicated thing that happens to peoples' heads from time to time, where we just lose all hope and meaning in the world. Its something we need to try to get past, but its not somethimg we made happen to ourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 00:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Murder a person in game. You won't regret it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 00:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have the same tech level? It can make a big difference. Also, their naval tradition is usually through the roof, and the Ottomans are usually a more army focused nation. I think their traditions make an impact and I know they go after naval ideas all the time. Ive seen people play as Britain and take out huge fleets with fewer ships on their side. I think Britains navy is usually just OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 00:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmao, Putin has conqueror maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 04:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's great! I'm glad to hear you doing better and that you got the photographer you liked!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 04:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, I hope I didn't upset you or anything. All I meant was that we usually misunderstand our situations. We're all just human after all. But I understand if you don't want to hear that rn. Just so you know though, there are others who feel what you feel. You aren't alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 03:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, the only person who would try to figure out if i died would be my mom. Don't worry about how many people know you, I'm just drawing off of my experience here, but not too many people know me either. I have a few good friends that care about me, and I care about them, even if we don't talk every day. I'm sorry you feel that way, i know I've been there too, it sucks, it really does. Don't give up though. With 7 billion people on the planet, at least some of them enjoy your company, I'm sure of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 03:10:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry. Having a lived one pass away must feel so horrible. Especially one you were so close to. Just remember all the happy times, dont let go of them. I wish you the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 03:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you were nothing, you would take up no space, id you were nobody, you wouldn't have any thoughts. Feeling like empty space is horrible, being isolated from peopld sucks. You're a person, just like all of us, don't forget that. No matter what, you matter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 02:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad you're seeing a therapist. It's good to talk about these things, we're a social species, after all and keeping all your thoughts in your head usually isn't good. My friend has started saying she's feeling numb, she's going through alot rn, and it kills me to hear it, but I'm still there for her. I think it might be a good idea to talk to your vest friends aboit this, i mean, if you "seem sad" and they still like being around you, they must care about you. I hope all goes well, good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 00:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry! Being ridiculed hurts alot, especially when the people you see the most do it. I'm sure there are caring people close by, it might be a little difficult to find them, but they're there. Screw those dicks that don't care about your feelings. Be yourself, read whatever you want to, they have no right to tell you what to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 05:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know its hard, but you don't feel guilty for being you. Feeling guilt at all already makes you better than plenty of people. It sucks though, always feeling ashamed and undeserving. Cut yourself some slack every now and again, you deserve it, even if you don't think you do. Hope your party goes well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 04:49:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Antidepressants are definitely one of the most annoying medicines out there, but medical research has shown they can help. I hope you feel better soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 04:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think alcohol might be the biggest problem right now for you. It's incredibly addictive, and it's medically considered a depressant, it reduces what your nerves can do while you have it in your system (that includes your brain's neurons). You should also maybe find another psychologist to see if the one you have right now isn't enough for you. I'm glad you're still able to not be a shitbag and cheat on your girlfriend though, thats definitely a plus to your charecter, alot of people would do whatever they want and not care about how it affects others close to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 05:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the clone wars cartoon, the older one, he gets his chest crushed by Mace Windu with the force, like 3 min before episode 3 starts. But then he has the cough in the new clone wars, so who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-30 17:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hate when people do that. Like don't ask if you don't care, you're not helping anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-30 04:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't do that. You're not a burden. Some people won't understand how it feels, but maybe he will underatand? Don't let a fight with your boyfriend decide your future, or lack of it. Trust me. Give it some time, you'll feel better again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-29 19:11:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, I wish I could just make everything better. If I was better woth words maybe I could. Give this another shot maybe? Get out there and show the world that you're here and that you mean something. Giving up has never made things better. We've all felt like we should, it just hits some of us harder than others sometimes. Again, I'm sorry I'm not better with words. Just give it another try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-29 18:51:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand. I'm sorry I don't have alot of helpful things to say, still trying to figure things out for myself too. Just don't give up please. You deserve to be happy. I'm younger than you, so maybe I have a more naive way of thinking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-29 18:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, I didn't mean to make you unhappy. If there's something up with your memory or attention span, talk to your doctor about it? You might not be sleeping well or something. How old are you? Most people have no intellect honestly, don't worry about that, it was just the first thing that came to my mind. Alot of people I know and alot of people I know of say they aren't good at anything, so that isn't abnormal. Don't worry about how good other people's lives are, there's always someone who's happier or better off, no matter how much they don't deserve it. I'm not trying to tell you how to live, I just mean that there are alot of people who have gone through what you are, and who feel the way you do. Your problems won't go away over night, and sonetines they feel unbearable, but don't give up hope. Things will get better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-29 18:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bullies are assholes. They have no good reason to act the way they do. I'm not gonna tell to just let it roll off your shoulders, I'm sure you've heard that a thousand times, and it definitely isn't easy. What they think doesn't matter, though, because, honestly, they don't end up with happy lives most if the time. They surround thenselves eith other assholes and they become less and less important to everyone else over time. 
Also, you don't have to loce yourself right away. Healing takes time and effort. Take it day by day, find people who aren't assholes to talk to, build up your abilities, like get great at math, or science, or anything that will help you. You don't beed to be perfect, because no one is. Just cut yourself some slack from time to time, and remember, you are as deserving of happiness as everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 17:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're aren't shit. You're a person going through a tough time. Don't lose hope, this will pass. Believe in yourself. You can get through this. You don't have to be perfect, that's impossible. Just try to be happy with who you are and don't blame yourself for this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 00:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem dude. Anytime you need to talk, we're here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 23:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  WOO WAY TO GO!! Wish you lot's of joy and good luck!!! Thanks for sharing, I'm sure this is gomna help alot of us :) (sorry, i feel like this sounds sarcastic, but its not, im really happy for you and happy you posted this) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 23:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm doing good. Thanks. It feels good to talk about it, especially to someone who gets it. Try not to let it stress you out too much. I mean, we can't possibly be making EVERY decision wrong, right? We gotta be doing some good, even if it's just chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 23:29:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. Just feels like whatever I try to do, someone else could've done it better, or it's just not the right thing to do. Like there's no point in me trying, cu whatever i want to happen won't. Hope you feel better soon though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 06:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't put any more time into someone like that. Doesn't matter how long you've been with her if she doesn't care about you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 06:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry. I don't know what made you say this, but alot of us have been in this place. It sucks so bad and it feels pointless to even try. It can get better though. Sometimes it takes alot of work. This feeling doesn't last.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 06:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mistakes happen, don't beat yourself up about it (I know you don't control all of your emotions, but still). Every human makes mistakes, it's in our nature.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 20:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem!! Good luck!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 20:40:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think so, but I live in the US, so we might have some diff things in health care. You might be able to ask to get e-mails only though? I hope it goes well for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 18:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your doctor should have suggestions on where to go and what to do and have to keep it a secret if you ask them. How old are you? I'm not 100% sure if young kids get doctor patient confidentiality, but as a teenager or older you should be all set. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 17:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know that artillery van engage from the vack row, so having a full bavk line of artillery is optimal. Cavalry's advantage gets smaller and smaller as the game progresses, so I know there is less need for them, but I don't think they're ever completely useless. There isn't much point in putting in too much cav tho, because it gets harder for them to take on infantry on their own, and sinse they're always on the flanks, having too many units will force your farthest cav units to only recieve support from other cav units and artillery, which isnt good, because combat switches from shock to fire over and over again, and cavalry have horrible fire compared to infantry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 17:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate taking my pills. It's so annoying to take it every day just so I feel the same. But scientific research is trustworthy, and it says antidepressants can work. It might take a few different tries, it might only imporve your mood slightly, or it might only make you slightly more stable. But the evidence is clear, it does help. Wish you the best, stay safe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 17:25:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry for your spouse and you, that sucks. The chance of something like that is small, but it does happen. Don't worry too much about it happening to your parents, its still unlikely, even if it happened to someone you know. It might've just hit you really hard, when people have to face their or a loved one's mortality, we usually freak out for a little while. I think you should just try to enjoy the time you have with the people you love, if you worry all the time theres no time left to be happy with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 17:12:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmao, same here. It makes no sense, and it gets in the way of the plans i make.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 17:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer spain because they get a PU over Aragon and Naples, and sometimes even get Burgundy's inheritance. Just makes it easier to take on France, England, and the Ottomans as them than as Portugal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 05:03:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Took the words right outta my mouth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 20:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It gets pretty dumb when you use it for a whole conversation, can never tell when someones being sarcastic or joking or if ehat im saying is coming off wrong, and if someones mad and you dont realize... better to just say quick things, like times and places and yes and no stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 20:07:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's pretty annoying when you give someone an answer and they decide that you need to say more even though your answer is good enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 16:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw a scientific research paper that concluded that it might ease some people, but it was just one paper, so its results aren't supposed to be taken as fact. I have heard some people say its because they feel like its something they can control, and some people say other things too. I did a few times, not too deep, but it felt kinda good. No idea why, honestly, just remeber, if you do it again, not that I'm condoning it, but if you do, sterilize the blade with a lighter and clean the cut right after. Put a bandaid in too. Don't put yourself in danger please, keep it under control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 20:53:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here, being not depressed just feels a little weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 17:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!! You too!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 15:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if this world is unfair, we have to make of it what we can. Humans came frim tribal life life, which is beyond brutal. Insects live in a world where old age is rarely a cause of death, usually you get eaten alive. We have the chance to make something out of our world, because as unfair and cruel as it can be, it's better than veing any other animal. Except tardigrades, nothing can even kill those guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 13:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't give up. Dealing with depression is hard. But you can get through it. You dont have to do every last bit of your schoolwork, but do what you can. And talk to your doctor about this if you haven't. You can talk to them in private. As for friends, if you haven't already, join a club or something. Don't give up, and good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 03:15:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, obviously you dont need to talk all the time or to everyone, but humans are a social species. But no rush, take your time to build up your courage. 
And i agree, great game series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-22 18:55:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry. Depression isn't taken seriously by alot of people. If you have friends that deal with something similar, i would go to them. Especially go to your doctor, they should be able to help too. A counsellor or therapist might be good too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-22 18:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know what you mean. Sometimes it just feels useless to even talk at all. Like no one is even paying attention to what you're saying, especially in a group. It feels really annoying. I hope you can conquer this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-22 18:15:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend told me I have selective mutism. It's when you stoo talking in certain situations. I still talk to some people and in some situations, so maybe this isnt helpful to you? From what I've read, it's nor uncommon, it's not your choice, and it doesn't mean anything, like it doesn't mean someone's stupid just because they don't talk alot. I hope this helped at least a little </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-22 18:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a great friend in a terrible situation. I mean it could be worse, but she deserves so much better. I haven't been able to help her much, but she tells me that she's glad I'm always there for her. I guess one of the best things you can do for someone is be there for them and listen to their problems and not judge them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-22 18:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please don't do anything extreme. Drinking and driving can hurt alot of people besides yourself, and can leave you handicapped, which won't help anything at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-18 20:52:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You aren't the problem. Some of us just don't understand others as well. Especially emotions, those make no sense. Honestly, the only advice I have is to be more outgoing and trusting. I know that probably sounds like something everyobe says, but logically, you can't make an emotional connection if you're alreafy expecting it to go wrong. It's hard to change the way we think, but it is possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-18 20:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry. My friend's step dad just got cancer too. They said theres hooe for him, and I hope there is for you too. I wish I could help. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-14 18:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's terrible! Dont worry about "ruining his life," hes honestly probably a psychopath or something. I think you should go to the police if you havent already, and maybe get some friends to walk around with you on campus, or anywhere you might see him. If you ever cant have a friend with you, i think theres some kind of in campus this you should be able to go to? Maybe theyll let some campus police walk close by, to make sure he doesnt do anything. Best of luck, please stay safe, and take care of yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-13 20:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a freshman in college, and i think i know what you mean. Im majoring in chemistry, and its pretty hard. Alotta of people have switch out of the major in just the first semester, but it doesnt seem like a big deal, actually. Not that you should be too laid back about this, just that its unrealistic to know exactly what you want to do for a living by 18. Some of my friends work full time jobs, some are going to college. Theyre all doing pretty ok at least, so as far as i can tell, you only need to be thinking about where you might want to be in the future, and taking steps to start getting out there. Don't stress it too much, but don't take it lightly either, if that makes any sense. Hope this helped  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 23:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry. Feelimg tired all the time sucks, especially when you cant figure out how to stop it. I hope you feel better soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 23:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 22:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time I've talked to a therapist or counselor, I've been anxious about what to say becasue i was afraid of them being dissapointed. I think this is just an anxiety thing though, I dont think they actually judge their patients. Talking about whats on your mind is good, and I hope it does help you alot. One thing I know is that staying in bed only makes you feel less bad, it doesn't make you feel better because it doesn't solve anything you miggt be dealing with. I hope you feel better soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 22:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't do it every night before bed, and I don't pray to a god, but I constantly just want to not have to live anymore. I think this is common in depressed people, but not in others. I'm sorry that you've felt that way for so long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 22:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so sorry. I can't believe nobody answered you, i just read your last post. That sucks, bad. I live in MA where people mostly dont care about weed, and it did help for a while, but I get paranoid all the time now. I know that church isnt going to help, unless you'd want to become a priest or nun, or something, which isn't the life most people want. Your case sounds more complicated than mine, so I might not be much help. If therapists and counselors haven't helped, honestly Im not sure what else to do. I'm sorry. The only thing I can think is to find friends who you love and love you back. I got lucky, but it isnt easy for everyone. It takes alot, and you have to find people who won't take advantage of you and will give back what you give to them. Im sorry if this isnt helpful. I hioe you feel better soon. Sorry about the whole weed thing too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 22:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I know how you feel, at least in some ways. I'm sorry, it sucks. I promise you though, people aren't avoiding you. People think about themselves alot that way, that others "have to notice what I notice about myself" but most people don't. I'm not sure how to make new friends, but having good, reliable, caring friends helps alot with anxiety. I'm sorry if this wasnt very helpful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 17:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I'm alright, though, at least for the time being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 17:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem, we're all here for each other. I hope you feel better soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 17:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trebuchets use a counterweight I think. At least the European kind. So instead of a force of tension, which makes a catapult work, there is another object on the other side of the Trebuchet's arm which uses gravity to fling a 30kg projectile over 300m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 17:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you haven't done anything dangerous, it doesn't stop the feelimg in the end. I'm sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 15:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend in a similar situation, though not as extreme, and she's more than capable of taking care of herself. Don't doubt yourself just because there are peoole who doubt you. You deserve a happy life, despite how some people act to you. If you can help yourself, please do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 13:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so sorry. I'm not sure what I can say to help you, but my heart goes out to you, truly. This is a horrible way for family to act. I'd suggest finding a way to leave that house, but I'm sure you already have thought about that. I am sorry, you deserve better. I'm sure you're beautiful, no matter what your mother says </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-10 18:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been through something like this alot, and I know others who have too. I'm not a psychologist, but I think it's sort of an ebb and flow thing, sometimes life is ok, and sometimes it isn't. I'm sorry you're feeling bad, but the Earth is still spinning, you're still breathing, and we all still care about each other here. You aren't alone, don't forget that. Have a wonderful day, i hope ypu feel better soon :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-31 20:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How hard is it to just make a 1, b 2, c 3, and d 4?? Like for me it takes more energy and thought to out them out of that order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-30 17:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's rough, sorry to hear that. I know I've had that feeling too. Things just stop being fun, everythings just a chore. For me, its more of an on and off thing. I hope you don't lose hope. I don't have any advice, but you're not alone. I hope that helps you a little bit at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-28 21:21:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem, friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-28 21:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry you feel that way. I've dealt with depression since muddle school, and I've felt alot of things since. Sone days it's not too bad, others, it just sucks. Life can feel hopeless or pointless, but I think you should keep going. If you have a doctor, it might be a good idea to talk to them in private about this. Depression is a really complicated issue, many people deal with it, and there isn't a perfect answer yet. But they can help at least. Plus, with the recommendation of a doctor, your parents might be more sympathetic to what you're feeling. I don't suggest going to teachers because, at least in the US, they can't really do much and sometimes, legal protocol just makes the situation more complicated. Again, I hope you keep going and don't try to hurt yourself or anything, but don't feel guilty gor what you're feeling. This sub is also a good place for talking if you're feeling really down. GOOD LUCK!! I mean it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-27 22:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Conquer the galaxy in stellaris </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-26 07:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This honestly feels so relatable to me. It feels so shitty sometimes. Hope you feel better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-25 22:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I listen to Shawn Mendes alot, kinda got a big crush on him though. His new song "In My Blood" is pretty good to cry to though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-23 16:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you need someone to talk to, I'm all ears. I'm not very busy lately, except for classes in the morning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-23 16:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry. I've been growing apart from some of my friends too, it feels really bad. I hope you have people you can count on. I'm sorry I don't have alot to say, not so good with words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-13 04:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm honestly so happy to hear that :) I don't know you, but as far as I'm concerned, you deserve to be happy amd safe :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>