<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2961</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 12:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmmm. I read about this but i didnt read all. I just thought it was to make it into liquid form.
But ill check it out again and if it doesnt seem too hard ill try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 12:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i think thats a good idea because i dont want to get nausea or vomit.  example if i smoke weed my perfect amount is one normal joint And two full bowls from bong, and i turn a bit pale and feel super fucking amazing, chill, the world spins but no nausea or any bad feeling at all. But if i take even one more hit from bong, i feel the same effects but get really bad nausea and feel like vomiting.

So yeah thanks for that! I first take 4 or 5 pills, wait an hour and if not feeling too much of anything ill take the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:21:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah im not an regular basics drug guy. I have anxiety and im searching for the right drug with my doctor or trying different drugs( havent found the right yet). 

So i usually never take any drugs and for this i dont have anymore or i dont have an place where  could get my hands on these or i might have mut have no intentions to try to find more. Also im getting better so im just taking something just rarely to help with the hardest days. And yeah as i just said in the different comment i get some iron in my system pretty often (which helps liver functionality).

Thank you for the warnings tho. I appreciate that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:17:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats an amazing question!
Id also like to know.

I know some things but im not 100% sure if they are real facts so i wount say them ( also because im new to spirituality and have watched just few maybe 20-50 videos about different things and subjects of spirituality, also reading few books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also i eat a lot of foods that contain iron and sometimes i take fe+ pills(that have iron yes. I dont need to take them but they are good for you).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 11:05:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright! Yeah i just checked,  it contains paracetamol. 

But i still think that im just gonna take the 7 pills. 
I just want to feel super chill because im having too much stress atm( even that i dont have anything to stress about. I just have bad anxiety ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok thank you!
I will take them in abou 7-9hour(then the time here will be about 9pm and i will update the effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So the good thing i dont have too many connections so i dont get drugs too easily and these pills were prescripted to my father but he dont need them anymore and said if i have bad headache or something like that i can take one(i told you this because i didnt go and get the pills and have no idea where i could get more so there is no chance that i would use any more of these).

But Alright. Thank you so much for the information and i will check that site out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:27:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok! And actually i have no school tomorrow so thats cool. Whats the max amount that is kinda risk free . Im some what buff, i weight about 95kg (im 19y old male)? I also think there is four more pills in the medicen cabinet.

 I tried to find info from internet but found just a little. So it lasts abou 3-4h. What are the effects? What if i take few shots of alcohol with it.
Im interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> About codeine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 10:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So i got these pills called panacod. 
They contain 30mg of codeine each.
I have 7 of them so thats 237mg of codeine.
Should i go all in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 00:30:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually im reading a book related to that so if youd like to give it a read you can give me your email here or send me an message so i can send it to you. 

Its not that long its only 116 pages.
I have read about 60pages and already helped me because im also in progress of not judging people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 00:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah they do but i can put the feeling/pain away. Then it just feels like you are kinda floating and helps the idea so i start to feel like floating but i usually meditate for an hour so at some point usually i get so deep that i dont feel any part of my body almost at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Felt something new again! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 22:09:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While im meditating first i got the basic feelings of calmness and lightness. Also for some time i felt really cold. Then i started to feel pressure on my forehead (about where the forhead starts and right in the middle, kinda between my eyebrows), it was like some one would push my forehead with a finger, but little bit different. Its interesting that i have gotten the exact same feeling ones in a while. I just realized that! Like three times a year, some times more. I have no idea what isit. 

I remember the first time when i was yonger maybe 12(now im 19). I was sitting on a floor and i felt the same feeling and out of no where i got an idea to close my eyes and closely bring my finger closer to my forehead and i felt the pressure rising. I did it few times and every time when the finger were closer the pressure started rising. I dont feel it always, i notice it sometimes when i just start to feel the pressure on that certain point. Also i remember this because i think meditation has made me remember stuff easier. I love that i found meditation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 21:53:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 18:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt the same untill i shouted SHUT THE FUCK UP to myself and stopped judging my self (i read a book that had really good points about why we are depressed or anxiety etc..).

Also i started meditating and take some drugs ones in a while. Starting to feel a lot better.
Also i told a doctor about my situation a month ago (i have had depression and anxiety for 5 years) and we are trying to figure out a drug for me. Telling to some one really helped to get started on chanching myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 18:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you dont judge yourself and if someone would judge you, you woudnt care shit.
The problem is that we are too harash to our selves and too easily influenced by others.

But to the point umm if it were for me(i have bad social anxiety but getting better every day!), i would drink some water and take few pills(any pills that helps you relax) or if no pills i would make my self just a little drunk and remember to take deep breaths before and sometimes during the presentation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 17:56:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We can switch places?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 17:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes thats great! Its good to push yourself ones in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 17:25:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all OMG thats amazing that people of your age is here :o no mean to judge or anything ;_; its just cool! (Maybe because my mom is almost the same age, a bit older).

To the point im 19M and no, my anxiety is the same strength who ever (random person) im talking to. But the worst is if im in a crowded place i always feel like dying. 
But im starting to get better. 
I started to meditate and im in progress of totally quitting to judge people. And also reading shit ton of self improvement and knowledge books.
Also i take drugs sometimes, but very rarely because i dont have big social circle(small but i know everyone as good as they know themselves). Usually weed and im trying to find the right medicen for me with my doctor(i laso have depression). But yeah im kinda starting to feel better.

I hope youll get better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 17:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am the same... it sucks having this mask because of social anxiety.. only my best friends, gf and family knows who i really am but heyh they are the most important. 

Still it would ve nice if i could be me all the time.
Just someday.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 16:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unmotivated, lazy, over emotional, feeling like shit, i over eat or eat too little, nothing is enjoyable or interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 13:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will look it up thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 11:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 10:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a bit high on tramadol. Took 200mg last night.
Im thinking what books to read next(knowledge and self improvement). Because i have a way to get most of the ebooks free(a place in dark web). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 09:58:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me i dont like small talk because i dont see the point of it... im more interested of peoples stories and REAL feelings and emotions. 

But to the point i read a lot of knowledge books   self improvement and research stuff on my own. 
I have always stuff in my mind id love to share and talk about but the thing is usually average people dont care about these things or dont have enough knowledge to even try to understand.

I also dont like to judge people too much and im trying to stop judging totally so i usually keep my mouth shut in some sitsuations.

Also im diagnosed with anxiety and depression so it makes talking a bit harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 09:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to get stressed about EVERY SINGLE FUCKING THING.... i still have diagnosed anxiety and depression. So for me personally; drugs and meditation have helped A LOT. Also its always have someone to talk to, to let it all out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 09:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the awesome info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 09:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gooood job man!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 08:36:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh damn! No i have never tried lsd :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for that! 
I think i might try it the next time i get my hands on cough syrup(with dmx ofcource). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i have done that two times(alcohol and tramadol).
 I usually just pop the pills and thats it. But sometimes i just would love to get fucked up but never gotten really... im going to try shrooms some time soon or i asked my friend if he could get me some.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:31:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im interested to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a painkiller like for example if you have painful nerve pains it helps etc. But yeah it makes the tasks i usually find boring, really interesting. Only down side is if i take too many, i will get an really bad headache. But my usual dose is 100mg and i have never gotten headache from that. 
Its also addictive because it makes you feel so good. 

In the long run with continius use i think its not good for you it might do some damage to some organs or something. Not sure tho i havent researched it too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 01:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well im not 100% sure how it will affect you but for me it usually takes 30min to kick in and i feel super euphoric and motivated for about 8hours and every thing i do seems interesting and also im usually shy and i have social anxiety but under effect of tramadol im so talkstive and i feel like i never even had anxiety.

Its really good drug for me personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i would love to try LSD, shrooms and some other psychedelics. Im very interested to try psychedelics because i love to meditate and i want to make it more powerful experience.

I just dont have too many places where i could buy any... but my friend said that he could hook me up with shrooms soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:41:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just wanted to try if it has any different effect but not really. 

Thank you for the info tho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I love drugs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 23:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took 2 pills of 50mg tramadols normally and drank half bottle of wine and snorted 100mg of tramadol. I feel pertty good and fucked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 21:57:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg thats so amazing!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 08:43:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright!

Hopefully youll get out of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-06 08:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 22:11:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes sir thats correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 22:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah the thing is you cant be nice all the time sometimes you need to be more alpha. Because we all know there are a lot of bad people out there. They are the reason why some ones question so much why thei should be nice when every one else is a dickhead. But the thing is being nice is hard but usually rewarding(for me personally). 

Im kinda good at social skills and words but i have anxiety so its hard. But thats true that some might thing that if you are too nice its turning into weird. Try not to care they dont deserve your positive being. 

Take care! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 21:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah everybodey should have someone that helps you to get through the hardest times.. 
Im so sorry that your sitsuation is not that good ;_;

I wish i could help you. But im sure that we live no where near... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 21:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the fuck... real friends should be more than happy to help you.. thats weird man. My friends always try to help me as best as they can... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 21:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i have told my friends alos that i was getting better and few days after that i was feeling super down.. but for so long i told myself that im getting better and it actually worked! Also i started doing meditation and learn avout buddhish things. Now i feel even better! I have had depression and social anxiety and i was diagnosed fot having those.

But yeah im getting better every day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 21:21:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg i feel absolutely same! Glad to have people like you aroud here. People now days are so disrespectful and judge everyone. We need more positivity to the whole world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 21:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tomorrow when i meditate i try to send energy to you. So if you feel any weird energy rushes i hope its mine. Im pretty new to this stuff but ill try my best!

I wish the best for you!!
Stay strong brother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 21:04:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah im socially anxous so for excample i always avoided presentations etc.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 21:03:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my friends are the ones who are mad because im usually alone. I just appreciate alone time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah you are correct. My apologies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah true but i dont smoke always. So i can afford it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont stop being nice. You need to be able to stand your ground and say no. But never stop being a nice person.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:30:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah and the wors part was that my face turned super red and when that happended i felt that i wanted to die on that spot. But yeah meditation,  drugs and friends have helped me alot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually when im in gocery store and if i get stuck into a long line i get very anxous and feel like wanting to just drop my items and leave.
But its getting better haven felt that in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow thats very interesting!
I think i need to research more about nootropics my self because i have my own problems and id like to make them less alive. 

Im glad that the interview went well^-^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:14:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i have read some articles, and thats about the way how its usually done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just gotta say i feel so much love and passion in people who help and even if dont have straight answers, still tend to come up with something. You are the heroes of society!

Take care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 19:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so sorry that you had to get heartbroken by a peace of shit. Some people doesnt understand how much they can hurt people Or they know but  then they are so low level as a human. 

I would love to help in you in person but i cant ;_;

Regretting past events is a bad thing i know its hard but you need to let go of that. It helped me personally and i woudnt be alive if i didnt learn to let go of my regrets.

The best way would be to have some one to help you to go through your hard times and guide you.
But we arent living in a movie right..... 
this is one of the reasons why im depressed.. because i think too much about why the fuck there are so many rotten and fucked up people.
This is why i have hate against humanity. 

You can do it by your self as you have gotten so far(im 19 and im struggling a bit). You are strong! Some people would have quit already but you had the strength to keep going. Actually when i read your story i got inspired by you!. You have gone through a lot of bad stuff and you still are there alive. I think you are strong enough to keep going and usually good things happen to good people but sometimes it will take time. Sometimes life tests us so fucking hard but we cant give up. Fight for your happiness untill you can live in peace. 

You inspire me! 
Have faith you can do this , i believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 18:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you told anyone about your situation? ;_; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do you do this? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 18:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So when i meditate i take really deep breaths after about 5-10minutes into meditating. Usually it takes me really deep and makes me feel like i dont have a body or makes me feel really relaxed. 

Do you do this or do you just keep breathing at the same pace?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 18:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant say much i have had depression and  anxiety for 5 years and i didnt tell anyone. Nowdays i meditate and recently told my doctor about this and i got diagnosed with social anxiety and depression. We are trying to figure out an drug for me. Havent found yet.  Sometimes i take tramadol which helps alot. But yeah i dont have much experience from meds/drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 18:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His message is important and hopefully will affect the future teens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 17:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> today i had really bad headache or more like hangover from antidepressant drugs( i took too many). I meditated for an hour and the pain went away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 17:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Today i first meditated for 30min and about 10minutes ago i just finished meditating for an hour. The time flies by so fast when i meditate. I had two candles  lit up and i also had meditation music from my phone and its interesting the candles were new (they were really small candles) and in the end when i came back to my body and opened my eyes there were only one candle burning and had almost half left and the other was burnt out. 

Also i live with my parents, sometimes they make loud noises and today they did and i was kinda distracted. I heard what they said but i didnt listen or i didnt even think what they were saying. My mind was empty the whole time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 15:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes i noticed this. I usually strech and breath deeply before i start.

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 15:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im anxous when my gf sends texts with someone using different kind of chat apps. And im anxous because she has cheated on me twice by sending nudes and talking like they were together...
The next time she does something like that ill dump her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If possible try not to get too excited when dreaming. So if you are lucid dreaming just kee yourself chill and you dont wake up in middle of the dream. Getting  too excited forces you to wake up!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 14:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright! I meditate everyday usually 30-60min and its making me be more aware of my self and what i really feel. So my next goal is that ill try to get ti the root if why i smoke. And thanks ill keep that motto in my mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 13:40:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also i don think im addicted, i dont get side effects if i dont smoke. It just helps me to relax.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 13:34:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok thanks for the info! Im very new to this so thats why i asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 13:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need advice! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 13:12:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to smoke cigarettes sometimes.
Does it make me a bad person?
Does it affect my spiritual being?
I think it does not but id like to know what you you think about this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 13:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is really interesting actually. I sometimes myself have thought that if dreaming is anither reality or something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 12:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its really good to hear that you have awesome friends! And yeah if i have something in my mind that i cant get around on my own ill PM you!

Thanks for listening me as well, I feel better 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love to hug you irl ;_; 

*hugs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah its a struggle :D 

Oh jesus you were crazy . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I take usually 100mg of tramadol at eavning so i still feel it the next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 11:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah buddhism is really interests me because i have problems figiring out who i am and what i really want to do. I think that when i learn more about buddhism i start to see things differently and with meditation i can release my stress and worries away. 

I love to hear what you have to say! And YESS its really relaxing to get your feelings out of your body. I usually dont speak too much about my feelings and emotions so they build up insinde of me. And sometimes i just blew up (usually to my gf) and this is why i need to learn to be more open so i can talk about my emotions and feelings.

Here in reddit its really great to let go of the build up feelings and emotions because people usually listen and some might give answers. Reddit has helped me alot with many things.

Im glad that this makes you feel better!
I love to be helpful because i know what being down is like( where im still at). It fucking sucks.

Take care man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 07:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Living with parents :d  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 07:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friends love me too much almost.. they get mad if they dont see me enough. When i was feeling super anxous and wanted to be alone( i have this feeling pretty often) they send me an essey long text of  it feels like i dont care anout them anymore   but its not that i love my friends but i need alone time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 06:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But the thing is, im still diagnosed with anxiety and depression but the name reminds me of the hardest times i have gotten trough and didnt give up on life. It reminds me of who ive become.
It reminds me who i am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 06:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Message me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 06:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im glad that it comforts you! 
And same for me i never was shy or anxous, i was the exact opposite and full of energy and then at 7 grade something changed and i started to feel socially anxous and depressed and felt it ever since. Im 19 now, so ive been dealing with them five years.

Whaaat i have the exact same feeling about meditation  meditation is the start of something beautiful because it has already helped me to feel better! And the cultures around meditation, they are very interesting to me. Even tho i never religion stuff but now its starting to interest me a bit. Maybe because i have gained a lot of knowledge and im more open minded. 
Life is starting to feel some what good after these horrible years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 06:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nono i have never tried phenibut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah same for me and because im socially anxious its horrible if i notice that some girl is trying sneakily take a picture of me.. i usually turn red </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:34:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ask that question every time and it keeps me alive because my life goal is to find an answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great! It feels so good to hear that people sre getting better! Much love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:29:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i had that same problem but then i got to the point where i wanted to do the things right away so i dont need to do them later. I just did it.
Nothing special i just started doing them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recommend meditating!
It has changed me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why? Reddit is an amazing app/site and you can learn so much here.

But i kinda see your point its 3.23am here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i was thinking about deleting instagram(nit snapchat because so many of my friends are there and plugs) and using only snap, reddit and pinterest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:21:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think some meditating books, at the moment im reading the mind illuminated   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 02:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good job! I highly recommend its an amazing cure for higly stressful days(every day for me) and even just to feel better about everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:55:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good job i have drivers livense too but i havent done the phase 2, 3. And i dont like my teacher and im fucking anxious and i started thinking that maybe i sont even want to drive anymore. Public transportation is just fine for me and i sometimes enjoy ti be in a bus but not too often because of my anxiety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the same feeling plus super euphoric and every task is interesting but i take tramadol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our world needs more people like you! 

Take care! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was an amazing answer for him! Good job man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:44:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate... when i wake up and if i have this pressure and like dry feeling on my face the day is gonna be akward anxous and shit.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well i think 30min and today i did 1,30h and it felt so good. It felt line it gave me same amount of energy as a night of sleep. But the bad thing is i did it at 10pm so its hard to fall asleep now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry i dont and i just took 250mg of tramadol and like 10 pills of lame antidepressant and i cant look straight and im feeling too gooood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate. So many times started a plan to get a six pack ,plan to eat better but always failed. But then i wanted to start mesitating. Didnt fail and it helps me relax so much.
 I highly recommend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My problem was that i tried to do everything at the same time. Its important to take a breath few times a day. Like for me im a student and after school my plan was to, practise programming(python), doing my website project, reading a book about programming and practising art. i burnt out and i still am unmotivated and feeling like shit.

Dont do too many things at the same time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been dealing with depression and anxiety for five years now and im 19y old :)

Love you too man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate. I know pretty much exacly how i could change my life and become the best version of my self but its hard. 

I have my own problems but i still go forward and i never quit, sometimes i just go slower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:10:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok mom :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 01:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Comgraz thats a big accomplishment! Im still in school and im failing pretty hard
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 00:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can only smoke at night so i have an cool spot in a small forest, there is like natural nature made chair. And the spot is 2min away for my home.
And when i have weed( pretty rarely) i smoke it for my anxiety  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 00:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i think i will start doing it in 30min sessions. 
Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 00:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok good to know and thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 23:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ill add it to my reading list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 23:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok great! Well If thats the case(havent read much of it yet), does he tell about different meditation techniques in the book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For free of course </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 23:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you like a copy of  the mind illuminated
Its a book about meditating.

Hit me up in messages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 23:39:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have depression, anxiety and my mind is super active all the time and i usually think about everyhting and i keep asking questions and i have ideas flying trough my mind 24/7.

so when i meditate it is the only time when my mind relaxes. Also i dont feel anxious when i meditate. I think its going to change my life eventually. I love it already!
Im reading a book called  the mind illuminated  its about meditating and i recommend it!

If you want i could send a copy of it to your email(ebook of couse).If you want it just send your email to me. And its epub format so for example if you have iphone download an app called apple books its free, really good and it supports (all for i know) pdf and epub formats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 23:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you read the whole text? She said that he kept asking questions even when she said no the first time. 
And its pretty good hint to go away if the person you are talking to doesnt look at you at all and its not too hard to see that the other person is a bit uncomfortable.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 23:07:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like it would be better to go with company 1.
Especially if the people are nice there. Good work envoirment is really important! Example if you are having a bad day the telling the about it to the people there can make them help you and make you feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:56:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This might sound stupid but try meditating.
It affects your brain in the long run.
Give it a try! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:53:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If the person you are talking to really cares about you, you should be able to open up to them without scaring them off. 

Few of my friends(girls) have said the same thing to me(that they dont know me anymore) but i know that they care about me so i explained everything im going through and now everything is fine between us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes but still people should respect others and be kind. Sadly thats not how things go...... society is fucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes less social media is great! Like instagram its useless and full of show off people. That makes almost anyone depressed.

Reddit is great because i can release stress by writing my experiences and feelings and also i have learned a lot of stuff here.

I think pinterest and reddit are apps that you can really benefit from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my country the bar is almost only place when people approach each others. 

If we dont count the bar in I have never approached anyone and no one is approached me.

Usually in public example in bus, everyone is just quiet doing their own thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have a point there no guestion about that.
So yes im sorry my opinion is based on my feelings and experience, because i feel so uneasy if some random person comes and talks to me in crowded place.

But if she says no then he should respect that and stop asking or leave and not to push the questioning. That could make someone feel threatened even.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NEVER FELT ANYTHING LIKE THIS </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 22:15:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im new to meditation and this was my third time meditating and i meditated for 1,30h. It was easy and amazing. The first time i meditated i didnt felt anything unusual and i meditated for 10min. Second time i meditated for 30min and it was relaxing. But today i meditated for 1,30h and i felt so many different energies and sensations. 

(I lit up two candles in front of me and put meditation music playing from my phone) i sat on the floor legs crossed and my back was against my bed and closet. So first feeling was like i was getting super tiny and the room was moving. Then i felt something going through me and i felt like i was in some kind of void. My whole bodey felt numb. The last was, i felt like i got some kind of invicible bubble around me.

now im laying in my bed and i still sense it. I feel like im already changed person and i have meditated three times. I dont know if this affects it but im super open minded and i dont judge enything if i havent tried it first.
Aslo with people i dont judge anyone because everyone has their own story and reasons why the act how they act.

Meditation is just simply the best thing for me to relax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 20:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id like to know too :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 20:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im more emotional than before. I mean my emotions are much more strong than usual.
And i also turn red pretty easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 20:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started to meditate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 200mg of tramadol </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 20:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 09:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw this orb too but without psychedelics. It was first kinda in front of me and then flew past me and didnt come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 09:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the same problem but how do i do it like after my bodey feels numb, do i start to think about an nice palace or what should i do? Im new to meditation and its VERY interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 09:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry that there are men like that...
they dont realize how uncomfortable the person can feel. People should be more polite but society is just straight Fucked up... thats why i hate some people, who have head up their ass.
I too have social anxiety and its super annoying if some random person comes and talks random shit... i hate small talk there is no point in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You will recover the memory much faster if you have learned it in the past.

But i think there is no shortcut so just keep going! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt it a thing that if you are not an adult and if you smoke alot of weed it can change your brain a bit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you man! 
You are so amazing person for sharing this!
I saved this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope you are alright. Sometimes i feel weird pain in my throath(im a smoker) but i also have bad anxiety and that might be causing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry for you man. 
This makes me sad.
Love is such an amazing thing but also can be fatal. I have been cheated on twice and because of it i got depressed and its fucked. I was happy and motivated and everything was nice, but then it all went down because i was blindly in love.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should go just to be sure.
But for example im depressed and socially anxous. Usually i cant leav my bed and i skip school and every planned activity and sometimes when i think talking in front of a big group i usually throw up. Life is fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not an alcoholic, i like to drink sometimes.
I just dont like the taste of alcohol at all.
Vodka is super hard to get down the throath.
Even if i mix it, i taste it and its so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont have words anymore!
You are amazing!
Thankyou! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its really helpful and you can empty your thoughts there. Please go it could help you to get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 23:15:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg thank you so much! You are such an amazing person!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:54:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got the book(eBook) and ive been reading it for few hours and its really good book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im diagnosed with depression and social anxiety.
Im still trying to find the right meds for me with my doctor, no results yet. 

A short story of my dad so my dad has many diseases( he has gone through many surgeries example kidney, heart and differen kind of vein surgeries) and he has loads of meds and example one time he needed tramadols for his nerve pains and the pain stopped and he was left with many pacs of tramadols so i took some of the tramadols( i would never take something that he needs everyday and could die without and propably would kill me ) not full pacs just few sheets yes they are a bit addictive but has antidepressiant effects and when im under the effects im super outgoing and talkstive and my anxiety goes away completely, i feel so euphoric and im super morivated even the most boring things are interesting and i get so much shit done. But i need to be careful with drugs because some drugs cause liver damage in the long run and i have diabetes(type 1 so cant do anything to make it go away) so my liver is already under pressure. But to the point i know there are anti-addictive drugs and some no prescription nootropics that are mood boosting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 22:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suggest meditation! It has helped me a lot. It was so hard to be still with my own thoughts even for 10 minutes. But i promise when you learn it a bit it will be so helpful. And i have bad social anxiety but i still have friends, not many( both girls and boys) but they all are very close to me and i know all of them very well. When you are trying to make friends the best thing to do is to be yourself. You dont want to try being some one else because thats not gonna end well for you. Just be yourself.  Push your limits. I know its fucking hard and stuff but you have to do something to improve. Otherwise nothing will happen. Have you contacted a doctor? If not you should do it because you could get some medicatoin and it can help you to be more social. Im normally super itrovert but in my meds im the same me but much more outgoing. I hope youll get better and i hope my message helps!
You can come and talk to me if you want more detailed advices or if you just want to ask questions! You dont need to you can check stuff online but i have personal experience and im diagnosed by a doctor and i have depression and social anxiety. I just want to be as helpful as i can! 

Take care bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 21:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im at the last year with 60 points... i need 180 to graduate. Ive been skipping and failing because of my anxiety and depression. But im not hopeless and im pretty sure it will take two more years to finish but im going to finish it! 

Dont lose hope man!  Just be there its the most important part. Dont get into skipping because if it forms into a habit, Its gonna be BAD.

I also think the classes i have left are so fucking pointless and i almost want to die but its better to be able to do some jobs is much better than nothing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 21:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its screaming because you are winning and it will dissapear soon. Just be happy and it wount get energy from you. Kill the entity inside you with happiness and love.

Keep going bro you are so close to victory, I believe in you, YOU CAN DO IT!!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 21:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the motivation! This really gave me a boost! 
Me and my doctor are trying to find the right meds for me. At the moment i dont have any good meds and i feel super awful and unmotivated. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 21:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If i have a good night sleep, I love to wake up early and do my own projects or something but if i dont get a good night sleep(more likely to happen) im unmotivated an lazy and feeling like shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 21:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Finland
I never call because im Finnish and the pizzeria workers usually arent and i cant understand what they are saying etc... but we have an app that covers almost all the resturants and you can order food with it and also straight pay to their bank so you only need to take the food when they bring it to your door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 21:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is your dog okay now? And i got this energy feeling in my toes and fingertips and i felt like i was floating and in the end i felt pressure in my head. Im new to meditation too. And i set up the alarm but didnt turn it on so i meditated for 30min :D. But it was super relaxing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 21:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do the same. I have collected videos from youtube, pins from pinterest and Books from some palces but never used them really.
Except now im sickof my bullshit and im starting to meditate everyday and do the things i told my self. Actually i just mesitatet for 30mins and i hve never meditatet over 10mins. I just forgot to put an alarm :D . It was nice tho i felt almost like floating and my mind was empty there were nothing. I did not expect that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 19:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have anxiety and sometimes i turn red in social situations. Also sometimes when i drink i turn red for some minutes(even when im comfortable). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 18:47:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely going to read that! It sounds awesome
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 18:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for writing your experience! Id love to try this because i have anxiety and depression but i dont know the root cause why i have them..
Im going to try this today before going to bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 18:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely going to watch this later! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 17:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im new to meditation(only meditatet few times) and id love to get same kind of experience that you had. I know the basics and i have a small book whitch is for beginners its really short i read it in 15minutes, it has loads of pictures and short sentences like thoughts can become obsessive and intrustive; they can also become stuck and repetitive. Its a really cool book called Quiet the mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 17:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 16:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I Read books, play games, research stuff, exercise and programming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes dont get into skipping because its fucking hard to get out of.. im in this skipping habit and its mostly because im depressed and it takes all of my enegry to do even the smallest things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When im in anxous situation i turn red and my muscles get stiff. Its so stressful and i usually avoid social situations when i know that could happen... im sorry i dont know if its serious and im sad to hear that u get nauseous.. i hope you get better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont really feel any good effect of nicotine.. sometimes i even feel like shit after smoking cigarette. And caffein, i dont notice anything.. is there anything that could boost the effect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 10:19:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im good looking and ive never been deniend by a girl. But im still super fucking anxous because i was bullied in highschool and two of my friends died and my confidence got crushed. It was 5 years ago and now im socially anxous and i have depression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 09:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate... i just want to go to some amazing house which is somewere amazing and be alone or with my gf and have drugs, computer, books etc and be there for the rest of my life.. i cant handle this life i have, I have problems going to school and i skip alot... i need to talk to my parenst more about my feelings.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 09:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok! And i watch psychedelicsubstanse or what ever it was but he has videos about ego death and i have watched them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 09:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to hear! I just have to figure out my self where i would get some </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 00:46:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok. Thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unexperienced drug use </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 00:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have anxiety and depression. Sometimes I take tramadol 50mg just to feel motivated and euphoric.  I have sleeping problems and thats why i usually skip school(thats why im stressed all the time). Now im watching youtube 1 am, feeling like shit and i just wanted to feel good so i took 2, 50mg tramadols and 10, 25mg atarax pills. I dont have much drug experience other than weed(id love to try LSD and shrooms someday or salvia whitch is smokable right?). Suddently i started to heard weird noice like high pitch and then it started to lower and now it sounds like im under water. Im feeling super relaxed tho! (And because im in these drugs they make me super extrovert and wanting to talk to people maybe because im normally introvert and socially anxious)

Any thoughts? What is the best antidepressant for you? What should i try, any suggestions?

And what about smoking? I smoke cigarettes and sometimes it makes me feel good and sometimes it makes me feel like shit, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 23:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 23:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did it go?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 22:24:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its so weird to feel suddently good. 
Yes i sometimes take tramadol to feel euphoric but sometimes without that i get the feeling of happiness. I have no idea why. Maybe im getting better? I dont know.(im not suicidal tho, and i feel sad and broken reading your message. If i could use magic to make you feel better, i would.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 01:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are stronger than the most of the depressed people. I have problems leaving my home. Ive been skipping school and i take pills to feel even little bit of euphoric. You are working, so you have some strength in you and you have self discipline. Keep working untill you find your true calling. Doing something is better than doing nothing. Keep going! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 01:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So your boyfriend is not helping you? Then he is not worthy for you. You are amazing an unique no one can take that away from you. Everyone has their own beauty and its in the eyes of the viewer to be experienced. So if your boyfriend is not helping you ( i would definetly help you and listen you and give answers if i was there even that i dont know you but still) you should see a doctor. So you would stop harming yourself and maybe gain confidence and self love back. Please try to get better, you are worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 01:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been skipping scool so much.. i have so much undone work. Im failing. So dont worry just dont make it a habit because it will become a habit if you skip too many times in a week.. you could skip like ones or twice a month. You can make some kind of long weekends example saturday sunday and monday free. It can help alot of you are under stress and hate mondays. DONT SKIP too often its so hard to stop skipping school if you got into the taste of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 01:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah first time i caught my girlfriend cheating on me was at night i was going through her phone and she was sending nudes to a guy she said not to worry about. The second time was few days ago and one time she was playing a game and she talked to him  (through discord) for 13hours straight at my home and she was talking so dirty and perverted stuff and i was anxous about it and askd her what was going on and she said not to worry about and thet few days ago she forgot her discord open on my pc and yeah i found out that they were talking like they were together and i felt so numb. I gave her a third chance but i just dont know and cant get my head around it but  how she could to this again and what the fuck was she thinking... 
She said she have no answers why she did that but i really cannot trust her so im fuckig lost.
And i also have depression and failing school so im stressed all the time and that does not help my sitsuation. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 00:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We are depressed so we propably dont compliment ourselves enough. Even the smallest compliment feels amazing and its okay. Dont be sad or weirded about it. Accept all the compliments you get, you have earned them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 00:48:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes you really cant know 100% surely if someday the love of your life is going to fuck you up.  Because the love of my life i have depression and im still with her. She has cheated on me twice. Not sex but flirting, making other people to fell in love with her and sending nuded. She did this twice and she got me fucked but im so pathetic that i love her so much i just cant leave her. 

Love is fucking hurtful thing and it can be the most amazing thing in your life and propably will be but it can also be fatal and put you to the path of suicide. Be careful and dont rush into things and move slowly in relationships. Get to know the person super well and then make your moves if you want. Just be careful and move slow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I cant finnish anything [help please] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-02 00:35:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have this bad habit that i almost never finish anything that ive started. Im depressed, socially anxious and lazy. I love sience and usually i skip school and research things and make a video out of it. I think the school im in  is a waste of time and i have so much undone work and im at the last year and i have 60 points (should have 120 points now) and in the summer i should have 180 points to graduate. Im so unmotivated to do anything school related and my passion was programming for a while and thats why i chose the shcool im in but i have always liked sience and researching things what i usually do in my freetime. The things i have undone is mostly normal subjects like english, swedish(whitch i fucking hate), math, chemistry etc... its just that im so anxious that i get uncomfortable if i walk past someone. I just want to quit school and do the things i love but even with knowledge but without school graduate i cant get a job that i would enjoy. I FUCKING HATE NORMAL JOBS. I got so fucking depressed when i had a summer job that was about keeping some outside area clean. I literally everyday how long i would be there. Also i started smoking because i coudnt handle the stress that i had every day. I just want to quit everything and relax and learn to calm and relif all the stress i have. How could i handle my situation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 19:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started doing youtube recently i have just few videos but this helped me. If you are writin about a certain subject, research and learn about it untill you can teach it to someone who has none knowledge of it. And then write a full research document and then write a smaller document of it whitch includes the main things and some interesting facts. Now days average people dont want to read super long texts of anything, they get bored. So after writing the smaller document you can show it to your friend or your family member and ask if it was too long, too short or just right. Im not an expert but i think this is a good way. But if its for school or some other really important thing that needs every information you have from the subject you should post the whole research document of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 00:22:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the same thing that i turn red if my friend or someone talks to me in a public place and also yes people call me good looking my friends are saying that i could have anyone who i ever wanted. The blushing thigy limits so much what i want to do because i avoid some situations and example in a bus my anxiety kicks in super hard and even when im walking in street and even if one people walks past me i usualy check phone because of getting so anxious if im just walking. I dont know why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 23:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man i feel you.. Im 19 and i feel like failture peace of shit that doesnt deserve to live.
I have depression and anxiety. 
Life is a fucking joke and i believe that nothing really matters but still i some how keep on going. 
I have a girlfriend that half a year ago cheated on me and i got depressed and i had no fucking way that i could have left her. She is the love of my life i love her more than anything. because of her Im crying at the moment and i have pain in my heart like real pain i feel like some one is poking it with needles. 
Im failing school im failing my life. I really dont know what to do because im scared of everything. im scared to go to the bus that i use to get to school. Im so done, i dont have answers to anything. So whats left.. Everything. I have this feeling in my brain that maybe i wasnt supposed to win. maybe i was made to fail to feel like peace of shit. So im fucking going to show everybody what i can do and reach my goals and finally fucking WIN. after that im gonna help people i want to help the people who are going through the same as we are. you dont want that feeling you are feeling to enyone else? right? then no one wants you to feel that way about yourself? i bet there are loads of amazing people to talk to. the most important thing is to SPEAK. even if its through your phone, it helps. Please dont give up on your life. you have so much to see to experience even bad things but that is part of being a human right? there cant be good if there is no bad. Think about it. Think for your self what you really want and start looking for ways to get closer to it no matter what. dont give up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 22:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 19. I feel like a fucking loser. im not confidence anymore i have anxiety i have depression i have trust issues to my girlfriend and im crying my eyes out i feel pain in my heart that i have never felt before. its 00:00 a clock and tomorrow is school. Last week i was only on monday at school. im failing my life im losing grip on my self. i dont want to live because im scared of everyting but also i dont want to die.
 im fucking lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>