<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2903</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 07:41:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was not at all how it was, but not gonna lie, I read that book right to the end. Well done! 

Edit: a letter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 07:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats quite interesting actually. Maybe its just me immediately thinking of the one with the same gender instead, hehe. Norway :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 22:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 22:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one on the right is classy and elegant with a great figure for you. 

The one on the left is sweet and romantic. 

Id go for the right as thats more my personality, but the one on the left is also beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 21:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 21:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey. Im Norwegian, of the right age, but Im studying in London which probably has an impact on my drinking habits. Could I still participate, or is that a hard no? 

Edit: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 21:38:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grddost, brie, gouda, edam or Norwegian brown cheese. But top one, probably the grddost. On toast with melted butter, and grapes on top is the best. 

Edit to add Parmesan! Ugh I want pasta now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 21:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Norwegian with a British partner here (his heritage is Vietnamese   Philippino). It is so bloody difficult to find names that work in every language, and so many favourites are being thrown out..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 21:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Matteo/Matheo (pronounces the same) is super popular in Scandinavia - and were as white as you get em!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 21:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done. However, this survey was quite annoying to fill out due to the fact you have to answer each question, even if it doesnt apply to you. Filling out info on 8 siblings when I only had one other than the focus sibling for example. 

Also, I dont live in America. Was this supposed to be only for Americans? Zip code will probably look strange. 

On the question about contact with the focus sibling you only asked about face-to-face meetings and phone calls. In the world of technology and social media there are a lot more ways to keep in touch, especially for people like me who moved to a different country to study, and thus is living away from the entire family now, not just away from my sibling. This makes it seem like Im only living far away from him in the questionnaire. 

Also, I am 25 and have a masters degree. Does that go under college? Should maybe add higher education as an option. 

Im also curious, why did the focus sibling have to be within 5 years of yourself? My focus sibling in day to day life is not the one I had to choose because of age. The one I chose because of age was the first born, and a boy. The one I would compare myself with naturally is the last born, another girl. 

My parents also treated us all differently during different times. For example, my dad and I had a special bond when I was a child. As a teenager I became more unruly, and both my parents then favoured the other siblings. As an adult now, the youngest seems to be favoured (shes also the only one still living with them), but its me they come to for advice and help, not the first born. The last born takes more time and energy for them and requires more attention than the rest of us did, as she struggles with depression and anxiety. This did not come across properly in the survey as all the questions are did/do your parents favour this or that child type. 

Otherwise super interesting topic, and lots of interesting questions!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 20:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The rectaliner (rectal recliner).
Too lazy to get out of your recliner to go toilet? The rectaliner is here to save the day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 20:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the cats in the circle and a silver spoon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 19:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man on a bus taking up the entire back row by sitting in the middle and blocking it so that no one else can get in. Full bus, people standing, makes no move to scooch or open up for people to move in past him. About 50 years old, looks otherwise like a generic adult, greying hair, glasses, suit, dad type. Maybe he has long legs. I dont know. Trying to analyse him and come to a good reasoning, but cant. Walk up to him. No response. May I come past you? Guy moves and lets me in. I sit down by the window. Guy closes the gap. Feels safe, but slightly amazed at the casual rudeness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 18:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Delilah just reminds me of that song Hey there Delilah or whatever its called. Sweet song though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 18:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ee-sha? I love the way the names Aiofe and Niamh looks, but dont like the pronounciation unfortunately. Also not Irish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 17:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, my boyfriends ex. It was his bedroom window (not mine), and we had been together for a year and a half. I had never met the girl before, and she just stood there. 

Another weird/uncomfortable/kinda creepy one was when I lived on campus at uni (very nice uni, but everything outside of campus was.. not very nice) and I saw kids (actual children) picking up drugs to sell from an old man in a car multiple times a week on the street below my window. 

A young man also jumped to his death from the roof of the building across the street from my window, but I didnt actually see it happening. Only the commotion after.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 17:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Filled out. Might actually have been better to have the I would feel hurts before the it is cheating, as that might have made people question it more, as just because something hurts you doesnt mean its actually cheating. But I dunno, just a thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 07:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got the first cat I owned by myself when she was 4 weeks old, as the other kittens were sadly put to sleep. As she was so young I had to feed her milk replacement and watered down cat food etc. We also had a large dog at the time (Bernese mountain dog), so the kitty lived in my bedroom until she was big enough that the dog wouldnt accidentally sit on her or something. 

The bedtime set-up was her inside a riding helmet in the corner between my pillow and the wall, as I was terrified of squishing her. 
I would stroke her belly until I fell asleep every night, and I would talk to her all the time. She grew up to be like a dog when it comes to belly rubs, and she would talk back to me. Wed have entire conversations while I stroked her belly. 

Edit: I was a child myself when I got her, and she lived to be 14 before cancer killed her. 

Edit 2: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 10:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jorbjrg.. og Asrun.. not my favourites, haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 07:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, did he only tell OP because the ex got pregnant??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 07:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They told us weeks ago, how am I supposed to remember??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 21:24:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pecking order.. peeking.. peeking order.. no? Thats why it sounded cute. Like they were in a row taking turns lifting their heads up to take a peek, pecking fur out of each other does not sound very cozy at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 20:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Peeking order sounds adorable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 18:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both me and my boyfriend are like this. During the honeymoon period however, we were tangled up like a ball of human body parts as we slept. Neither of us had ever experienced that before, that need to be as close as possible. Somehow it got flipped, we would both wake up if we werent touching anymore instead of the opposite. Been together 4 years now, and a foot is usually touching a leg, but the rest of our bodies are now separate again. But that foot touch is still there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 18:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriends the same, except he doesnt like handholding (only super rarely in bed, right before going to sleep). He enjoys me touching and cuddling him, but does it back maybe twice a year.. its a weird thing. 4 years together and he still seems like hes scared I will reject him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 23:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jerry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 23:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fish parcels are healthy and super easy to make. Just put a fish fillet on to some aluminium foil with some oil and any veggies you have (cut into stir-fry sized pieces), little bit of oil and some seasoning, close the parcel and pop into the over until the fish is flaky and veggies are cooked. 
To be fancy you can put pesto or something in as well, but its good as it is. A knob of butter after cooking makes the veggies more yummy though. 

Made this today with salmon, potatoes (sliced), broccoli and mushrooms. Great way to use up leftover veg as well! Bonus!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 13:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you happen to be Scandinavian by any chance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 13:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mar-ee-uhs. But Im Scandi, so the r is rolling for us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 13:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for clarifying!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 13:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im torn, on one hand I find Vivienne to be too posh for my liking, but paired with Winter it suddenly sounds like a literary character and I quite like that. Vivienne Winter Knight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 01:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Regina De Lara sounds like a celebrity name, possibly because of the similarity to Lana Del Ray? I dont know. Regina means queen however, and is a lovely name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 01:10:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this as well, but always use old people names like Mildred the ladybug   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 01:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Duncan Damian and Duncan Donovan sound too close to Dunkin Donuts to me.. Alexander is lovely as a middle name for Duncan though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 01:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I quite like Lulu for a nickname, or Lola. If you find a nickname you like you can block Lou by using another nickname first  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 00:28:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My parents did that with me and my siblings. I always sign my name in the following fashion (not real name): Rhiannon J. Lastname. That J is for my first last name (my dads surname). Ive always been very happy to have both of those names, and will keep them also after getting married. Will do the same with my kids and give them my last name and their dads last name (not the middle).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 00:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah everythings going well here. How are you, Marius? Its definitely been a while! Looks to be a whole(quarter/half - hopefully) lifetime! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 23:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know your struggle. Norwegian with British partner here, and the name game is so bloody difficult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 23:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive just answered it, but as Im from a country where people normally eat other things than turkey for Christmas you might get some strange answers of what goes with your turkey :) maybe change it to apart from the meat/main food item or something similar? Or not, as its a casual survey. Just a thought as its open to anyone who celebrates Christmas. Christmas isnt celebrated the same way everywhere :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 23:00:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? Maybe that was what she meant then, and not Quoc meaning king. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 22:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you my ex boyfriend? Because this is exactly what my ex boyfriend did to me. He also called me by his exes name in front of his family once. Everyone noticed except for him. Ah, fun times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 22:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great suggestions, but for closeness to Killian I would add Kelian (pronounces Keh-lian) :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 21:32:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partners family is Vietnamese. All the kids have their Vietnamese names and a more international name that they go by. My partners Vietnamese name is Quoc Vuong. One of his sisters told us that Quoc means king, but I havent verified that. It is however interesting if its true, as my name also has royal meaning to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 19:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in Cannes when this happened, on holiday with my family and partner. We were also out celebrating, in a similar setting watching the fireworks out on the ocean with thousands of people. I remember getting back to the hotel afterwards and realising my phone was blowing up with messages. Thats how we found out what had happened in Nice. It felt so surreal, we had just been in almost the exact same setting just one city over, and had to go back to Nice to get to the airport when we were leaving. It took 5 security checks to go through, and that was a week after. I specifically remember standing by that beach with all these people, and noticing two parents holding hands while they each had a child on their shoulders watching the fireworks.. 
My heart still breaks just thinking about that day, and I am so sorry it happened and that you had to witness it. I hope youre doing okay now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 21:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good choice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 20:09:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, at least Dildora can go by Dora.. Dont know what I would have chosen between Dik, Diks and Shit...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 20:49:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would you even suggest putting mayo on a pizza... what kind of monster...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 23:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pineapple is amazing on pizza (in/on hot food Im general), but mayo? Nah thaaaanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 05:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id add Tora (like Thor, but female - Thora/Tora). She was queen of both Norway and Denmark. And fucking badass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 05:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi Anton Im Scandinavian as well, but I have lived in the U.K. for five years now. I studied anthropology for 3 years here (bachelors),  and Ive done 1 year (masters) in coastal and marine resource management. Send me a message if you wanna chat!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 22:28:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work 7.30-4. I get up 6.25, pee, brush my teeth   get dressed, out the door by 6.45. Do my hair on the bus. Mascara from the day before, no other make-up. Buy breakfast at the grocery store next to my workplace, and eat at work. 

Is sounds like Im up super late and thus always tired and in a rush, but I honestly go to bed before 10pm every day. I just really love to sleep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 21:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also worthy of note: Do not try to get your drill fixed on warranty if you broke it doing this. It will be classed as user fault, you will have to pay, and we do not want to have that argument with you about how normal it is. The drill was not made for this, so if you fuck it up while doing it, its your own fault! /rant over

Source (of aggression): did customer service for one of the worlds largest power tools suppliers for a year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 20:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on where someones from in Norway geographically. Some places make a sh sound for kj while others (most) make a ch sound. However, Ive never seen Od as a name, or heard the pronunciation Ode, its always Odd with the pronunciation of odd (as in strange). 

Side note: Simen is the Norwegian version of Simon. Pronounced See-men. Double names are common. Imagine the poor man called Odd Simen on his travels around the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-14 22:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a similar dream, but about a dog. I was so happy with and proud of the name I kept slipping it in to every conversation. The name of the dog was Harald. As in the Norwegian version of Harold. I 100% do not like this name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-11 22:13:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive got my dads surname as a middle, and my mums surname as my last name even though my parents are married (neither of them changed their names). Honestly, I quite like it that way. I am a product of both those families, not just one, so having both names always felt natural.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 20:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner gets hit on quite a lot, both by women and men. I once had to show a gay man in his 60s pictures of us together as proof he was my boyfriend as he would not leave us alone. Not really anyones best story, but thats the one I remember the most.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 23:18:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make sure to watair your an germern sherperd or else it will not an grow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 23:08:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who said theyd be buried next to each other? The question is if they should have a funeral. I believe yes - as a funeral is for the family not the deceased. In my personal opinion it would be most suitable with a small, private funeral somewhere not affiliated with any of the victims (basically another church etc)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-26 23:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just gonna casually add Death row to immediate associations to Jethrow in here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-26 23:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, sure, now what about the persons family?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-18 11:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats the name I have set aside for a future female pup, and Kenai for a male!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-12 23:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a teenager anymore, but theres one thing I keep noticing my parents doing - and that is to treat their teenagers problems as if its not a big deal. Yes, In the grand scale of things it might not be a big deal. Yes, as older and more experienced people it may seem like a small issue. But to your child/teenager it may be the most difficult thing they have ever experienced, so take it seriously and help them to learn healthy ways of coping with problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-11 16:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure did. Just saying you shouldnt devalue yourself based on your height as it really isnt that big of a deal to most women (maybe it is to party girls?), and that the way you think and talk about women and other guys may actually be your problem (and what is putting women off of you) - not your height. But this discussion is clearly going nowhere so its going in the fuck it bucket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 23:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. And also put effort into keeping your surroundings tidy - itll give you a better start to the day when you dont have to play catch-up on things from the day before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 23:22:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saaaaame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 23:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pets are family. Dont give up your cat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 22:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool, whatever you say. Short guys get laid all the time, Im really struggling to see how THAT is your problem (I think its another quite obvious one), but hey ho. You continue being bitter if thats what you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 17:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one - attitude and how you make people feel is still more important than looks, whether its a relationship or a one-night-stand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 16:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a white female in a relationship with a short Asian guy, the only thing that comes off as unattractive in this post is your view of women as a prize to be won, and your view of other guys as unworthy. Not everythings about looks dude. Your attitude is make or break when it comes to attractiveness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 11:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They sound very professional. I struggle to picture them as little girls playing in a sandbox tbh. However, Molly and Heidi (without the middle names) do have that child quality to them, so I guess it works, just not my personal cup of tea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 09:27:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so happy you took her in and are taking good care of her. She is beautiful!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-09 22:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That first picture is absolutely heartbreaking!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-09 17:13:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 22:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Got sent to the principals office for handing my friend a pencil once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 22:21:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cucumber slices dipped in low sodium soy sauce is delicious! Or Apple slices with cinnamon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 23:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How could she have forgot though, if she actually told them it wouldnt fit with your schedule?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 23:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister is Tyson (her name is Kaja, pronounced Kaya so it went from there to Kays, then Tays then Tyson), anyone and anything cute/loveable is munchkin or bubba, my boyfriend is Cookie (his Vietnamese name (that he doesnt use) sounds kind of like it), my mum is Mokkala or Mokka (her name is Monica).. And then theres Fat Joe (he nicknamed himself this as a teenager - he thought it sounded like a rappers name. Obviously we cant let him forget that ever).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 19:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The sort of pop-crush of a duck being run over by a car. Im assuming it was the ribs that made the sound. It happened years ago and the sound still haunts me.

Also the absolute silence after an old couple got hit by a car in France. They both ended up being fine, but that terrifying silence between the hit and being told the damage was only a broken ankle and bruising was absolutely awful. It was however extremely emotional to see the man stand back up and go straight to his wife and help her up, and get her to a chair, before sitting down himself - even with a broken ankle. That couple is real life relationship goals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 21:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My heart goes straight into my throat watching these videos, Im terrified the dogs are gonna get that egg stuck in their throats and suffocate. Im actually helicopter parenting other peoples dogs, this life is too stressful for me 

Edit: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 18:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had an ex show up on the doorstep I shared with my new partner while my new partner was at work. He cried, apologised for cheating 3 years earlier (which was the end of the relationship), proposed, and laid out this whole life plan he had for us. 

My heart broke for him, but I had to tell him I was happier in my new relationship. Were both in new relationships now. We still talk from time to time, and have a friendly tone. There were too many memories, too many lessons and positive learning experiences between us to completely stop contact, and we are both genuinely happy to see each other if we bump into one another. Hugs and hair ruffles all around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 17:59:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you implying interracial relationships is a bad thing? Or simply stating you might find yourself watching interracial porn by accident?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 17:09:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats your robin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-05 19:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for replying! Im happy to read about your friends, and the guy clearly wasnt right for you anyway. Thanks for doing the AMA, and good luck in your future endeavours!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-04 20:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nell is adorable! Im a fan of short names so Nell is right up my street!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-04 19:46:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mateo/Matheo is fairly common in Norway.. Ive had at least three with that name in a nursery I worked at, and I was only there for a year. I dont see a problem with it. 

I think naming a child says something about the childs parents and the family heritage, but also about the period in time the child was born into. We are becoming more and more international, so its to be expected that names are beginning to mix more.

As Im Norwegian and my partner is British Vietnamese wed probably choose names which were either international (British/American) or/and names inspired by our combined heritage. Im not about to tell other people they cant name their child something they love just because its a popular name or originated in a country they have no connection to though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-04 19:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! This might be too personal, so feel free not to answer if it makes you uncomfortable or you just dont want to get into the topic.

As you were around 20 when this happened and youre now 22, how have you coped with the change to your social and romantic life?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-04 19:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do it. Leave it all, and keep your mind and heart open. Itll all work out - and the bumps in the road will be worth it. Itll be the best decision youve ever made, and youll never have the what if.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 21:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cat had diarrhoea all over my homework once. My teacher didnt believe it, even with a note from my parents, so my parents had to come to the school to tell them face-to-face  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 18:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough, but encountering an asshole driver in Europe and all youve gotta do is write down the number - whether theyre from the same country or not. I see the positives about the US system, but personally I kinda think personalised number plates are tacky, and prefer the simplicity of the European system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 17:17:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seconding this, and adding that when arguing with people no one ever brings up my race. The only thing I can even attempt to compare it to would be people calling me stupid/unintelligent/worthless because I am blond (going for the blonde jokes). After meeting my bf who has parents from the other side of the world I have suddenly become much more aware of these differences as he has accumulated quite a collection of stories where his race was directly mentioned in a lot of ridiculous circumstances over the years.

Edit: I guess a white person in another part of the world might have a different experience than me though, as I live in Northern Europe where the majority is white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 07:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because if theres a lot of countries/states/provinces you can go through easily on a regular basis, chances are youre gonna be similar to at least one of them. Best way is for them all to be different from the get-go, so you avoid the issue completely,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-01 19:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres actually a pretty useful reason for our boring numberplates though.. we can roadtrip to other countries with no problems, which is pretty useful in Europe. If you get ManUtd1 and someone else has that already in a different country theres room for quite a bit of confusion. I imagine road tripping to a different country is less common in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 22:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-11 08:13:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha because drinking alcohol and watching television is of course basically the same thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-11 08:10:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats basically nouc cham :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-10 22:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. I did my undergrad in Anthropology and my MSc in Coastal and Marine Resource Management. Literally aiming for any job that has to do with how humans utilise and exploit the ocean, and how to keep it sustainable. I wrote both of my dissertations on the same topic too. 

I think the clue with an anthropology degree is that you have to incorporate it into something else, or make your focus more specific to really make yourself needed in the job you want, if that makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-10 22:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, this one time he hoovered under the table and around the sofa too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-10 08:11:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I dont see the need to drink alcohol if youre having dinner with your kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-09 22:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes he does his own dishes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 23:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think someone forgot to have a word with your dad, hehehh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 08:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive just seen your message and replied there :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 22:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My uncle. I thought it was creepy that he always kept making almost flirty rhymes with my name, and he just seemed kind of sleazy. One day I went downstairs to my room while we had family over, and he followed me down and started asking me questions about what I was doing that weekend. Suddenly my dad is sprinting down the stairs, bursts through the door, and tells my uncle to go back upstairs and leave me alone. About a year later hes in court accused of sexually abusing his own daughter over a period of years. He was convicted, but is out of prison now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 19:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personal opinion: no alcohol around kids that young whatsoever. I just dont see the need for it. One beer or glass of wine with a fancy dinner or something - fair enough. But having a party with alcohol in your house while the kids are there? Not cool in my book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 13:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He might just be overcompensating as his mother basically controls his life, and hes trying to pretend like he is actually in control.. it could also be a way to pretend he doesnt care - as in him trying to not be sad and basically shutting off his emotions. I dont know. Just hang in there, this is a weird time for both of you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 02:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the beginning it was nearly every day. Then it went down a bit (2-3 times a week?).. then back to nearly every day, and now we live together. It all depends on what other things youve got going on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 02:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably a direct translation from a native language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 01:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I looked after identical twin girls for a while. The parents used pink hair ties for one and purple ones for the other. If I remember correctly they used bracelets of some kind when the girls were babies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 01:24:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our cat is training us. Shell knock on the window to be let in (yes - she knocks with her paw). If we take too long opening the door shell attack our legs. Only one bite (and it doesnt hurt), and then shell be on her way. If we open it quickly shes fine. 

Shes also trained our puppies/dogs with sort of the same tactic. If theyve done something she doesnt like, like if theyre being too energetic, shell slap them (no claws). It takes them a little while, but they learn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-06 22:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem. Itll take some time, but I promise you everything will be okay one way or the other. Just try to focus on taking care of yourself right now. Anything can happen in the future, and you wont know how things turn out if youre not there to see it. Try to enjoy other aspects of your life and let time do its thing. Hopefully his mum will come around, or youll reconnect at a later time where he is in a position to make his own rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-06 17:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck I just remembered my parents have a picture of me and my cousin giving each other a peck as toddlers, all dressed up in our sailors costumes. My first kiss was with my cousin. Damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-06 17:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 12-ish? Although I did have a couple nursery kisses before, haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-06 17:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel for you. I know its rough, but try to take care of yourself. When you feel like shit and are having anxieties, try to do something that calms you down. Do you have a pet? In that case, maybe bring your pet into your room when you go to bed. Find some music that makes you relax. Personally I listen to podcasts, or make up stories in my head. I have a few made up day dreams which have been going on for a few years, and I can easily close my eyes and switch right into them now, continuing where I left off last time. I also like to run, so if my head is going crazy I go outside and run until I cant run anymore. Yoga also helps. However, youre the only one who knows what will calm you down - but try to find something. You can also PM me any time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-06 12:17:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jeg skriver p dialekt nr jeg sender melding til/chatter med familie og venner, men ikke nr jeg skriver offentlig eller i en profesjonell sammenheng.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-06 12:03:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or you know, if its super important to have a party at your house that specific night - see if the kids can stay at someone elses house for the night  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-06 12:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hopefully shell realise shes being unfair and hypocritical. Im crossing my fingers for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-06 00:09:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought the same thing, Im more uncomfortable that there were kids in the house at the time of the party than about the dog tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 23:57:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marley and me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 23:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My family has called me Gia since I was little, as I couldnt pronounce my name properly yet so I called myself that. (My name is not my username btw)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 23:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just have a new sex talk with them, say youve seen a few condoms in the rubbish and you just want to make sure they know what they are doing or something.. or do the camera in the hallway thing. But definitely do not accuse them without any solid evidence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 23:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youll be alright. Everything will be good in the end, and if it isnt - then its not the end. Just try to stay positive. Keep talking to him, and just wait and see what happens  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 23:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poisonous jellyfish sting.. first I nearly drowned because I couldnt use my right arm and was out quite deep. Then had to get urgent medical treatment for the sting after a man fished me out of the ocean. They found a doctor who was staying at the hotel, as everyone but me and my family (we are from Norway) realised the seriousness of the situation. Apparently a grown man had died the week before of the same thing - I was a tiny 13 year old female. Luckily I was stung on the back of my right shoulder, so even though the sting was literally bubbling white puss , rapidly growing, and had taken out all feeling and movement from my right arm, I got lucky. 

Edit: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 22:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are some great names being suggested here so Im not gonna repeat them, but Vera? If you like the short names with a V-sound? Vega is also pretty badass in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 21:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its actually painful to look at your picture, I want one so bad but cant have one yet.. I grew up with one (called Goya - hence the username) and although weve had plenty of other breeds since, a Bernese is at the top of my wish list.. just gotta get a more permanent place to live where Im allowed to keep animals first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 21:49:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loooove fish sauce, Im one to ask for extra fish sauce at Vietnamese restaurants. Nouc cham if for spring rolls/bn etc, but please, may I have some extra fish sauce for my pho?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 21:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will your disabled child have access to any medical attention he might need?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 21:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your mum sounds like a great person. He might just be feeling hopeless because he has to deal with (and I assume live with) all the negativity coming from his parents. Give it some time. I know how urgent and intense it feels, but you do have more time than you think. Speak to the therapist, counsellor and your mum. Try to enjoy all the other parts of your life. Youre not the only one who will feel the what if, he will too. And as your mum said, the opportunity to pursue a relationship with him might strike again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 21:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The suks/souks in Marrakech. Its quite high up on the scary-list, especially going in thinking it would be amazing.. terrifying experience. Id rather go back to Malta where I nearly died than back there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 20:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two separate occasions; two separate pairs of boots. I still remember exactly how they looked, and have since found one of them - only a lot more expensive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 20:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I havent even read it and I want to cry. I just read the headline and and to restore my faith in humanity by reading the comments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 19:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one who took me in and let me stay on his couch when I was so drunk I could barely walk as a teenager and had lost my wallet and phone. I left before he had woken up, so never spoke to him while in a more alive state, but I WILL BE ETERNALLY GRATEFUL FOR YOU! Youll also be happy to know it never happened again. Thank you for helping me, and I hope life has and will continue to treat you with kindness and generosity. You are an actual hero, and I am forever kicking myself for not getting your name so I could thank you properly for your act of kindness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 19:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with that. As they are still in a relationship - shell now see if he values the relationship or not. If hes not okay with helping her out even though shes helped him so much, then the only logical option is to end the relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 19:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *many hugs* if its meant to be, it will be. Lots of people end up back with their first love as adults. You will be fine. At times, youll even be great. But I do understand the heartbreak.. I hope you have people to talk to, like your parents or a friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 17:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, he is not legally obligated to help her out - but thats not OPs question either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 17:24:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, IBS is used as a rug to shove anything bowel-related they cant figure out under. Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 17:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 17:22:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem, Im 25 and have this too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 17:20:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with you, and didnt say she should move back in with him and forget it never happened. She has to protect herself and the baby. Im just saying there might still be something to work with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 17:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Feelings are very intense as a teenager too, and the sense of urgency attached to them is very stressful. I remember that time well. Im crossing my fingers for you two, that youll at least get a chance to see what it is - even if it doesnt last for the rest of your lives. Otherwise there will always be that what if. Sending hugs your way!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 15:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uhscuse me....? Are you planning on paying for absolutely everything for your family then? Rent/mortgage, food, clothes, bills, phones, spending money...? For you, your wife/girlfriend and all and any children you might have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 13:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whaling
Introduction to my job
Studying in London as a Norwegian
The Bajau Laut
Introduction to anthropology
Introduction to coastal and marine resource management
marine spatial planning
marine conservation
animal behaviour
primate biology and behaviour
evolutionary anthropology 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IBS. Literally anything bowel/belly related that docs cant figure out is called IBS. Thats why you get a bunch of people with very different symptoms but all have the same diagnosis (and very often no medications or treatments). Its very common.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A serious case of precordial catch syndrome?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any type of storm (I love them), especially thunder storms. 

The northern lights

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The sex has never been an issue with us - its getting there in the first place. We had a bit of a rut about a year ago which lasted a few months (we were both very busy), but then we started flirting again, touching each other in normal settings, putting our arms around each other while cooking - things like that. And suddenly sex was back to being amazing. I think if you maintain that mental connection, maintaining your sex life is much, much easier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:27:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think hes an Olympic skier if I remember correctly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, it looks like you need to step up here and talk to your parents. You have an apartment with your bf - you dont live with them anymore. Set some boundaries with them. Tell them that it is incredibly unfair of them to expect you to choose their happiness over your own. That you have your own life to live, and you are not an extension of them but your own person, with your own feelings. If you love the guy you need to stand up for your relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:09:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sam Cooke - Portrait of a Legend on vinyl. Damn thats some smooth shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a committed relationship you help each other out.. she helped him when he was down on his luck, I dont think its out of place for her to expect him to do the same if he can now afford to (and pay her back a bit tbh)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:05:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesnt matter to me if hes there or not - you paid for him for six months. He owes you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 11:00:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This might get downvoted, but get her a vibrator, and then play with it together. I didnt even realise I could have orgasms until I bought one - and now I know exactly what makes me orgasm. My boyfriend knows how to make it happen too - and its since been easier to orgasm without the vibrator as we both know where there stimulation needs to be. I have a tendency to squirt during sex, so a few of my exes thought that meant I had an orgasm, when in fact I didnt even feel it happening. Vibrators dont have to take away from your sex life - they can add to it if used right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 10:43:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Resilience, integrity, patience, compassion, understanding, curiosity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 10:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This actually looks filling and yummy - well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 10:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive never been on the receiving end of creepy messages from female (I am also female), but there sure are a lot of creepy dudes out there. Would be interesting to hear from guys though, if they have received messages like this from women   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 00:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow okay, this is where I leave you. Hats off to anyone who can calmly continue this discussion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 00:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you should read the comments again, as you are misunderstanding the whole whites have been the most cruel race thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 00:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mother passed away last night, and Im too heartbroken to go to school
*Let it goooo let it goooo* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 00:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then tell her straight up that you just wanna hang out and see what it feels like - if you feel just like friends or if there might be a potential for more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 23:59:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive had fwb turn into a relationship twice. Although we didnt cheat, our past as fwb was never an issue. Maybe you were holding on to each other for this long because you always loved one another, and your time has finally come? 

Basically what Im trying to say is you dont know if you dont try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 23:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah Im sorry to hear that.. I honestly hope you guys get to see where the relationship will go somehow. The boyfriend I had I was with for three years (the parent thing happened right at the beginning of the relationship), and although it didnt last I would not change the experience for the world. If we were forced to stay away from each other I dont think I would have been able to fully move on from it either. Honestly, Im rooting for you guys. Parents dont always know whats best even though they think they do and act out of a place of love and protection for their child. Im really sorry this is happening to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 21:59:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had something similar happen as a teenager, but it was my parents refusing to let me see my boyfriend. Luckily they did come around. However, at first I was only allowed to see him if he came to visit me - and with the curtains to my room open (my bedroom was in the basement). Slowly but surely they started letting go of control again.. dont know if this lady is like that, or if shell stand firm. Maybe you could suggest for all of you (both sets of parents + you and bf) to sit down and have a chat about things?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 21:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it a collar and attach a note to the collar :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 21:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bernese mountain dogs are my favourite, Ive had two, and one of them I grew up with (the other arrived after my best childhood friend unfortunately passed)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 20:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really much of a gamer, but I have Nintendo wii (favourites Zelda: Twilight Princess, Super Mario Bros), the mini Super Nintendo (favourites: Yoshis Island and Kirby) and PS4 (favourite: Fortnite)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 20:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, for anyone whos pissed that I think this is way too little food to start the day with; low calorie does not automatically mean toddler-sized portions. And about asking if OP is okay - genuinely curious if there has been an eating disorder involved here, but hey - if you dont agree with it and you dont believe in breakfast is the most important meal of the day or try to have close to equally sized portions for your meals then thats your business. Doesnt mean I cant be on this sub or comment freely just because Im on a different opinion when it comes to breakfast? 

Also, for the person calling me stupid for not thinking this is healthy; my dad is stronger than yours  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 20:34:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know right?! I had a friend who did something similar to me, and I havent spoken to him since tbh.. he sent me a text to apologise and yeah nah.. I cant believe he thought the right time to make a move was when I was sleeping/trying to sleep! What the fuck.. ask me to hang out alone and watch a film or something and try to kiss me first - that way youll find out without pressuring the girl into an obviously uncomfortable situation.. even if the girl did end up sleeping with the dude shed probably be pissed at both him and herself the next day, and ta-daaa friendship and the potential for anything more ruined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 19:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uhm scuse me but Its what women do???? Think you meant to say its what some people do/it happens all the time/everyone at one point of another, regardless of gender, experience this in one way or another or something along those lines. Pretty damn sure women didnt evolve on this planet to cheat on men, and pretty sure women arent the only gender who cheats. Some people cheat. Cheaters cheat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 19:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you kidding me.. Im sorry, but that is not even enough food for a toddler. Are you okay?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 19:21:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ed Sheeran ft Rammstein  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 19:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm that could possibly be a thing? Haha yeah at the coffee shop I worked at we had the same customers every day as it was in an office building, so got to know peoples habits quite well.. but also picked up on what time NOT to go to the toilet, as there would always be a queue twice a day at around the exact same times (most people had coffee twice a day - morning and after lunch)  so yeah, I basically know of quite a few peoples toilet habits!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 19:00:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At this point I dont even really try anymore unless Im really tired, and then it varies.. but experimented quite a bit when working at the coffee shop, and nothing would really sit well unless just one small cup, and that I had food in my belly to soak it up a bit.. I have one of those dolce gusto machines at home, and mostly use it for hot chocolate on cold days, but have found that the coffee pods for that seem a lot weaker than normal, so I can actually have a couple of those in a day without feeling shitty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 18:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with the above comments. It is possible that you still feel that love for your ex because she brought you joy while you were in a dark place. Going back there wont work out either way, youre not compatible and literally want completely different lifestyles. Neither of you should have to give that up. The new girl seems to have potential though. Id just say, dont rush into it before youre ready and have let the ex go completely. You dont want to fuck up something that could be great by still being hung up on your ex. Let her know you care about her, but are not ready for a new relationship yet. Hang out with her without the pressure of trying to form a relationship, and see if one forms naturally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 18:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to use athletic wear in such cases, as its usually comfy, gives me enough stretch to move, and actually makes me feel productive and energetic. Slightly athletic dresses too, such as dresses made out of sweater fabric (sweater dresses?) with a tie string in the waist. Those, and t-shirts and dungarees, are my go-to clothes for days where Im just hanging around the house doing things or popping out to run errands etc. If Im just staying in at night itll be pyjamas though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 17:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? I would feel ill immediately, and spend the next few hours in the bathroom (tmi- yes, I know).. did you have to build up a tolerance for it? Or were you just born with magical powers? I worked in a coffee shop for over a year while studying, and have never been able to have more than one small cup a day or any coffee on an empty stomach without being seriously uncomfortable in a bathroom for a while afterwards  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 17:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ailyn Marina! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 17:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe just give her a bit of space, and then straight up ask her. She could be feeling rejected, as she tried to get flirty and relationshipy with you and you called her out on it and basically made her stop.. or she could be moved on. Its hard to tell unless she talks to you, and if she doesnt want to do that right now you might as well try to focus on other things for a little while and then ask her what happened after shes had some time to digest it all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 17:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please let us know the outcome of the study </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 17:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honest to god I would have reported the shit out of this woman. Like, called the fucking police if I had to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 17:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excuse me, but as a female, if one of my friends tried that move on me I would be super uncomfortable, and quite frankly pissed. Even if I liked the guy as more than a friend. How about you kiss her in a normal setting first, instead of trying to sleep with her without having any clues if she actually wants to? Dont ask to stay at her house, invite her over to yours for a move night or something. Dont do the night time creeper, be the normal-time sweeper (as in sweep her off her feet.. yeah that was bad)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 16:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbh that was kind of funny  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 16:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Silas means of the forest/wood, so although it wouldnt tie in with the star/sky theme, it is nature based  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 16:27:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think the pasta and sausage is one meal? But otherwise I second these tips!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 16:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this happened to me I would be genuinely mortified. Honestly, try to tell him at least so that he understands why youre rejecting his advances and doesnt think theres other reasons for it. Just be gentle, say that you didnt really want to tell him as you didnt want him to feel embarrassed, that its kind of silly, but that you saw him pick his nose and eat it and that the mental image of it has burned itself into your brain just as hard as he sucked that bogey off his fingertower. He might laugh, he might be super embarrassed, but at least he wont feel like youre suddenly rejecting him and dont understand why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 15:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just want to throw into the mix here that he is not obligated to share all his thoughts and feelings with you. You say you just want him to be honest with you and himself, well maybe hes not ready for that. Dont push him into something hes not comfortable with just because it would make you feel better. He should get to decide if this is something he wants to share with you or not, and if there even is anything to share. You may be in a relationship, but he is still his own person and is entitled to some privacy. Checking his messages as youve been burned before is one thing (although still crossing a hard line for me), but why did you even check is browser history? And why do you think youre entitled to know something about him that he has not chosen to share with you? You forcing yourself into his innermost private thoughts and potentially confusion is really not okay, and would certainly not make the situation any better for him. So maybe, if you believe there is something he might be trying to figure out, think about him for a second and not yourself. After all that is what were supposed to do for the people we love, no? (Sorry it might be a bit harsh, but thought you needed some tough love here)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 15:37:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah okay. I can now think of a couple, but theyre not very good, and really are a bit of a stretch for kids. Im sorry she made you feel bad though, and tried to embarrass and humiliate you. Almost any word can be hurtful when said in the right way and context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 15:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand the caution, but at the same time, he let go as quickly as he had grabbed her, and looked completely shocked himself. OP did well staying away from him and leaving the second she got the chance, but I believe theres something to work with here. As long as it is made perfectly clear (and underlined for extra measure) that this is to never ever happen again, they both get some therapy, and he accepts any other terms she might have, there is a good chance this would not happen again. For all we know hes already scarred for life himself, heartbroken that he did something so horrible, and already have severed the cord in his brain that made his body move without the rest of his brain realising. Maybe in future arguments he will be the one to walk away before it escalates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 14:58:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would honestly have loved it (although sorrowfully) if I received a letter like this after a break-up. I dont think its bad that you give this to her at all - especially since she already gave you a letter first. Youve clarified in the comments that friendship will not happen right away (that she had estimated months herself), so I genuinely see no issues with this at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 14:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel you. Being around someone who is constantly bringing your mood down (even though its not on purpose) gets very tiring, even though you care about them and want to help them feel more positive. In my experience just trying to keep yourself as positive as possible and trying to share that positivity whenever its natural (not in a my dad died at least he wont be telling you you cant visit me anymore! kinda way) is really all you can do. People who are stuck in that rut often cant get out because the feeling never stops/they get addicted to it and bring the feeling out on purpose because its familiar or something (probably many more reasons), but they will not be able to change the way they think unless they make an effort to do so themselves. A friend of mine was like this, and ended up becoming very passive about his life - then spewed out waterfalls of negativity because nothing good was happening to him. He did eventually end up taking more charge of his life and go seek out what he wanted instead of just riding the wave, and is a much more positive person now than what he was then. 

I dont know what to tell you, other than try to stay positive and share that positivity, and that I understand that it is exhausting - and that this does not mean you dont love or care about her. 
Good luck, man!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 14:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would honestly be pretty damn happy about it. Im not much of a cuddler anyway, and wake up as soon as even a toe touches my toe. My SO and I share a bed, and I wake up multiple times every night. Its not a problem, I fall asleep again quickly, but if they needed a bedroom to themselves and I got one for myself, Id be more than okay with that. It also gives you your own space to disappear into if you need to just clock out for a bit - and all the space in the bed!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 14:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Breathe. Just fucking breathe. Youll be fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 14:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stella Dawn Lake
Luna Julie Lake 

I would potentially make it Juliet instead of Julie

Luna Juliet Lake  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 14:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Georgia Julie is another mouthful imo. Georgia Dawn works better for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 13:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now Im super curious about how your childhood frienemy rhymed Abigail to something awful.. Ive never thought of that name to be one you can easily rhyme like that? I do get the Cooper thing, although I wouldnt really worry about it too much if it was me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 13:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a 25 year old serial monogamist. Have barely been single since 14. First a 3 year relationship, then a 2 year one, a 1 year long relationship, before the current one where my SO and I have passed 3,5 years together. Im just not happy living the single life, and prefer to be in a relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 12:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same! Especially Captain America. I understand the sentiment of wanting to think a superhero is looking out for soldiers during a war, but he is still a damn poor superhero.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 12:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First guy I met up with from tinder. Weve been together 3,5 years now, and live together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 12:43:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> McDonalds about once every two-three months. KFC too, at about the same intervals  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 12:18:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In all honesty, if she has been cheating, and treating you badly over a period of time without making an effort to communicate with you what her actual problem with you is to try and find a solution - your relationship is no more. People are not things you use and throw away, and although you might feel at this point that youd be the one throwing her away - she already did it to you. I understand the family thing makes it more difficult for you, but sometimes even good things have to fall apart to make room for something amazing. So moving forward, alone, at least now you know you want someone who has a great relationship with their family, and who will invite you into that. Thats something! You deserve to be happy and not have to feel like youre walking on eggshells or that you are not worthy of someone who isnt even treating you right. Youll be okay. Itll be tough, but you will be okay, and youll even have the potential to be great, which at the moment it doesnt sound like you do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 12:01:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have very different associations with Vladimir and Vlad. Vladimir is Putin to me, but Vlad is a vampire. If I were to have a Vladimir (human or of fur) Vladimir would only be on paper, and Vlad (or as mentioned by someone else - Mir) would be used.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 11:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How can you handle that much caffeine on such little food? Coffee without breakfast in the morning would put me out immediately, and you had two cups! How are you still alive?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 11:30:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the name Malachi/Malaki. The Hebrew meaning is a bit cheesy; my angel/angel/messenger of God, but the name is gorgeous, and can easily be shortened to Kai. 

Kenai is also gorgeous, and means Black bear in Native American, hehe

Otherwise Cameron, Xavier, Koda (little bear), Gabriel, Samson (sun), Caleb, Ezra, Silas (of the forest/wood), Idris, Levi, Micah.. I dunno man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 09:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fish sauce isnt veggie though, but everything else sounds great! Might have a go at this myself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 22:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my gosh what a gorgeous kitty!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 20:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smoked salmon, poached egg and hollandaise is my favourite breakfast combo - especially with asparagus as a side. English muffin, bagel, sandwich - Ill take all, please  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 20:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah everything thats supposed to be eaten together can touch - but nothing else! Buffets where people put dinner food and dessert food on the same plate make me super uncomfortable, what if the dinner touches the cake??? What are you, a madman?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 20:02:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haaah that made me giggle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 10:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, but we dont need to borrow clothes as often now, as we have our own right there ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 23:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriend and I are the exact same hight and the same size in clothes  was great for straight-from-work sleepovers before we moved in together  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 23:29:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah man Viet Food in Soho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 23:28:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I might be basic, but Im quite pleased with Las Iguanas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 23:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah you didnt rape her, but your actions sure were rapey. Better keep yourself in check dude, thats not cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 23:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *food quirk panic intensifies* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 22:59:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not Dekshit for obvious reasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 22:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bor i England og har britisk SO, han sier college. Kan vre dette er slang, men slik jeg har forsttt det er da high school (US) og college (UK) det samme. Det blir s college (US) og uni/University (UK).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 22:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Team Coralie! Rosalie is too feminine for me. Cori works both for a tomboy and more feminine character, Rosalie can easily become ironic if say going through a goth phase  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 22:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So America? Hehe.. was just thinking about name origins  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 21:59:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im panicking that your cherries are touching the runny egg yolk. Everything looks delicious, but I dont like my cherries with egg on them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 21:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are you from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 21:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tenker ikke  si s veldig mye om denne saken, men har en kompis som vknet etter en natt med festing med hodet i fanget p en like blacka-ut Trond Giske. Helt rlig tenker jeg at de aller fleste har vrt litt for pgende i fylla en eller annen gang, men at han er i en maktposisjon over unge AUF-jenter gjr dessverre saken ganske mye mer seris.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 20:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Norwegian living in England, dont follow any other forums. Native language Norwegian.

Top five is difficult but heres my current 0.02$:

1 Tora
2 Ada
3 Freya/Frya 
4 Selma
5 Nimh 

1 Silas
2 Koa 
3 Jonah
4 Falk
5 Bodhi

So yeah, a good mix of origins here (and my list is definitely longer), but these are the ones I can think of right now that I really like. I have a thing for short names, hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-02 19:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surveillancevan003, GEWTOFFMAHLAN  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reddit, which current bands/artists are amazing live? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-01 21:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-01 20:07:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anything where someone does or could get hurt. Pranks, people falling/crashing into things, mean jokes aimed at a person or a group of people (racist, sexist, homophobic jokes etc).. Tastefully made dark jokes are great, but know your audience for those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-31 01:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks yummy and pretty but I would definitely eat that x2 or 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 22:54:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont like mayo, so I use creme fraiche. I either mix in spring onions and sweet corn, or red onion and sweetcorn. Salt, pepper.. if youre feeling a bit adventurous pop some soy sauce or curry powder in (only a little bit of the curry powder). Have with pasta (mix it all together) or on a sandwich. Rocket is also great with it, salad leaves if you want something milder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 22:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pasta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 22:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Understanding. When someone fucks up and most people would be angry (and I should be too), I automatically focus on understanding the intentions behind the action(s) or what lead to the action(s) being taken. Im thus also very good at forgiving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 22:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Discrimination and/or bullying. Just dont fucking be a dick, its really that simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 18:04:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will actively avoid people who look (or speak) hood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 17:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres no guarantee for snow in the winter

We are uncomfortably close to bringing our wolf population to extinction

Although we are well known for being nature lovers, we choose money over preserving nature quite often

We so concerned about staying friends with the big guys that we sometimes back them over whats right (we are not as innocent as the stereotype goes)

Guess the country!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 10:50:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Malibu and orange juice, or pineapple juice if preferred  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 10:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was planning to take my boyfriend at the time camping to get to know him more. My ex was very happy to go, and was looking forward to it. Then I overhear my friend saying to another guy who was also coming that they should bring acid and weed and that my ex wouldnt have a choice but to join in. My ex was from another country, and would have no idea how to get back to mine from the camp site - or even know where he was. He had also never done drugs in his life. Fuck that guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-28 22:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wholeheartedly agree with all of the above. Fuck people like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-28 22:52:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, Im not sure. No one remembers where it came from as it started when I was really young. Im assuming it was just something tiny that turned into a slightly psychotic phobia over the years. However, at this point in my life, I can proudly say I have touched a ketchup bottle as I have picked it up and handed it to my boyfriend. Ah the things we do for the ones we love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-28 22:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ate my first ever piece of tomato this year *bowing for the crowd*, but have always enjoyed tomato based meals such as spaghetti bolognese, bacalao etc.. No one remembers where the ketchup thing came from, and generally I have always eaten just about anything (lots of shit that kids normally hate). I do have a few other weird food based quirks, but most of them I know where came from and are not as bad as the ketchup thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-28 22:23:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats actually a thing that bugs me - no one remembers. It started when I was so young I cant remember it, and my parents have no clue either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 23:53:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I shower with my glasses on the reg because Im a rebel and I dont live by my conscious brains rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 23:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this multiple times a day. The thing Im repeating also very rarely has anything to do with the sentence I was actually trying to string together. Guess its a new thought that pops into my head and distracts my subconscious and in my subconscious confusion I just start repeating it over and over  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 23:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Badum-tssss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 23:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Milk in the bin, banana peel in the fridge

Also, one Apple each way; a core in my handbag and a brand new phone in the public bin that was collected before I realised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 22:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my gosh it has a name, thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 22:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay so this might be a bit long, so doing the TLDR first:

Best friend got new gf to beat ex-gf to make her lose baby. Weirdly not the reason we broke contact.

So my best friend of many years is quite a special guy. One of those who can smooth talk until the sun goes down, and by being super protective makes his female friends weirdly dependent on him. Its hard to describe. 

After his first (and only) serious relationship broke down after they had a kid waaaaay too young, he drifted from one girl to another for years, never really caring about them. Also managed to sleep with many of his female friends (weird magical powers), but thats another thing. So he starts sleeping with this one girl, lets call her A. A has two kids, and has recently split with baby daddy. Hes using her for sex, she falls for him. He then breaks it off when hes done with her, but she wont let him go, calls constantly and is being a pain in the jackass ass. She then tells him shes pregnant, and sends him a scan... douche freaks out. No way is he having another kid, he already has one he didnt want (has loved her since birth though), and is definitely not cool with having another one - especially with this chickadee. He flips shit, and convinces another girl whos head over heels for the douchmaster that if she helps him with his problem they can be together. 

They hash out a plan; hes calling girl A to meet up, to try and convince her to have an abortion one last time. New girl (lets call her B) is hiding around the corner (they were on the grounds of a school sometime during the late evening), waiting for her cue. Cue is when he puts on his headphones and walks away. B jumps out, attacks A and kicks her in the stomach multiple times to fix the problem of.. the man of her dreams *cough*. Douche suddenly feels bad, turns around and stops it, calls police himself while B runs. Douche waits with A for police, B is picked up in the city centre on their way to the police station. 

B is a minor, gets a slap on the wrist. Douche goes to prison, befriends drug-dealing commercial diver, and goes straight off to commercial diving school or whatever its called when he gets out. Starts diving, and selling (and doing) drugs. Dates B for a good year or so after (man of his word?). 

Plot twist: A was never pregnant, she sent him a scan from when she was preggo with one of the kids she already had. 

Obviously I didnt see this happen, but was informed the morning after, and he told me himself as soon as he got out. Oddly not the reason I stopped having contact with him, but easily one of the most fucked up things hes done. 

Didnt know B very well, but from an outsiders perspective (with mutual friends) it didnt look like her life changed even in the slightest, and both she and her new bf Mr Douche were welcomed right back into her friend group no questions asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 21:49:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude. You witnessed a murder and you didnt say anything???? And still havent????? You better get your ass down to a police station ASAP, her family fucking deserves to know - and so does anyone who ever comes into contact with him again. What. The. Actual. Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 21:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta know your audience for those kinds of jokes you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 21:25:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really feel for him, I have the same thing with ketchup. Literally can not deal with it, and if anyone comes near me with it I wont even try to fight them out of fear I might touch it, but I will walk/run away depending on the situation. Also if anyone threw ketchup at me I would honestly never speak to them again. Its fine that other people find it ridiculous, but that doesnt mean its not very real for the person it happens to, and mocking that person by threatening them with their phobia is straight up disrespectful and horrible. Id rather be locked in a casket full of snakes/rats/spiders/whatever than have anything to do with ketchup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 19:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes I get a really sharp pain in my boob/chest area.. its like theres a needle in there, or Ive just been struck with a long, thin, sharp object without it touching the skin.. sometimes I get confused and a little concerned its in my heart and not my boob as I cant remember having that feeling on my right side, only the left. 

Also got restless leg syndrome, which is a pain in (below) the ass to try to fall asleep with  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 19:00:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hei is how you'd say and write "hi/hey" in Norwegian, and it's quite common for people to say it twice, like "hey hey! ". Kind of cute when you think about where she's come from, it was time life gave her a new hello :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 18:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ow my heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 17:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That last sentence with the picture hit me right in the giggle dick. She is gorgeous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nature based names please! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 19:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has anyone got any great suggestions for nature based names? The last name will fit with nearly everything, and any origin is perfectly fine (we are a mix of Vietnamese/Norwegian/British). Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 19:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got a sister called Kaja (pronounced Kaya - she's Norwegian). It really is a lovely name!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 19:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about Amaiya, Maya, Mika or Amira? :) I especially love Amaiya (heartbroken I can't use it as it's my niece's name)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 19:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like it for a girl. Have a niece named Mika, so Luca isn't too far off. You get used to it quickly :) also it's become more and more popular to use male names for females (think Blake Lively and her daughter James for example). It won't take more than hearing it twice before the mental picture of your little girl sticks to it :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did you order? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-27 17:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Commenting on this as I'm on their website ready to order right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Samuel Davis and James Perry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tora (Torbergsdatter), queen of Norway and later queen of Denmark. She lived a most fascinating life, and although her first husband is not remembered as the most kind hearted person, she definitely is. And she was strong as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would do Cornelia instead of Cordelia. Favourite from op's list; Cleo. The rest I think are too "princessy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-02 19:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would't pick fn and mn with the same ending (like Logan Ryan), but that's just my personal preference. I also think Jameson is a last name (it literally means James' son), but I love the little lion reasoning (inside joke; is it lion king?) for Ari. Ari Logan would probably be my pick from the names on the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tora was the name of one of the first queens of Norway. She grew up as the daughter of one of the king's first men, that king being the one who "made Norway a whole country". Tora later married the king's son, and took the throne with him. Viking queen! Awesome name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 18:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Scandinavia it's "Sren or Sren",  and the / sound is basically the same as the ea in the word learn. Also we do rolling r's.. but ya know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-01 01:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm Norwegian, and if I was a boy my parents were gonna name me Fabian. When they found out I was I girl, they originally wanted Martine (Mar-tee-neh), but that name was really peaking at the time. They ended up calling me Regine (Reg-ee-neh; hard d, pressure on the ee), which is very uncommon. Apparently it was common about a hundred years before my time, both as Regine and as Regina, the latter being the most common version. My mum thought it was too 'pretty' with the a at the end, and wanted it to be a bit more tomboy-ish. I agree with that. To this day I have only met two other girls with Regine as their first name (I met one with it as a middle name, Lone Regine (Lo-neh Reg-ee-neh), and the parents of one of them actually got the idea from me and asked my parents if it was okay for them to use it. She also happens to be born on the same date as me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think there's anything wrong with it at all, and actually like Ezra more for a girl than a boy. I would probably go with Reigh or Raine as a mn, but that's just me. Boy's names for girls are becoming increasingly popular, and I personally think this is a good thing, as it also helps create more acceptance in terms of gender issues (what I mean by that is that 1: the child is more free to identify with whichever gender they want and 2: other people will be more open to the fact that some people don't have an obvious gender). Obviously it'll easily be portrayed by clothes, hair etc, but I actually really like blurring the lines a little bit. Take for example Blake Lively. She has a "boy's name" herself, and also named her daughter James. I probably wouldn't have used James for a girl, but Blake and Ezra I would see as unisex. Lovely names.
Edit: Punctuation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister is called Kaja, pronounced kay-a.. (We're Norwegian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My so's niece is called Amaya, I think it's absolutely beautiful! Her nn is Mai Mai, which is adorable too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cassius and Hudson both sound fine to me, but Cash? I would die before anyone called my child "Cash".. "Got any cash, Cash?" "You gonna be a rapper, Cash?" "Cash Money my man!" Sounds like an absolutely terrible nickname for a teenager who thinks he's a gangster and runs around selling drugs for... you guessed it; cash.

Edit: I would also pronounce it CASS-ee-us. Not Cashus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Elenora!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree! and I think calling him Link would be the cutest thing.. If anything I think people would rather think of the game character, which is all positive in that case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:29:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good books, a musical instrument (preferably piano for me), and something that will make me laugh.. I almost cried when I came into a guy's home and saw that he had a south park style Darth Vader plush toy displayed on his bookshelf for the world to see. Absolutely loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:24:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was a film about Tweety travelling around the world.. I can't find it anywhere, there's literally nothing on google or anything, so I can't even find out what the film was called in English.. All I know is that it was called "Jorden rundt med Pip" in Norwegian, and I freaking loved that film.. I still say "ARRRRGHENTINA" instead of Argentina because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm very concerned about my future. I'm in uni atm, and I'm terrified of not getting a good job, not being able to have kids, not passing my exams, not having enough money to buy my own house, take care of my kids (I'm staying hopeful) or do the things I want to do. I'm basically terrified of not being happy with my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 18:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking Katie Hopkins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 18:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chuck Bass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 16:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfect childhood, rough teenage years. Coming out of it now, learning to be independent alone in a new country at 22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Learn how to play the piano, become fluent in a third language, dive with sharks, swim with whales, have children, travel the world, do something so spontaneous and big that I get that "I could die right now and not be mad" feeling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I put all my housemate's dirty dishes either in her bed, or stack them up on the dining table with a very visible peace of paper with her name on it for everyone to see. Shame and disgust all the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My inability to be alone over longer periods of time. I always look for comfort from others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this, and also bring books/magazines, psp etc.. bring headphones. Don't drink too much alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 15:05:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gabriel Iglesias, Jimmy Carr, Lee Evans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:28:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marley in Marley and me, The little prince (what a fucking sad story), and the owner of Hachiko in the film with the same name. The fact that it's based on a legend, and also has a statue of the dog by the train station just makes it worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gift means both poison and married in Norwegian.. *awkward silence*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BANANAHAMMOCK!!!!! *screams in terror* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 02:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretend you don't speak the language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 01:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you've had explosive diarrhoea all day and can't eat anything as it just shoots out the other side like the last bit of an empty, shaken ketchup bottle, so you down 5 pints of chocolate milk. The feeling of that chocolate milk, man.. It's pretty fucking fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-27 00:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do your research. Find out what they like, what they like to talk about etc, and find something you can either read up on or you know something about from before to use for bonding. Bring a small gift as a thank you for staying. Do they like wine? Then buy them a bottle of wine, maybe from the area you're from? Let them get to know you on terms that work for everyone. Are they private people? Then don't share too much private information. Just get your boyfriend to tell you as much as possible about them, write things down if you have to. I'd like to have prepared some icebreakers and points of bonding before going if I was in your situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 23:13:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're 26 and have Ask.fm?? I thought that was a 13-15-year-old thing.. Damn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:08:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so awesome! I did the same thing two years ago (well, I moved to London from Norway), and I've never regretted my choice. I had just turned 20, and was in a relationship where I felt 50. I couldn't handle it, and brought it up multiple times to my boyfriend, whom I shared an apartment with. After a year of no change, where he had gone out to look for engagement rings even though he knew how unhappy I was (!!!!), I ended it, moved out on the day, and a couple of months later I was on a plane to London, without knowing anyone there. I have loved every minute of it (yes, I did get lonely and homesick at times, but there were a lot of distractions), and don't plan on moving back any time soon. It's such a great feeling, making a huge life change in the direction you want to, without help from others, and being able to live your life exactly how you want to without having others critique you for it constantly. That freedom - I'm not sure I'll ever be willing to give it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 48 hours since your first date, and you're already calling him your bf? damn. I think you should calm down, you're gonna end up scaring him off by coming across as desperate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:10:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you have kids together? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> may I ask where his parents live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 00:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> try being high up north in the winter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 14:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well, we have parachutes now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 23:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bring the girl to the event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 23:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hear, hear!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 23:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cut the poor guy loose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much!!! I think it's the latter, that he doesn't know what he wants from me really. I think the whole situation is confusing him a bit, and that it overwhelms him from time to time, and that he needs me to give him more ground to stand on so to speak. I'll try to come up with a few changes I can make and some ways to make him feel more loved and appreciated for the next month, and see if it makes any difference. Thank you so so much for the advice!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to be this girl. Most likely she has some sort of emotional trauma (I don't know her personally, but as I used to be like this I'm just throwing my experiences out there), and she is scared of being alone, which is why she's stringing along her male friends (they probably know she's seeing someone, but I'm betting she still acts flirty towards them to give them hope that maybe in the future something could happen). If you want commitment from her, you need to take charge and tell her straight forward what you expect and need of her, and tell her that if that's too much for her then you can't stay in the relationship. If she freaks out - stand your ground. She's pushing you around and testing your limits, she's trying to twist a relationship that is supposed to be equal into her benefit, because she needs support and flirting with guys is the easiest and quickest way to get it. Stand your ground, and she will either adapt to make you stay or run to one of her back-ups. If she runs, you dodged a bullet. Good for you, Keanu.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I basically did the same with my now bf. We just went with the flow (we were both scared because of past experiences and also the situation we are in now with me being an international student), and it took us six months to label ourselves as bf/gf. My advice would be to not stress about it, just relax and enjoy the ride, and if it comes to a point where it's been about a year and you're still introducing him as "the guy I'm seeing", then I'd have a conversation about it. It took us 6 months, but then it naturally came up in a conversation with friends (as in "yeah, but she's your girlfriend dude, she has to say you look good" and "yeah I guess she is" and then we had a little teenage giggle about it and that was it). If you ask for too much before he's ready to give it to you, you might scare him off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 22:01:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes sense. I have had this conversation with him a few times though, and he keeps saying he needs to see it in my actions, but when I ask him which kinds of actions he wants or in which way, he just says I should know. I feel like he might want some kind of grand gesture from me to show him how much I love him, but I'm not the grand gesture type of person. I'm up for doing anything I can, I just can't think of anything to do, and I'm also concerned that if I do put my heart so far out on the line then I won't be able to handle it in my usual calm manner if he realises it wasn't enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand where you're coming from, but I'm not just gonna act normal and see what happens. Obviously his trust issues comes from something, and he's not confident that I actually only want to be with him, and that is something I can most likely change. I don't mind working for what I want, and even though normally in a relationship you don't start "working" for it after only six months, but because of our situation I completely understand that this is something new and scary to him. He is 100% worth the work, and so is our relationship, so even though I see your point, I'm choosing to show him that I care about him and that I want this, instead of just being like "it's your problem, so if you can't let it go by yourself you can leave." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It might work to make it more structured, as in planned skype/phone sessions. The only thing I'm worried about then is the fact that he's quite emotional while I'm practical, so when something's bothering him he needs to get it out right away, while I'm more calm and either just let it go without talking to him, or calmly mention it whenever the time feels right. So structuring it might also put him off, and make him think I don't have time to comfort him (which between work and family gatherings when I'm home, I actually don't, but I make time by almost neglecting friends and family a bit and not sleep much), which could make him trust me less. I already try to FaceTime often so he can see my face and hear my voice. I'll reflect on the scheduled skype dates a bit more, but it could go either way. Thanks anyways! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was more of a casual thing, we were drinking with my flatmates and we all started sharing experiences (this was before anything serious happened between the two of us, it was really more of a friendship with some flirting at the time), and he shared some of his too. He is definitely no saint himself, but I think he was taken aback by my casualness towards the topic more than anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happens to me and my bf too. We've actually resorted to a drink limit for now, and hope that time will change it, as we're still a fairly "fresh" couple. Hopefully after enough positive experiences and us getting more confident in the relationship, we can take away the drink limit and be more relaxed and more of a "we'll talk about it tomorrow"-type couple than a "THIS SHIT'S GOING DOWN RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW"-type.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you actively tried interacting and building a bond with the dog? One of my exes had a massive rottweiler (I grew up with big dogs, but this one was huge!) who I didn't particularly like, as I thought she was too rough and explosive and didn't have clear enough rules. I took her for walks without my ex and started trying to get to know her, and let her know me and my rules, and slowly but surely she started behaving better around me, even though she still knew she was allowed to do whatever she wanted with him. I found out she loved boiled eggs, that she loved to play hide and seek, she is too shy to poop in front of people and hides in bushes with only her nose sticking out when she does her business (makes it close to impossible to pick up after her sometimes), and that under that massive formerly unpredictable body was a great friend. She still had those explosive traits around my bf, as he loved play fighting with her etc, but she also learned that I have my own set of rules, and that bonding with me in my way wasn't so bad either. (Yes, I showed my bf everything and he knew what I was doing, but he saw their relationship as "fun" while I saw it as a little bit scary. Big dog with big jaws play biting my arm without me having raised the dog myself was a bit too much for me)    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> see her a few times when she's back and see if the feelings come back. You don't wanna dump her now and then regret it when you bump into her next. This may be your only shot, and you liked her for a reason (or multiple), so there's a big chance the feelings will reoccur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 17:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much, that makes a lot of sense. I have told him similar things, like how I have no sexual drive when I am away from him (which is true, I always bring a travel vibrator but only use it maybe once in three weeks and only while sexting him), but maybe I should try what you suggest, as the "temptation" he's thinking about might not just be about sex, but also flirting etc.. Again, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The separation is new to him, as he's only been with girls who lived close by before.. I think it's something he would get used to over time, but with summer coming up we're running out of just that - time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-19 21:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a cheeky joke works :) and maybe something that makes you different from other guys. Maybe you once climbed a tree and left your boxers as a majestic flag on top? Or maybe you have a dog called Cat. Or live on a houseboat.. or think that life is too short for girls to spend 30 minutes getting ready while the guy is waiting downstairs ready to go. Or maybe your grandmother used to throw apples at soldiers during the war. Or maybe your favourite food is marmite on toast- You get my point. Make yourself special and memorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 18:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My SO got a picture off of my laptop of my mum and my horse that I often look at when I feel homesick (I'm an international student), added my favourite poem (which goes quite well with the picture) and got it blown up on a big canvas to hang in my room. So incredibly sweet, and really shows that he cares about the small things and that he actually listens. I bawled my eyes out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 18:30:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have insurance that covers absolutely everything.. So basically just pictures, maybe some clothes for the next few days. Letters, notes.. my favourite jacket. Maybe some of my jewellery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-02 18:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a parent, but worked in nursery. Bracelets in different colours! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-01 22:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When it's clean it's the same as kissing any other part of his body, it's just skin. Don't know how it is with hairy guys, but when shaved it doesn't smell much either. Then precum comes out, and it's just a bit salty, but doesn't really have a flavour to it. I kinda like thinking of it as cuddling my number 2 man hehe.. I wouldn't do it unless I was monogamous with someone, as I would want to know what bacteria I put in my mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 21:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edam is great for toasties! Babybell or Norwegian or Danish Grddost are great with crackers and fruit, so is Philadelphia. Norwegian "brunost" (brown cheese) tastes almost like caramel, and is great on warm waffles with a little bit of jam on top!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-28 21:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're at uni then become part of societies you are interested in, it's a great way to meet people with the same interests as you! Go to the library and do your work there, and start conversations while waiting for the copy machine or in line to buy a cup of coffee or whatever. Ask them what they study, remember their names and ask them if they're going to a uni event that's coming up or something. Maybe you could even predrink together? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>