<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1167</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 03:28:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats news to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 01:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really didnt and you kept saying only forced anal intrusion was rape which is clearly wrong and weird. As if vaginal rape isnt rape? But I digress I have homework to do and people to see. So uh bye Bye, and next time maybe educate yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 01:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats a sociopath. I dont know what to tell you. Nor do I care in all honesty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 00:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh not really. Thats all fake. I care about my karma. People just usually respond better when they think Im sweet and docile. Guess I over did it this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 00:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm oh I gave up. I remembered the effect ( cant quite remember what its called) where people who are presented with new facts opposing what they thought was true they dont usually actually change their minds. They just double down on whatever their believe. Its actually why religions like jahovas witnesses send their children door to door. It isnt to spread the faith. They know the kids will be rejected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 00:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh ok. I didnt realize any of that was bad Im really sorry Ill delete it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 23:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh well thats weird. He said yes, and to put them everywhere. It was a bunch of sources </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 22:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 21:48:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude its in the rules. Men arent even allowed in that sub. Thats sexist if Ive ever seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 21:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/emojipolice calm down sir just a ticket. Five Hail Marys and youll be good to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 21:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Atm bad. Still bad. But more my normal bad and not toss my self out a window and land head first bad. Kinda wanna stab someone but thatll go away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 21:28:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you read the post? Well I guess you mustve despite the question. Well my dear stranger Im bad. Im a little better than I was earlier but Im still bad. Empty and hateful. Almost a whole human (minus the emotions). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 21:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean.... she is a little rich white girl. That is a pure statement of fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better is a relative term. Better than 5 is 6 but better than 0 is 1 so I guess you could say that I am doing better in the way that I will in fact not jump out a window. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My fingers are slipping and Im gonna fall man Im just choosing to fall faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh well hey. So you snooped on my post history that nice. Thanks for the info on melatonin. maybe if I take enough I could just sleep through next week? And as for it wont help nothing does. As for school well school is a living nightmare and probably where Ill be sent in hell. As for dogs with jobs that joy is fleeting and temporary as well as doing nothing to ease my cold dead heart. Im just done I have no energy left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:30:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well hi. Stranger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:23:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No prob go live your best life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. No
2. Occasionally but its harder for me than others
2. No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Was it just me? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:04:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id be fucking partying like yes FUCKING FINALLY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 19:01:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah Im just..... Im just tired. Im just done. Life has thrown everything it can at me and it won. The scars on my mind will never heal and Im just done . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cake is a lie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We dont want to hear the whole story because that usual ends in being the man is right. There fixed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont even know man.... te keep from opening and subsequently jumping out the window maybe. Oh wait never mind. Someone years ago must have beat me to it because I just saw that the windows at my school are sealed. So goodbye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im sorry and goodbye. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To all of you I bid a hearty goodbye. I cant stand it anymore. Im so tired tonight Im just going to go to sleep. Can melatonin pills be fatal? I sure hope so. Thanks for years of strength. Wish me well off this mortal coil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No prob bob. Go have some fun Im gonna go uh honestly idk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just keep trying. Were all waiting for you on the other side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No prob but were still gonna talk. I need to keep my hands busy anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I doubt youll use what I did because it isnt the healthiest but why not Ill do it anyway. Well you see I stopped giving two fucks. I shut down so hard I barely feel anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:37:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah Broski. I used to feel like just as much of a burden as you do, but then I realized. Why do I give a shit if I slow down their day a bit. Drop the knife close the window step off the ledge. Just take a moment. Breathe. Close your eyes and image where you would like to be at all times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure why not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:31:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Music helps me calm down. Lately the effectiveness is slipping though and I can feel my madness creeping in on the shattered prices of my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in class trying not to jump out the second story window behind me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 18:29:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey. Were gonna talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 15:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah..... maybe the public should stop giving that any attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 15:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah so this is just the first time, 2 women do this thing. Which is not important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 14:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah just sacrifice me already. Just come the fuck on super villain come here bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 14:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didnt an all female space walk happen already? It was only one but still. Why is this special? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 14:01:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No Im not giving up. I had to go to sleep because I have actual people things to do, like school. You should go to one, it might really help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 06:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah see, case and point. This is why Im just gonna go have an intelligent conversation because this, this just isnt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 05:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the  women cant really rape men comment. What about the shit ton of marital rape where men just wake up with a chick riding them. Did they consent? No. Marital rape towards men actually happened more to men by the way. What about the celebrities who have come out saying they have drugged and raped men, and nothing happened about it. What about the men who are mentally and physically abused in a relationship into sex. ( relationship abuse actually happens more towards men as well). How about all that. How about women can really rape men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 05:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow ok. You know what, Im just gonna. Im just gonna go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 05:13:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nuh bad.*sprits sprits* bullets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just won a battle for my life </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 05:10:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 05:10:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just swat em all the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Triple e? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope Im a yee haw Boi. Still more humid than hell down here and weve got a fuck ton of the lil shits rn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:46:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Currently in a battle for my life </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:37:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spaghetti monsters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hes suck a great guy and actor. He should be put in a place almost with Keanu. Dont get me wrong not quite Keanu but almost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude come on. Thats the same logic as  dude you didnt get raped you got free sex! And  come on man youre lucky shes so hot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:27:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude just.... just no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never claimed to make dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Im sorry about those guys. I upvoted this and did my part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did my part I call Thor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That kids gonna do things. Maybe not great things, but things nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 03:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That third panel got me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 03:46:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No! Con ganas mijo. Kill it kill it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 00:55:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if instead of just harassing girls I harass everyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 00:44:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, logistically since gay people are the minority. She is not like other girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 23:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 22:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess your probably right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 22:08:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like it could still be  easily looked over. I mean when you see lights attached to whats going to look like nothing youre going to look over them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 22:07:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why cant the future be human dang dummy dumb dumbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 22:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about at night. Can they see the car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude rule nmero uno, Dont stick your dick in crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:52:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoever should be out there shouldnt be based on who has a dick or  not. I want the most qualified and over all best people up there representing us. Wether the have a sausage between their legs or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:50:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit fuck dude. Mind if I uh, borrow these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldnt go with all men. But certainly some. Although I dont feel guilty about doing anything to anyone. That may have more to do with my mental condition than my dick though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Queen! Queen!queeeeeen! We got her boys! We found the new queen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 17:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want choccy coffee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 17:52:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell yeah i wanna </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 16:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend like that and Ive found its best to come back at her with the same intensity if not more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 16:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah ok thanks Broski. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 05:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is her username? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 05:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the Cleavage of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 05:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mr. Stranger, since you seem so wise would you answer me one question. What do you do, when you dont feel sad. When you dont feel mad. When you dont feel happy or scared or anything. When you just feel cold. And tired. And you want it to end and you want to go to sleep and fade away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 05:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I havent found one yet. But lately Im thinking, maybe I should live to prove that I can. Do it for fun. Do it for all the people I have left to steal from and the money I have left to spend on booze and drugs. I will die at 40 in a comical pile of cocaine, and the best part is that my death wont be from the cocaine. I dont yet know where to get all that cocaine from. So I have to live until  I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 03:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like Im a mix. Because Im just a little ball of hatred for all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 07:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They took the picture made a couple books gave it to them. Took another picture. Put that on a book. And released it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im just so tired. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 07:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im just so drained. Im tired of it all and I want it to end. I want to sleep forever. Lay in my bed think sweet thoughts and drift off into the abyss. Is it so bad to just want it to be over? Is it so bad to just be done? Can I just.... can I just finally rest now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 06:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont get asked anything by anyone but my mother.y friends havent asked if I was ok in a while. Im used to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 06:10:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry I was going to have the sex and I used it to add an inch to my size. Then I had a whole two inches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 06:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My ass after Taco Bell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 06:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly this looks like a joke. I dont think this is serious I mean, use your cooter to stop a shooter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 05:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I know imma do great shit. I can feel it in my bones. Im either going to be the biggest fucking drug kingpin. Or the next Elon. I have no in between. One way or another I will be remembered. But either way imma die at like 40 in a comical pile of cocaine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 05:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luigi 
Got
Big 
Titties 
Queen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 05:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jokes on you I play in third person mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 04:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 18:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 18:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude. Whos joe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 17:01:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow that came way out of left field. Whats up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 08:19:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem I tried to get them to go upvote your stuff. But the mods wouldnt let me put upvote or go show him some love in the title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 06:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 06:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. It makes it easy to get away with shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 06:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh a girl. You know... satanic cults usually hold ritualistic orgies. But as the cult priest I have deemed that we can do it with just two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 03:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant rn give me a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 03:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I know. He used a bunch in that continue conversation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 02:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *in British accent* this explains so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 01:51:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Below average is still not average. you are different! Just a sucky different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 01:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh dip, Jason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 00:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> go bomb him in his dms. He used way more off screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 00:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I called they will come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Came across this sicko </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 00:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 00:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I guess that makes me satanist? Yeah that sounds right. Hail satan brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 00:49:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/emojipolice imma need some backup! This guy is a real menace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 00:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woah woah woah sir calm down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 22:26:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually Im pretty sure that one is acceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 22:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now now I was being nice dont make me call back up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 22:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like like when they cry. Im like uuuuuggggh. Can we skip this part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Third try is the charm. Can it please stay this time mods. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 22:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 22:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/emojipolice just a warning this time sir. Be safer next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 22:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if you change countries to continents its still not right. She forgot left Russia and right Russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 22:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was so confused then the bricks started spinning like someone gave em cocaine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 21:58:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This guy is going through a hard time. Please go on his profile and shower him with love. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 21:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 21:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean... look at what hes wearing. Hes wearing scrubs. Hes a nurse. So its either he gets to work and saves lives. Or whatever they were protesting for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Felt a spurt of wholesomeness coming and saw this. Go check out his account and upvote some of his shit. Hes going through a hard time. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 21:44:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 21:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah do I have to worry about any lies then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Innit tho. Im sorry for this tho but uh r/emojipolice actually you know what Ill let you off with a warning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:48:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You see the secret to happiness is not having a dick. If you got one chop it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What ails you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Im not falling for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tablets like pills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell ol dovakin your troubles friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey did you hear about that true story movie that got made? The one where strippers roofie rich guys and steal from them? And nothing happens to them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe we judged you too quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No more than a regular hot tub would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nuh uh. Fool me once shame on me, fool me twice shame on you, fool me three times and I just want some fucking nudes Broski. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope I see those comments. I know whats going on here. You put the finger circle as your picture didnt you? You sly dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww shucks. You know how to make a guy blush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell yeah you can. Your so amazing you deserve waaaay more compliments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So hour parents were right? Thats about as far from hot you can be without being named Karen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just... eh... just stop. That joke was just.... AMAZING I love you have a nice day internet stranger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 18:43:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 18:40:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want whoever made you to delete you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 18:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, Im fourteen so sometimes me and my friends will get dropped off at the movies but at four?! Jesus Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 18:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes children included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 18:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey u/sad-giraffe why u so sad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An interesting title </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 18:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 18:09:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If its fun do it. By all means that by one knows Im an exemplary kid. No one ever has any trouble with it when I say the kid that has a track record of doing bad shit did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 15:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/notJB1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 15:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That had us in the first half not gonna lie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 14:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cmon sir this doesnt have to be a big thing here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 14:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just smile and nod I guess. As for raging, I dont really get mad. Just mildly annoyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 14:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When red guy slammed his face on the ordering machine. Fucking priceless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 14:09:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/emojipolice just a minor ticket right now sir stay safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 04:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit. I just saw that. God damn what are the chances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 04:37:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean.... if my sister is anything she to go bye. Ive only ever called my dad anything once in my life and he deserved it ( Im a little brother) . But my sister on the other hand, well. Shes sweet and nice... until she heres those to letters (no) then shes a bitch. Insults and shit everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 04:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg Im in chem and I cant write that well.

(Chem is a year above bio) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 04:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think therefore I am.
*Ren descartes intensifies* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 01:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My history teacher two years ago did this once in a test. She made all the answers a except for the last one. If somehow you see this mrs. Maldonado I love you your still my fave teacher and Sam was the best time Ive ever  had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 01:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just did this In chem with one of my homies last week. He most certainly wouldnt have passed that exam without me. Best part, Im a freshman hes a junior. I helped someone in a higher grade than me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 01:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You see Im pretty sure if you look at her contact on your phone, youll see a button that says block her. Push it, and suddenly she decides to stop texting and calling you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 01:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha. Sin hasnt bothered me since.... uh, now that I think about it its never really bothered me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 00:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well have a good satanistic, fun, and most importantly *you* day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 00:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh. Wow. Im not used to people agreeing with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 00:56:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. So the things that people say are the divisa work arent wrong. For the most part they are a form of self expression or being an individual. We agree? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 00:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean yeah but some of the things that people say is the devils work like gayness, and rock and roll music such and so on. How are those wrong? My point is they arent. So by the things people say is explicitly say is the devils work, is in no way wrong by the actual moral standard we should hold ourselves to. My point on god still stand tho, that son of a .... well nothing, but hes narcissistic from everything Ive heard and read. I guess you could say hes got a *god complex* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 21:34:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so about spanking. For the most part no it is not an effective punishment, but when used as a last resort and not as the only punishment, it can work. Ive only ever had to be spanked once maybe twice. I learned the line and I know not to cross it. I also damn well deserved it. It can be ok as long as its not all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 21:26:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not like I follow that rule anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 19:57:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One thing Ive always thought about the typical depiction of satan is that what he stands for doesnt seem bad when you look at it. It seems fun, it seems freeing, it seems like whatever you want. God on the other hand, or at least the one these people del real about wants you in his image and anything else is wrong. Kinda seems like god is a class a narcissist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 19:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry something might be wrong brain wise O.P but thats kinda normal. Most parents these days parents dont know a whole lot about mental illness. They were told it was nothing so thats all they know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 19:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean yeah I guess thats narcissistic but its small potatoes compared to the other shit Ive seen here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 18:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont get how thats wrong either? So now we are going after people for having and expressing any religious beliefs? She didnt attack anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 18:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the insinuation that moms who vaccinate arent real moms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 18:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I get this yeah. Actually one time last year a friend and I (we are best friends) were talking and I said man why are you so stupid and he laughed and shrugged it off. But then this other kid in the group that neither of us really like was like ha ha yeah ed why are you so stupid. And we both just kinda stopped talking and looked at him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Middle row and four to the right knew what he was doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Strange interaction with my peers. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do yall get paid? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this sounds like a dumb question but do yall get paid by fire or something? Or is it hourly? And what do you do when there isnt a fire? Do yall just chill and play card games till the alarm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 14:12:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im feeling called out right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 14:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know those are subreddits but I have no idea what theyre for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 13:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well thanks man. Idk either but it has negative 13 points which sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 05:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just wanna say cuz I havent seen it (correct me if Im wrong I dont have the audio) but how do we know she isnt just facing the phone behind her while watching the road? Like my aunt does that all the time. Shell get the camera hit record and put it on the kid without taking her eyes off the road. When shes done videotaping, she just stops the camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 05:24:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad made reas that in first grade when I was sick and had to go with him. Once I finished that one he gave me hitchhikers guide to the galaxy. Once I finished that one, he realized I would go through any book he gave me and just let me watch cartoons. He gave me books as a sort of warning. Like if I was gonna stay home because I said I didnt feel good it wouldnt be chillin and watching tv. It was to make sure I was actually not feeling good. Every time Ive ever taken one of those at test where its not on a book but its to asses how good you are at reading and vocabulary. On the last one I took in 8th grade it told me what percentage of people I did better than. Not to brag but I got better than 99% of people who took that test. I also got the highest score in that class that was so far into the above grade level category that my teacher practically let me breeze through that class. Fun times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 05:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 02:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> rapunzel rapunzel let down your hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably. You also may not be you and Id just wake up with a different body. Never had my head taken so Im not quite sure of the specifics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah sure why not. It seems yours doesnt work anyway, so being the kind generous souk I am, Ill give you mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt though? I think you may have misread that. Or do you just not know how to read? Well in any case it quite clearly says  off with two f not one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are you talking about? I think you may have misread that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oppsies ever so sorry your grammar lord. May you deem it fit to cut off my head for this most heinous transgression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate but at least hes trying to get better.  Once the withdrawals stop it will get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I occasionally do that but not on purpose. My add means I zone out really quick. When I zone out I like dont blink,  and it can seem like Im staring at you. Not only have I gotten weird looks and asked to stop. On time I got slapped by some girl who thought I was being pervy. That was fun, I barely even knew her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:20:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I occasionally do that but not on purpose. My add means I zone out really quick. When I zone out I like dont blink,  and it can seem like Im staring at you. Not only have I gotten weird looks and asked to stop. On time I got slapped by some girl who thought I was being pervy. That was fun, I barely even knew her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. The only thing I do is for my six year old cousin and I dont even let her win. I let her get me to where like one hit will kill me then I beat her up. Then I finish the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a way of manipulating you into staying in an abusive relationship. When you leave her you will prosper like never before having dropped the dead weight. Once you drop her and prosper, you can buy 10,000,000 phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 00:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont want it off. Since my school allows for costumes on Halloween it means the girls get and take a chance to wear uh... provocative, clothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 00:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless its Julia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 00:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres this homophobic kid in my class. Me and a couple girls in my class (Im a dude) really enjoy playful teasing you know an arm around the shoulder and when I do I like to whisper in his ear  extra homo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 00:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I upvote and post minimally. Not even sure if I can on r/memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 00:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time I get new glasses I feel like my eyes hit a reset button, and I see my height. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 00:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My upvote got it trending! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 23:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well thanks for that attack on the very land where I sleep breath eat and learn. Sorry for being proud of the men and women who sacrifice their lives, having family have died in service. And my current step-father having been in the navy. So uh yeah, thanks for that. 

Cmon dude I literally didnt say anything about any other country. I didnt say anything derogatory, plus thats super off topic. Come on man cool your jets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 21:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you know the u.s army has recently dropped its standards for female recruits to get more in. These are the people fighting for my god dang nation and I want them to be the god damn best of the best. Standards shouldnt get dropped for anyone to get into anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 18:05:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is no one going to mention that BOTH of the guys are Mario </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 19:08:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing is are these real? With Elon I genuinely cant tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 18:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Broski samesies Im in ninth too! Chemistry has so much math, and avagadros number has so many decimal points its crazy: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 18:43:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apple has a dark mode now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 18:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bitch? La chancla es de Mexico! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 07:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But.... but... but I wanna buen down Paris! Not out of anger or anything, I just think the fire would dance in your eyes making you even more beautiful than your already amazing self! 

See what I did there, I just said I wanted to burn down Paris, but I still got you to walk away thinking I was a nice guy cuz I complimented you. My point is a little compliment goes a long way. Oh and op I didnt lie or exaggerated you look amazing today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 07:47:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive seen that damn meme for years now and I will never not love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 07:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just marry each other already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 01:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This man looks like every ps2 character ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 01:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. Im thoroughly impressed. You took all the time to write that response for little ol me? Wow mister have a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 23:54:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 23:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no I like Shakespearean speech. I cant do it but I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 23:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woah dude, Shakespearean much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 19:43:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess its different from person to person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 17:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listen, those assholes should have no say over how you feel. Fuck em, they dont deserve you in all tour elegant grace. Any single one of them would be lucky to even see you. You are above them in every way shape and form. They dont know what theyre talking about. You are amazing, you are the best of them. People mock those they are jealous of, theyre just jealous of how god dang awesome you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 17:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess that makes some sense, but still be careful about it. Ive head that saying my whole life and I know how it can make one feel. Like failing is unacceptable. Maybe it was just me but still. Well anyway that makes sense so go on your way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 16:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh. Well thanks for the heads up Broski </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 16:40:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is he a scammer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 16:21:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah we cant be like them, dont lower yourself to their level. We need to stay above them. And if nothing else, remember it gets the point across better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 16:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh shoot Im sorry I must have accidentally skipped that one. Im really sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 08:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it could be a fear not of death itself but of the pain that ending it would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 08:18:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unpopular opinion? Do you know what sub youre on? Thats everyones opinion here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 08:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah they yelling is called discipline. Parent shout sometimes just sit him down and talk to him, apologize. I know you may not want to apologize but its about the long game. I cant stand being yelled at because when my mom snapped at me like that she never apologized and it made me feel unwanted and shit. Also make sure he knows he cant be doing that anymore. If he thinks he can just run to his mom when youre mad at him, all your punishments will be null and void, he will get out of control trust me Ive seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 08:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One time in class when I had a bunch of shit going on at home I just broke. I snapped and all my shit fell. I was sobbing horribly but quietly. I was told to shit up and  man up instead of people asking what was wrong I was labeled as a bully. My father had just moved away and I was being hit with the fact that I would no longer be able to give him his goodnight hug and kiss every night. I know Exactly who labeled me as the baby, Jessica if your reading this fuck you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 08:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, be sensitive, I get this is bad but try and have a bit of sympathy, not for your humanity or anything like that but its been shown that when advice comes people are more likely to take it when I comes without insults. Its more useful to be kind when speaking because it gets the point across better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 08:08:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok about this saying as its quite common. You have to try before you can do. You stumble before you walk. Saying just do it dont try promotes the notion that failing is bad, when in fact its expected. Yes eventually you will get to the do part but first you have to try, slip ups are ok shit happens its called humanity. Im not trying to attack you or anything just inform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 08:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you know that the estrogen ( the female chemical) chemical is scientifically linked to mood swings? Hmm where have I seen that before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 08:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually for most of my life I didnt even realize that was a scar. It doesnt look like any of the other scars on my body and I had very little idea of what it was. I didnt know I had been circumcised. I only just realized that was a scar and ever since looking at it puts a sick pit in my stomach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 07:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the smell of brownies cooking. So many memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 04:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do. I dont have friends or an on call therapist so I do I like to post when Im feeling stressed or nervous. I like to read the comments and respond to them. It takes my mind off other stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 04:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I just make bad jokes when Im nervous sorry Ill delete it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 04:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it was meant to be a joke. Sorry I make bad jokes when Im nervous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im kinda scared </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 03:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I was in the restroom thats connected to my room. And my stepdads room is right next to mine so while I was in there I heard him say your drunk and your taking it out on me to my mom, that kinda scares me because Ive head stories about when she used to drink and I heard she wasnt nice when she was drunk, like rlly not nice. Now Ive seen my moms not nice back when my parents were still together. That scares me. So Im posting here, to calm down. Posting helps me calm down I like reading and responding to comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 21:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo Angelo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Learning in class:( making memes instead:) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 21:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 21:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I spook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Test test 1,2 can I post on r/memes yet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 18:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 18:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol its ok, I had fun talking to you anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 18:25:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh you were talking about the brand thermos I thought you meant like the cup. And are you sure? That looks like a hydroflask to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 18:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/emojipolice put your hands behind your back and come with me sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 18:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hydroflask is a brand that sells thermoses its just a widely hated brand, so Im calling out on that hate for internet points ok. Chill let me hate a brand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 17:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 17:18:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watercup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 16:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no I dont. I mean hydroflask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 16:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit can you imagine how scary that must be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 16:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I oop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 16:01:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wtf dude, I care. Why you gotta be such an ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 15:43:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Extra homo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 15:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a #hydroflask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 14:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean if you have life you shouldnt be getting parole anyway. You gotta do some crazy shit to get life, if you do that kinda shit I dont want you out here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 14:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont get the point of anything plus life. Past life they cant serve anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 14:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caaaaaaaaarl    It isnt even my birthday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 14:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah something like that. I would never hurt my magic dragon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 13:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, Lydia didnt uh...... last very long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 13:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  No problem, for your compliment I wont shout you off a mountain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 05:11:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit I found the missing link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 00:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I rlly like that kinda emojis vibe your giving off. You look cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 00:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not the hentai shirt!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 22:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/emjipolice hold your hands in the air </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 22:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well it has been theorized that it could be created. My thoughts were one arm giving energy to the other arm and the other arm giving it back, and so on and so forth. This could theoretically create a motion machine and end all energy problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 22:55:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like my things and I tend to get pissed when people mess with my shit, but only because messing with my shit usually means getting in my way. I dont like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 22:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt realize until I saw the brand and I was like whaaaa..... oh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 22:23:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is her name fresh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 21:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about a father? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 21:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R/EmojiPolice HOLD YOUR HANDS UP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 21:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh its not a school paper but the topic comes up more than you would believe during lunch conversation or lectures during class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 21:26:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah fuck it Ill just get me a dude instead of a chick ( Im a dude) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 21:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok Im that case it isnt domestic violence since he isnt in a relationship with her at that point in her time stream. She is a trained warrior, he is a foreign unknown attacker. So once again watch the movie, take a chill pill. They didnt kill iron man because he was a white male, his contract expired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 17:35:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well thanks Broski. Will do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 14:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah dude, insults get you banned, words can hurt, this is kindergarten stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 14:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> About gamora its a movie dude, guys get hit so do girls take a chill pill and enjoy the show. I can remember what he did but Im pretty sure he deserved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 14:48:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang I was going to use this in class but I live in the u.s.a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 14:01:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who said its a joke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 05:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont understand is he like psyching himself up or does he expect it to come to him or what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 05:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that... is it... is it HIM though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 04:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmm do that though? Like how do I know Im not dead and this is just my personal hell? Cuz it kinda feels like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 04:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah. Kinda forgot that story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 04:53:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did it happen to you too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 03:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why... why would that be what you wanna do for you life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 00:24:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that.... did you.... did you count all the skely boiz on that train? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 00:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dear neuro-typicals 
If you wish to keep all you money and/or blood, dont trust us, and dont think you can change us. Or do, its entertaining to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 23:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah he was just preparing to fly in Australia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do I deceive and lie all the time. The very consent of the masks we wear is a sort of deception dont you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im the same. I wanna fuck wether it be dude or chick I dont give a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:50:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would explore this more. Find what makes you cry and try to be able to cry on command, it would really sell fake sadness. Ive Been trying but I just cant cry, I have no tears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have three people my mother my father and my best friend. Not including my pups of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I got an so that was Mormon. I got an so for sexual stuff. Needless to say I was not fully pleased when she wouldnt do anything. But after time and playful jokes we did do stuff. So basically what Im trying to say is, you are a tool and I will make you want go be used like one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:45:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh ooh I excel at this. Im very good at faking everything from sincerity to even lying. The trick for sad is the head tilt and the eyes. For happy just seem energetic. If you want more just dm me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im look for the ultimate enjoyment. I want one super complacent person that I can do whatever with. You know the holy grail. Then once Ive sucked them dry Ill move on to another one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister went off to college and my mother cried. I still dont really understand why, shes only six hours away and they didnt Have a great relationship anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find it interesting, its a source for entertainment, when Im bored and have nothing else to do, go text my girlfriend tell my girlfriend that I want to break up and watch her cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All the time. Ive even *accidentally* choked someone out before. I almost did it but I got caught and I said he attacked me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive never been in love I dont think. I thought I was once but I realized my feelings were no where near as strong as hers and she was very emotional, that led me to the conclusion that what I was feeling was not love, and maybe some other form of bond. Whatever it was it was easy to break and it was interesting to watch her cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:33:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have absolutely no idea how. I do this in class all the time. I just fucking check out and suddenly Im in a tv show or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I have trouble with that to. But I love noticed that if Im in a group, and I say something, then that all go quiet, I probably offended someone. Not that I care a whole lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know and Im sorry its off topic but I just had to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:30:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont self destruct but I do get destructive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm what term can we find that has a high negative connotation, where you are bound, blamed, and hurt? Oh Ive got one TORTURE. In torture you are bound so you cant escape or fight back, you are hurt, and you are blamed for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just wanted to say that I upvoted this to NICE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:18:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait so the womens bathroom was full. So you *a man* got kicked out of the mens room, so a *women* could use it? Am I getting that right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You must be swift as a coursing river * be a man* you must be strong as a great typhoon, mysterious as the dark side of THE MOON. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just had to work with ah *shudders* partner in English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah si it knows DE WEH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 21:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad had a shirt with the front on it but not the back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 19:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I just like to clarify.:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 18:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not a furry but I like zoology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 16:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Help myself you say? Now that I can do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm. But what can we do? I as a dude am crippled socially. Even been suspended for fighting against a female bully, Ive seen firsthand the bias in the custody system. But Im just a kid. Im sitting in Spanish class having just taken a test theres nothing I can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:40:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean willful ignorance is still ignorance. And in my opinion the fact that its willful just makes them less intelligent. The fact of the matter is they dont want facts, they dont want logic or reason. They want to be mad, and the patriarchy is an easy target. The fact that men cant fight back against their lies, coupled with their structurally perfect logic. It makes the perfect war machine for creating a social uprising against problems that dont really exist. Case and point, the wage gap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bad words! *sprits sprits* no lolis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:32:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sprits sprits! No! No underage girls! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those arent his hands theyre his paws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one with the long hair reminds me of pearl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welp Im 14 too so fuck it, Im down. Shes not *wrong* though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is that scary? And that really just seems kinda lazy. I mean a stick figure?really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:16:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes, the lumberjack cafeteria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How the leaves go down is simply amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Duuuuddddeeeee stop that youre gonna get the human race sued! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 14:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude! Sweet a perpetual motion machine! I love those. Can it actually run forever or will it stop eventually? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 14:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmao he was calling you stupid while he made so manny grammatical and spelling errors his whole side was almost impossible to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 14:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes yes I am ready to die. Bring it old man.
(This is a joke please dont downvote me into oblivion) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 14:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A:tax fraud.
B:rob a billionaire.
C:murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 07:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm, so what Im hearing is; when I get my license dont speed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 06:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a heads up shouldnt this have a progress flair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 06:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sooooo what I got was he was never proven guilty, but from that final one innocent until proven guilty doesnt apply here for..... some unexplainable reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 04:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No but I have friends that go in both, and second hand experience can still be called experience. All my friends who are female talk to me about the gossip and such that goes on in there, in turn I tell her the wacky shit that goes on in the mens room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 02:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes but Im going to guess that one says female. Im also going to guess this was a very poorly received and very poor attempt at a joke. If I saw the op I would ask if they gave a female brain one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 02:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something like that but if you read the bottom it also says. OGA BOOGA CHAD NO LISTEN TO BABY CRY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 02:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess thats possible but in my experience they are MUCH more civilized. Like we would whip each other with towels, and uh, do you know what a sword fight is that actually happened. Cheating, that happened, gossip we did that, fights, plenty of those. If I kept listing them it would take a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 01:58:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt that the point? Isnt that what ... that area is for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 01:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The difference is, that not like other girls is the difference in a gender. Those boys locker room pictures are about the differences between genders. One is funny and satirical, the other is completely true. Boys locker rooms are fucking wild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 21:41:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats the thing about feminist logic, structurally its perfect. Because by their logic anyone that doesnt agree with them is automatically a misogynistic pig and a rapist. Leaving only people who agree with them and affirm their beliefs, leaving no room for intelligent and logical conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 17:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have fun you two. Always never say no to drugs.drink and drive. You know teen stuff. I ship it, have fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 14:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmm I was thinking more, die in a comical mound of cocaine at the top of my penthouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 14:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I just dont have access. When I do find one nearby Ill drink it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 14:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no I never meant that fathers are good and mothers are bad, Im saying everyone is shit. Were all fucked up and maybe no one should have kids because we end up suffering when adults cant keep their shit together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 06:32:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly my dear fellow. Some tricks I use to try and humanize myself in their eyes is fake nightmares, and say that thinking of talking to them stopped the nightmare. They find it endearing and they think they helped you which grows the bond. Oh and make sure not to help them too much, if you do they wont need you, and then youll have to find another one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 06:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No prob bob. But make sure to seem sincere and tortured that way they think youre like them and that way they trust you more. Now go have fun messing with their already fractured minds! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 06:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah. I know these weak emotion filled people see me as almost a savior. No matter what I say theyll follow me, even sympathize with me. Its actually really amusing you should try it. Just go on almost any r/mentalhealth post and dm them  do you wanna talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 06:15:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no I realize it. Im even open with those I help about it. They dont care or dont believe me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:50:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I realized that if I helped people with mental illness feel better about themselves and better their lives, they would shower me with praise and thus fuel my ego. If they happen to feel ok in the process so be it, I dont really care about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not quite sympathy. But a feeling where they got hurt. I quite enjoy watching it in fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I chose not to press the button because I gain, and the after effects arent my problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would never hurt my doggies. People on the other hand, or cats......... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Minor joy at a funny meme. And annoyance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im just bored in school. But I dont follow any religion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Actually in one of my classes we have a random person present a random topic. Everyone is surprised at how well I can do it, because Im just not nervous about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I do like people but I dont feel love like you. But for those few that I like I would happily kill for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 21:15:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. No question about it. You need a nap, a nice calm bath maybe with candles. And whatever else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 18:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt that how its said in French? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 18:13:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R/emojipolice PUT YOUR HANDS IN THE AIR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 16:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My life is on a constant state of change my father lives six hours away from me I dont see my mother during the week and my step dad is moving away so is my brother. I am unable to cry about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 05:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, you are wrong. And to fully explain why, let me tell you a story. When I was about nine or ten my parents got a divorce. At this time, my mother was batshit insane. To the point where she was yelling at me for not doing something she hadnt asked me to do and calling my sister a bitch. She was a stay at home mom. My dad who worked all the time. Couldnt make any time for us because my mother was insane and had a status to uphold. So he had to work all the time we understood and we were fine. But when custody time came rolling around my mother got full custody. Shes fine now having realized my mistake. But in a fair trial my dad would most certainly have gotten custody. I also want to say that my father is my superhero and always will be, he did what he did because he had to. Not because he chose to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 04:19:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *forty three </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 03:24:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it happens with most births. It doesnt mean you arent wanted. Not a mistake, a happy accident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 09:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Morally its fine. Legally dont have sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 09:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, then again, Im most likely a sociopath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 09:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as its more than just  hibernation Im down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 09:04:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nooooo this was deleted I need the code </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 08:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 05:26:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh ooh Im good a seeing if someone likes you or not. I have a couple questions but Ill dm you to ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 04:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a running joke between me and my bff actually. Since I was the one you were looking for. maybe a gold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 04:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you should talk to him. June was a while ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 02:22:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 02:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude are you ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 01:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang. Oh well thanks anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 23:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah thats cool and all but look at how much waste that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 23:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks like a god damn star </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 22:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But satan post the best stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 21:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She has a great sword he has a short sword, it doesnt mean he cant win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 21:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Daddy Johns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 21:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PAIGE NO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 10:27:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just keep in your heart the knowledge that they only shout the loudest because they are the least firm in their belief. By making you believe it it reaffirms their own beliefs. But those who are sure and strong in it say nothing unless it is brought up to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 10:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all this is amazing. Second of all this made me sad because I realized how few of it applies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 09:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know a dude that would ever actually say besito. Not because the word is cringe but switching from english to Spanish and back to English is cringe. Spanglish sucks, choose a Language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 09:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men have oppressed womens rights even to her own body!* turns around* Im going to cut of a bit of my sons dick and there isnt anything you can do about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 09:27:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey thats what I was gonna say.*holds up hand* high five between like minded people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How I got the scar on my leg.( how I fucked up as a kid) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 09:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so Im not sure if this belongs here or not but let me tell you a story. 

When I was maybe seven or eight, I went to the birthday party of a dear friend no name given. The party was held at a video game store/ old style arcade that her father owned. Since the party was at this place it was in a commercial plaza with other stores, and at one point a group of friends including me, started running in the alley behind these stores. Now here comes the fuck up. So about the alley, to my right there was the stores and to the left a fence, in between was tubes and ac units. So the dumb part about the fence is that at the bottom it curved up like a fishhook. So me being the dumbass I was, tripped over one of the ac tubes. I tripped and the fishhook fence tore a huge gash in my leg, like I could see the bone. Like the trooper I was i hobbled out of the alley. At that point the parent supervisor saw my bloodstained jeans and called my mother. That sucked. 

If this goes somewhere else tell me. If I messed up with grammar tell me respectfully in the comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 00:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He looks so pissed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 00:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are some good meds for sociopaths </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 00:23:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You see the death penalty is deeply rooted in religion. It comes from the old belief that hell is the worst punishment of all ever. And if all bad people go to hell. Then the death penalty is sending bad people straight to hell. Im not saying its right, just giving some facts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 00:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Finally.  Someone saying the truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 22:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I agree. Man spreading on its own isnt an issue but on planes and things try and keep to a minimum guys, Youre making the rest of us look bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 22:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean she does need the car though because yes with two steps she could be there. But only her feet would be there, the rest of her would still be in front of her house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 21:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for this Broski. Also she complained about not being able to find a guy, then named the reasons we say she cant find a guy, then dismissed them like come on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 19:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to seem racist because Im not but how is this about mens rights? This seems from the title to be about racial equality. Im in class so I cant listen to it now so excuse me if it says something about mens rights in the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 19:22:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saw this at ni.ce K upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 18:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah I know that yes just why the x when you could make it 10 for spooktober </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 16:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 14:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup(; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 14:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean Ill kill some of the people too but in theory yes. I mean why should both of us go to jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 14:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well cute may have been an overstatement. But it was fun for me anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 06:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually theyre pretty small lol. Anyway, are you the one downvoting me because if you are Id like you to stop and reverse them or at least tell me why. Im just having a fun cute conversation. I mean no harm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 06:43:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take my god damn upvote you cute motherfucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 06:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im fourteen. High school freshman. To me he looks like maybe a junior or even a senior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 06:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes but doesnt just the thought of getting closure and feeling ok with your past make it worth a try. And worst comes to worst she reminds you why you hater her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 06:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Samesies bitch. Wanna go on a murder spree? If you say yes I get all the credit though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 06:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you should talk to her. Not to forgive her but for closure. Wounds like these can fester and leave scars. Its important to tell her how you feel and what she did to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 06:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HE HAS A HEART NOSE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 05:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taste the rainbow, boop the rainbow, kiss the rainbow, CHOMP the rainbow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 05:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kiss the rainbow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 05:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good dang it you beat me to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 03:53:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about strap-ons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 03:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. yes in fact I have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 03:28:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no. That is weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 00:24:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ask for a sequel but its happy and I have no troubles in my life ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 00:22:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaaay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 23:10:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no I feel safe. I know all the students in my grade and none of them would do anything like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 23:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah pretty much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 23:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude Im not being pretentious its like a thing. I never said it didnt happen anywhere else its just like an actual thing that America has lots of school shooting. And cool your friggin jets dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 23:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah we know. Its like one bloody bouncy house full of shitheads over here. Its like if the purge was a place. Hell I go to high school and have to deal with the fact that any day now I may be gunned down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 22:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 22:02:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaaaay. Gather round children. Grand pappy is about to tell us a story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 21:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 21:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang. Last week? Can we have a story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 21:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed. But the spooky cult is not this. Tis the cult of the doots the spooks and the skely boyz. Long last spooktober </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 14:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It waaaayy to late now. Im a freshman in high school. Id never be able to get ahold of the witnesses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 14:02:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it happened. Idk what to tell you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 14:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I didnt break any bones I just put her on the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 14:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I didnt break any bones I just put her on the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 06:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in a similar boat Broski. The only thing stopping my from suicide is my knife isnt quite sharp enough. Ha ha * cries* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 06:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No Im wrong dont avoid your problems its bad dampened is bad feel your emotions and all that schnazz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 06:15:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In fact I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How I got suspended for fighting a bully </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 06:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So back when I was in sixth or seventh grade, there was this really fucking stupid bully. The bully was a she, thats important. Now I had a reputation for not taking shit at this school due to my last encounter with a bully and for that reason I was not bullied myself. But one day I was waiting to be picked up with a friend of mine, and she started throwing shit at him. After a while I could tell he was not pleased but wasnt going to say anything himself. So I asked her kindly and politely to stop. She did not. She kept throwing things at him so I asked her to stop again a little less polite this time. She asked me what I was going to do about it and stepped real close to me. I said I really dont want to have to fight you but I will if I have to. She punched my square in the jaw and from there I used my years of karate classes to put her on the ground. We were still on school property so a teacher was called.  Seven other students told the teacher that not only was she bullying my friend and many others but she hit me first. For some reason though she got off with a slap on the wrist and a now dont do that again young missy. And I got like a weeks suspension. Luckily my mom knew the situation so I got ice cream and tv the whole week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 06:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was always taught as a kid that I was never to start a fight. But if I came to it, beat that mf to hell and back. So it never got explained to me that this rule did not apply to women for some reason. Then I got into a fight with a bully that just happened to be a girl ( long story I might post about it). Then I got suspended and she got nothing l. I was pissed and only then did it get explained to me that I was not to hit a women under any circumstances. Luckily my mom knew that was bs and it was just how the system works. So I still got ice cream and tv during my suspension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 05:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hating the stereotype doesnt mean they dont fit the box. Sorry to tell you but hist because they say it doesnt make it true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 05:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh thanks for letting me know it was deleted. I was about to waste my time asking a question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 05:38:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont even yall go them anymore. I talk to one non family female in my life. If you see this willow youre the best love ya hun have a nice night and dont forget your algebra homework. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 05:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh hi so what your saying is that. When women actually talk and listen to men. They gain a new different perspective and learn that not everything the learned in their social media is true? Huh, its almost like, oh but I couldnt say it its unthinkable. Well I guess I will maybe. Just maybe. YOURE WRONG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 05:34:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing is no man is good enough for them. They want the all out packages when all they deserve is a garbage bag. Maybe on fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 05:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kill the emperor? I cant seem to remember how that saying goes but that seems historically correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 05:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doodle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 01:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ey ese, no ases malo chico </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 01:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god.*throws up* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 01:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 01:29:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the  according to science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 23:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cancer will always be here. Spook is only one month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 23:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1-3 are no but number 4 is true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 23:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love how its next to a cross and shit. This is a religious totem of its own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 21:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes tis i. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt that god Johnson? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are rookie numbers you gotta boost those up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:09:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not exactly while working. Its the setting, its not safe for any professional setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 13:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cushioned is good tho no? Its better than the full force. Plus you get the added bonus of avoiding your problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 05:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im stage four but from stages 1 through 4. What Im trying to say is the only thing that changed was the hand holding the gun got bigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 05:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welp dude youre wrong. I upvoted and the arrow thing went from grey to blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 05:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would just like to say because I think its cute. I dont know about all but I know at least the porche boxter comes with vets shaped like the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 05:21:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Username checks out. (Ive always wanted to say that so thanks) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 05:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think give it two earnings instead of just one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 01:18:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok. Please excuse my ignorance I understand now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 01:00:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes yes Im good at torturing its a gift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 00:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 00:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I think that would be to quick I mean a bear is gonna go straight for the kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 00:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welp throw em in a hole full that hole with bullet ants then after 10 min light it on fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 00:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow hadnt even thought of that. Welp never thinking of him again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 00:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or 420,069 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a product. A product of my SINS haha lol *crys* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess you could say it was coming but its here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im torn. Do I downdoot for the hypocrisy and mob joining. Or do I updoot for Phil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha ha. Jokes on you, thats where my dog lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shut your dang trap and uproot the skely boyz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My last name is actually laugher or something like that in German </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 22:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok I will when I get the time but Im not sure when that will be. Fuck high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 22:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. Im jack 24/7 get it because Im dead inside ha.... ha. ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 22:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1 if by land and 2 if by grave! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 21:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasnt that like a long time ago? Forgive my ignorance but Im  on r/teenagers I dont deal with banks yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 20:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theyre more just neutral. They do a required service and they do it well enough but we dont quite like them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 19:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean the bank isnt doing anything wrong here. The charge is the sane for both men and women right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 19:11:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no dont worry about it. And I dont shit on stuff just cuz teenage girls like them. Ill go for Starbucks any day of the week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 19:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No dude its called a hyperbole. Its an exaggeration. Calm down dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 15:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I literally have no idea why trump may be impeached. I just know its a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 15:23:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no its not. Spiders zuc and I hate them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 15:21:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  NO. Tis spooktober its what we do. Learn to love the skely boys or go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 15:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol I meant everything genetic. But I mean. You ancestors could have died in the rock that became your computer. You could have an ancestor computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 15:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh. All the girls at my school have it and it just weirds me out. Its like a friggin cult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 15:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wtf indeed. In fact I do not even know what the fuck o was thinking when I said this. I apologize for your eyes now needing bleach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 04:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh planet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 04:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh planet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 04:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really wasnt that long. I cant last </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 04:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imma steal your box </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 04:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know what imma steal your house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 04:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fine Im a thief but what are you gonna do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 03:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is every girl I have ever known. Not to say all females tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw a post there that said men destroy family not women and I called them on their bill citing many stories that I have. Needles to say I got banned. I asked the mods why when I hadnt broken any rules. No response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:52:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would just like to point out real quick. My sister got all the special treatment, hell she got a car for her sixteenth birthday, while Ive been told not to expect that as well and I will probably not get a car as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope when nurses take a baby away after birth they fuck it and give it a blowjob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Por que no ay un chica que tiene los tres </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a tits man every day all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mario wouldnt muy uh super Mario,......, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can I please get a hold. It would be my first and Im having a hard week. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:08:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro samesies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 02:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh ooh do you wanna hear a story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sir are you implying that 1 stole those pants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 cuz he can just shoot ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything is from our ancestors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taking one trip is the only thing standing between me and insanity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:15:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hes off a bit but hes got the spirit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to see you seeing the bs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look at the skin the color the tone. That is not the same child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 01:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THAT BACKPACK. What is that god damn symbol. The one on the back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 23:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 14 and never stung </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 22:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> # oh thanks dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 22:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive been super busy I havent had a chance to but as soon as I do I will and Ill post it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 20:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww thanks. I try to recognize when Im in the wrong because I know I feel better when someone does it to me. Which doesnt happen often. Always try and put as much good in the world as you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 19:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre right youre right. Im sorry I was Mean. It was just supposed to be a joke. I didnt really mean any of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 19:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. Thanks for the info it makes way more sense now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 19:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant today I was just wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 17:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont worry Broski Im here for you. SLEEP IS FOR THE WEAK. *passes out* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 17:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saw this while not paying attention in chemistry lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 17:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk I think thats a dude. Miss me with that gay shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 17:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We need a sub called not like other dogs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 17:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats a weird ass hairline for a big sister. That hairline looks like shes 40 so if we assume the mom is at least 20 years older then shes having a baby at 60. If you go by the hairline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 17:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh isnt today national boys day? Or am I mistaken?

Edit: I google it I was wrong sorry about that. National mens day is November 19. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 16:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imma grab my 7 inch Bowie knife and uh. Go hunting. If any of you wanna come dm me. (This is a joke dont dm me with actual requests to go hunting with me). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 16:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait you dad or your sons dad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 14:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you do the bold thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 14:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer numb to depressed. Dont you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 05:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok sorry about that. I get heated when someone blames a whole issue on men. When I have experience with it not being that way. My neighbors mom tried to stab him. When he was SEVEN. So dont try and say women dont have any part in this. Also I gave her human decency, so I cursed I got heated I did not target or harass her. So chill mod its called an argument and its a normal part of being human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 05:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok fuck you. My father did every god damn thing he could to please my mother and she was insane. Never ever say men destroy families as if women have no part in this. Just say families get destroyed, and weep for the children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 21:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like cocaine Columbia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 21:40:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have a friend around at all times. When this happens he should record it. Then once you have enough evidence, you can hit back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 21:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet! Day for the boyz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 20:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Australia 100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 20:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah call the cops if she comes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 18:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh thanks. This was a while ago so I just googled it. But Thanks anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 23:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was actually in a very similar situation the only difference being that my sister was only the normal level of meant to me just because I was the annoying younger brother. It got better once she moved out because my mom was always least mean to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 21:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its because they dont need them. Everyone knows about Starbucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 20:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ThE BeLL DOeSNt DiSMiS YoU I DO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 08:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh thanks Broski </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 03:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes that part seemed real to me its just the term gut flora that seems odd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 01:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gut flora what a psycho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 01:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waifus and when Muslims fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 14:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait.... what? Did.... did you say post birth abortion. That uh, that just sounds like murder with extra steps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 14:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. But I find that when I ask something here I get very..... interesting, answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 06:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mind if I steal this for an art project? No! Ok thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 06:04:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I..... I need him/ her. I can see all the cuddles and shows we will have together.  I CAN SEE ALL THE CUTE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 05:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude mine is Mac high bulldogs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 05:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mac high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dees nuts.
Joe mama
Ben Dover 
So on and so forth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah remember that hen she admitted to drugging and robbing men, and NOTHING happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or what about shebagging a less known term that is about the phenomenon where a women puts her purse on another seat or sometimes on two seats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a circumcised who ha and the scar feels weird. I didnt know ven know it was an actual fucking scar until I was 13 1/2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking seven days. She killed a newborn. What the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IM STILL HERE OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 02:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its babytron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 01:13:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What in hyuk is two spirit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 20:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  No its all good my dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 20:02:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I thought these were things you believed I was like why would he admit that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 19:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aww </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 19:26:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 19:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I...  I cant tell if youre joking or not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 01:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok take the upvote and maybe edit all that stuff in to the post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 01:10:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean. Not to be disrespectful to you and shit but couldnt you have just like brought it. You knew you were gonna be going to math class right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 23:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 23:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As if. I dont even know how one would contact them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 22:51:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait how was the teacher following the girls letting them get their stuff when you couldnt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 22:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What even the motherfuck. Is this real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 22:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 69 updoots say no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 22:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha as if I could just *get rid of it* without being absolutely ridiculed for showing emotion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 21:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are right Im sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 20:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a great drawing but the eyeless dude creeps me out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 20:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least land mines are quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 20:28:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, but alas nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 20:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yeah but Im only a teenager I dont know how or who to report too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 20:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmm no lol this is a school after all. Edit: I only meant that in the way I cant post shit about that part of the body at school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 20:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah Ill do the thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:54:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe but she will probably not let me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow ok I should make it known it isnt about the heart disease itself it about the fact that the school will take down any posters for men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh thanks Broski I just joined </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:26:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course!!! We love anyone intelligent and open to conversation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A: its sad that youve never done much of that before
B me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh oh no it absolutely sucks. I wish I wasnt tired of it. Im just kinda .... done with it but I have so much longer to go with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes that too. It just all around sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are strong though in your core you can do this. I dont know how you do it. Im only fourteen and Im already so done with my mask of  being a man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just want to let you know that no, if you were born female you would not be aware of your privilege. It would have gotten drilled into your head from birth that we are the ones who have privilege. It would be like trying to get out of a cult mindset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well Im not a father but I am a son and I can tell you what it means from my perspective. My father will always be my superhero and I love him for it. It means being there to support. It means answering the hard questions mom cant answer. It means going to work and still making time to watch a movie with me. It means so much and there is no chance you could get a glimpse into how much a father loves his child from a post on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hes fucking autistic! They do these things. As a whole autistic people tend to be more affectionate and kinder and all that (not all of them) you cant blame this kid when he cant quite think the way you or i do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you check it the comment where the mod says it got locked says  sorry the boys couldnt play by the rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 16:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 15:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No Ive tried. So have others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 15:29:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive been in a similar situation I was just on the other side. My parents used to hate each other and my older sister and I would be caught in the crossfire. It feel in my older sister to make breakfast and hold me when I cried as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:22:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no they take mens ones down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:21:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe my info was outdated sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh wait sorry I just realized which one this was. I reposted it with some other facts in the title. Like the fact that when someone puts one up for men it gets taken down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:13:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry bad experience causes pessimism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that this is aimed towards women when the issue actually effects not more. Thats what its relevance is. It shows the sexism inherent in the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 04:34:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know what youre talking about. Every adult woman Ive met has been very aware of it. While Ive never met a man who said he was watching it. Also you cant take that as a given. Plus it kills men more which means awareness should be more focused at them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 03:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh really thats pretty neato I dont use Twitter so I didnt know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 02:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MATT SMITH DOCTER IS THE BEST DOCTOR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 02:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 02:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ill do that Ill take a picture of them both Ill put them side by side and shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 02:03:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ex: testicular cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 01:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it sucks especially because it affects men more then women </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 01:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All of the above </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 01:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course good man. Go fight the good fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean Ive been on here for a while Ive just never posted before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah ok yeah that makes total sense. I agree completely, and it sucks that they do this knowingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For women its 1/5 of all deaths Is heart disease but for men its 1/4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My school has these around the school and if you post one for men it gets taken down </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I doubt it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um ok I love the awareness but what does this have to do with my poster. Im sorry I cant make the connection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean..,. The cat is a black cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My school has these type of things all around the school and if anyone puts one up that says men it gets taken down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are 100% right Ill comment it right now sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:29:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant it would get taken down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 00:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree on its own there is nothing wrong with this one on its own ..... but its a different story when they are all around the school and administrators take down any saying saying men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The babys look like she ran out of ink lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean ok idk what this has to do with my comment but ok. I know I know Im missing periods and commas and all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know what that green book is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe because she is trying to force him to give her access to his private documents and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:36:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welp you work your life away only to have a female tell you it isnt enough and then leave you because the fact that her ever money consuming life style is too much for you. Then kill yourself because she left you while everyone praises her for being strong and leaving an abusive relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My parents are divorced and.... well I love my mom and she is sane now but when it happened she was not. In a truly legal and fair case my father would have gained full custody but my mother did. I love her though just wanna make that clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanna see her video and how she spun it to be 90 percent of these people are sexist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cuz you know, mens health isnt important. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Did you know heart disease is 1/4 male death but only 1/5 female. Found this at my school </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 23:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. Now you get me( mods this is a joke please dont ban me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 21:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh lol I for got about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 18:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I take chem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 16:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say murder but thats against the rules. I am not not suggesting it though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:41:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in the USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:27:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh no.. no thats not legal. The age of consent is 18 at least here it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean..... this is the exact reason I dont let my mother, Sister, aunt, grandma, take me shopping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok then you should still go look and upvote my memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok then you should still go look and upvote my memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you looked through my profile. Thats fine I hope you upvoted my memes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay then go on with your day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woooow that must be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 05:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh well now I have to read that one too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 05:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh its all hypothetical didnt I say? Im pretty sure I did. Nothing came of it but a tiny scratch on my foot that didnt even draw blood.  If it makes you uncomfortable to see I understand and Ill take it down. I got the response I wanted anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 04:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats for for what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 03:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok carry on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 03:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes but why did you scroll through my profile looking. I saw your comment on the other one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 03:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Near the top yes that makes sense. Thanks for your help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> No one answered my question so Im asking again. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 03:27:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 03:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need a support donkey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 03:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh I can hang out!! We can be cutter buddies!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 02:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 02:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool idk that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 01:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No its good Broski but thats what you should do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 00:21:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just read up on this case real quick and it is fuuuged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 00:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I meant report him to the actual cops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 00:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 14 and I dont get 10 hours of sleep??!!! How does it feel to be well rested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 00:04:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh wow have you tried reporting him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 23:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh it is watching as the carnage goes down and people pick sides as I sit there with popcorn. I had never thought of making friends with a gossip girl for blackmail though thats a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 23:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That absolutely sucks and should not be legal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 23:16:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh because there is so much use for people beyond what is normally seen. Let me explain. Friends buy you food or give you money they also give you answer on homework and sometimes test. As well as my favorite use. Entertainment oh but not the usual entertainment I mean a whisper hear a whisper there and you can get two best friends to hate each other more than anything its quite fun to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 23:11:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I did know this person and I had known them for a long time. It was painfully obvious it was fake trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 23:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no its fine and its probably true too I really do love fire. Plus the teacher who sent me didnt really like me so I suppose he could have just been looking for a reason to send me out. But yes I do have a bet convincing mask. No one suspects Im hiding anything. Im very good at what I do, that being lying and hiding and stealing and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No they actually got pissed at me. They thought I was being an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The top picture is a mood. In fact its my constant mood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One time I called a girl out on it at school. She was in the middle of the cafeteria and it was quite obvious she was saying it for attention. So I pushed through the crowd around her and told her  do you hate getting out of bed every morning. No. And when you wake up do you wish you werent conscious? No.   then shut the hell up because some of us have actual issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whered you go friend? I was enjoying our conversation ever so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok but yeah theres a bunch of banned books here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not its just a charter school. Which basically means really stuck up public school. I took this picture I didnt just find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I know that but apparently the school doesnt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:31:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was. I dont know sadly enough I cant read minds and dont know what was running through their heads as the gym teacher called the counselor on me. And what do you mean over exaggerating what they are feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean I was freaking out teachers and stuff for me someone to go is usually outgoing and loud ( mask on) to go so quite I dont talk all period was cause for concern enough I guess Im also told I give off a vibe something along the lines of  you seem like you would burn down my house for fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The me bothering you part was the part about my mask with it Im very timid and quite very awkward and clumsy. As for going a day without my mask I have once only once. I freaked a lot of people out and it was fun but I got sent to the counselors office and counselors really tic me off so I dont </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 21:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a freshman at my school and I feel like all the upperclassmen hate me for it I dont know why. I dont vape or anything I dont think Im annoying and I know I havent done anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 21:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Without my mask. Im violent, calculated, and uncaring, as well as scary Ive been told. With the mask Im oh sorry Im bothering you with all these texts arent i. Oh I just sent another one Im so sorry. I cant speak for most sociopaths but personally I have mine because its inviting and makes people feel like they can trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Because banning a book for lgbtqa+ content is just what we do here. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 21:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 21:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I dont get very angry in the first place so that helps and even if somehow someone does something so horrible it does make me mad I breath first then I close my eyes. If your asking how I scare I do it by singing a song quietly to myself and swaggering over to them with a crazed look in my eyes and an erratic smile. When people see a reaction they dont expect like that their automatic reaction is to perceive it as unnatural and fear it. Once I get close to them I get real close and I whisper into their ears  if you do that again Ill break both of your arms but say it in a low volume so just they can hear. Back up stare at them with a blank face and walk away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 21:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I dont really get outbursts Im calm I find it scares more I dont really do angry either I meant my movement are precise. As in I know how to finely tune my punch to stop less than an inch before I hit I know exactly how to move my hands and such with enough precision to get what I need done. Be that cause fear or pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 20:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh huh sure buddy I love seeing every passing peer as a target I love feeling the intense urge to break and stab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 20:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally Im quite calculated. I use my words with precision to cause the most fun (pain) or did you mean physically because yes Im calculating and precise there too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 20:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no its real trust me Im currently in a murderous moment I think if I did have my knife on me right now someones flesh would be cut wether its mine or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh fine you Debbie downer. Im completely content in my madness you know. And by the way you never answered my original question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:43:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont got one yet. Not just had my first therapist appointment. Im going to see how long I can keep my ruse of sanity up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh you see Im insane and murderous my thoughts are no longer those of the sane. My brain has gone and broke in its place is insanity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah that assumes something is causing my pain but no. Im just broken. my brain is shattered in 10 million pieces gone in the wind. You mustnt worry I did say it was all hypothetical after all and I left my knife at home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh its all hypothetical of course and uh cant it be a little bit of both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you sure? Cuz Im kinda feeling it ( or not feeling) hypothetically of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have a question for all yall </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean like its rude and mean, but it isnt wrong per say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 05:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haw haw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 01:11:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you live with her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 01:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont go that hard. The mother just wants to spend time with her child which is a normal thing. She is however taking it too far, she/he should try talking to her about it and how college is for her to experience independence and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 00:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 00:30:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I love the vampire eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 00:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do have good reflexes and while I did report her I dont think anything happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 23:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HITLER DETECTED HAIL INITIATED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 23:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Myself better it worded have couldnt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 23:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See I just cant really get with argonians I dont like the eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 23:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See shit like this is how I end up in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 23:08:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww Im glad. On that note would you like to come to my kahjiit orgy afterwards we sacrifice our souls to dagon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 22:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you should see Monty python go watch the holy grail one. Its on Netflix. What are you doing still reading this?! Go go watch it now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Time to bring me my money </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 21:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 20:56:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But 
A: I love orgies
B: I love skooma
C: elves can suck my khajiit dick
D: the lords can have my soul if they want it
E: I went there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 20:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes that is true however orgies would never be the same if romans hadnt added women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 19:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is is horny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 19:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My thoughts exactly. If you use the poop one youre putting the shit back up your ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 19:17:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh i thought he meant an actual banana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 19:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That happened to me and my mom took my computer away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 19:11:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got banned for posting proof that the wage gap is fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 19:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  No sex was invented by the condom industry to sell more condoms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 19:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no you mean orgies and you are correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 18:36:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I agree that is a much better example. And for the people who downvoted me, I didnt say it was right I didnt say it was good I said it was legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 10:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 09:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See a lot of parenting though cant be taught. A lot of it depends on the kid that comes out. Like spanking or not. I got spanked and it worked but I know for my sister it didnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 09:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt elderberry a fictional thing from Monty python? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 09:38:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit should be a democracy. We should vote for the admins once a month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 09:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 would boop anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 09:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that sucks and Im sorry I want you to know that I think youre pretty cool. I think your hot. I think youre amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 08:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with this  you are an amazing person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 04:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not people in truly healthy relationships.  I tell my SO everything I have nothing to hide. You on the other hand.... are what is truly classified as a man hoe and just Incase you didnt know thats bad. Maybe get off reddit you spoiled bitch. I hope you never make that 50k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 04:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do those people who say healthy relationships are built on truth know. Ahh what do they know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An interesting title. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 04:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 03:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im very lucky that in my life I have always been given praise for my intellect. The thought that some dont get that motivation sickens me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 03:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You say that casually but it shouldnt be a normal thing. You should celebrate intelligence equally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 03:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes my pp become THE BIG PP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 02:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it bad that I want one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 01:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmm could you pass the bowl Im craving some bees </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 01:30:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 01:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre pretty great and I hope you have an awesome day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 01:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww. Man you are just the sweetest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 01:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww youre too sweet. You know how to make a guy blush </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 00:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh thanks anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 00:57:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Frogging weirdos. Do you think you could give me an upvote to bring me back up to 0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 00:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok. Excuse my ignorance Ive only been hunting once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 23:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im an urbanite and I still dont think this is insane. But if you looks at the bird in her hand it isnt going to be enough to eat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 23:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Not insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 23:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But they are gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 23:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know who downvoted you but they are wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thought this fit here </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 23:24:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 23:15:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See the thing is they dont really want equality. They say they do and they really do.... until it means they have to give up some stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 23:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Women: we cant stand being away from our babies for so long!

Men: yeah do you think I could please see my children every blood moon I miss them since I can only see them every February 29th?

Women: no you monsters! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 22:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes you will. There are no other options </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 20:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean to be fair when the child would be getting circumcised, he cant make the decision on his own. Not that this is okay Im just saying what she did is legally ok. And getting the uterus of your baby daughter removed would not be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 20:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I refer to my best bro ( hes a guy) as sis all the time just jokingly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 04:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate this this is wrong. You can see the pain in his eyes as he talks about how he was forced to be happy about being raped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 04:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I mean Im fucked up and warped anyway so why not add another thing to the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 03:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah my mom used to be mega insane. And I got used  to not pointing out the crazy and just saying ok mom  and now that she isnt crazy I still have that problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 03:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This poor kid. As much as I hate school it is important for social and mental growth. It also also important to protect those who are more likely than o get the disease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 21:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No dont worry about it and Mandela effect is having a false memory of something. Like my false memory that its wonderful and not beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 17:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wtf what happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 17:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh fuck Mandela effect. I apologize for my mistakes please forgive me i will delete my post and retreat into banishment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 14:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know its just this is easier. I really do appreciate you explaining. Have a nice day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 06:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I wasnt aware. Dont reply Im trying to sleep please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 06:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok have a nice night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 06:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont really think its insane for a mother to say shes missed her child. And its not like she was looking for suitors for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 06:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 05:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A: try taking it out and wiping it down
B: use glare to check for scratches
C: check the ps4 for updates.
If all else fails get new disk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 05:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im no doc but I think so I mean isnt a vaccine just like a less potent version of the disease </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 05:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really depends on the person. Dont change for anyone but yourself. Do whichever you like more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 05:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey dude I just had my first yesterday. Dont be nervous you will be helped. Just some things to expect.  He:she is prob going to ask a bunch of questions to get to know you better. Im happy for you. did I help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 05:37:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Work hard do sports join clubs join the student body etc etc just be a model student </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 05:35:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im really sorry kid I dont know what to tell you but to suck it up I know it sucks now but just think how satisfying it will feel to finally send that Im fucking blocking you. Dont text me dont even look in my general direction. Text </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 04:22:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I join do I get... perks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 00:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Course not you fecking hecker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 00:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wit but by that logic... OMG i have it solved. Ok so all the Vikings are dead therefore Valhalla and ( cant remember the name of their hell) are full so when you get there they tell you its full and send you back until ragnarock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 00:10:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love my librarian. I have advisory with her and today she had an appointment so instead of getting us a sub or something she basically cut class short and we all just roamed the halls. I got a bag of Doritos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 00:07:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who.... who do I murder to get one of these precious beasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 00:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You ok op? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 23:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I downvoted this because Im a party pooper ( thats a joke I upvoted) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 23:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kyle is the antithesis of Kevin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 20:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And you have succeeded indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 20:44:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *sweating* uh no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:55:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because my mom is a bit strict </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do not have your babies give you head I repeat do not have your babies give you head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please sir take it back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take it back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I got the joke I just like to point out that kind of stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Match the posters with similar paint designs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You arent making investments from the time youre one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, thats not how this works. For something to be your favorite you have to like it more than the other things youve seen. So how can you like it more if youve never seen/read/heard it. You mean the thing that could be your all time favorite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:15:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> H e l l </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:14:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Help me Mr. Wizard LMFAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 19:13:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk I think its dumb as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 17:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That boy helicoptering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats weird dude that really shouldnt be surprising.  And what do you mean its not like ... thats exactly what happened. Also good on you for getting a compliment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah Im kinda done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really?! Thats weird. I just copied the format of everyone else here. You shouldve seen it coming bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:48:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Bro have you had tacos those are the shit. I live from taco to taco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 cousins dont count </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forgive me little ones. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 14:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And they switch it back whenever it suits them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 14:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem but uh can I as why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 14:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 06:00:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My door got taken off one time. Yeah I used to have the most fucking insane parents. And it was for the dumbest shit I think it was that I was having trouble pushing the trundle bed back under my bunk bed and my mom called me fat and lazy and stupid I WAS FUCKING SEVEN so I did the normal kid thing and cried she then got so mad that I was crying she told my dad to take off my door. Fun life. Note my family is much better now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha ha dude the kid isnt getting vaccines we dont have to worry about it turning 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Back before my parents divorced if my mom got woken up or if anyone woke her up she would go on a rampage it was horrible. Shes better now but to this day I have a paralyzing fear of waking people up. For example: my father snores bad and he only has a one room apartment with one bed (its a long story)  so we have to share the bed and he always says just wake me up if Im snoring to bad. But I just cant do it and I end up not sleeping all night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:48:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because makes have been made out to be sexual monsters and women can do no wrong. When a woman looks at a man the man gets happy because she has graced him with her divine beauty when a guy looks t a girl hes a creep and a weirdo even if she is wearing two dimes and a dorrito if you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this isnt quite trashy per say its more just gross and a bit distasteful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually that video got removed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:28:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No Im only on episode like t or three because I have to watch it in secret, due to the fact that my parents wont let me watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you actually trying to speak Spanish or is this a joke. Im curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait isnt skipping school a good thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 22:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make it clear how you feel some boys really have no idea about hints and if he keeps coming for you just drop him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 22:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course its normal they are family. Yes you should text them and if they are bad then at least you can know they are dipshits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 22:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Terrible pms cramps. Dead grandma. Dead pet. Dead parents. Sick. Mentally sick. Etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 22:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh yes like super illegal. Unless its self defense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 22:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You will feel better when you tell her I promise you. Come what may </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 17:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welp you gotta look somewhat passable and you need to be charismatic oh and be funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 17:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 17:38:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are rookie numbers you gotta boost those up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 17:35:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The comment has 22k likes so either he doesnt know his numbers or people keep liking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 17:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You want to give me a treat 

I want to give you a treat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 05:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im fourteen and its awkward at 14 trust me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 05:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You, I like you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 05:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont do drugs kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 05:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 02:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So honestly Im just a kid dude and I want to help a lot but I cant all I can tell you is look for opportunities keep your head up and when you come to America, be normal about maple syrup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:55:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok but feelings arent always the truth are they </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so first of all suicide is never the answer just take that right off the table ok. Now what you need to know is that everyone has different expertises you may be bad at one thing and great at another </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well just to get some salary coming in try and work at Walmart or something. Did you go to a university? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go out and watch it chapter 2 at the theatre. It doesnt require physical activity and it includes horror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:37:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go now and post the memes of your destiny with every </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:34:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yesnt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This should be eeyore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I serve the communist nation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DRAGON </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 18:53:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I concur. Another rule is if someone ask for help try to help as best you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 18:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no that is a bad rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 15:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no problem. did I help you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 15:17:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That really sucks but if they didnt seem mad I dont think you have anything to worry about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 15:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is he neutered? That helps with aggression a lot. If not try to do that immediately. Did the guy seem mad? Did you get his number? If you did try to invite him over to your house to apologize serve cookies and lemonade, and grovel without making obvious that you are groveling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 15:09:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes make fun of the younger generations as well for they are too small to join our glorious ranks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 15:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats with the post op are you good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 15:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I do concur these are the rules but you mustnt forget Karen bad as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 15:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks kind sir and I already have. Ill be watching for anything out of the ordinary but I like to think the best of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks that should work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey so I have kind of an awkward thing to ask. I know you said I helped you earlier in your first reply but the auto bot didnt pick it up I think I had to be in its own little sentence at the end. Do you think you could just please kinda respond with helped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe stop physical torture and go more to physiological torture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tend to go with nothing much hbu unless something big is actually currently going on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jacks chop shop you kill em we grill em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:18:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the summer of 16 when I got that old six string soon it was come and gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey if they dont appreciate you for the amazing person you are then they dont deserve you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hi Im 14(m) and bored as heck so I wanna make new friends </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im looking for any teenage friends to talk to dm me if you think we could be friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey so they dont seem like your friends they seem like bitches. Just wanna point that out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes that makes sense. Anyway Im glad I could help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:06:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats good, thats very good . do you have any other passions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry to say it like this but some people just live off causing pain in others. Try surrounding yourself with new people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:03:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok listen and listen good. Staying in is bad for you it may seem more comfortable or better but it isnt. Find some way to go out just little things at first like taking a walk or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 04:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It may be about your surroundings. Try using online dating. If you dont mind me asking how exactly do they treat you badly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 03:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah thats pretty important personally I find they tend to bloom right next to my ps4/Nintendo switch/Xbox 360. As well as near books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 03:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope there are no options. Your life is worth living. There is help out there. And above all I may not know you you may be a stranger on the internet but I fucking love you and I need you to know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 03:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No prob I love being helpful but you need to remember not to study too hard. It can become easy to lose yourself in the books but dont. Always make sure to stop and smell the roses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 03:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you def have to warn her. Make her aware of his bad tendencies and try to make him aware of them as well but for the most part Im sorry there isnt much you can do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 03:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first thing you need to do is the most important. You need to calm down. I know it may seem like that is the last thing you want to do but trust me. Right now there is nothing you can do. And for your gap year along with hanging out with your friends try to study for the coming year if you walk into that school with the knowledge to walk through with ease it will be much better. Also have like a bike or a scooter or something to get around campus to save gas on the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im trying to post to AMA but the post wont upload is it just me or is it something else. What do i do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 03:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Did google just go down for anyone else? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 03:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok then. Just uh, is it for me or him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont give the horrid wretch ideas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I was really confused, cuz theres a guy that says he is filthy frank on TikTok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait filthy frank is dead?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who tf Is George </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grooms bush </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It not a square its a shortened rectangle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm I guess we just found the hoe. (this is a joke do not take it seriously) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 01:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you I had no idea what the diff was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 00:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I thought you knew from experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 00:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one about how to lose all your karma and Ive been trying to find the one where you said something good about pewdiepie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 00:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was stalking your profile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 00:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Total erectile dysfunction day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 22:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or vag pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 22:41:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yes but actually no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 22:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big dicks, suck mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 22:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh dang I just broke up with someone and I was like uhh is this ____ then I saw the dude and I was like nope. It will get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 21:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When your a killer but they aint pushing you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 21:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *laughs in gay* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 21:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg it took me a second I was like why would he be taking chem in English class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 17:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey at least we know theres at least one whos self aware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 17:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If only </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 17:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so done with women Im thinking of going gay.( this is a joke meant to bring joy do not take it seriously) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 20:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yummy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 20:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you mean 

Because you make me want to hang myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 16:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sit with her at lunch, and when/ if she asks why say because you seem really cool and I want to get to know you better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 08:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got something else I wanna stick in your ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 07:48:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wheres the link op </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok thats fine but you should still stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:32:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would you do that. We just want a place full of supportive people to bare our pain to or to talk to when were lonely. You suck, or at least that sucks. You should stop. Are you even a teenager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmhm. Sure I dont believe you but that doesnt really matter. Just stop being an asshole online. This is your brain *egg* this is your brain on drugs * scrambled egg* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats fine also dont do drugs thats bad for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not cringy, its just stating a fact and opening up discussion on the topic. He/she is right they do suck. If you dont care then just keep scrolling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then dont be an asshole. I call em out its how I was raised. See I was raised right you were clearly.... not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:10:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the fuck dude why are you such an asshole. If you dont care, just keep scrolling and dont comment at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is like 1:30 too but it gets taken up by my sport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 06:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I just want you to know, I care about you, I love you, and above all else, no matter what, you will be ok; you will get through this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 05:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha ha Im  already on my knees for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 04:51:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh Ill drop. Drop on my knees for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 04:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Laptop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 04:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I know and I hate it. Im going to go break things now as well as vandalize things and just generally be a hoolagin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 22:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow this text was a long time ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 06:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about no hetero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 00:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy fuck what a ride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 23:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok then Ill keep watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 21:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit and archerio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 21:44:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not sure you know what the word accidentally means. Sure being curious is human nature no so is literally killing cute animals. Im not kidding thats why your body says squeeze when you see something cute. Humans have been resisting their nature for eons in favor of functioning society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 21:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah sure. Lets see what you can come up with. Im open to the idea it might be real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 20:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do these people think this is ok. They want no sexism but to do that we need get this, sexism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 16:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you mean he got a new piata this morning. And look at all the candy that came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 16:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He thorsty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 16:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont use the precious butter for your unholy drinking.(this is satire) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 16:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No they are not. Not if you give them the love, affection, and training that we give to every other dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 15:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its another kids hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 15:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He cumming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 15:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course I doz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 14:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He gets the outstanding 15/10 borks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 14:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done bro. I hope you win your bet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 14:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it helps like when I dont know my address but my mom needs to pick me up she can just go there and find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 04:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg ur my new favorite person imma go follow you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 04:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He looks like he isnt sure how he feels about popsicles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I need help resetting my Apple ID password. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 04:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 04:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No this is Patrick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 04:23:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He looks like if asians were stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 04:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But....but..... the sacred texts said so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 04:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its been 90 days are you still looking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 03:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha ha thats why I plan to die at 23 you losers gonna live a full life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 03:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No lunch is when I eat. Or when I do the homework I was too fucking tired to do the night before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 03:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fuck teachers do you have. I wish I could, Im already like a week ahead so if I slept nothing bad would happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 03:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I go to bed at 10 Im just constantly spent. Not quite physically every time but emotionally and intellectually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 03:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A: idk if youve ever seen a five year old chase her brother around the house but it can go on for hours and hours.

B: as a high school kid I can guarantee you I do not have any time for naps. I wake up at 6:50 in the morning go to school I dont get back home till like 6:30 then I have to do a mountain of homework and be in bed by 10 only to repeat it all over again. Given I go to the hardest high school in my town. but still I do not have time for any naps whatsoever unless I want to take them during chemistry or geometry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 22:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God I hate that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 21:40:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god is roblox porn really a thing?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 21:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think hentai is one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 21:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hentai for the win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 21:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The on. He is woke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 21:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im glad youre ok now I really am. And youre right, toxic people dont deserve your time your thought or your presence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 16:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What In the swiggity swaggity fuck is this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 16:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is dark mode there are no others. Seace your snooping boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 04:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its fine but why nsfw? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I need help resetting my Apple ID password. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 04:24:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 03:08:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah dude its all good. If you look on my profile you can see my doggo Felicia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 02:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah I can see it just poking out on the left side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 01:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk it just looked off. And I will, pasta every day all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 01:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know that dude. But I didnt know that you didnt make it. Anyway have a mice day imma go eat now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 01:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ik all that but I just wanted to know why you gave your monstrosity one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 00:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the double op? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 00:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup. Met a girl named Hannah who believed she was a cat person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 00:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is just so extra fucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 21:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup my inability to focus and near constant hyperactivity is somehow caused by the government. FUCK BIG PHARMA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 21:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That final text almost made me throw up. To tell your own son to kill himself is.... utterly and completely insane as well as incompetent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 20:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See in some special occasions its ok. Like my mom made me put that life 360 app on my phone and I really dont mind. Its just for my safety in case she cant find me or something. I did some hacker man shit so I get a notification when she checks in on me and she never uses it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 20:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 20:46:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so yeah wtf. thanks bro this makes it much clearer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 20:43:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we all know what she uses that lone cucumber  for boys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 18:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 18:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats fair, I understand now. Thank you kind stranger for this pleasant conversation but I must go now as I am in class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 18:16:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean he isnt wearing any clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 18:05:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no problem I love to help out and yes you should try just dont worry too much. Hate those fines dont we </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 18:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes definitely if you live in a place like that the collective is against you. But that isnt always a bad thing. To be mad in an insane world is not madness it is sanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 18:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 would buy a poster of him and put it in my room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 18:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no idea but cats are built for doing exactly that. Their tails help them balance and their paws are specialty made to cling to things. Although it is smart to watch out for them, I wouldnt worry too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 17:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude mansplaining isnt real those people dont know what theyre saying and I may not have been there but Im sure your presentation was just fine. It is literally the job of the person presenting to explain everything like you are teaching the class. Im sure you were fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 17:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was probably in oil form but still even for epilepsy at that age your brain is so sensitive even in oil form ( because Im sure they didnt pass him a joint) it is going to have harmful effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 17:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Skyrim because its amazing. The game almost never ends giving you countless quests to do once you beat the game. Plus you get to a certain point of power where nothing can kill you and youre just a god, that part feels amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 17:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but still. Like the other stuff Ive heard of before but giving a four year old weed is like next level insane to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 14:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but still. That baby is still growing and developing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Around four </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neither. My father is a bigot and my mother is a manipulative person... which I guess but if I had to choose I choose mom. Im just closer to her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I learned that one real young! Oh wait thats a bad thing right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:26:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to but not anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck sports I just cant care enough about them to get into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive met these people. They see my cold indifference and get obsessed with me. I think they are attracted to me because they think in my coldness they can stay by me for safety I dont like these people and see them as cowards and worms beneath me. Although if they come to me and ask for protection I will give it for a fee this is well know at my school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like is a strong word Ive stolen a fuck ton of money from my best friend but another friend of mine I would never not because I just like her that much or anything. It is because logically I want to keep one shred of my humanity left. I do that by choosing one person conforming my personality to suit theirs and they become my person. I am currently choosing a new person and when I do that I can drop the old one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont praise it trust me if your money goes missing you know one. If your friends stories arent adding up, you know one. I am genuinely by most peoples standards a horrible person just objectively. Stop being edgy and shit. God dang I dont feel anger and you still annoy me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont make many decisions with emotion. I do them without giving it the proper thought but not with emotion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont be jealous because of the stigma. if I told anyone what I am they would automatically assume I will hurt and steal and lie... given that is true in most cases but dont assume shit. Like what if I was on meds for it and you just made me a social pariah for no reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not diagnosed but I suspect it highly based on a very set of traits I have. And as for embracing it I dont give a fuck, I will use you to get what I want and I will do it again and again. Im good at it too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh uh well then. That answers the question I came on this sub with. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im recently noticing my sociopathic tendencies, such as my near lack of real emotion, my manipulativeness my compulsive lying and stealing as well ass a complete lack of care for other human being and most animals( dogs are my weak spot) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do I love my doggys and honestly nothing else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:55:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont have a solution for nihilism. I love it I subscribe to it. If nothing matters then I get to do whatever the fuck I want. And if it does Im still going to do whatever the fuck I want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my experience yes. And no at the same time. Ive been around not normal girls my whole life and none of them knew I was sociopathic. Also sociopaths arent genuine we lie all the time and change our personality to get you to like us so we can get what we want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good question. I do find myself compelled to study a person but not because they seem interesting or things like that, but to better shape my personality to get what I want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope I dont really have relationships, its more fuck buddys to fill my needs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 29 but then again Ive never been in a marital relationship or anything, some of these questions dont apply to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:46:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really because since I cant really feel much I cant feel bad for the things I do and if I dont feel bad why would I care enough to stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Not really. I lie cheat steal and all of it means nothing but a fleeting thrill afterwards I think of nothing but the next object do break or person to steal from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not much more than nominal but yes. My mother and my friend. I respect them because they are the only ones who make me actually feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I got like 4 of the very outer ring ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is true that Im some cases I have read they do use aborted fetal dna BUT the fetus was already planned to be aborted it was that or nothing. Might as well help some of us breathers over here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean at least he tried something right. Ive never been given anything like this from my parents for lunch on 9/11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My Abue always comes to my house when Im sick to give me a big hug of her special lemonade it always makes me feel better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See this isnt your fault though its bad formatting you read left to right not top to bottom this isnt China </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 01:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dislike documentaries. I know its very broad but I just cant get into them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I am a teen with add and I am possibly a sociopath. I go to the hardest school in my town. AMA </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 22:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 22:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She gave her 4 year old cannibis holy fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh idk then bro I live in the USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh where do you live </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why.... why does the tall one have a crotch bulge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does everyone include doctors? Could it be other things with symptoms like depression? Could it be hypochondria? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welp now I have to try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But scp 096 has no hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The answer is yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:14:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What anime is this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw the meme showing this sub. Thought Id make myself known. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 14:01:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And she didnt even get fired. After trying to physically harm a student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 05:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No time and the way we calculate and measure it is man made. Our universe is linear one thing happens then the next. Our measurement-of time is just whats in between point a and b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 05:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One could argue that it does in fact oxidize the human body therefore creating the slowest poison ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 04:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is basically the if I fits I sits but for dogs. If I tired I sleeps anywhere anywhen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 04:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 04:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both equally edible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 01:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idfk bro, they were probably too insecure to go on stage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 00:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah thats insane. For you to be out of state and her be saying she needs to know what your doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 00:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends how old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 22:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mm no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thought this might fit here too </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 22:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 21:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is nothing. This is an over reaction. It is perfectly normal to want to make sure. If he had told you he wasnt sure they were his even though he still loves them with all his heart, you would have freaked out. Ive seen the situation. did you talk to him about it after finding out l? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 21:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The words are ok but the picture is the problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 21:28:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Women can do whatever that fuck they want and nobody can do anything. That sucks ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 18:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 18:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ima baaaad guy. Duh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 17:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup this happens and it kinda makes me mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 04:54:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bitch tell me something new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 21:41:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You ever been on r/insaneparents ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 21:25:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem have a nice day bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 17:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 02:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  But I have no friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 00:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I did and I saw it. I just dont remember doing it twice but I guess i did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 21:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats not how that works bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 21:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The next day sucks bad tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 18:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah I guess I did. Thats strange I dont remember doing that twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 14:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Naps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 14:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry the wording was bad on it what I meant was its a place to have some fun and do dumb shit. Nothing too horribly bad but cursing with your friends and teasing your pals its fun its a place to find yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 14:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree very much. I mean its not like Im doing anything super duper bad but still </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 05:00:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ttyl bro night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 04:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah its all good. Listen man its getting late here I gotta go Ill dm you in the morning cuz you seem like a cool guy/girl and I wanna keep talking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lets talk about my choir teacher </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 05:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so Im in high school now (not going to say which grade), but when I was in 8th grade I took choir and ooooohhhhh boy let me tell you guys about this abusive horrible person.  I hear you typing oh how bad could she have been, your probably over reacting, well no so hold ur thumbs and listen to my stories. 

Ok so lets call her Mrs. Martinez (not her real name). so when I walked into that class on the first day of school I thought it was going to be a cool class because there was only 9 people in the entire class, ( thats important later). so this teacher would have regular breakdowns, and I know that doesnt sound that bad, I dont know what was going on at her home so it could have been for a good reason. Although when you start calling students shitty kids and disrespectful for talking when she said we could. Or for getting water while we were on break then you cross the line but that isnt the worst of it. She chose three people for some random reason and berated is constantly it was me my friend Lauren and Gemma. Gemma got the worst of it to the point where the teacher would make her cry openly in class, and Gemma had told us that she had cried at home too and at one point I decided fuck it this isnt right we have to report her to the principal. So the three of us went to the counselor because the principal was never anywhere to be found and told her about what had been happening to us. There know you know everything you need to know about for me to tell you what happened next.


Me:mega erection. L:Lauren. G:Gemma. T:teacher 




So we walked into class and the teacher was late so we all sat down in our assigned spots.the teacher bursted through the door and...


T: ok who the heck reported me to the counselor!

(My whole class was just facing forward and she was behind us) 

T: well who was it! You might as well tell me because I have an appointment with the principal and Im just going to ask her. Shell tell me!

( that is very wrong when you go to the counselor it is super confidential and they arent allowed to tell anyone)

M:(quietly to Lauren) fuck it Im going to tell her it was me so shell shut up.

L:no dont do it youll get in trouble.

M:fuck it Im so done I dont care.

G:m no dont 

( I then stood up and turned around to face the teacher) 

M: you know what T it was me I reported you because you consistently stop class for your breakdowns. Which I can handle but you make Gemma cry every week.

T:Im giving you a referral!

M: do it I havent done anything wrong. If Im suspended Ill spend my days eating ice cream watching 

T:tries to slap me.

M: grabs her hand before she can touch me.

she then fell on her desk and cried. She called the office to send an aide to replace her as she was too emotionally distraught to teach. You should know the aides help the disabled kids. So when she got over herself and went on the aide got there she just sent the aide back waisting valuable time the aide could have used to help disabled kids. 


Sorry if the grammar is bad English isnt my first language and Im on mobile. Ask any questions you have down in the comments below. Mods dont take me down none of the names are real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Testing testing, can I post on r/memes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 04:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it possible to start a sub if so how? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 00:39:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Credit to u/criptidcrisis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are you doing up so late? Go to bed you hooligans. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 03:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I wouldve posted on r/memes but I dont have the karma </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 04:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Keep it rolling boyz </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 00:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> if I go to class its golf but I can also just not go and it wont matter since they already took attendance. Should I go? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 22:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An interesting title </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 02:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do I find my product key </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 00:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The product key on my iOS 10 computer has disappeared and everything I see on finding it says that I should have an email with the product key, but the problem is that I got this computer years and years and years ago. I dont even have access to the email I had when I bought it what can I do? Am I screwed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My fam has a secret </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 05:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so let me explain something my mom and aunt are adopted but not traditionally. So originally my Abue (grandma ) was married to my bio grandfather and they had 2 kids my mom and my aunt but they got a divorce and my Abue met my current grandpa and married him as a show of love he adopted my mom and aunt to make them a legal whole family. So apparently my bio grandfather did some pretty bad shit and Ive only heard about like 2 things but apparently he did something so bad at some point that was supposedly the last straw on my Abues marriage but its a huge family secret what he did. To this day I have not been told what he did and anyone I ask refuses to tell me anything. They just shake their heads and say its not my secret to tell. Im not sure if this is this the right sub to put it on please give me orange arrows and English isnt my first language so be kind. Have a nice day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My computer wont run </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 04:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing on my computer will run except for steam download games not my web browser or anything I think I may have a virus but my malware wont open either. When I try and reset my computer it just says error and that something went wrong but not what. What do I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My computer wont run </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 11:58:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a desktop computer and whenever i try loading up chrome it opens up the closes I think k I may have a virus but my malware wont open either what do I do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thought I should post this so yall out there have all the facts. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 02:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just happened to me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 00:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is my baby Felicia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 00:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do yall want dog pics? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 22:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pictures I took in Montana </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 23:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pictures I took in Montana </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 23:44:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dont mind me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 04:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> lol hey reddit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-23 06:48:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Entitled dude at AT T </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 22:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So Im a teenager and my birthday just came and I got a new iPhone XR to replace my old shitty Samsung. the next day my mom took me to the nearest AT T to get it activated and get a new case, but while I was there, there was also another man there he was behind us so I didnt quite get all of it but from what I understood he came in and was asking to buy a SIM card, but as store policy they will not just give you a SIM card they need the device and will switch the cards in house, and he was getting pissed off he was yelling at the lady helping him and yelled at the poor girl for the manager when he told the man the exact same thing he flipped the fuck out. he was yelling and shit all around the store so the manager asked him to leave, he would not so my mother and I having finished activating my new phone, were walking out and he looked to my mom talking to the manager and said ask this lady Im not being disruptive why should I leave and my mom replied you are being an asshole and you should get out  he then called corporate to file a complaint as we walked out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>