<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8756</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 16:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1000% I've lurked in their sub before, starting back in 2016. Contrary to what some men say, MGTOW has always been utterly toxic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 15:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please report him. He probably has a sexual interest in children and has/will molest others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 15:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok. I understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 10:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I deal with this by just ranting on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 09:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This can be counted as sexual abuse. There's a reason why parents stop bathing with their kids or don't do that at all. Kids eventually start being more self-conscious about nakedness, especially after starting puberty. They need their own personal space. Any adult that violates that is committing abuse. And the fact that you asked her to stop and she didn't shows that she completely disregards your rights and your intrinsic need for privacy.

A call to CPS and it would be taken care of right away. But it's your choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My mother thinks I'm a parasite. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 09:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As is normal with narcissists, my mother literally says that her love is conditional. She thinks that if your children aren't 'successful and obedient', you are not obliged to provide for them.

She also calls children parasites, and thinks I'm a parasite. I am furious at her because I was 100% planned. So besides her insane standards of success and obedience, she chose to have a child when she knew on some level that she would regret it.

Why am I a parasite? Truth be told, I don't exactly know. I'm a university student, I have a job, I keep my room clean, I don't bother anyone. But I also have ASD (which my parents don't believe and deny), which makes me very crappy at social situations and means I often have zero friends. According to them that makes me a complete failure. My mother constantly gloats that regardless of what I do, she has the right to kick me out.

I promise that when I finally leave, I'll get some sort of justice on her for the physical and mental abuse she put me through. I'll tell my entire family about her true behaviour, and I'll open a court case. And I'll have fun watching my parents cry over their 'happy family' image being ruined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 09:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi there. Running away should only be a last option after you've exhausted all other options. If you're living in an abusive or toxic environment and absolutely need to get out, you have 2 options: either call CPS and they'll have you removed, or wait a year and apply for emancipation from your parents, where you will be classified as an adult who can make her own decisions. Running away should only be an option if the state has failed to take you away from abuse, because it's incredibly dangerous. In the meantime keep growing your youtube channel by any means possible. Sure 1K a month is not much, but if you get another job you'll be earning much more, perhaps even enough to live on. There's also other ways to earn money online, such as paid fanfiction and paid surveys, questionnaires and product reviews. Also can you link me to your youtube channel please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 16:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  "girls usually don't grow after getting your first period" 

Wtf no. The average age for a girl to get her period is 11. You telling me girls just stop developing at 11 years old????

But yeah. As my body has matured over the years, my Nmum's comments just kept getting more numerous. Because she is so so jealous of me. She's jealous of my physical beauty (I'm average tbh) when her body has always been fucked up from medical conditions. She's jealous of me being (looking anyways) 'happy' with very few/no friends when she has not a single friend. And yeah it's very very common for Nmums to be very jealous of their daughter's beauty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 16:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's probably not an uncommon experience. And tbh I'm furious at the trans community for immediately hopping on the hormones bandwagon any time a young person has identity issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 16:48:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if hypothetically you were the same age, it is still wrong, and if authorities found out they would most likely order serious therapy for her. But you were not the same age. You were a child (at 10), while she was in her early teens. Teenagers, though not the smartest or most moral of people, know the difference between right and wrong. They know how to manipulate, even 2 year olds know how to manipulate. Cognitively, a ten year old and even a 12 year old are on very different levels of development. One is still a child and the other is going through puberty and thinking about love and sex and experimenting with life. She knew it was very wrong, she knew she was being manipulative, she knew she had power over you because of the age gap and the fact that you were siblings, and she knew it would harm you.

Please report her. She probably has a sexual interest in children and will molest other children in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 16:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never experienced this but it's easy to tell why they do it. They are narcissistic. Of course they want their kids to look like them. They see all their kids' accomplishments as their accomplishments. Therefore, if their children are successful and strangers don't link them to the narcissistic parent's 'efforts' for all those years, they get angry and resentful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 16:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would feel a need to report my abuser. Simply put: abusers are not going to stop with you. They are going to do it to someone else too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First time properly drinking. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 08:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. Before this I tasted a few shots of alcoholic drinks (non of which I liked). Of course when you mix the shots with some fruit juice it becomes much more tolerable.

So I went to a dance club and properly drank for the first time. Tried more single shots I didn't like and had to settle with pineapple/cranberry vodka
I took 4 small cups and 1 and a half big ones. I ended up being literally the most sober one out of my 25+ university gang. Everyone complimented me on that, and I had to help the rest of them get back to the hotel.

I know it sounds stupid but I'm paranoid that I in fact did get tipsy and couldn't tell. People told me some can get drunk on 2 glasses of what I had, and others on 10. I had 5 and a half and people told me I have a high tolerance level. I remember pretty much everything from last night. But I think I experienced a bit of a decline of cognitive ability. I was a bit unsteady on my feet, felt a bit weightless and a bit freer I guess. At one point when I was thinking of ordering another glass the word pineapple just couldnt come to me and I just kept thinking 'lemon vodka' even though I knew it wasn't right and that they didn't have lemon vodka. But all that could be a result of it being so late, the nervousness of drinking and clubbing for the first time and the annoying loud music and lights. And I'm pretty stupid in real life. 

Finally, I physically couldn't drink anymore because my stomach was feeling upset by the sheer amount of liquid I was drinking, especially since I ate a big meal before. And I didn't wake up with a headache, just tiredness from sleeping at 1AM.

So what do you think, did I get tipsy or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On a live-in, still am totally inept at socialising. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So my social life has always been nil. Whenever I try to make friends it either fails or never goes anywhere. When faced with so much rejection and loneliness, you get used to it, and you become a little selfish. Why do I keep trying to socialise? To please my parents, because everyone keeps telling me it's good for me, provides experience, and I know it might make me better at my future career or at least desensitize me to anxiety while socialising.

My first day of this blessed live-in and it's already started to go bad. I didn't participate in one of the activities which was a drinking game (I don't, can't drink), coupled with doing stunts like pole dancing and picking random psychological conversations with random bar patrons. Then, my roommate, who I bonded really well with in the afternoon, left. She left to a room all on her own because she claimed she moves a lot during the night. So now I'm on my own. And I can't help but suspect I weirded her out or something, even if we got along really well and were similar in a lot of ways.

I'm constantly questioning why I keep trying to socialise if it never works out. I'm pretty sure I'm depressed, because I have no joy and no hope, and when I try to socialise it's like I realise I exist again. But still, I exist in a world that I can never fully be part of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 11:36:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't stay quiet. Shatter people's wrong beliefs that can harm others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 11:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is BMI meaningless? Then what should be used to calculate if one is at a healthy weight or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 11:03:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I apologise cause my parents are kind of conspiracy theorists. They believe that exercise burns fewer calories than we think, a calorie is not simply a calorie, and that people's weight is heavily determined by their genes and metabolism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 10:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are you talking about? From wikipedia:  **normal** weight: 18.5 to 25.

At every doctor's visit they told me I was at a normal weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why am I at a normal weight? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 10:44:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  #x200B;

This seems like an odd question. But people keep questioning why I'm at a normal weight and I've wondered myself because based on what I eat, I should be overweight. As in I'm not skinny, just at a normal BMI of 25/26, and I could afford to lose a kilo or 2. I was a bit overweight at 12 because I stress ate a lot.

My whole family except my grandma, me and my brother, are fat. My mother has diabetes, PCOS and hypertension and I inherited the body type and PCOS from her. My parents' weight has gotten slightly better because they're following a fasting/keto diet. My father tells me I'm at a normal weight due to metabolism/genetics. But if that were the case, then I (and my brother) would be genetic miracles.

So why am I at a normal weight when the best my parents can be is overweight? Well I generally accept it that my mother's body and metabolism is fucked up because of diabetes and PCOS, plus the many medications that she takes. This is all while she does all the housework and makes sure to walk at least an hour a day. Ironically her weight was worse when she was young and she lost weight as she got older and learned how her body worked/got better medication. My father spends long hours working and doesn't walk much because he doesn't have much time. He's kept his weight sort of under control with a keto diet and fasting. My brother is a gym junkie and is also on a sort of keto diet. Enough said.

Pretty much everyone in my family is a tiny bit jealous of me, and tell me I'm at a normal weight because of my metabolism or genes (based on what I eat). I'm sure it doesn't solely have to do with what I eat, I do walk quite a to just get to places. My eating schedual is not existant and I just eat when I'm hungry, and because of this I skip meals but also snack a lot. But I also eat quite a lot of fat and sugar, more than is recommended by health experts, with not many fruit and veg in sight.

So tell me, why am I not fat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why am I at a normal weight? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 10:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 09:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have a horrible mother. Parents are supposed to uplift their children, instill confidence in them, and actually want them to be as successful as possible. A good parent wants their child to be more successful than they are. Narcissistic parents on the other hand want to tear down their children and keep them in an infantile state so they will never leave. Work hard and do not give up on your dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 07:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no excuse for physical violence. Some parents were never meant to be parents. I don't know why some people refuse to believe that parents can be abusive and regret having their child. You have to fight to make a place for yourself in the world, because you sure don't belong in your family. Your needs will never be met in your family and therefore you have to leave as soon as you can. Study hard, go to college, go on student exchange, leave and make a life for yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 05:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 17:26:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scared and unsure. I'm terrible at adulting, terrible at life. I'm dumb as a rock and people have let me known that. I can comfort people all I want behind a screen but I doubt I could do it effectively in a real life therapy setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 15:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know a fact that's worse.

There's this movie, don't know if you've heard of it, it's called Mommy Dearest. Somewhat well-known in narcissistic abuse victim circles. In short, the movie depicts the supposed real-life histrionic behaviour and narcissistic abuse from some famous actress in the 80s towards her children.

Some people who watch it think the acting of the mother's tantrums is exaggerated and not believable, while people who have actually had the misfortune of living with someone like that can say it is 100% possible. And then, there are some people who actually sympathise with the mother and really do see her children as disrespectful when they're completely innocent. Scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 15:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry your family doesn't believe you. Though they are blood relatives, I don't think you should waste time on people who deny abuse. Sometimes it's better to walk alone than follow others off a cliff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I am cursed and I want to die to prevent the inevitable. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 15:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was born into an abusive family. I have autism spectrum disorder which makes me weird and terrible at interacting with people. I'm terrible at the sciences and life in general. Yet I decided to go into psychology because I'm very interested in the subject, it's the only thing I'm good at, and on some level I want to help people. But I can barely interact with people or relate with many of them. I can be a straight-A student but I'll probably be crap at the job of a psychologist or therapist. 

If the meaning of life is to help people (which I believe it is), then I have nothing left to live for. I can barely help myself. I can't confidentally say I could talk anyone out of suicide because I think of dying every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 13:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who make more money than it takes to live very comfortably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 13:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you tell me more about that psychology? I don't understand it. Statistically I know that poor people who become rich are still likely to become extremely greedy and hoard wealth. But at the same time I don't understand it, am sure I would not be one of those hypothetical people, but would be scared shitless of turning into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 13:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then say it out loud. Don't let people talk over or deny your experiences. Just because they don't have an awful family doesn't mean there aren't those who have shit families. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Most rich people are bad and corrupt. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 13:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before anyone says it: I'm not jealous of rich people. I don't want to be rich and I certainly never want to develop the attitudes that come with being rich.

Rich people are terrible because their greed knows no bounds. They earn way more money than they could ever spend. Research shows that if all the rich banded together they could do endless good for the world. But what do they choose to spend their money on? Watches and cars that cost as much as houses, private jets, gold toilets, billion-dollar yachts, the most expensive brands out there that aren't even long-lasting etc. etc.

If I earned the amount of money a billionaire earns I'd donate 80% of it to good causes. Money that can change the world is hoarded by people who will never use it or spend it on the most frivolous things. And yet some of them have the nerve to complain that they aren't happy. You know what can make you happy? Doing some good for the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 11:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing is I have PCOS which gives me bad acne. It's far from the level of cystic but it's bad to the point where my family points it out all the time and is visible from a distance. I'm trying medication for my condition right now but it will take months to see any progress. I do apply moisturizing creams but it doesn't make it much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Everyone tells me I 'need to be like the others'......... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 10:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 18F

I'm crushed because my father has been pressuring me to 'be like the others'. I thought he was semi-ok with me being an oddball or at least wouldn't vocalise his disapproval. Throughout my early teens I didn't used to take care of myself at all because of a lack of awareness, no familial guidance, and a depressive mood. And it looks like all that I've improved on since then has been for nothing. I will never wear makeup except for special occasions, and even then it will only be a little, because I ain't gonna waste time and money on that and it smudges no matter what. I will always struggle with my clothing choices because of my sensitivities to temperature, layers and material and my inability to match things. I will always struggle heavily with my hairstyle because I've been dealt a condition that makes my hair thin, flat and dead, and letting it down bothers me because it tickles me/feels like I have ants crawling on my shoulders.

I mean if my own father is pressuring me to fit in, no wonder no one else wants me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is TEFL really worth it in regards to pay? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 08:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Malta and TEFL schools pay 10-15 euros an hour. However I've realised that it's very unlikely I'll get more than 3 hours of work each day. And if I don't find a school that pays more than 10 euros an hour I might as well just go for a full-time waitressing job. I mean at least with that you don't have to deal with unrealistic expectations and planning lessons for 5 hours. Plus, the TEFL school I worked with pretty much scammed me. They promised me 3 hours of work 5 days a week, but then their students started reducing and after 2 weeks my work hours steadily went down until they didn't even call me in anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Everyone tells me I 'need to be like the others'......... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 08:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People who have changed their name (excluding trans people), what was the reason? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 13:30:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 13:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. My mother is an armchair critic, conspiracy theorist, crazy woman with no friends and very little to do. So she takes everything out on her parents and her husband. Whenever anyone manages to get a word in she starts ranting about how she knows the real truth and that everyone else is a stupid sheep. She thinks she's an expert scientist just because she spends hours reading on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 10:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If she tries to stop you just call the police. You're an adult and she can't control you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is anyone else very sensitive to temperature changes? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 10:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I think I have no choice but to quit because of this stupid thing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 09:20:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 20:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oops. I completely missed that part sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 18:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should be ashamed of trolling. There are people here going through actual abuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 18:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also feel I'm impossible to love. At this point I've accepted that I will never feel truly loved, and even if someone loved me, I wouldn't believe them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 17:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From when I was a child my mother called me a parasite and told me that if I didn't do my duty and did well in education she would kick me out the moment I was of age. Back then I had no choice but to do well in school so my life wouldn't be any more hellish than it already was. But of course as a grew older I naturally started to dream of better things. I didn't just work so my life wouldn't be any worse, I worked so I could make my life better. I worked to move out, to study abroad, to have a career I like, to be the best I can be and to have the best life possible. 

You have to know intrinsically that you are not the problem, your mother is. Your mother is not normal and you have to adapt to that. 

Unfortunately trauma sticks. It will never not affect you. You can only learn to minimize it and push it aside. Sometimes, much like a disability, it can stop us from doing things others do all the time and take from granted. Some people will never be able to walk, and some people will never be able to have sex because of trauma. You have the right to go at your own pace and take care of yourself as you see fit. And if you can't do something because it's too much for you then that's okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 17:20:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has CPS ever been called for your situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 17:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you have to think: "I don't think he has the guts to hit me", that's a major sign that you should turn tail and run before things get very ugly. Because no person should ever make you worry that they might hit you. That's what a healthy relationship is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 17:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes it is child abuse, and I will detail why:

 #x200B;

* Constant name-calling and insulting. Even if your child does the wrong things, it is a parent's duty not to sink down to the level of hatred, name-calling and insulting to purposely bring down the self-esteem. Religious abuse, aka using religion to manipulate and demean someone falls into this category. All those are very different from discipline.
* Falling under religious abuse too, your parents are neglectful and abusive for wanting to take your brother to a Christian counselor after trying to kill himself. Know that it is against all mental health guidelines for mental health experts to advertise themselves as religious because it shows a heavy bias on their side.
* Forcing someone to have sex with anyone is 1000% abuse. That can seriously damage a person for life.
* And wait..........did you say your parents don't beat you every day? That implies that they do beat you right? That's 1000% abuse and should not be happening. Yes there are horror stories that come out of CPS, but they are primarily there to get you out of situations detrimental to your mental and physical well being, and you sound like you're in that situation.

I suggest you call CPS right away before your brother ages out of his status as a minor. Please support each other, especially your brother. Your brother needs to know that his attractions aren't wrong or caused by the supernatural. If you work together maybe you can get out of that place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 17:00:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know. It's a very grey area and I can't say for sure if it was wrong because I wasn't there. Like, I think it makes a big difference whether she was clothed or not during that. It depends for how long she was trying to do it. On one hand, you never explicitly said no and people are not mind readers, but at the same time most people can identify when someone is uncomfortable. And then, if she knew about your past sexual abuse, it was certainly extremely insensitive of her to do that to you. I'm sorry that I can't give you a straight answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 16:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was assault, I just don't think it was sexual assault. If someone kicked a guy in the nuts it's considered assault but not sexual assault.

Childhood sexual abuse can cause both hypersexuality and hyposexuality, as well as intense feelings of guilt, shame and panic about sexual desires. Asexuality is a supposed sexual orientation where there is a complete absence of sexuality and is supposedly not linked to sexual assault. But personally I don't think complete asexuality is possible, and I do see links between asexuality and mental illness despite what the community likes to say.

But don't sweat it about sexuality. Our brains aren't completely formed until 24, and it happens that people don't experience much sexual attraction until their 20s, especially if they have underlying mental issues. 

But I hope you get justice over your mother. What she did was deplorable child abuse. Perhaps you can help your case by getting a doctor to check you out down there and get proof of any damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 15:16:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I wouldn't be considered mentally challenged. My ASD is category 1 high functioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help. I think I'm unemployable........... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 15:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 13:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you should try couples counseling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 13:23:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's messed up. It's messed up that you 12 year olds went that far with sex, but that guy was pretty shitty. Also, there is not such thing as a virginity test. The thing about the hymen is a myth, you can tear it during sports and it's not technically supposed to 'tear' during sex either. So I don't know what that doctor was on about unless they tested for sperm/dna. I'm sorry about what you went through. A good mother would be concerned about her daughter doing something like that and get to the bottom of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 12:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally no, but I know that a lot of people with abusive backgrounds do. Meekness can be a magnet for controlling people, and abused people are less likely to stand up for themselves or break up during future abuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 12:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you previously agreed to be monogamous and private and she still does these things then she 100% doesn't care about your feelings. Many narcissists and abusive people are like this in that they think abuse only comes in bruises and don't care about what people feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 12:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately some degree of narcissism exists in most parents. They see children as little toys to fawn over, to dress up, to impress others with and to gloat about their achievements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 12:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't tell if her way of coping is healthy or not. Certainly she should be talking to a therapist to help her process her memories and thoughts of the abuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 12:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. I am so so sorry for what you had to go through. Unfortunately many people who are supposed to help you will only harm you. You have to be wise and work around the system and be confident in yourself and the truth. It's clear most people around you are mean-spirited. I suggest you get proof of your mother's bad behaviour and mistreatment with your phone's microphone. Also do the police know about the drug use? Police may not take abuse seriously but they'll take drugs seriously. But otherwise, a good education is your only ticket out of there and you have to work 100x harder than other people for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 12:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it's not stupid. It's natural to want to get away from things that remind you of your trauma. And one should be grateful that moving can make such a big difference, because some people, such as those with severe PTSD can't get away from it. When I am able to, I will go no-contact, emigrate away from my country and I'll even change my name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 07:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean you've been doing it? That's good. I hope you told the therapist about your anger and are working on it. If you find that the therapist isn't competent go for a better one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 13:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then I think therapy would help you a lot. Perhaps you might even need medication. Can you afford therapy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 11:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think your parents are borderline pedos and most definitely perverts. Narcissists in general don't have a sense of boundaries, but it's a whole other level to make nasty and sexual comments about your own kids. Doing sexual activity in front of kids is considered a crime and for good reason. I've read of cases where it looks like voyerism and other kinks have their roots in childhood from when the parents are overly sexual in front of their children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 11:21:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not that I didn't realise these things, but I never had a chance to experience them. My teenage years were spent wasted and depressed because of my parents.

 #x200B;

* As a teenage girl I could barely be bothered about my clothes and appearance because I was too depressed and isolated.
* I couldn't experiment with my fashion because my mother made a huge fuss any time I had to buy something I actually needed. And she always insulted me no matter what outfit I picked.
* I couldn't go out in the weekends with my friends. I didn't really have friends because I was too depressed and anxious to make any. The few I did make, whenever I tried to go out with them my mother became overdramatic and insulting because she had to drive me.
* I could never talk about boys or my crushes, even before I realised I was bisexual. From the few times I did my parents would mock me and say I'm too ugly to ever get a boyfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 11:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a great and victorious post. I'm curious, what were the comments on facebook? Did you get any people disagreeing with you? I'd be surprised if you didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 11:02:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it won't ever go away. You can only manage and minimize it. Our trauma sticks with us for life. You seem quite successful on paper, so you would greatly benefit from therapy and perhaps a few sessions of couple counseling. You don't have to keep struggling and things don't have to get worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 10:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old is your mother? Usually incontinence strikes in the elderly. Perhaps you can contact some disability organisation to maybe get a carer or get her put in a care home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 10:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you chase her with your car? One should know to never physically fight back or sink as low as the narcissist. This is to keep your situation stable and to appear more credible when revealing the narcissist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 10:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. I'm sorry you're going through this. Your mother is horrible and your tutor is an idiot who should have his teaching licence revoked (if he even has one). It's good that you're trying to learn more than the basic garbage your tutor is teaching you. You are in school right? Because it's important that you pass your exams and get O-levels at least. If you're still going to school perhaps you can skip a few tutorship lessons and ask a teacher there to help you in their spare time. When I was in form 5 about to do O-levels, I finished school like everyone else but kept going for some extra lessons from teachers who were willing to help me. If you're homeschooled your mother is pretty much denying you an education and she can be arrested for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 10:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you mean they want to put you in a mental institution or care home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 10:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. I was insanely jealous of other children, even those younger than me, for the longest time. It wasn't until I started to see the subtle signs of child abuse in every day families that I stopped wanting to be in their place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 10:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No please don't run away. That's the worst thing you can do. People would target you for trafficking and abuse. If the police find you they would take you back to your mother. Keep trying to get the attention of a guidance councilor or CPS and explain your situation. Try to get proof of the abuse through pictures, and recording with a camera or microphone. There are apps that let you record without showing that they're recording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 06:56:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally no one regrets NC. But people always regret breaking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 06:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Books I don't know. Search Dr Ramani on youtube. She's an expert at dealing with narcissists and has written books about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 06:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally normal for narcissists. They are incredibly histrionic (if you don't know, Georgina from Mean Girls has long been theorised to have Histrionic Personality Disorder). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 06:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old are you? I cannot say for sure if it's mental a mental illness or has a neurological component. If it's neurological it's not your fault. The good thing is your anger seems to be mostly directed at stressful situations rather than people who annoy or anger you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 06:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old are you? You need to get out asap. That neglect in your schooling when your mother took it upon herself to homeschool you is 100% child abuse and if you're a minor CPS would get you out of there. What level of education have you received right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 06:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  My mom got drunk and told me that she had me because she was so lonely, and needed a friend. 

 #x200B;

Totally normal for a narcissist. They don't think of children as autonomous human beings. For them children are extensions of themselves to fawn over, to dress up, to control and construct, to gloat about their achievements, to impress others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 06:38:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>   *The advice Im looking for is how to cut family out completely without falling for guilt trips or concessions. Im also looking for advice with nparents and nsiblings and the combination of both.* 

 #x200B;

Recognise cries of help, gift-giving and apologies for what they are: manipulation. Everything that the narcissist does is to gain attention or control, nothing is genuine. If they have appeared to change it will only be for a little little while until they go back to their own ways. You will never get what you need from your mother, what a mother should give. I don't know the full story of your substance abuse or how severe it was, but I sure know that probably your mother never saw her own contributions to your problems and didn't do anything helpful. So I don't see how I could still care about a person like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 17:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your parents are utterly psycopathic. They do not deserve love and you don't have to give them love. Other people call their 'parents' egg and sperm doners because they don't even deserve the dignity to be called purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 15:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No honey you're not dramatic. Slapping and any physical attacks is 100% abusive unless used in self-defense. Even if that weren't the case, continuous and damaging words and phrases counts as emotional abuse. You should call CPS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Still a bit hazy about where can I go in psychology. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 15:42:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 15:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy crap your dad beats you up? You sound like a really responsible and independent person and you should not be suffering like this. As a general rule, narcissists will avoid feeling guilty for abuse by putting the blame on you. Please focus on moving out, you sound quite capable of doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 15:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3.7k to me sounds like a good number to start off with, but please don't take my word for it. I don't know about the rent prices in your area so be sure to shop around for affordable places with flatmates. As a general rule, not more than a 3rd of your income should go to rent. A car is infinitely useful but not always essential. You can bike it, get one of those automatic scooters or take public transport. But the most important you have to do is get a job as soon as possible. If you don't think you can get a job ASAP or immediately after you move out maybe you should wait a little.

Best of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 15:13:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not heartless. We are biologically programmed to fear and run away from things that do us harm. If all your mum has ever done was mistreat you and doesn't love you, it makes no sense to have any attachment to her. When my mother dies I will be overjoyed. The only pity I will feel is for my mistreated father who kept loving her because of his own issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 15:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Why the actual fuck do I have to deal with this? There has to be some mental disorder that causes our parents and relatives to act so shitty.*

Personality traits are partially nature and nurture. Mental disorders are also part nature and nurture, though some mental disorders like schizophrenia have stronger genetic components than others. I don't know about narcissitic personality disorder. But NPD results primarily from being spoiled too much as a child or child abuse/neglect. With all those factors it results in many cases of generational narcissism where entire families are very narcissistic and egotistical, especially since sometimes there is the golden child and the scapegoat.

 #x200B;

*Does anyone here have really a fucked up sense of sexuality?*

The vast majority of people who grow up with Nparents do. Narcissists will shame anything about you, especially with things close to people's hearts like love and sexuality. My mother raged at a 13 year old me because I liked the 9th doctor instead of the 10th or 11th doctor from Doctor Who and for that claimed I had terrible taste in guys. I don't show that I have a sexuality to my parents, and certainly not that I'm bisexual. I read a story of one guy, a furry who was convinced that his Christian parents' insane control and opinions regarding sexuality made him direct his sexuality to anthropomorphic animals. I suppose there are theories related to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like your post. The rare moment that a narcissists falls is a great thing for every victim of abuse. Unfortunately most narcissists maintain some level of attention or control over a few people right up till death. With any luck she'll remain alone until she's put in a caring home with underpaid staff who ain't gonna deal with her shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanking as a legit and frequent method of discipline is psychologically damaging and a sign of a lazy parents. And frankly it's disgusting how society jokes about spanking children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's very normal and good to be scared about that, it means you want the best for your children. I'm going to tell you the cold hard truth here: most parents are not mentally fit to be parents. Most parents eventually regret having their children on some level. This is because society over-romanticises and glamorises children while also treating them as toys to be owned and played with. Parental instincts and money is in my opinion not enough to raise a child right. Go read some child psychology and parenting tactics books. Above all, don't have such romanticised expectations for parenting life, and don't expect your children to fix your problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:41:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheating is cheating. I don't know your situation and I don't know the other problems in your relationship. But if he says he loves you after cheating he is 100% lying and manipulative. Cheating does not stop. Don't be that submissive girlfriend who endlessly waits for her boyfriend to change when he never will. You deserve someone better. There is literally no rational reason why you should stay with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I explain to them what it was like as best I can. When they start being really triggering and pretentious I will unashamedly tell them that they have no right to judge my situation harshly because they never experienced it. And I will tell them that there is a whole underbelly of abuse happening because of people who close an eye and are in denial, people like them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have seen abuse and regretfully never stood up...........

 #x200B;

* One was a typical low income-looking family composed of a mother, aunt and a 6 year old girl. On a packed bus. I don't remember exactly what the girl was doing but it was a little something to grab their attention but not annoying any passengers. The mother and aunt kept telling the girl and each other of how she's such a decietful liar. Imagine calling a little girl a liar and decietful for simply wanting attention.
* One was a sort of tantrum in a store where I had just walked in the middle of it trying to buy some clothes. I think the problem was that this 6 year old girl kept trying to touch or take the shoes on a pile of display items. The father kept telling her no. In her attempt to grab the shoes she accidentally knocked them over. No big deal right? Apparently no. Her father was extremely angry with her and screaming at her about ruining their shopping trip. She started to cry because of the screaming and he yanked her out of the store, the mother was just being submissive the entire time. I didn't feel like standing up because I didn't know the entire situation.
* This is the one I regret the most. This was the aunt of my ex-best friend. She had two children, 4 yr boy with ADHD and 6yr girl. I would see them at most of their family gatherings and feasts we attended. That makes a total of 4 times that I witnessed the abuse and did nothing. This aunt did not want her children, I know they were either a result of rape or completely unplanned aka an accident. The aunt, and even her father, had real beef with how her kids acted like any other kids in that they just ran around and played. Though the boy with his ADHD was harder to control because he would not respond to his name or stay still. Still, to me they weren't annoying, and my friend managed to control them better because she was actually nice to them. Every time I was there there mother would shout, yank and slap them for not staying still, obviously making them cry and behave worse. If looks could kill she would be 6 feet under 100 times over. I literally self-harmed in public because I was so triggered by her behaviour. I didn't stand up for them because I knew it would ruin relations with my friend and her family. My friend would always try to justify/defend her behaviour by saying 'well she's my aunt what do you expect me to do -.-'. She ended up being a garbage friend anyway and we separated, which makes me really regret that I never stood up for the kids. That could have really made my grand exit.

 #x200B;

I'm proud of you for standing up for that kid. You did all you could even if it didn't make the situation much better. The best thing about it is that maybe that kid will keep remembering you as the one person who stood up for them when everyone else closed an eye. The reason why lots of abused kids grow resentful towards the world is because subconsciously they will never get over the people who witnessed their abuse and did nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely, I feel this all the time. But the thing is, I'm confident that some level of emotional abuse runs in most families. And this is also because I am convinced that most people aren't mentally fit to be parents. Everyone over-romanticises the idea of having children, and few parents are prepared for the sacrifices they have to do to raise a child. This results in a lot of parents secretly regretting and resenting their children. Besides that, there is definitely a culture (tying it with the over-romanticisation), where children are seen as extensions of the parents, or like pets or objects. In other words they are there to be fawned over, to dress up, and to gloat about helping them achieve things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:06:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely. Narcissists construct a reality for themselves. They are extremely delusional in their reasoning and recollection of social information. My mother has accused me of words, entire sentences and claims that I have never said and so conveniently denies anything I bring up regarding what she said and did. It has been so bad that she once denied she did something serious while a witness was present, and only when that witness reminded her did she reluctantly admit it, but she still tried to downplay her behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 14:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are the more milder symptoms of narcissism. As in full-blown narcissists will always have those behaviours, but you haven't given information in this post to say for sure if it's the malignant kind of narcissism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:59:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Narcissists literally can't love. Their relationships with people are purely transactional. They trade their care for validation and attention. Once someone stops giving them their attention and validation the narcissist will do everything to tear them down and put them back into their place.

But besides that, are you literally going hungry? Can you buy food for yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a horrible thing to go through. It sounds like you were really depressed as a child. Are you still as depressed now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me she doesn't sound like a narcissist but extremely damaged and sensitive. As in that's also narcissists but the key is in the ways that they act out. Your sister needs a lot of therapy. A childhood filled with abuse can make someone into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:53:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so proud of you for putting in the effort into going no-contact. That's a really great achievement. Yeah I know it can be hard but know that you have a life ahead of you free from them. Your self-esteem needs building up. You need to treat yourself sometimes, however you define that. You should focus on making good friends and having a positive relationship with people. And it's entirely ok if you need a little therapy to help you and boost you up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you tell us more about how cps acted? Verbal abuse on its own should get cps to do follow ups, but breaking your stuff, past physical abuse, and drug addiction should full on get you out of your parents' custody. Did your brother become an addict recently? I have a feeling CPS/police would care more if they found drugs in the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  WHY ARE PEOPLE LIKE THIS!  

Many reasons. Many people don't want to rock the boat, and so they remain passive. To protect themselves from abuse many people try to justify it. When witnessing abuse, especially on children, many people close an eye.

No you don't have to accept your father as he is. He has to be held accountable for his own actions. And if he won't change, you have the right to just walk away. And you totally can choose another father-figure in your life. There's a reason some people dub their fathers as simply 'sperm-doners'. You can choose your own family, your own friends, and certainly your own therapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not stupid to get worried over this. It made you incredibly uncomfortable and still does to this. Whether it can be counted as abuse is debatable since you were both young children of the same age. But it was definitely a violation of your trust, your privacy, your boundaries, and he took advantage of your age-appropriate naivety. That kid was behaving very abnormally. He was probably getting sexually abused and repeated it on you. Probably he's still out there, and if he isn't a full-blown pedo, probably he still hurts people and violates their boundaries in some way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:34:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old are you? All is not lost just because your case is closed. If there's still abuse taking place you have to fight for CPS or anyone to care about you.

But until then, you have no choice but to just shut yourself off and disassociate from the hurtful words. Search up the term 'grey rocking'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sound like you have a lot of baggage. I'm sorry you spent so long tolerating your horrible family. Your wedding should have been the happiest day of your life, your moment to shine with your accomplishments. And you absolutely had the power to bar your family from entering the wedding (unless they paid for it).  If your husband supported you, why did HE tolerate your family's behaviour in the wedding? How did he agree to invite them in the first place? Are you sure he sees how crappy your family is or is he blinded by their hospitality for him? Anyway, your family will not change. Your family is composed of narcissistic, garbage people and it's not your fault. It's hard but you can create your own family without them. I hope you choose to cut off all contact with them because that is what you and they deserve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah Nparents will always take credit for things they didn't do. Nparents always gloat to outsiders how good their kids are and how they made them that way, and behind closed doors they'll tell their kids that they have never and will never do anything without their help and influence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry for what you've been through, it's so horrible.........

Your family, especially your mother are utter psychopaths. PSY.CO.PATHS. I understand that you're young and financially dependent on your parents, but you need to get out. You literally could have died under your mother. If you do anything that's even slightly more rebellious she could very well kill you. Please see about moving out, because I see nearly no benefits of staying. Even if you reason that you're financially dependent on them, there's nothing really stopping them from stealing or demanding money from you, if they don't already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's very good. I hope you're practicing mindful boundaries with her. You can try to help her, but see that you're not sacrificing your happiness for her. I doubt a person like that will change. Those kinds of people cannot truly love, therefore no matter how hurt you are they will never see that they are the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go for it! The vast majority of people get better after moving out from a bad environment. The wide world awaits you and you'll be so happy at what you can do and achieve while not being under your parents control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 13:07:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand your fears of police corruption and nepotism. But the likelihood of your case not being taken seriously if you have definite proof is small. And it's not like your father is a high ranking officer or chief right? You can record conversations with your dad via your phone's microphone. And you can semi-film or full on film his rages and physical abuse with apps that don't show they're recording. Seriously, you can pretend to just be holding your phone lax in your hand while in reality it will be recording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 10:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely.

Narcissism has a correlation with lack of intelligence. Less intelligent people are more likely to become old and lazy before their time. This is what happened to my mother. At 35 years old she acted like a 50 year old. She was lazy, chronically unhappy despite having everything, completely set in her ways in routine even if it harmed her and even if learning new things would have benefited her. She's also a huge armchair critic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 10:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old are you? This is 100% unprovoked domestic abuse. You need to get out of that toxic environment.

Truth be told, I'd rather you slam your head into a wall than try and physically retaliate. Both are terrible, but there's the least terrible option. If you hit back part of the blame will fall on you and police and everyone else will take you less seriously, especially if you're male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 10:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry for what you're going through and what your mother went through. But at the end of the day, your mental health matters. Bad experiences does not justify someone's bad behaviour. We need to hold people accountable. I don't know the details about your mother or how possible it is that she may change. You need to focus on your mental health and move out if possible. But if possible, you should try to reason with your mother logically, find counter-arguments to her flawed reasoning and try to get her into counseling or therapy. 

I hope everything works out ok for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 10:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. It seems like you're quite independent if you made a decision to temporarily move outside the home. Are you looking to move out permanently? Because I think this is the right time. Getting the police involved is not pointless. Probably nothing will come of it since there's no concrete proof. But being that your parents are abusive, it might benefit your mental health to get some sort of justice. Narcissistic parents are obsessed with keeping a good family image. Going through a police investigation will scar their ego. As a matter of fact don't just tell police, if you get an opportune moment tell all your friends and neighbors and extended family and anyone who knows your parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>