<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1517</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 23:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aye, given that economies of various levels of govt. intervention were pretty uniformly battered by the US sub-prime crisis I somehow don't buy the argument that much *really* could be done at a UK level to substantively negate the worst of the crisis beforehand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 19:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> international consensus and the political will to follow through with what comes after </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 01:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In future join a bloody union </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 21:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it's bloody Brecon it's so posh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 21:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think anyone pushing an honest assessment of Labour's chances in the area seriously thinks we should be winning there, in an ideal world our vote share is increased but I don't think anyone's particularly arsed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 19:22:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bumping Nick up would be such a good move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 19:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ashworth's been pretty solid at health tbh, it's pretty one note as a dept these days anyway but he's good on the stump and reliable at health Qs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 14:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean for most of the important stuff we use metric, it's also a bit of a generational thing as people who grew up using imperial still refer to things by it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 15:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> think the muscle memory of voting Lib Dem is still quite strong down here, don't see a seat like Truro and Fal going LD for some time tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Westminster Voting Intention 02-03 July </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 23:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 00:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> education is devolved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-28 14:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> engage your brain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 15:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See pal if you actually read the article there are relevant links contained within the body of the text, hope that helps x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 17:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "PoliticsHome understands that Keith Vaz led the moves to reject a recommendation from Labour staff that Mr Williamson be referred to the party's National Constitution Committee, which deals with serious disciplinary cases.

He argued that because Mr Williamson represents a marginal seat and that Labour MPs have less than two weeks to tell party bosses whether they wish to stand at the next election, he should be let off with a warning. "

How on fucking earth are we supposed to put any stock in the complaints/disciplinary procedure if decisions are made with reasons like this?

Absolute joke of a party, Keith Vaz is a disgrace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 22:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dunno why your lot would want him at this point tbh, nominally quite good at the bread and butter of politics but surely shot of any and all credibility by now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-03 22:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he can't be forced out at this point and will only go when he's knackered/properly fucked it - him and those around him are well aware that this is their one punt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 01:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> most probably aren't arsed one way or another </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 16:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Robert, Barristan and Jaime talking about war stories was all new content iirc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 20:26:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need to knock on more doors pal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 19:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a lot to unpack here but a lot of the issues pertaining to dem soc/soc dem closeness or confusion concerns contemporary understandings of what these words and symbols actually mean. A lot of people, Bernie Sanders being the first to come to mind, refer to themselves as Democratic Socialists when really (by the definition of the words themselves) they are in fact Social Democrats. In my country, the UK, the main left of centre party (Labour) explicitly refers to itself within its constitution as a democratic socialist party. But that's more of a description of the way the party operates in regards to being democrats and understanding socialism in its most broad and generous sense. If you look at the various leaderships of the party itself we've basically always been one strain of social democrat or another - with the red rose logo a lot of people on the UK left denote/associate themselves with being a logo dreamt up during the days of Neil Kinnock's leadership, who was ostensibly more of a centrist than a fair few leaders that preceded him. 

Alliances between various left factions are largely a product of the voting system each country has, lots of people who'd considered themselves Democratic Socialists (in the proper sense of the term) are happy to grit their teeth and ally with Social Democrats (who have historically commanded more support) both within party structures under FPTP and in formal coalitions under PR as a stepping stone to Democratic Socialism and for an immediate improvement in living standards. Or indeed just to have a say in the governance of their country. In a more reductive sense it's also just about values too, Democratic Socialists and Social Democrats broadly agree we should give a shit about one another and that redistribution (to varying extents) is the best route to applying that. Defining ourselves against Democratic Socialists among each other is useful certainly, but it can just exacerbate confusion with your average Joe and make things tactically difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 17:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thought we'd figured out that calling people thick isn't a way to get them to vote for you by this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 19:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cracking how they've managed to concentrate something that's relatively hard to grapple with for the average person into an ad like this, we've really come along leaps and bounds with our ppbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-25 21:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> uhhhhh, as with all things with the Labour Party's internal democracy they do hold sizeable sway *in theory*, but the reality is the leadership of the day can typically regularly get it's way on just about everything. A couple people I know are on the NPF and a lot of it is just being presented with policy offerings the party has drummed up with very little actual room for member-led contribution. And even with individual departments creating their own reports a lot of that flows directly down from John McDonnell and his team at the shadow treasury as they have supremacy over other departments. With Brexit specifically they hold next to zero influence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 17:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably worth stating specifically that Iraq and Afghanistan are the ones you're going on about if you don't like military intervention. Benefits undoubtedly outweighed the costs in Kosovo and Sierra Leone when we helped intervene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 16:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> plus if you're on a roll there's a prize for highest break </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 17:59:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fucking state of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 20:47:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do one you fucking roaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 20:18:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> absolutely foul article from a foul organisation, stuffed to the absolute rafters with cranks and crank apologists - disgusting that John McDonnell is still its president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 00:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fuck off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 19:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whichever way you fall on the matter of Williamson (I hate the fucker) surely it's inappropriate for a CLP to be commenting officially on a case that's ongoing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 15:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Christine Shawcroft is still a director of Momentum and their last NEC slate was shared with the CLPD (who voted as a committee to oppose Ken Livingstone's expulsion. They're chancers who fundamentally don't take the issue seriously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-19 15:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fucking christ alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-10 18:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> always mildly amusing seeing 'Corbyn ally' Jon Ashworth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-10 16:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Walker's gonna end up being readmitted isn't she? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-10 16:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The conventional wisdom being that keeping different Left factions in the tent makes dispute management easier as those in control of the party's levers of power can set the agenda to a much greater degree. FPTP also allows the party who wins the election to have an incredible degree of power which would be diminished to an extent with a move to PR. 
edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-05 17:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> see previous comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 19:15:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah fuck off you whopper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 00:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't really share the views of Momentum on a factional basis but all the best to them, an unenviable task to say the least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 22:07:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seem to remember Margaret Hodge publicly hauled over the coals very rapidly too, meanwhile Williamson pals about with antisemites for months on end with literally no recourse. Funny that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-22 22:17:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Got yelled at for saying it during the election but I could never see how electing an Englishman to lead the fight back against the Nats would end particularly well. Could never see the same thing happening in Wales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-22 22:13:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this shouldn't really be a story should it?lads just a nipper after all, why on earth we're giving time or a platform to a literal child is still perplexing   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 22:14:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> John Cock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 13:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have they even media trained this lout? What possibly can be gained by making yourself the story and punching downwards? Utterly bizarre behaviour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 17:47:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can't complain about the notion of people rewriting history when it's evident you don't have a very strong grasp of it yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 21:21:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except Burnham stayed on in the shadow cabinet during the '16 leadership election and was pretty hot shit as shadow home sec during his short time there. Also, engaging critical faculties for a second, what can honestly be gained by browbeating over something that happened three years ago and is at this point totally irrelevant to the wider party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 17:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dunno whether to laugh or cry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fiona Onasanya's "Inspired" Moment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 17:54:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-31 15:48:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rayner and Ashworth are among the few in the shadow cabinet actually doing their jobs and doing them quite well, level your disappointment on the likes of Burgon and the fact our DWP sec is practically anonymous imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 17:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe brexit is good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-20 17:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Please, please, I'm not Christ. He was quite a scruffy man" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-16 03:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how on earth do you go about making that kind of gold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-14 20:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know how you're able to afford to buy a house but Brynmill and Uplands tend to be the main student areas in Swansea (they're close to singleton), avoid Mount Pleasant like the plague as it's pretty rough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-10 05:53:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lived on HSV last year had a good time and it's definitely not as bad as people meme about it. That being said Singleton is where pretty much all the society/club stuff goes down and if you're studying there it's dead convenient being able to roll out of bed to your lectures. Also the next academic year is slated to be the end of HSV so I imagine it'd all get a bit depressing because they'll be less inclined to fix things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 07:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering I broadly agree with the party's handling of Brexit and that I've already spelled out why I didn't like Drakeford's campaign/platform, no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 03:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean I'm not really saying that am I? You can be a Welsh FM from the left of the party without overtly riding on Corbyn's coattails at every opportunity - that was essentially Eluned's pitch during this election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 23:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is it really though? A key part of governing Wales and holding back nat sentiment is the idea of Clear Red Water between UK Labour and Welsh Labour. Drakeford presenting us as a subsidiary of UK Labour and positing his own popularity as a part of Corbyn's is a recipe for electoral worries imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 19:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By all means call it boneheaded, but it's hardly a disservice to democracy when Labour MSPs are explicitly elected on a platform that includes the Bain Principle. Also important to remember that the rules are different for parties when in opposition, in the normal run of things Labour in Westminster would seldom vote with the Tories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Welsh Assembly votes to reject PM's Brexit deal </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 18:31:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 18:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also a lot easier to work with Plaid generally as they're a smaller party than the SNP and don't command the same degree of uniformity on the issue of independence   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 00:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The government technically isn't all the Tories incidentally, it's all the cabinet ministers as junior ministers are excluded from it and although backbenchers of the same party, they typically always vote with the government but they are not actually The Government  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 17:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is a really good piece on the matter, heartening to see that people on the left of the party are starting to take the issue more seriously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-11 00:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> somehow doubt O'Flynn is exactly in the know... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-06 18:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clyne's also off ill atm, might have had something to do with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 21:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> god I fucking hate this man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 13:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Corbyn has triangulated on a fair few things tho...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 01:59:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> imagine thinking that you can derive any substantive knowledge about a book from a summary, wild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 02:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bay campus was only built a couple of years ago and all the rooms have double beds, some have en suites. Singleton is cheaper and has a more community feel to it but you'd have to pay for transport to Bay if you're studying there (a bus pass is around three hundred pounds an academic year). If you live on Bay you'll miss out on some of the social stuff and it's a bit inconvenient to get anywhere, but you'll be right on campus for all your lectures. If you live on Singleton you'll have more of the social stuff going on and be closer to everything but have to pay for a bus pass and travel into uni every day. Personally I'd live on Bay, it's the nicest thing being able to roll out of bed straight into your lectures, the commute from Singleton is not enjoyable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-13 19:27:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Detailing how awful Welsh Labour are only to then speak fondly of the architect of much of that apparent awfulness (Drakeford) sure is one hell of a take. Suggesting a coalition with Plaid is also just thickness personified. Could genuinely sit here all night and go through everything wrong with this shite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-11 17:29:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> one of these a week at this rate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-15 17:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aside from being a bit crap as leader I've never heard a bad word said about him, seemed like a properly genuine bloke and it's sad to see his memory maligned like this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-10 22:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what a woman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 21:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cans are on me lads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 01:43:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> depends where you're staying, if you're on the village you could probs get away with it, on either campus they'll not be happy. You probs won't use it after the first week or so anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 15:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Read more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 14:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably skip bringing the fryer mate, you need to bring all your own pans and cutlery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 17:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [He's been threatening as much since 2015](https://twitter.com/georgeeaton/status/1035184405998956548). Mixed feelings about this one, undoubtedly crap on things like Brexit   abortion but he's been the main person holding the government to account on Universal Credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 17:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [He's been threatening as much since 2015](https://twitter.com/georgeeaton/status/1035184405998956548). Mixed feelings about this one, undoubtedly crap on things like Brexit   abortion but he's been the main person holding the government to account on Universal Credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Frank Field Quits Labour Party </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 17:16:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-29 21:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what the hell are you even on about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-25 13:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really rate Miriam  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 20:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, seeing as this bloke is the source you've linked for this information I hardly think it's irrelevant. You could've just linked to the article itself after all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 20:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably worth noting [that this fella has spent the last month attempting to downplay antisemitism](https://i.imgur.com/yrMgxzr.png)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 15:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not 'invoking Jo Cox' to point out that the woman Williamson is promoting called Jo a terrorist, get a grip lad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-19 22:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wish this slaphead would fuck off already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-17 23:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun times? Like a game of scrabble? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-15 00:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And this article is just an exercise in whataboutery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 16:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 00:24:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Curb Your Wreath Laying </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 20:06:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-06 15:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The AS issue within the party has been going on for months at this point, the idea that Watson's just been sat on his hands not confronting the leadership over this privately is frankly farcical, reports from NEC meetings suggest as much. You're right that it makes Labour look weak, and that confirms the level of severity we've reached over this issue where figures within the leadership feel they have no other option but to speak out publicly over the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-06 14:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get your tetanus jabs before living on the village </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 23:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 22:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He'll have to manage it properly for the rest of his career as well, best to not rush his recovery and get things right first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 23:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you don't spend 60 million quid on a keeper and hand him number 13 lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-18 22:00:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asking people to give someone kicked out of the party on the grounds of antisemitism a chance isn't behaviour becoming of a Labour MP, if you can't recognise that you're part of the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-09 02:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hasn't got the MPs backing him to become leader anyway, there are other far bigger beasts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-26 17:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It'd probably have to be a confidence and supply arrangement, doubt my lot would go for it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 23:40:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cornish Labourite checking in, I'd be down for a couple of gentleman's agreements in the marginals if you lot are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-22 21:29:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's just saying outlandish things in the run-up to punting his book, stop promoting him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-11 00:38:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'd hope they'd take more notice of one of their own MPs publicly getting chummy with antisemites, maybe that's just me though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-11 00:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not publicly but it was quietly briefed to a couple publications that they'd had a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chris Williamson pictured with Wadsworth and Livingstone after being asked by LOTO to "tone it down a bit" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 21:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 01:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> traditional cm or cam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-03 17:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We also played him out of position for a lot of his spell here, didn't help things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-01 00:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If Labour leadership are willing to slap down an MP when they're in the wrong in a relatively minor way they should be doing the same when an MP is wrong in a major way like Chris Williamson is. It's not whataboutery, it's just asking for a basic level of consistency within the leadership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-31 21:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what an utter milkman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-25 14:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean I was thinking about Lisa Nandy with her centre for towns stuff (which is important) but ok lad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-25 03:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Problem is that those MPs most likely to offer a meaningful alternative to Corbyn have either ducked out via a mayoralty or have checked out on pet projects on the backbenches. The vocal critics left either aren't brave or clever enough to break away so we're stuck with them whinging about things but not actually acting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-22 20:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Harry Potter, he's coming for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 14:28:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's also dull as dishwater, which isn't a bad characteristic to have in a chancellor but McDonnell has that over him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 14:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> second time it's been brought back into public hands in the last ten years, daft country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-14 01:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably end up dicking about in the championship for a few years and get sold to another bunch of shiteheads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 04:18:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dark fruits is an indie twitter essential  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I rate this meme four out of five stars </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 00:00:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 02:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I don't believe people should own their own homes" all the best pushing that line chief whew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 02:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ye's fucking with all ya'll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WOOPDEDESCOOPPOOP! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 02:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 19:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Assange is more than welcome to leave the cupboard at any point chief, it's not a crime committed on British Soil that's keeping him there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 22:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eluned Morgan is a name that's been banded about a bit, bunch of people in the student movement I know have already started stumping for her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 04:02:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drakeford's been the brains behind a lot of stuff happening in the Senned for a while now. Shame he's utterly dull as dishwater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-20 14:22:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Matip is lanky tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-08 03:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trent played a blinder against city last week and will be rested to a greater level than Clyne will be, it's gotta be him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-08 03:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're still not really sure what Salah's ceiling is and Suarez played a substantially different role within an entirely different setup. Also comparing 3 and a half season's of play with not even one seems a bit futile tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 19:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably a combination of the international break fucking us (as always) and the fact the players we've lost highlight our lack of squad depth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-30 02:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> very Thick of It </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-30 02:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She didn't just fail to get rid of him immediately, she actively tried to prevent his removal. Now that either betrays a total ignorance to the case at hand through negligence or a frankly repugnant outlook on the issue of antisemitism, neither has any place on the NEC. Also if you think any amount of "context" can make the promotion of antisemitic material acceptable then you're an antisemitic melt like the rest of them - looks like you got one half of your prediction correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-27 22:43:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to fucking die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-18 19:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope she doesn't win the selection tbh, Jayne was a cracking candidate and brilliant on the doorstep. Deserves another go of it given the swing she achieved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Equality of Sacrifice - Labour poster from 1929 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 17:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rural Labour Members! Help the Fabian Society research different approaches for Labour to start winning these regions. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-15 16:42:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-06 03:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The level of bile thrown in Lily's direction is absolutely disgusting, she doesn't deserve any of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-25 15:44:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'm more than coming around to the idea of her as leader, I'd happily stump for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 22:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> France has the biggest military capabilities within the region. And the comparative strength of other member states puts them on a relatively level playing field, nothing like the kind of defence spending discrepancy we see with the US and other countries. The only thing that puts the UK above non-nuclear member states is our trident missile system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 22:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When put to polling the main reason time and time again was the immigration issue. This was just a part of the myriad of "muh EU superstate" scares that Brexiteers pushed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 18:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if we whipped the vote down we wouldn't have had the numbers and a fair few of our own ranks would have rebelled (Hoey and friends, plus some remainers sitting in leave constituencies). But yeah, either way we as a country are fucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 17:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Voting against results in the UK leaving in a 'no deal' scenario](https://twitter.com/christopherhope/status/930113752975933447) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 17:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting implications from this to say the least. Would voting down a final Brexit deal end up with us exiting on WTO terms? Or would it completely derail the whole process? It's also contingent on the government limping past the article 50 period, which in my mind at least is looking increasingly unlikely.
Edit: it would seem voting down the deal results in us exiting without one. [Source](https://twitter.com/christopherhope/status/930113752975933447) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-04 14:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By ditched I mean 'not actively on leadership manoeuvres for anymore', they all realise that Clive is not horse worth backing to carry the left in a leadership contest. Corbyn's statement is not mutually exclusive with Clive being moved from the main group. Having one of your main lieutenants defy you on one of the more key votes in the commons is never a good look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-04 01:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's got no outriders left (Owen Jones et al have ditched him) and the rest of the PLP think he's a tit. If he hadn't made such a tit of himself he'd be JC's natural successor right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-04 01:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [That's top swearing](https://youtu.be/cX6Hz5I_QLI?t=22s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-03 21:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think his leadership chances have been compromised ever since he made a tit of himself over the A50 vote and JC kicked him out the core group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-27 19:59:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been pretty impressed with what I've seen of Pennycook in the recent parliamentary debates, one to watch for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 00:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean she never turns up to vote so she's not that great... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-21 21:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The scene were Robert Baratheon, Barristan and Jaime are trading war stories in S1. Really great to see the directors let actors slow down and sink their teeth into a scene, added a lot of colour to the Robert and Jaime's character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-20 22:28:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think it'd be an unnecessary hill to die on to be honest, stigma around marijuana specifically is still pretty big in the UK  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-20 19:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was really well put and I agree with your analysis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-19 18:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another nifty move by Stella Creasy, can't help but think she's wasted on the backbenches... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Labour eyes plan for windfall tax on PFI companies </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-19 18:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-16 17:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm obviously not privy to all the information available to JC and friends but there's no denying that Yvette is an effective person to have on the frontbench, I'm of the view you'd quell a fair few internal divisions by bringing her into the fold. She's one of the dying breed of MPs who actually served in the last Labour cabinet. Maybe I'm just being idealistic about wanting effective operators in high office rather than those who have always toed the Corbyn line. Gardiner would be alright on balance but there's people higher up my list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-14 16:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Starmer's only going to be tied up until the bulk of Brexit negotiations are over and done with. After that I imagine the dotting of Is and crossing of Ts will happen as a function of the foreign office. I couldn't really see Thornberry at the home office but maybe that's just my own personal inclination. Yvette Cooper is a name that's always going to be chucked about in regards to it, she's probs the most appropriate for the job and giving her a big brief would solve a fair few internal rifts in the party. That being said she's pretty unpopular with the Corbynite wing in both the PLP and membership - Corbyn's big on personal loyalty after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-14 15:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean with respect, I don't think Dianne really is either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-13 00:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not revisionist history to give your own personal account of that time period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm Living Proof of New Labour's Success </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-12 13:58:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 02:10:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair play mate, I've got a mate on the PPE and the workload is doing his nut in. I'd say that maybe in oxford terms maths/PPE isn't that hard but relative to the average Joe it is if you get me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 01:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it's not raw Physics or Maths but it's not a cakewalk lad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 01:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's safe to assume that's the arena she's headed into </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 01:46:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fuckin aye mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 01:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basically one of the most brain busting courses they offer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-08 20:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering the degree to which he ostracised Thatcher when he came to power I'd hardly say he was her mouthpiece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-08 18:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably the quietest remainer of the bunch though, she sat well and truly on the fence so you she could be all things to everyone once the ref happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-07 15:24:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Labour in power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-24 23:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They've definitely been doing stuff (Yvette on the home affairs committee comes to mind) but nothing quite the level of significance that Sadiq has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-24 18:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad we're seeing a consensus forming from all wings of the party that Chris Williamson is a colossal turnip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-24 18:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the Tories and Labour are in a similar position that the majority of their respective frontbenches wont get a look in at the next leadership contest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-24 18:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also I think Sadiq is considerably more charismatic than Keir Starmer is. Keir is someone I'd want in one of the top cabinet positions for sure but I'm not certain he's got the chops to front a campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-24 18:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd disagree with your first point about Khan not wanting to. Being MOL grants you a considerable amount of power and name recognition within the country. Becoming mayor has put Khan in a better position than previously because people know who he is now. It's also meant his hands have been kept relatively clean in the Labour forever war unlike a lot of other high profile contenders (Umuna/Cooper). I get a lot of the criticisms surrounding Sadiq but a lack of ambition is certainly not one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-19 23:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having followed him and his content for a while now I don't think this exchange was particularly out of character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jones Your Enthusiasm </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-19 22:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-18 17:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thornberry's repatriation as a Corbynite has been interesting to watch to say the least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 16:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get the impression he just sits about eating crisps not really contributing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-08 13:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If democratic accountability is the price you pay for expediting the process then you shouldn't expedite the process. Transitional deal is the sensible option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-24 03:47:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> him and his team spent a day listening to blonde and yah was the result </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 21:52:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reminds me of Ned talking to Jaime about not fighting in tournies so others wouldn't know what he could do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-20 22:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair, that's not what the piece is stating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sadiq Khan Shitposting (sorry) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-19 19:50:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-08 16:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> part of the 'everyman' kind of look alongside the tie that's too long, it's not just him either loads of politicians wear ill fitting suits to make them seem more relatable   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-17 01:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I hope it does anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-17 01:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think history will remember GB more fondly than we currently do right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-16 15:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dress shoes are your best bet here man, chucks would lower the tone of the whole fit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-16 15:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Benn did a talk there once or twice too IIRC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-11 21:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like Hilary Benn and think it would make for a great moment to publicly break with the past, not sure JC and friends would be up for it on a personal level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-11 15:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would be a real display of unity from JC to bring back members of the old shadow cabinet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-10 22:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that or "the bell tolls for thee Theresa" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-07 17:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NO BRAKES ON THE GAPES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-07 17:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably not, his majority is pretty huge and he's an iconic figure within the party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-07 00:15:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better suited for Defence/Northern Ireland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-01 17:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> quiet bat people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-01 03:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Given the hand she was dealt of any of her answers having the out of "you're not the PM lol" she performed admirably. Having seen the format of this debate May would've been absolutely steamrolled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-29 19:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Narstie is the realest  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-26 18:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is the song Frank interpolated on Seigfried, for those who haven't heard - it's beautiful. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-26 02:40:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-25 22:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree it's a bit tenuous, but I think they would do well to needle it as a point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-21 22:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I was talking about MPs sorry. I'm well aware of the criticisms (was fairly vocal about the IRA stuff in my CLP), only to have it fall on deaf ears as you've mentioned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-21 21:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think if we weren't in the run-up to a GE there would be more open and widespread criticism. Everyone's kinda painting on a smile right now cause it reflects badly on them otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-21 21:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> does anyone actually like her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-19 23:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was a lefty way back in the day, but he's very right wing nowadays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-19 18:53:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Naturally. It's been nine years since Wikileaks leaked anything about Russia- draw your own conclusions about that. At the very least I'm of the opinion that that's an odd situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-19 18:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *other than the fact I have no insight on the Russian administration* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-19 18:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think that at all, I just find it extremely hard to believe that in nine years there hasn't been a leak of any consequence coming out of the Russian administration to be reported by Wikileaks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-19 18:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To suggest they haven't been given any information on the Russian administration over the past nine years is frankly ridiculous. It suits Assange to not damage that relationship and subsequently we've heard nothing. I don't specifically *want* leaks from Russia, I just don't want them to put themselves forward as a neutral source of information when it's clear by omission that they have serious vested interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-19 14:27:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's been 9 years since Wikileaks leaked anything about the Russian administration though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:43:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean to be fair PETA are fucking dreadful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:09:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [*all I can hear reading this*](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kDIuApfVxBg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:10:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could definitely see a transitional leader taking us through until Sadiq becomes a sitting MP again if he comes back for 2022  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get that they're trying the whole problem of evil thing but tapeworms aren't really that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-14 16:54:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The age gap between Macron and his wife is the same as between Trump and Melania  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah absolutely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surname doesn't hurt him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Feeling some kind of way about a girl who's into Kanye on the same level as I am so I feel you man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh this is legendary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:02:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't worry we're still flying half a plot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well my comment doesn't exactly apply to you then does it? Seeing as I did state 'If you want the Tories out...' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:34:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want the Tories out putting them as your second preference or failing to put the main opposition to them as your second preference sure is an interesting way to go about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:17:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You start by denying her at the ballot box, then dismantle her from the ground up. I'm not arguing that winning an election against Le Pen will suddenly stop the rise of fascism in France, but that's where you start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You start with the dismantling of her movement by denying her at the ballot box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or y'know, we as the left can be better and spend the next ~4 years offering an alternative. Anti establishment rhetoric swings both ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an outsider looking in I can't help but feel like this is incredibly narrow minded from those doing it. Macron is by no means a socialist, but I'd take a few years of centrism over being ruled by a literal fascist any day of the week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bit hyperbolic but hey, you gotta take what you can get right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:09:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vans/Converse look better worn in and beaten up. But hey, you do you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The newly elected leader is more moderate IIRC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> chance the rapper core </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:40:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More screen printed gildan? yaaaaaaaay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think ripped jeans ever really went away boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think Melenchon beats Le Pen in the second round(if he were to make it that far). Also you're understating support that has seeped away from Fillon to Macron- if he wasn't running a Le Pen/Fillon second round would be quite likely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'd prefer he won over Le Pen/Fillon if that counts for anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is an amazing way of thinking about things, thank you for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wassa joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If Corbyn's socialism continues Attlee's legacy, surely we wouldn't be losing by-elections? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bit played out at this point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We've seen Corbyn on a bad week- party imploding/losing by-elections </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get a bunch of bikes and ride 'em around with our friends, that's the shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These are clean as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's what I tell myself anway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a speech but the right answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:48:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> we watched this man build a staircase in a poorly lit room for 2 days, we're damn sure it's him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:43:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Universal healthcare truly is a beautiful thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Sadiq's good polling also comes down to him being pretty likable as a person not just his politics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What Labour in power looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kanye supports the LGBT movement, stop being such a headass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Posted by a person with 40k followers, suspended from the party on grounds of antisemitism. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Centrist, was pretty content maintaining the neoliberal status quo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *bypasses MSM by being completely ineffective at the alternate medium all the while tanking in the polls and losing by elections*- he's really sticking it to MSM lads! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If he didn't get ousted after losing Copeland, he won't get ousted at all at this point. There's very little left for him to cock up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one that comes to mind is Clive Lewis who's one of his main allies , very similar ideologically save for Clive supporting the continued use of Nuclear deterrents. The problem is for any socialist succession to take place a certain number of MPs need to nominate the individual for leadership. Given the current party demographics (a significant proportion of MPs being openly anti-Corbyn or more centrist) Clive would likely not make the ballot paper. Also he's pretty politically inexperienced and more accomplished centrist parliamentarians are probably more up for the job (These being Chuka Umunna, Dan Jarvis, Liz Kendall and Yvette Cooper). Also important to remember that the London Mayoral election happens during the 2020 election so we could see popular Labour Mayor Sadiq Khan throw his hat into the ring if he sits as an MP again(Khan being more leftwing than the previously mentioned alternatives). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think the blame of 7 years of Tory government can be solely placed on Blair's shoulders. Don't get me wrong I agree with the majority of what Corbyn says, but he's absolutely useless dealing doing PR both inside and out of the commons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really got used to this live version and now the CDQ version sounds off to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> asking the important questions boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nikes by frank ocean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cartjacked on the black champion hoodie rest of the drop was certi dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean that's the Lib Dems for you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smith's stance on Brexit (overturning the decision or at least forcing a second referendum) makes him pretty incompatible with the Stoke central electorate(the 'leave capital' of the UK and all that). It also poses issues with the wider electorate as a large portion of remain voters want to see article 50 triggered because of it being a democratic decision and them 'respecting democracy'. I think Smith would've been a better leader without a doubt- he's a more accomplished parliamentarian, better public speaker and he wouldn't alienate the majority of the PLP upon being elected. That being said, his line on Brexit is about as suicidal as you can get in the current climate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:25:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make loads of beats, keep practicing until you get good. Kanye made 5 beats a day for three summers before he got to where he was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> niche, I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:24:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mate I live here, *I know* and it frustrates me more than anything else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kanye </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> West </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> *coldest winter comes on shuffle* </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Keep a place for me, I'll sleep between ya'll it's nothing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:39:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he's an MEP but failed to ever become an MP (tried like 3 times) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> talk shit post fit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the fact you had to put why people should give give a shit in brackets is reason enough not to give a shit about what this man says </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she left you high and dry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:27:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I GOT TWO VERSIONSSSSSSSSS I GOT TWO VERSIONSSSSSSS I GOT TWO VIRGINS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:03:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah it's a British thing, my b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Rule 5: Don't be an asshole" , seriously though if you're taking time out to whinge about the quality of posts on an internet forum you need a hobby or something. If you don't wanna see 'thoughts?' posts you don't have to click on them and view them, downvote and move on with your life man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stop trying to police content that doesn't break the rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You do know that Spotify exists my guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man it's a street fighter sample smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Support the artist and buy that shit man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah if you look at some other MVs (Touch the sky being the one I'm thinking of), he definitely uses corny lines/delivery for stylistic reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What I say to tabloid readers telling me that Kim and Ye are splitting. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-07 21:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:48:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> C O L D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that I was dreaming when you said you loved me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> welcome to heartbreak for the person who ditched it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BEAUTIFUL MORNING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-11 14:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GOOD music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-11 14:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I totally agree with you there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love dropout an awful lot, but I'd argue that 808s changed the game way more. While CD pushed rappers to be better and try new things, 808s broke down the door for a whole load of new artists and honesty in rap. I don't think  it was as immediate as CD but I think 808s' influence on the culture and artists in the game right now is much more far reaching and long lasting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thicker than a bowl of oatmeal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what if this is all just some next level mind game from ye, what if he's playing the long con on Trump? Or maybe he's chatting shit again I dunno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> absolutely haram </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can we talk about Love Lockdown real quick? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When those drums start it makes me wanna nut every damn time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can't say no to </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering how effectively it broke the doors down for other artists/experimentation within the genre it's definitely ahead of its time in my mind. It's like a shot of the future  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just beat the fucking shit out of him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3 years on and Yeezus is still ahead of its time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I swear to god it feels like Kanye is smacking the shit out of me musically every time I listen to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> guitar chords/picking arrangements  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At this point Corbyn's image and following are so damaging he could promise the most comprehensive and perfect set of policies and people still wouldn't vote Labour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:23:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It gives me some heart knowing there's an alternate timeline where Ed Milliband didn't eat that sarnie so weirdly and we're not in this Brexit shitshow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That can be attributed to the 'honeymoon period' after a new PM is elected rather than the political leanings of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When can U be finally releases it's gonna be the loopiest day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hong Kong/China relations are a bit *strained* to say the least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shit my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-29 23:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it'd ever get to the point where they absolutely fucking hate each other like the Gallagher brothers. Also Jay isn't really active musically as much anymore so it's not like they're trying to out-compete one another or butting heads creatively. There's a Ye without Jay and there's a Jay without Ye but Oasis can only ever be the Gallagher brothers and friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:03:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alright Fantano, turn that 6 upside down it's a 9 now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-25 20:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is incredible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-25 17:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't personally rate it with those trousers/shoes but it's dope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:55:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ain't nobody fresher than my mothafuckin' clique </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shame they're way heavier and less reliable than the standard box magazines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't pretty put him as an 'icon', his fits are simple and pretty understated a lot of the time which is pretty reflective of his personality. It resonates with me because he's authentic in the way he dresses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah, especially seeing as the AC games have always had amazing instrumental pieces in them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:06:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> we're gonna need a link OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:53:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> anyone know if these are gonna be at retail price? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-15 13:05:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah the 'collaborative ceo' way of writing records or whatever it is will stop him from it. I reckon K dot could probably win  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> got a pair recently and dig them a lot, still would take the 750s over them any day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vennu? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The start of a new era of beanie art </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-11 22:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-06 14:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Brit, probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brit doesn't have any tangible negative connotations associated with it but Paki does.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-31 23:03:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe wearing something like this all thru summer might get you a few funny looks but it's autumn now(ish) so you'd probably be alright </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the contribution?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think stating that, given current trends, the workforce we know today is going to be increasingly more and more automated is 'fortune telling'. I think you do a disservice to his predictions and reasoned thought by reducing it to fortune telling.

Anyway, come back in thirty years to see who has bragging rights on the matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a really good CGP grey video which highlights a lot of key concerns about an automated workforce and its affect on wider society. [Here's the link](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Pq-S557XQU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-26 01:04:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A mew shaped pool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're doing a re-release in certain parts of North America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:21:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is dope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-07 22:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remote is the 'pidger' but that might only be localized to my house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any live version is better than the original imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:16:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kanye and Kim are just fucking cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does this man sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:22:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nah this is fucking funny mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-16 16:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wife material  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just a kid with a bit of hair, maybe it's a blunder for you or those who know you personally but compared to [others](http://imgur.com/wht1zSK) on here you're relatively unscathed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-19 13:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bloody hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-16 21:31:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Daddy needs to express some rage" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:33:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Move just had his head caved in by Gillius holy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-31 23:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok, I'm tilted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-28 21:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 years 'vet', oh my sweet summer child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-28 21:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WildturtleDoublelift, good meme my man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-07 16:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ye's gonna make him vote republican, so everybody knows he loves white people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-06 17:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would love an ID on that bomber  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-05 12:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get Dumbledoged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:34:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is a valid point, I just think it's wack giving players a timer for a camp they never had vision of </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:03:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My "I've never listened to any of his music outside of gold digger" detector is ringing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really not a fan of these jungle timer changes, also disliked it when they changed dragon and baron to be global timers too. Completely devalues players who can effectively time camps (I like the auto time on camps you have vision of) and removes another metric for one jungler to beat another. Timing enemy camps was one of the things that marked 'alright' players from 'good' ones and they've just removed that entirely T_T . I think Doublelift was right for once in that riot seem intent on just lowering the skill ceiling across the board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> we all fuccbois out here I ain't gonna doll it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-30 19:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> come over to /r/streetwear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-30 16:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sub has conditioned me to expect Max B in every link now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is lit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-26 22:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grime bois </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-25 19:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> majority of top chinese teams scrim korean ones IIRC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-25 17:47:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alternate day fasting g  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-22 22:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> exact same reaction, magic night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-19 23:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [I think LS is right here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R1TAuOAJBQc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-17 20:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no, it's valid in that the original comment made it seem like Kikis was new to top lane. His comment states that he was not in fact new to top lane. Just because you don't play at a worlds semi final leveld doesn't mean you're not a top laner you melt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-16 20:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah that was my first thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-08 14:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Phreak's diamond one so by this thinking he should have better game knowledge than Monte right? In reality does he? Of course not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-07 22:01:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't need to be a chef to be a food critic, you don't need to be high ELO to have good game knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-03 14:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> make a big tsunami up in this joint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-03 14:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bunch of wavey dudes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-02 21:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Majority of artists have basic and profound moments, I feel like with Kanye his basic lyrics are the most focused on (cause the media makes sick scrilla off him) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-02 21:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chef </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We out here leaking onto other subs, keep it loopy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-02 19:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-02 19:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your ignorance is showing fam, it's one line in a 3 minute song. The rest is him talking about he's the don with clothes and helping a bird with car payments. Also I kinda think he doesn't actually want to bone Taylor and just said the line to court controversy and get more hype around the album. All press is good press etc etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-02 18:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you a wavey dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-02 18:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was about to respond with the Gorgeous verse aha.
Also one from all falls down :
It seems we living the American dream
But the people highest up got the lowest self-esteem
The prettiest people do the ugliest things
For the road to riches and diamond rings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/kanye is leaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 21 grammies, 21 million record sales roughly, created one of the most genre defining hip hop records in My beautiful dark twisted fantasy. I'm a stan for him but you're just straight stupid if you don't recognise these accolades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-27 15:11:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He really like dropout and late registration IIRC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-06 22:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably should invest some time into doing that before making sweeping statements imo. SKT have a lot of issues in the early game that weren't properly exposed at IEM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-06 20:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have been watching ROX play right? They're on another level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-05 18:26:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scoring a goal like Harry Kane did is way more difficult than scoring at the near post. It's common goalkeeping practice to follow the position of the forward with the ball so you can intercept the shot earlier (that's why he was at the near post). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-22 23:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the calls lads and lasses. Decided to put my worth on myself and not knob this bird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-22 20:50:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> respect for that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-19 21:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same reason why anyone watches sports live, it's more fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's subjective whether or not you like the analyst desk sections or not. Personally I think the less analysis the better but I'd definitely miss the interview sections. This wouldn't eliminate these sections but trim them down and focus more on the game itself which is y'know why I'm watching and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a good point, but I'm pretty sure they have spares for each piece of kit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Players have to shake hands with each other and generally dick about comparing damage stats. As soon as the game ends two 'refs' for each side (4 total) sweep on stage and pack the kit up. Should be mostly faster as they're not dicking about and looks cleaner as the teams can leave as a group after handshakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-15 15:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 24 years is the confirmed cut off point for being able to like Kanye. You're entitled to your opinion on him bud but saying he's not an artist just makes you out to be an ass tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-15 14:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably not the wisest decision to be dissing Ye on this sub of all places bud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-12 19:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 albums of pure ego just ripped down, so vulnerable so good   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-12 19:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had the whole ye discog but never got round to listening to it until just before xmas. Enjoy my fave Kanye record bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-12 19:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been really getting down to Yeezus lately having never appreciated it properly before  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-11 23:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this isn't the result of 3 years solid work imo. Dude's busy with other shit. Last 12 months maybe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-11 23:26:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> worth the wait for sure, ye is funny and back on form imo. Ultra Light beam is my fave track so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-07 22:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GAME OF THE YEAR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-05 21:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 808s is some of the realest music ever made. 3 albums of ego and bravado all come crashing down in such a personal, beautiful way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow you're fast homie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> UK English mate, don't be knocking me when my people invented the language you muggins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-31 21:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will check it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-24 22:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adrian is so freaking good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-23 00:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is that harsh shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-19 22:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it's still ya boi K-dot so it's solid shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The instrumental totally didn't fit Kendrick's rhyming style tho tbf. But ye definitely put out the better verse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-14 23:14:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Watching this game](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JeimE8Wz6e4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-10 00:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's credited as 'R2-D2 consultant' or something to that effect in the credits IIRC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gonna try and kick this nasty ass soda habit I've developed and overall get generally fitter(original I know). Also I'd like to have had a relationship with a girl before the year is out- we'll see how it goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-12 00:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where the fuck is Sean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> relative to the rest of his career  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> niceme.me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm all over the Febiven hype train at this point tbh and think he's the best western mid. It's just fun to play devil's advocate sometimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-07 09:45:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You did watch OGN right? Coco was the second best mid out of the whole league haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> -Plays in the most competitive, top tier region in the world
-Carried the corpses of Ambition and Shy through the gauntlet
-Gave Faker a run for his money at times
Also Febiven has played 2 international tournaments so that's hardly a load of experience imo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At that tournament sure, Rekkles played better but the context of each player's role in the team is important. Rekkles is a tertiary carry in his team with most of his kills coming through clean up, with (at this tournament) Huni and Febiven being the main carries on the team. Meanwhile Imp was busy carrying the limp body of TBQ who seemed to forget how to play League of Legends. GodV who was ramming his head against a wall before every game and Acorn forgetting how to TP. Not only was Imp the main carry of that team, he was carrying total shitters (minus Lord Flame) so naturally he's gonna be worse off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Faker is better, as is Coco. A case could be made for Easyhoon. Depending on who you talk to some might say Bjerg is better( not me tho). GodV in the regular split looked better than Febiven overall but he shit the bed at worlds so you can't really compare there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-05 23:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Moffat's set a mental precedent for Companion Deaths/departures with this move. The fact that the Doctor went through 4 billion years of hell to save Clara is pretty mind numbing to deal with seeing as I never really *felt* the connection between the two. If 10 went to the end of time to save Rose it would've been way more warranted cause their relationship was actually believable and well fleshed out. The exact same could be said of Amy and to some extent Rory but with Clara I just never bought her relationship with the Doctor. That being said I think Heaven sent was an absolute masterpiece just simply slotted into the wrong storyline, I think that's a symptom of Moffat liking Clara more than I do. To me the interesting plot point is how Galifrey escaped the pocket universe and how Rassilon is apparently still alive and kicking (and now Maester Luwin rather than Timothy Dalton). I feel like Moffat had all the right pieces for a cracking season finale but he just couldn't fit them all together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-29 21:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People bloody loved double but Link was hardly popular with fans, would be a hard push to sell seeing as he's not even in the scene anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-18 21:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not too shabby from UOL, should expect a decent middle of the pack showing from them with this roster. Also could be a good proving ground for newer players like Gilius and SB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-14 00:07:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Orianna has never not been relevant in the meta in one form of another so she's a safe bet to main. Mid is probably the most contested role in ranked tho, so you probably wont get it a whole lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-13 23:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you look at the teams he left tho, CW was utter garbage without amazing (not to mention kinda a shady org), SK had their own internal issues with management and Forgiven didn't want them to boot 4 other blokes and build a team around him(he specifically felt it wasn't fair to the other guys). As for Gambit, it's kind of a notoriously grim environment at the best of times and as far as I'm aware he was kicked rather than quitting with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-10 20:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> first us redcoats take your esports, then we take back america </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-10 19:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure we'll see him as the new jungler of TSM mate, seeing as he's in such high demand. Hell, I heard CJ Entus and Koo Tigers are looking to improve their jungle position maybe he'll go compete where he belongs (with the best of the best) in Korea : </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-10 19:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a best of one. At the end of the season. In a game which had no real bearing on the playoffs/gauntlet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-10 19:02:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If they can avoid the team imploding from all the personalities on that squad then that team is genuinely probably the best super team formed yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-10 19:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now we just need Impaler to TSM and before you know it baylife becomes tealife  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-10 19:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's the most vocal in comms during teamfights but people don't actually pay attention to what he's saying. Normally it's "Lantern in 5 secs" or "My hook is up" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-10 18:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say Yellowstar and you could probably make a case for Mithy if you were that way inclined(too hard to call for me personally) but Yellowstar is probably the best Western Support  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 23:25:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Football(soccer) young talent goes to the better well funded teams and the smaller squads get rewarded with a fat load of cash. It's the same in Esports, the cream rises to the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially with EU teams the money just isn't there to hold onto their stars in the smaller orgs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dodging is a tool to be used to help you climb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you're in the wrong place then if you feel that way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ban Yasuo then as he's the biggest gnar counter. Frozen mallet also helps deal with his bs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:31:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't be picking Gnar into Yasuo mate he absolutely wrecks you(source:150 gnar games this ranked season) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone is playing carry tops like Fiora/Darius right now my man nobody really has time to be playing tanks like him that offer little to the team. If you liked the role he played in the team, the more viable tanks right now are Gnar/Malphite as they have decent damage and fairly consistent engage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How and why is he not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:09:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because you like his style doesn't make him a top 3 jungler though mate. To be fair to him, his Lee Sin is pretty amazing but every other champion he plays he looks incredible shaky on. Just go back and watch some of the old Alliance games in S4, sometimes he would go off and 1v5 and other teams he'd be in Froggen's backpack with Wickd. Teams value consistency and current relevancy over flash aggressive plays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say even Loulex is a better jungler than Shook at this point in time (his world's showing was better than regular split) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you might be stuck in 2013 mate. You saw him get absolutely batty slapped on CW right? Also if he's one of your top 3 who are your other 2, because I'm worried for your sanity as a person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 21:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think anyone really cares mate seeing as he's fallen off a lot since he was a good and even at his best he was very inconsistent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-01 18:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had no real issue with Pobelter leaving when I found out that Huhi was gonna be the original starter. The coach Chris thing is a bit of a shock because he seemed like a solid bloke. But the Doublelift transfer really knocked me for 6. It can't of just been a culmination of the years of working with each other. Some serious shit must have gone down during worlds to lose 2 key individuals and the fucking face of the entire brand. I'm talking some fire and brimstone tier argument at this point because it's not like Double decided to leave CLG, he said in his own words that he got kicked from the team. I can accept that shit happens in teams and things don't work out, that's the nature of team based games. But what is truly unacceptable is the radio silence we've been treated to by Hotshot and the ggs.
Imagine if Francesco Totti got kicked from Roma to Lazio(Roma and Lazio are rivals and Totti has played for Roma for the best part of 30 years) and the Roma staff justified it with "ah well we had a couple of disagreements". Honestly CLG get your shit together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-01 00:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not really about fight w/nunu, more objective control and fucking with the opposing jungler. Making him as useless as you etc etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-31 17:08:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe the Bengi Nunu cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-30 21:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think when you're at the god tier of play like Pawn and Deft a lot of it is just intuition and their teammates pick up the pieces. But when you're scrabbling around with mediocre players it makes more sense for them to be able to communicate properly. Raw skill can you get you places but building a team that communicate properly is far more of a sustainable asset to have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 23:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either up his damage and keep his range the same. Or increase his range and keep his damage the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 22:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clearly the Riot Skrilla has run dry this month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 19:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please give Lucian a range buff lads, nothing crazy 525 or maybe 550 if you're feeling frisky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 18:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure at this point Xpeke and Soaz manage themselves and know what's overstepping the line and Mithy's on that reformation from being 'toxic' so is probably super careful with what he says. The only issue that could ever arise is Xpeke pulling rank as owner over the coach. And at this point it seems that the coaching staff provide them with information and suggestions and the team makes a majority decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 18:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So the best team ever must never lose a game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 18:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Korean society is different to the western one though, they have a heavy focus on respecting your elders/your superiors into you from an early age. So having someone who can manage players not just strategy isn't as important over there. I'm sure over the years as a now veteran coach KkOma's probably got that ability in managing players down also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yikes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-26 23:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's supposed to be a great asset in terms of work ethic and can very much be molded as he's still a young player. IIRC he's in KR right now grinding solo queue to improve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-25 23:14:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus the bottom tier orgs always seem to be folding split after split so it's probably more sustainable to have less teams competing in a more competitive league rather than a huge league that's essentially a free win near the bottom of the table for top teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-25 22:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry that's me remembering incorrectly. Either way they played the majority of the split in that one gauntlet run which is honestly depressing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-25 22:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We could probably lose like the bottom 3 LCS teams to facilitate this, could do without watching another split of MYM/NME and as a result the Challenger scene would be more competitive as better teams would be nearer the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-25 21:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cloud 9 actually ended up playing more games in the Gauntlet than they did in the entire LCS regular split which is outright stupid, best of 2 at the very least will be a welcome change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-21 19:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Alpha Draft plug keeps getting better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-19 19:43:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On the surface you're right but he's actually joking about the bloke with the Lamborghini </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-17 23:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [You know what they say about big feet](http://i.imgur.com/qyDEyuI.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-13 20:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whether you agree with this decision or not, it's pretty good of Gambit not to keep him in bench-zone hell like CPH did. That being said,if Forg1ven finds his way on another EU roster and starts wrecking face like spring split SK did, Gambit will have properly shot themselves in the foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-13 17:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you were actually watching any of the games in summer you'd know it wasn't him that was causing the games to be lost. His top/adc/supp were absolute trash tier and Fox is probably one of the less talented mids in EU. I implore you to ask any notable analyst/pro player in the EU scene of their opinion of Sven as a player and they're all gonna tell you a similar story. This guy can 1v9 unfortunately he was on a team of absolute shitters. 
Also I wouldn't play the 'hurr durr he got relegated card' considering CLG collectively are like the relegation kings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-12 19:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Token Sven montage](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ofmMM-x6RrQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-11 14:40:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a complete dribbler mate, nobody is on a level of Spirit/Mata in the West (at their peak). But you're kidding yourself if you think the 'intense competition' of NA will suddenly re-motivate him. I mean maybe some people would fear teams like Team 8 and NME however I don't think Mata is one of them. What I'm saying is there is good home grown talent that we as CLG fans and the org have turned their nose up to in the past. 
Obviously the cream of eastern talent is better than western but that's not the reason they do well at international tournies. Overall eastern teams have better team play and co-ordination. That's what wins them games not that one of their players is simply godlike. If CLG were to pick up some eastern talent we'd be back where we were with Seraph. Someone who's mechanically gifted but didn't mesh with the team. 
TL;DR- Team co-ordination and synergyindividual players  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-11 14:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I take it you weren't watching LPL this year. Mata is totally not the same player he was during his time on Samsung and Spirit's buyout clause would be so monumental it wouldn't be worthwhile due to the language barrier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-10 21:03:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kasing would honestly be incredible for support seeing as he does the teamfighting calling on H2K (same as Aphro) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-10 21:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes, more players who don't speak English : There's enough good western talent out there- most CLG fans just turn their noses up at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-10 21:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CLG has would TSM and TL never had and that's someone to keep egos/attitudes in line(my main man Chris). Heck if he can tame double I imagine the hamster would be hella easy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-10 20:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think if you're on TSM you're making bank my man, next time any of them stream you'll see what I mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-10 19:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure the prize for 3rd over 4th is pretty meager to an organisation as big as TSM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-10 19:17:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is Dyrus' last game, for the sake of the guy who's played for the team for six fucking years, the least they could do is give him top priority and one of his signature champs imo. CLG did it for the whole team for god sake (minus P.O.B) really poor taste from Loco tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-10 18:40:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He has his place, especially as a Fiora counter. Idk how western teams manage to fuck him up so frequently tho, most Korean teams execute him pretty well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-10 17:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lissandra for engage? pls no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-08 21:31:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbh I'm glad that it weeds out the band-wagoners, sucks to lose in such an appalling fashion but at least we won NA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Lose one game to get rid of all the band-wagoners*
Seriously though, don't be picking Blitz and reset for next week- there's no shame in losing to the third best KR team. You've just gotta own it and come in stronger next game- this is your group to win boys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd still put CLG over TSM at this tournament. And anyone considering LGD a top team at this moment in time is deluded tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought BKT were in group C? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought BKT were in group C? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-19 20:00:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure a similar thing was said last year and Looper pulled it out once if memory serves. I'm sure he'll see play in one form or another- probably if a team qualifies to leave the group stage with games remaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-11 21:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Me right now](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CFDCKlAWYAEdtHu.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-07 22:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The normal Brayllcs rumor circle, may or may not be true but I can't see them sticking together after a performance that bad.
Also when RNG tried to poach Quas it got revealed that he was being payed entry level LCS salary when he's a top 3 player in his position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-07 19:26:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seeing as the TL roster has apparently 'blown up' I think TSM Quas could be on the cards seeing as I think he's a NA resident at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-05 23:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every Goldper10 link ends that way ah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-05 19:00:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This series](http://i.imgur.com/0WZMgHg.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-05 18:52:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would rather have Doa tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-31 12:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Late Registration had better singles off the track whereas GKMC was more of a project you had to appreciate as a whole album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-30 20:30:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Breaking the guest right is certainly questionable but seeing as he's a southerner it doesn't hold as much weight. I think people are quick to hate Tywin because the Starks are portrayed in a very sympathetic manner in both the book and the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-30 18:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After reading A World of Ice and Fire I don't really consider Tywin to be evil, he's out for his family and his own ends sure, but the guy is not an evil character in my mind. Everything he does can be rationalized quite reasonably whereas 'evil' characters can't be done so well. Evil is more along the lines of Ramsey Snow(maybe I've been jaded by Charles Dance's portrayal of the character)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-30 18:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "God damn you, half-japanese girls" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-23 20:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not LCK or LPL, but Samsung Blue respected Sneaky's Lucian so much it was banned away from him at S4 worlds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-22 20:09:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything below FNC is just NA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-22 20:08:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the sake of Europe at worlds I'm glad H2K won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-16 00:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't mean to be smug but.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-14 23:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rush Hour should beat Adrian/Apollo and Pobelter will most likely school Gate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-14 23:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe TIP with XiaoweiXiao could, but honestly Gate looks like a huge liability to be exploited </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-14 21:00:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's your opinion and you're entitled to it, thanks for giving it a read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-14 18:33:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Zion and Impact are pretty similar mechanically, but Impact has better and more consistent TPs so that's why I'd rank him over ya boy Darshan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-14 18:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe in the goldenage, thanks for the kind words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-14 18:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-11 00:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is pretty well written, you probably want to consider putting stuff like this on sites like Gold per 10 if you haven't already (it's better formatting and looks more professional if you want to be writing more articles) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-10 19:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's meant to be entertaining on some level also, which at least for me it wasn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-10 16:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry but this was the most obnoxious and irritating thing I've ever watched </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-07 20:11:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [ALL ABOARD](http://i.imgur.com/PaDxitl.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Judging by your opgg, stop picking Vayne- you're winrate is trash. Start playing more Wukong, in both top and jungle. Pick up Amumu also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the song choice and clips used but you may want to consider using a shorter intro, it was kinda off putting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-05 16:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird ass stuffed crusts. Why would you put a HOT DOG IN A PIZZA CRUST? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-04 19:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Impact has a history of being more clutch than Zion but we've seen Zion play better than him in their respective matches. All depends on who shows up on the day really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-04 19:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's not unreasonable to think that we could make finals, all depends on the severity of how bad Rush bodies Xmithie tbh. At the very least we got a top four finish which is more than could be said for spring 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-29 11:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He didn't perform well with that champion overall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-28 23:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You did watch Bjergsen play Ezreal right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-28 23:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never saw your post T_T , I'm a big Garfunkel and Oates fan so I thought it was relevant sorry... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-28 22:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely forgot about that, Dignitas did look their best when he was about. Thanks for the tip!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-28 22:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a fair point and my thoughts on TSM aren't from a perspective of someone who is a fan, but someone who is critical of them as an org. I'm strongly of the opinion that Santorin is criminally overrated and that they've got some major issues right now. I probably should've detailed this in the piece but I think the rookie nature of GV will hinder their progress at playoffs. For all of them, except maybe Altec who played relegations, this is probably the most high pressure scenario they've faced in their careers. Whereas TSM have 4/5 experienced members who probably wont choke at a domestic level(worlds is another story). Even in more recent games there seemed to be at least some signs of life coming from Turtle in his play(albeit on Tristana). As for the Dig prediction, to put it mildly Rush is going to cave Helios' head in. I appreciate your thoughts and I probably should've been less lazy in my description of cheese 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-28 18:54:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fr8HKRTavM0) is somewhat relevant?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-27 11:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stay salty my man, I'm sure the best jungler in NA will pull you through these difficult times 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-26 23:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello again mate, did you watch the latest game? I assume you did. Hai was allowed not only to stack his devourer but also farm and entire bortk with no punishment from Santorin. I must say this has confirmed that TSM has the best jungler NA 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 13:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone who thinks he's garbage tier has clearly not been watching the actual garbage support players  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Relatively new to this sub ;_; acquiring one now~  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 22:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it's only a best of one, but they did just beat Origen. Stats are not the only thing that determine the worth of a player's play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 19:08:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think right now he's a middling support, sure he's no Yellowstar (but no westerner is) I just disagree that he sucks. You know who sucked? PromisQ sucked. You know who sucks right now? Nrated does. There's more adjectives to use when describing players than 'good' or 'bad'. Also I'd hardly call him consistently the weakest when NiQ was on the team and with the shaky nature of Diamondprox's play (see Volibear games). That's my two cents anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [mfw people think that Eddy sucks](http://gyazo.com/79f5a314b994b8ac26fb8b9cdc1b859d) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 18:37:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a joke mate, relax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hate to crush that dream but I've been a CLG fan since season 3 T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 13:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now THAT'S the kinda attitude!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-13 12:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello friend, did you watch this weekends TSM games (I assume you did). I just want to tell you that Santorin had a great performance and is totally worthy of the title of best jungler NA : </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it is inflated by teams winning (also given that with Keane and his cheese picks doesn't deal a lot of damage relative to other mids). Altec has for sure been looking impressive in their victories though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:27:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can't deny that Altec has been performing past expectations though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may have a differing opinion, but [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PHQLQ1Rc_Js) roughly sums up my thoughts currently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you go by the stats Altec is doing the most damage per minute out of any ADC in NA- do what you will with that information 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 
[MFW Fnatic lose early and keep winning late](http://i.imgur.com/skYOFwB.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 20:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a Sivir comp lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-09 19:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **FREE** **FREEZE** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-05 23:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [As a CLG fan](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/82/cf/9a/82cf9ac92ad6cdbad31409fc40b40f3b.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 12:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My point is that putting Santorin on Team 8 might very well be an upgrade- but is it going to elevate them to a position of a top team? Do you honestly think he's that good? Has ever displayed the ability to hard carry games in that manner? I'm done with this discussion- I should've known it was pointless arguing when I saw the TSM flair. I'll admit that NA jungle talent is particularly weak right now but that doesn't make Santorin automatically the best. (I'll PM you the next time he afk farms for 30 minutes having no game impact : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 12:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Compared to their form of previous splits Cloud 9 was slumping did you watch season 3/4? They had two of the most dominant runs in LCS history IN THEIR FIRST TWO SPLITS, so yes-by default they are slumping relative to their previous form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meteos was on a slumping team, Santorin was on the best team in NA- he's a mediocre jungler on a good team, nothing more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (First of all ignoring stats) Rush Move IWD- I'd even say Xmithie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:07:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna condense this because you're so hell bent on using stats as your main form of argument. It's INCREDIBLY EASY to have good stats when the rest of your team are TOP TIER. Bjergsen is probably the best western midlaner and Lustboy easily top 3 at his role and it just so happens those are the two Santorin interacts with most in game. Here's a scenario, if Santorin went to CLG or for the sake of relevance C9, would he be an upgrade in any sense? No. Has he got any real shotcalling experience?No.Will other teams have the same extensive infrastructure as TSM?No. He's a mechanically gifted player who somewhere down the line could be considered a top player in his role but right now his performance is a product of fortunate circumstance. I think Doublelift described it best when he said it's easy to call someone the best in their role when they're on the winning team(I'm paraphrasing here). Idk I'm cherry-picking here but in [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sJNrGv_6Tfo)loss he displayed a lot of characteristics he does when losing. Hard farming, not impacting the map in any meaningful way- overall just looking lost. And with that game don't give me any bs that Sejuani isn't viable for earlier ganks(she's mediocre but Dyrus was pushed to turret with no jungler assistance hahah). Put him on Team 8 and see if 'the best jungler in NA' can carry them- I highly doubt that would happen, put Rush on in and the Team has a fighting chance. Whatever though dude, I see the TSM flair so obviously it's hard to convert an atheist into a believer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta try to appear balanced :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obviously they need to evaluate the situation themselves, but what I'm urging is at least them attempting a tryout rather than just passing up the opportunity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 23:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Outjungling is easy when the rest of WE was kinda trash  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And then he went to MSI and got his head caved in : Also he's technically not the best jungler NA seeing as he's more like Bjergsen's wet nurse throughout the laning phase. Calling him a jungler would imply there's realistic strats around lanes other than middle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 20:00:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The dream isn't dead yet boys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:59:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He got his head caved in at the first IEM they played and MSI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:02:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [All aboard!](http://33.media.tumblr.com/39c28f9f336eef0e957e7e0c261deb31/tumblr_muwnclvnw91suydjqo1_400.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 16:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So what? There's plenty of examples of TSM players getting emotional with Regi(that one Dyrus video and that time he made xpecial cry). Ultimately TSM cares about results- they've shown that with the benching of Turtle and wouldn't pass up on the opportunity to at least attempting a jungle upgrade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-03 15:54:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And last split when he didn't have the responsibility of shotcalling in the second game of the split he caved Xmithie's head in haha. And just cause Xmithie clears a bunch of wards that makes him the better jungler? I think others would disagree with him being only a slight upgrade. C9 shit the bed this split admittedly but that isn't really reflective of his abilities as a jungler. I'm for a CLG move because TSM will just turn yet another aggressive jungler into Bjergsen's bitch for their time spent there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 20:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At the end of the day, results do speak for themselves- and during Charlie's tenure they have garnered some success. Calling the guy incompetent is hardly fair when he's at the very least contributed to their domestic victories. As for your personal issues with him, that's life- some people are asses, some people are not and some people are just too busy to properly deal with every suggestion they receive from a fan- that's life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 18:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kinda difficult considering I'm not Jewish 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 17:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madlife/Mata seem to prove that point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 16:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are you sourcing that he is anything but competent may I ask? I mean it's a pretty sweeping comment to make with out any actual evidence... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lemon's been performing to the same standard he always has done for C9, consistently decent but not amazing or trash tier. I don't get where all of this calling for Lemon to move into coaching comes from- he does the job and plays decently (you'd sacrifice the Sneaky/Lemon synergy just because he's not an out and out playmaking support player?) Lemon is a role player and quite a good one at that. Balls of old was a carry top and we're seeing him not play as a carry on favored champions and perform to a sub-standard on other tank champions. To me he is the logical choice IF any roster changes should be made(not saying there should be). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the kind words, it is very sad to see unchanged rosters like C9 split but I think it's ultimately for the betterment of the team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 22:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 19:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> About 8 months of playing on old AP fizz, was proper filthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Thinkcard mechanically sound"- please lord no anything but that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's got a higher potential skill ceiling than WT so it's at least worth lighting a fire under Turtle's ass as he's pretty much a known quantity in his play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-22 23:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And TSM would convert another aggressive jungler into Bjegsen's bitch for their stay on TSM. Watch Santorin in the challenger series, the dude actually was quite the playmaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 13:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me it's got to be, "I never sleep cause sleep is the cousin of death"- Nas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because Dre played a big part in the production of Snoop's first album as well as his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Fluff] From a pic that Double posted on twitter- hoping that Pob drops a mixtape any day now... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-31 20:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best ADC champ for solo queue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-30 00:24:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ashe is top tier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-29 20:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's kinda clear that although slightly edgier than before, the page maintains itself pretty well. In this week we've seen more creative content from the community than ever before in various pieces of fan art- heck even a new medium of content in GIFs is making the front page. Most of these things that the community clearly enjoys are making it to the front page(the cream of the content is rising to the top). So my question to you is- why are you such a huge presence on the page in terms of content filtration ('low effort' posts) when it's become increasingly clear that the community can self moderate for the most part?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not 100% sure they benched him. From what I've seen from around the scene Dexter wanted out of the environment- who could blame him? There's a big ego on that team 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-28 21:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> #KEEPNIQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 15:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your intro is one quarter of your video length.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 15:03:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's still relatively young in the scene so it's not like his career is going to end if he shits the bed. He'll probably do as anticipated, top 3 in Europe but not the best. Even if he does do crap, Fnatic management like him a lot so I imagine he'd get another split at the very least. He could probably move to NA and do just fin also seeing as there isn't a wealth of ADC talent over there and NA teams love to import European players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-26 12:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I was trying to be nice initially but this is genuinely an awful article in a lot of regards- namely that they put Liquid at number 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:29:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a good perspective but you've got the Gravity section quite wrong.I can't find it right now but Cop stated in an Ask.fm post that he was burnt out (essentially) and decided to call it a day. As far as I'm aware it wasn't a move from management/coaching that caused Cop leaving- just the end of his career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have any proof he is?(other than what this account has tweeted) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate to break it to you mate, but there's nothing really crazy about this play. The only crazy thing here is that it's 33 minutes in and you still have the tier 1 support item. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a bunch of people sitting in the new section sitting in new downvoting all the stuff that's irrelevant etc (doing what the mods did), once a post reaches enough downvotes it gets removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This account is also claiming to have MonteCristo as a coach- QQ it appears to be a sad wannabe, P1noy is going to WFX sorry mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was exactly the same this time last year but with Lee/Kha'Zix/Rengar/Vi, change is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 22:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All of your thoughts on casters,- that's your opinion not an objective truth. It happens that Krepo kinda is hugely popular with fans so you won't get far with that one. It sounds like you've just come out of your phase of liking pro League judging by cynical you are. Idk man, watch csgo or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 21:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Each to their own, Reddit has a friendlier UI so that's my reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 20:46:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every reason I've seen for his shit being banned was to do with personal attacks etc- there seem to be a lot of mixed reasons behind it. Idk I'm probably biased because I disagree with content bans on general(I think those who break the rules should have their content heavily 'weighted' in terms of karma so it deters people from doing it while still making content visible). At the end of the day the guy's gotta eat and removing his main source of traffic is just a dick move as a whole. The irony is, they did this to hurt Richard Lewis and his revenue but as a result they've generated more interest and discussion around his work than ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 18:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So far it's been somewhat alright though, it'd be interesting to see if the white knights on the new section would actually be able to hold off the torrent of shitposting for a week. Don't get me wrong, lately the mods have been going power crazy as fuck in terms of content they don't like or have personal grievances with *cough Richard Lewis cough*. Their role needs to be restructured to a more janitorial type, but who's actually going to do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 18:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://img1.goodfon.su/original/5000x3500/a/90/bolshoy-brat-big-brother-1984.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 18:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasn't aware of this, I think my point still stands though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's pretty unsustainable to be honest, although the mods make some questionable decisions a lot of times they are what separate us from being /v/ on 4chan. The only reason the sub is relatively usable currently is due to people downvoting the shit out of any crap on the new section </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 15:42:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 11:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>            






le
toucan
has
arrived </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 11:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-25 00:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Thanks mate](https://data.archive.moe/board/a/image/1337/02/1337022434200.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 23:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll take it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-24 23:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (Yes this is satire, a shit attempt at it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 22:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a fair point tbh, just think how long that champion wasn't viable for-early s3 maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 20:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate to be pedantic but there was a shitty Ferris Bueller TV spinoff [Brace yourself it is total ass](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vy2kAfHHids) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 23:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heimerdinger cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 16:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except depression is a biological disorder often linked with psychological issues, it's a chemical imbalance. Being an asshole(toxic)is just because you get frustrated and have no other way of expressing it. Have some self control mate, it's not some biological problem making you act like a dickhead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saying "I think I am better than x person and beat them"
is different to:
"X team is going to crash and burn because they are garbage"
It's better to big yourself up than knock someone else down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They talked a lot of smack before the tournament in a very harsh and degrading way-See: [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SoQpYma-OcA).
Also more cursory/bandwagon fans aren't used to their team losing and because they're so entitled they feel the need to endlessly criticize in the echo-chamber that is this subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel TSM should take notes on how to talk smack from Huni. No talk about how garbage the either side is just your own team/region proving they are better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He does what he can with the resources he's allocated(which ain't a lot)- hence he's the 'Janitor' of FNC. If/when Rekkles does get put back in it's a case of finding a way of working him into the team setting and gold distribution. Rekkles is a more mechanically adept and overall more polished marksman and would've performed better in that situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's fair enough for TSM to have entered the competition confident, they came in off the back of a domestic victory and an international tournament win. They had every right to be confident in their ability and maybe thinking they could contest for a top spot but they executed it poorly when slamming other teams. It's fair enough to be confident in your own play but ripping down other teams is incredibly short sighted. Granted that hindsight is 20/20 TSM had no reason not to be sure of themselves going into MSI based on their recent performances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And this is helping how??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:08:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe step one is realising that it's only a game at the end of the day? I get that people get frustrated but maybe if you want to not be able to be toxic you should just stop being toxic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I somehow think it's highly unlikely that a coach of a team with a high profile like TSM would be allowed to do an AMA after that performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get trashed at one tournament and suddenly you know what it's like to be a CLG fan? Oh my sweet summer child, you know nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could just drag the chatbox off the screen if you really can't handle having a chat in-game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-09 15:01:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In other news, water is wet. This game's code is old as heck and built off DoTA which in turn came from Warcraft 3. Given how big the game is now (100+ champions), it's impressive that bugs like these are a relative rarity. Essentially it's well documented that the game's code is spaghetti and often fixing one bug results in the another 3 being made off of that(remember how long it took Shen to be re-enabled in competitive?). As for the casters, they're explicitly told not to highlight in game bugs too much as they are front of house in terms of competitive League- you wouldn't tell someone staying at your hotel everything wrong with it would you?
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-04 20:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "One often meets his destiny on the path he takes to avoid it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I am white http://euw.op.gg/summoner/userName=subject1517 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-03 22:29:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 90s gangster rap, primarily the East coast lot. Nas, Biggie etc. Also I'm really into the Chronic 2001 by Doctor Dre(I know it's west coast) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard to gauge how good something is when music is completely subjective... Of course there's a general consensus but ultimately whatever anyone says is just their opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All of this may be true but if you asked an average joe on the street he's likely say they were alright at the very least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It must be pretty boring to be your average TSM/Chelsea fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was a Liverpool fan when I was into football, I guess I've got a thing for the teams with *potential* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:23:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Each to their own I guess, but the vast majority of people would disagree that the Beatles are/were shitty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-01 20:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a valid point, I guess I was focusing more on them falling off as a whole- but the TSM comparison makes far more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 22:12:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Speaking of strong in-game leaders, a certain Russian was a free agent a while back.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a fair point on the issue of CLG needing a leader (I take it you watched Thooorin's video on it), at the very least it's an avenue to consider until they find a more permanent solution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate to ask but where are you getting this from? Also it's hard to make a judgement on a coach when none of us are actually in the house with them, Scarra stepped down not kicked remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not take that risk? LiNk just seems to roll over and die as soon as he's put under any pressure, he's had a number of splits to show up and hasn't. Pobelter may be a risk but he's a breath of fresh air at the very least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So Pobelter for LiNk is a poor replacement, or my thoughts on Double? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 20:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Each to their own I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 20:38:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Velocity in the chat managed to complete the Blastoise with 120K people watching, it's pretty hard to do so people go mental when it happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 16:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play what you enjoy for sure, but FYI it's an uphill battle playing Vayne right now, her laning phase is ass and her build paths powerspike at weird times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's not been viable since early S4, play Lucian//Graves- way easier but still with a bit of mechanical skill required. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-26 14:21:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good in low ELO, people can't deal with split pushing, in higher tiers he's kinda awful cause he can get kited quite easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 23:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (Skipping straight to 3)
Honestly I just want a team that fights for their wins and doesn't just roll over and die when their level 1 doesn't go to plan. I want to see some actual desire put out from the team and clutch plays to be pulled out from the jaws of defeat. I want more actual CLG the Ballista, the ball delivery system etc etc. They may not be the best team but I want CLG to fighting for every last inch in their games, think Alex Ich in the Gambit relegations, he played like a man possessed- it's that kind of passion I want from CLG. Not some namby pamby "our lane swap wins us the game" bs- I'd like to see a team that can teamfight and teamfight until the bitter end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 19:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a reason people don't upload 40 minute long VODs onto youtube, people don't watch them. If you're doing full games put that shit on Twitch and post the highlights on youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 19:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't mute everyone but drag the chatbox off the screen so that if I need to talk I can bring it back on at any time. Probably posture-wise it's better to play at a desk if possible, slouching for long periods of time can ruin your back!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 19:07:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fredy//Impaler and I guess at one point Snoopeh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 18:21:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fusion look like another mid tier team from what I've seen, just because no team is C9//Quantic level straight out of promotions doesn't mean that it's garbage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-25 16:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure Jack is the owner of C9 now, but Hai was the original owner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-20 22:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you feel are the best champs right now in Solo Queue for ADC, also any tips on Jinx/other immobile champs ?(I can't kite for shit)- thanks for the AMA mate 8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-18 19:26:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's put badly but last year we had a heat wave during the summer and a fair amount of older folk actually died- AC is a rarity over here and with global warming it's becoming a an increasing problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 13:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never done it personally- I may have to try it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Neat idea to solve the Pink Ward trade off. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-12 13:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So when you get to near full build as a support (or any other role, but primarily support) you're left with a decision. Do I complete my build? Or leave a spot open for pink wards? The solution I've come up with is an inventory slot only for pink wards (I'm aware the pink ward trinket exists but you're not gonna replace your Oracle's sweeper with that at any point). The way to balance this would to have it be a mastery unlock in the utility tree, that way it would be balanced as the only role who's going to spec heavily into the utility tree is traditionally the support role. Sorry if an idea like this has been posted before but I haven't seen anything of this nature on the sub-let me know what you think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 20:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's her placing herself already above others though, she's decided herself that she is intelligent and suffers because of it. Idk context is important and this girl is extremely up herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 20:01:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Black happens to be her long-suffering best friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-05 16:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This post comes around every 2 months or so, there's a multitude of reasons why it's currently not in the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lulu has been played in every position competitively except ADC (to my knowledge). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 17:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a common bug if you use an ability directly after spawning where it will go on a normal cooldown(not sure if this applies to you, but that's the one that is documented). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 16:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's like saying Reignover is the best jungler in EU and basing that statement on games versus MYM and Giants, of course x jungler is going to look amazing against the bottom tier teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 23:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or pick Vayne/Kog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 22:32:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Coast making Avalon look good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-29 12:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just wanna fuck bad bitches (Fuck you- Chronic 2001) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [DOES THIS LOOK LIKE THE FACE OF MERCY?](http://i.imgur.com/QoLacVM.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-22 22:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link got his head caved in by Bjergsen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-16 22:50:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [You know what time it is](http://i.imgur.com/innGjkF.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 15:02:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, kinda gutted that I've screwed over  people's ranked game tho :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unable to launch the game (can get into champion select just fine) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-15 14:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm the process of re-installing right now and am just wondering if this is a common issue. I can load up the launcher just fine but as soon as the countdown ends I can't launch the game (the logo doesn't even show up). Hopefully it is just a client side issue not my PC dying on me- any help or similar issues would be appreciated, thanks . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 23:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm damned if I respond to this, and damned if I don't- but for what it's worth I did see it on the chat and it gave me a small chuckle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-07 23:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Meteos building tanky is like watching Sasha Grey hug someone" - Twitch Chat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 23:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Learn to carry, if you can't carry a game it's on you- expect nothing from your teammates and you'll be surprised when they actually do good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-09 23:22:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're on tilt, don't bother playing ranked until the reset and just play normals with friends. Playing more solo queue is just going to make things worse. And the ranked reset will give you a clean slate also </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-27 21:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last season's ranked reset was January 11th (I think) so expect it around that time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-16 18:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kha'Zix is so broken, you've basically been given a mechanic to guarantee assassinations with your ult and poro toss synergy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 17:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [I'm not proud of what I've made](http://i.imgur.com/CMvZYsi.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-23 17:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The new Jungle items suit on him very well (on hit effects), it's preseason so balance changes are bound to happen. A similar thing happened when Feral flare was first released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 21:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah ok thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 21:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah thanks, probably should have kept up with the changelog a bit better. Thanks for clarifying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 21:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think so, sure the palette is kinda similar but in terms of structures and actual textures it's very different. You could attribute some of the similarities to the fact that League was a first (essentially) a Dota 1 mod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Performance issues with the new SR </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-15 21:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've played a couple games on the updated Summoners Rift and so far really like it, one thing I have noticed though is whenever a friendly Thresh throws out his lantern I experience really massive FPS drops around the lantern itself. I own a mid-range gaming PC and play on medium settings, so far I've never experienced this on the old map. If anyone else is experiencing please do comment about it. Cause then we'll know if it's an actual issue or just my PC's slow descent into becoming a toaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 18:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rework=changing the way a few abilities work, dmg values, scaling etc etc
Re-Release=complete overhaul of the champion's identity, lore and abilities
Poppy=Re-release </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 17:46:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's too early to say as of right now, maybe some changes made in preseason will make her completely irrelevant as a marksman altogether(highly unlikely). But seeing as she has quite a high skill ceiling it would make sense that she sees competitive play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 17:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not a rework buddy, they're pulling a Sion on her because she doesn't fit in with the rest of the game anymore (or ever has).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 16:32:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "you don't give a fuck, do ya mate?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-07 18:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get high Gold/ Low plat and work on my champion pools for all roles, and maybe have a bit of fun (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 17:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so confused </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-25 13:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why buy it then? It's just a waste of gold if you're not gonna use the active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 13:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you're (Samsung) right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-19 03:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By the way I was playing almost certainly not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Report (insert player here)" [Relevant](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8icKGCwhJ-w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **D A R K N E S S**(crying intensifies) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally, I think jungle is way more viable right now for newbies. With the timers it's pretty hard to miss buffs and that was the main thing setting good junglers out from the trash in solo queue. IMO jungle is great cause you can manipulate the game via ganks and general pressuring. You can set the pace of the game and provide general shotcalls throughout the match. You will also get the most hate out of any role so there's that also :^) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahri's death noise (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can play any champion effectively against people of the same skill level it's 'super op'. Yi scales very well with a solid lead and can push hard all game. He suits solo queue if you know how to play him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 23:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Renekton has probably the most potent early games of any top laner right now, lvls 1-11 he is untouchable with his lifesteal and empowered abilities. Once you've been itemised against you fall of real hard late. Unlike the majority of champions designed as tanks Renekton scales poorly and overall kit sucks for soaking up damage effectively. It's not the case that he does it badly but think of Mundo or Maokai ulti, he just isn't that great comparably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-18 14:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're going for irony here, but I hate to break to you that this video is just straight up not funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 22:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nidalee supports are the terror of low ELO maybe changing this would help avoid that one 'support' who always buys doran's ring and takes farm :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-15 22:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's probably one of the best duelists in the game so she can bully super hard in lane and push relatively well. Quinn has 2 major flaws in right now though, the first being she's mostly garbage outside of lane and her team fight is incredibly poor, the second being that there are simply better champions that fit the meta more right now (Irelia Maokai Nidalee Rumble). If you look at Irelia she splitpushes way harder and can actually teamfight very consistently. Not only that she can do loads of damage with only a couple of offensive items allowing her to provide utility for the team with Defensive stats.TL;DR Quinn isn't the greatest top laner because there are champions that do what she does but a lot better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 19:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Have you tried turning it off and on again" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 17:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nn2FB1P_Mn8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-10 17:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The monster with the buff will completely trash you while you clear the miniature ones, by the time you get round to it you'll be low on hp and potentially on cooldowns from clearing the little ones. Also securing the buff as soon as you can just makes more sense logically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-07 18:57:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not so certain, it's an entire re-release (new lore,gameplay and a complete VU) so he may cost 6300. I bought him before he gets changed just to be on the safe side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes you can be fed and the rest of the game doesn't fall in your favour. Admittedly Yasuo is pretty strong right now but he can't 1v5 quite :) Some games are just lost, it's out of your hands sometimes and you just gotta accept that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:37:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *cough Sion *cough (I'm aware he's getting re-released) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's perma banned right now (especially lower elo), when a champ is in that state it's a sign that something isn't right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Increased HP would definitely be a step in the right direction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It all depends on how fed your are but there are a couple of relatively ways to carry solo queue when you're ahead. The first being, buy wards! Light up that map like a Christmas tree, make sure to get pinks as well as denying vision is just as important as gaining it. The second and probably most relevant as a midlaner is to roam to other lanes once you've shoved your lane. When you're ahead in lane as mid, it's your duty to try and snowball the side lanes to make the weight of carrying later a lot lighter. 
Tl;dr- ward loads, roam when your lane is pushed.
Hope that helped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tristana is the meta right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-05 22:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's an interesting idea but I can't see why people would take mana over more hp personally. The issue is that there's no point building Ruby Sightstone and implementing this kind of change what just leave 'Sapphire Sightstone' in the same place Ruby is nowadays. I think Ruby either needs to be made viable through regenerating wards every 2 mins or so (for example) or just remove it entirely because it has no purpose currently.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 17:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't advertise on here man also with 1159 total views this isn't your first stream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-02 19:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't advertise streams on here yo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-30 17:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a very valid point,if played correctly CLG's top lane could be the strongest in the reigion IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-29 19:51:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I forgot that Seraph played a really strong mid lane, but it's unlikely that Nien would come back permanently IMO he stepped down of his own accord after the hate got too much if I remember correctly. There's no doubt he'd perform brilliantly though, his play during Super Week was incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-28 19:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She fits the 'high vision control' game very well, if you have control of an area, lets say the brush behind red buff it's incredibly easy to land a pick and kill someone in their own jungle. After that you can fight 4 vs 5 and win most of the time as you probably didn't burn much off the pick itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-28 19:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because his siege and overall range are complete garbage, if you're looking to take out towers there are better picks. I do agree that as an aggressive short range ADC he is very strong both in and outside of lane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-28 19:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think what's more important is the fact that Kabum managed to take down Alliance after their perfect match against shield- it's really big for the Brazilian League and Pro-Gaming scene as a whole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-28 19:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think she's one of the champions inline for a rework (Sion was top of their list but he's just got an entire re-release). But they're not reworking Poppy because she's 'broken' or anything it's just because she really doesn't fit in with the rest of the game whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:38:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People can have their opinions on my opinions it's not really an issue, all I wanted to do was contribute to the discussion () </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 15:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo don't advertise your stream on this subreddit dude, you'll get banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 14:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as I'm aware he went home to Germany on vacation, loads of players do it in the off season. I seem to remember Krepo goes back to Belgium to see his family after every split so it's most likely the same sort of thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah man, I wasn't aware of this, thanks for the heads up :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure it'll be up again soon, maybe you could try to cast some of the worlds games? They'll be pretty interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No you can't right now, I know it's dumb :^( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not gone, just the Shurima and World's events are covering them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:05:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the most played game in the world so it's probability that there's more assholes playing it. From what I've heard Dota is pretty chill nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:04:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it all lies in how Game one goes, if SSW lose that initial match I think it's anyone's series. I think if TSM lost that first match however, they'll go on tilt and get 3-0'd . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 12:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your utility as a support late game is near top tier (ish) but it's whether or not your AD can actually do reasonable in lane without a support with good lane presence, you see it succeed at high ELO doing so well because the ADs now how to read the game and play accordingly.
TL;DR your AD needs to be able to look after themselves more during laning phase IMO   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 11:56:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as I'm aware the season ends sometime in November (they haven't specified an exact date yet) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 11:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do agree with the issues around their entire team being centered around Dlift, not only has been been under performing as of late, that kind of composition/play style isn't viable in this meta anymore. Hopefully they'll move away from this strategy during the break and stop tunnelling bot lane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-23 11:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk, I think individually they're all good players they just have some major behind the scenes and shotcalling issues which are holding them back. Sure Link and Dexter tilted a bit near the end of a split but I think a roster change is the last thing they need right now. That's my 2 cents anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 19:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I said mid lane was the shortest lane in the game I meant that literally too, minions get to the players faster so they accumulate more cs, this is especially relevant seeing as it's virtually impossible to freeze mid lane and the denial of farm is way more difficult to achieve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-22 17:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mid is the shortest lane in the game so therefore champs who benefit with high amounts of farm such as mages and assassins benefit the most from being played there. Look at the LCS mid Laners will almost always have the highest cs in the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 21:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's unnecessary exchanges like this which are holding back esports as a whole IMO. I'm all for competitive trashtalk when t's relative to the situation- sure during playoffs you can rib the enemy teams-that happens in pretty much every sport. [Look at boxing] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WsAC4lhbE0g) this sort of stuff happens all the time when it's relevant. The key distinction here is that these attacks aren't relevant they're just mindless digs at an organisation they've already shown their superiority over. Monte is the kind of esports presence that Locco and Regi need to emulate, his opinions are thought out and objective, he doesn't go after and attack other members of the community and he's darn good at his job. 
TL;DR Regi   Locco should be more like Monte instead of tearing him down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-18 18:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they'll probably release a new set when group stages are over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 20:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think as soon as esports gets legitimized as an actual career path out in the west is the time we'll actually begin to see a drastically improved infrastructure .Look at the OGN, esports is way more accepted over in Korea and the infrastructure is vastly greater this sort of thing happens organically and IMO Riot can only help stimulate the process to a certain extent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 20:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's an issue with the launcher/client itself as far as I'm aware- they updated the visuals but the framework behind the software wasn't really designed for the sheer volume of players it experiences. Steam has a similar issue, sure they have the right amount of servers but the application itself is kinda outdated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 20:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's so hard to bug test a champion in a game as large as League of Legends think about all the different interactions and reactions new champs have with pre existing ones- it's mind-boggling if you think about it. Sure it would be nice to have him ready for play but if you consider how bugs there are with pre-existing champions it's hardly surprising that they're not quite happy with Azir yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-17 20:17:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flat health tricks the enemy into thinking you have less Hp than you actually do so there's that to it. Your best option is probably a mixture of the two seeing as a support armor is especially useful when dealing with AD champions in lane. Test things out in normals though and find out what works best for you :^) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 17:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're entitled to your opinion and that's fair enough, I'll admit that this video is probably garbage relative to other videos of this nature on Youtube but you've got to start somewhere I guess?
In no way was I trying to make a montage parody or 'mlg' video with this, primarily I wanted to try stuff out in Sony Vegas. 
The reason there's a lack of plays is the fact that I'm Silver V so essentially that makes me Bronze.

P.S you should get that disease checked out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-12 17:31:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clannad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-26 15:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> League. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-21 12:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you tense a muscle(e.g biceps) the boner dies faster than otherwise. With practice you can become a bona-fide boner slayer-no more awkward erections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>