<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8438</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 03:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Siberia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 19:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I literally spit my drink out laughing at this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 22:04:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Life As We Knew It collection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 20:22:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I did TA during one semester of grad school (General Psychology in 2011). It was an on campus position, but had an online component (Blackboard for papers and quizzes) that I was in charge of. I normally add that into my cover letter as experience, but I feel like since it was so long ago, it doesn't really help. My second Master's degree was online, so I didn't have the opportunity to be a TA. My PhD is online as well (I work full time and it is paid for through my job), but if they offered an online TA position, I would definitely be interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to get INTO adjunct teaching? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 19:51:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is the right place to post this, but I've been coming up against a brick wall when it comes to finding an adjunct job. I am looking either for a remote position. I have a Bachelor of Science in Psychology, Master of Arts in Mental Health Counseling/Certification in School Counseling, and a Master of Education in Higher Education. I am starting on my journey to PhD on November 21st. I have worked in the online atmosphere for the last 7 years, but have not taught. I did help teach a General Psychology course during my first Master's program (2011), but that was a long time ago. I have been an academic advisor with full access to a plethora of learning platforms, as well as a student online. 

Any advice for getting into the field? I have applied for just about any adjunct psychology position, and I never get a response (yes or no). I feel that I have a strong cover letter and resume. How do I get ANY experience if everyone requires experience? 

 #x200B;

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 19:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Haunting Ground - I believe it's PS2 only, and very hard to find. But this game gave me nightmares! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahhhh I just failed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beer bad, tree pretty.... 

This is one of my all-time favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats! You look great!!! I can totally relate to the diminished tolerance for alcohol... I do vodka soda with lime (pretty much zero carbs), but whereas I used to be able to pound them down, two or three will do me in! The thing I miss the most is... beer :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mouth is watering just reading this... Haha. 

I LOVE chili, and make it keto as much as possible. I have yet to try keto "cornbread"... I will have to attempt that! It's difficult sometimes, because my husband hates the "pretending to be something else" type foods (which is what keeps me sane on keto) so it's a struggle sometimes! 

One of the things I miss the most is cereal. So weird, because I didn't eat it THAT much when I was non-keto. But, I made my own. Almonds, coconut flakes (baked) and then add some dark chocolate chips. Add some almond milk and voila! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:08:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish they distributed all of these awesome beers ANYWHERE near me :( I search every time a new one is posted. My only options here are Michelob Lite (and I'd rather just not have any beer at all at that point!!!). 

Hopefully with the keto movement being as big as it is (and ever growing), distributors nationwide will wise up and jump on the bandwagon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 21:04:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are so right. I did keto from October 2018 to March 2019 (strict, no cheating, even on Thanksgiving and Christmas), and then I lost my job... I fell off the wagon super hard and gained 15lbs from March to August. Then I got a new job and was excited to get back on track.  Fast forward to October and I still hadn't gotten back into the groove. I would give myself multiple "cheat days", which didn't help at all! Then, after that candy fiasco, it was the last straw! I've been super vigilant now, and I finally feel like I'm in a "now I'm on it, and I'm ok" place. 

Moral of the story: Don't fall off the wagon! Haha. 

Mo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 19:19:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is great! I wish I had a happy story like this (although mine is happy in the end)... I got candy for my desk mid-October. I got it as a test to myself (was trying to get back on keto after a long hiatus), and I FAILED... One day (October 16) I just had a HORRIBLE day at work and binged on half of the bowl (mostly sweet/sugary things like Skittles, Twizzlers, Starburst - I was missing sweets hard core). I was so upset with myself, and that was the day I decided that I couldn't take it anymore... I made the decision that it was keto or bust, and I chose keto. I filled the bowl back up the next morning for my students, and haven't touched any since. I also survived trick-or-treat last night! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 18:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done, hope it was helpful :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 16:08:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi there! I will be starting my PhD on November 21st. Would I be of any help, or are you looking for people to start today? Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 15:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While inspecting my daughter's (6yo) candy haul last night, we found a "Jesus loves you" pamphlet with a "bracelet" that was akin to the crown of thorns. We asked her if she remembered where she got it, but she did not. So hopefully she did not get the same hateful and disgusting speech! That makes me sick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 15:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great job! I did the same, and I feel so validated today. It's a great feeling :) I just took some almonds along with me trick-or-treating, and any time I got the "urge", I just ate those instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 14:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think of the quote "History is bound to repeat itself"... If we don't learn about the historical benefactors to psychology, we won't understand psychology as it is today, or may even make some of the same mistakes they did. I have found it fascinating to learn about the history of psychology and where the field started, how it progressed, and where we are today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 14:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So creative. I love this! What did you use to dip with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Survived Halloween Cravings! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 14:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I survived Halloween and Trick-or-Treating with my six-year-old. She even got some of my favorites (100 Grand, Milky Way, Reese's). It would have been so easy to say "Well, just one won't hurt..." But, I was smart. I took some almonds with me, and munched on those every time I got a craving. Super proud of myself!!! Any other Halloween success stories out there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 19:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Sparrow/Children of God - Mary Doria Russell. I will forever recommend this series. You won't regret it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 13:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't been able to find them :( Just this newest Halloween special, which is in with Tri-Force. I would LOVE it if it was! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 21:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I think one of my biggest obstacles is that my husband and step-daughter (6 years old) love to do big breakfasts on the weekends, that normally aren't until 10 or 11. So I need to figure out what time would be best for me. Maybe an 11-7 could work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 20:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do a LOT of black coffee, tea, and water. It's always freezing in my office, so the hot drinks are my best friends in the AM. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 20:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am currently on keto. I did it from October 2018-March 2019 (lost my job - lost my motivation). Gained almost 20lbs back over the summer. Started back on strict keto October 21st of this year. So, maybe once my body gets used to that, fasting will be a bit easier. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 16:06:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Sparrow/Children of God - Mary Doria Russell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 15:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will do! I will probably start next week (I know, I know - no time like the present), but I just spent a lot of money on my lunches for the week (I always go Mondays and pre-make them - strict keto at this time). I'll keep you posted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 15:52:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry I must have missed that comment about your hours. I think I will try that! I feel like breakfast and dinner would be much more my style than lunch and dinner (although sometimes it is difficult, as I work in an office and people are always either bringing IN food or going out to lunch). I am normally up by 6 (work at 8) and home by 5:30. So actually thinking about it, that makes SO much more sense! 

But, I won't know if I don't try. Thank you for the tip :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 15:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look great! I am really trying to get on the IF bandwagon, but I struggle in the mornings. I had tried not eating after dinner (so around 7 or 8pm), but find myself STARVING by 9-10am. Did you have any trouble with that? If so, what are some tips to get past that hump? 

Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 21:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Older (80s), but Motel Hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 21:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hiddensee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 21:26:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Child of the Owl - Lawrence Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 21:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Duckman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 21:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mavis Beacon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 20:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the tip. I have never been a fan of scales, but most keto things I paid attention to said weighing is important (prior to being a Reddit user). I have learned a lot of new things in a short time, and some of it is overwhelming. I think I will order a tape measure to try that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 15:17:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bah, sorry. Thought I had it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 15:15:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh what about  Super Smart Science Series  - Author: April Chloe Terraza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 15:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was it Highlights? The magazines that used to be in doctor/dentist offices? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 14:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! When I first started keto last October (2018), I only weighed myself once a week (Wednesdays) and I did it in the morning and then before bed, just to get an understanding of those fluctuations. It worked well for me. I think this time I've just been a little too hopeful too quickly, because last time, I lost so much within the first week and I was thinking it would be the same this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 14:33:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Irvin Yalom has a lot of books similar to Oliver Sacks. I have all of both of their collections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 14:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is an amazing story. I remember, looking back, how I used to eat just to eat. Sitting in front of the tv or a video game, I would just stuff my face with chips, cookies, etc. (with a six year old in the house, it's hard to resist her treats). I didn't have the "a-ha" moment that you did, but I think that was a great moment for you. I also gave myself goals in "steps" so that I did not feel so overwhelmed with that far off scale number. 

Keep it up, and I promise you won't be disappointed!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 14:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess my biggest challenge now is realizing that it won't be as "easy" as the first time around, since I don't have as much to lose. I haven't gotten to the point of feeling "better" health wise, but I'm sure once I get there I won't be so down on myself. Thank you for the reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 14:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely agree with this statement. I did almost feel like a recovered alcoholic who then went on a binge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 14:19:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do plan on staying on keto from here on out. My depression (life-long) makes that hard sometimes, especially when other big things happen (i.e.: losing my job). At first I thought I'd be OK with some "cheat days", but I realize that isn't helpful to my weight loss, my mental health, OR my diet in general. Thank you for the reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 13:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't recall this episode exactly, but the Netflix series "Creeper" has different concepts each episode, although they all start and end with the "Creeper" and how he collects his stories. Could it be this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Struggling to Stay Motivated when Keto "Isn't working" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 13:42:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, I lost 40lbs between October of 2018 and March of 2019. I did strict keto for the entire time, logging into CarbManager (22 net carbs a day - my suggested macros at the time), plus exercise 5 days a week (yoga, treadmill, kettle bells). I felt amazing. I was down to my first goal (150) and ready to keep going onto my second goal (140). I hit a plateau, and wasn't losing any more. Then, I lost my job. I was at home all summer, from March until August. With that came a depression like no other, and I fell off the wagon. Hard. I couldn't get the motivation to exercise OR eat right. I ate the pizza and I drank the beer. I went back up to 168lbs. My new clothes no longer fit and I lived in leggings and baggy t-shirts because I refused to go back out and buy "fat clothes" (most of my weight tends to return around my stomach area). I finally got a new job in August and decided it was time for me to get my health/life back on track. There's a gym at my office, and I can pack my own lunches so I know what I will have each day. But, I still kept making excuses, and here I am almost three months later. I started back on strict keto on October 21st. Using CarbManager again and it suggests 20 net carbs per day. The diet hasn't been a struggle for me and I feel like I've jumped back in quite easily, but the motivation to exercise still isn't there (I'm dealing with migraine and tiredness from the sugar withdrawal). When I weighed in Saturday morning (Oct. 26), I was down to 164.7 and was so excited. Then, I weighed myself again this morning (Oct. 29) and was back at 167.8! My heart fell. I'm guessing that I am doing something wrong this time around, and I am not sure what. Has anyone else had trouble once getting back ONTO keto after a fall off the wagon? Am I alone in this? What can I do? 

 #x200B;

TL;DR: Getting back on the wagon, but not getting results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 21:07:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think there's an episode of either Angel or Buffy with this premise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 18:51:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When we make meatloaf, we use eggs and Parmesan cheese to bind it. We also use mustard, and a bunch of random spices (never the same). Recently, we have been adding bacon as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 20:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sounds similar to The House that October Built </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 20:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eurotrip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 20:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Grey Zone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 20:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Superwhy? Although I'm not sure of live-action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 20:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it "Bully" from 2001? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 17:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She is precious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 17:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Man in the High Castle. Or pretty much anything by Philip K. Dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 15:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jimmy Neutron? 

Ben10?

Garage Kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 15:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People at my old job used to play "the marble game". Everyone had to have their marble on them at all times. If someone asked to see your marble and you didn't have it, you had to pay them $1.00. It didn't have an official name, but it seems similar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 14:22:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It almost sounds like "Haunting Ground", but I believe that was a PS exclusive and the main character was a girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 01:37:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sparrow/Children of God by Mary Doria Russell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 18:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boogie   Eminem - Rainy Days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 18:14:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  ***Anatomy*** ([German](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/German_language): *Anatomie*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 17:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Final? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 17:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Bernstein Bears Get Stage-fright? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 17:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  

# The Sheriff and the Satellite Kid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 15:27:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mary Doria Russell - The Sparrow/Children of God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 14:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of mine are from cat scratches (two a$$hole cats), but I recently got quite a few from a REALLY bad bout of poison ivy. Mostly on my wrists and ankles. Nothing some new tattoos won't fix! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>