<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5583</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 22:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to be technical, the Earth is always moving (it will never be in the same position of the universe as it was 5 years ago). Therefore, there will be displacement, but I'm assuming that you are disregarding that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 17:39:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only got to states in eighth grade since the winner of the state bee went to my school until last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 17:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I got screwed over by the person reading the questions mispronouncing a lake and one of the questions was completely incorrect. It asked about the country that the Altiplano was in the east of. The answer was Peru and I said Bolivia. The region is in SOUTHERN Peru and extends into Bolivia and even Chile. Then afterwards I knew the answers to the rest of the questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should I self studyt his year or next year? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 01:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I  am a freshman have a good background in geography (tied for fifth at the state geo bee)  The class is offered at my school, but I don't have the schedule space for it. I'm either going to take the test this year or next year. I have had the Princeton's prep book since last year. I recently took a practice test and got a high 2 (after not having casually skimmed the textbook for 7 months). This year I'm also taking the NEWL Russian exam, which is basically an AP exam. Next year I'm taking AP American Government and Calc AB. I'm also thinking about self studying AP European History and/or AP Phsycology. I have a bunch of free time after school (at least now). So should I do it this year or next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 22:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't personally think that it was hard. You just divided by (a-12) on both sides and then see when the denominator is equal to 0 since you can't divide by 0. a has to be 12 since 12-12=0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When your school system removes class rank because they want to protect feelings: well yes but actually you can't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea and then I took out my backpack and APHUG textbook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:32:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just happy that it's over and I can take care of my other things that I put aside to study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took the 8/9 and not the regular one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:24:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm taking PreCalc and the questions were basically elaborately asking to divide 65 by 5 and to State the slope of a parallel line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 22:21:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone is complaining about the calc section. Im a freshie and took the 8/9 . Finished the no calc in 3 minutes and the calc in 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 02:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks I didn't know that the SAT stuck with real numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 21:58:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the explanation it says that the answer is 1, since it only can equal to 4. I know that it can't be -4 because of the denominator, but why can't x be 0? -0 = 0 and the sqrt of 0 = 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Am I being stupid or is the answer wrong? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 21:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 21:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In our school system, if you are smart you take it in 8th and even some in 7th grade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 21:40:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'd actually say that PreCalc is like algebra 3 and then calc is algebra 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 05:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And now that I think about it, a great start would be watching YouTuber Tom Scott's series on how to make an app. I haven't watched it myself, but it should give you a great starting point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 04:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. Either way, I am excited to see how this ends up. I wish I could help you, but unfortunately school greatly limits my time. However, I will try to look in to how to develop an app similar to Duolingo. If I do find something, I will be sure to inform you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 04:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know how you could do this, but I would pay a lot to have access to that app/website. Your work is honestly amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 07:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if you don't understand anything, you will still hear some sounds and words of the language. Immersion does not take too much effort and greatly improves your knowledge of the language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any book suggestions for a beginner? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 07:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hallo! Ich studiere Deutsch fr ein Jahr und ich mchte gern lesen einen Buch. Do you know of any books (preferably with the original being written in German) that are somewhat challenging but that are not impossible for a beginner to understand. I have just finished level 2 German on Rosetta Stone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thanks for the great encouragement! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 02:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 15:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it depends on like the language being verified or not. I don't really know, but I do know that the languages that I am learning do not have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 15:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The good thing about desktop is that unlike mobile where only certain languages have a lightbulb explaining features of the language that make learning it so much easier, all languages have that feature on desktop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 03:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my opinion, both of those are easy. Maybe the first time you try to say it in a while can be tricky on , but then it's super easy.  isn't even hard at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>