<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9849</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 22:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> came from a single parent household and i can definitely confirm this. i occasionally slept next to my mom until i was abt 8ish, and after i was assaulted at 15 (i still at 18 will find her after a night terror or flashback but thats because of PTSD and probably bc of my autism a bit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 23:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hi! im autistic and i always ask abt vaccines because im a college student so its important to be up to date (also a public health student so i know the importance) 

and i made the mistake of saying one time got any shots for me doc? i want to make sure i stay autistic! 

(p.s. i intern with a vaccine research institute and also tell people they have it backwards and autism causes vaccines!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 17:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes to the selfie thing!! especially to start out!! you have plausible deniability when you take a moment to think about your compliment!! 

as you gain skill in what she likes and doesnt like to hear, it will be easier in person! practice makes perfect and this practice harms no one lol! its win-win! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 01:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found hermitcraft through scar! i love peppy content and the joy in his voice is great! and then i just went down the hermit rabbit hole! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 16:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey! im autistic and i think the best way to put it is Extremely Blunt. Like just a I need quiet to work and sometimes i may chat with other people i would love to have a 15 minute conversation with you at the end of class! when we do that you can have my divided attention!

EDIT: one thing that may help but do ONLY if you are willing is to help her understand the assignment Once. like just breaking it down into smaller manageable chunks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 17:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA 16 is more than old enough for natural consequence. 

Stay up late? youre exhausted the next day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 23:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im going to look into it! :D ive been evaluated by SSDI so i have those types of forms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 20:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Library seems like a great job environment because its almost always low sensory demand and i can reliably pass and non-autistic in those types of places. It also seems like a very if x - do y type of job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 17:56:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its a texture thing for me lol! i recently found the light with cinnamon toast crunch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 16:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive been in college for 3 years (i graduated at 15! it was a lot of work but super worth it!) and everyone has been super accommodating! i have separate testing and i can type my notes and record lectures! (i use a program called sonocent that lets me import slides and put the audio over them.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 03:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its a very low sensory demand environment with a routine/algorithmic task so i think im going to do great! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 03:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yep! my job was, when the Chalupas were low someone would tell me and i would make the shells. anyone would have to do that job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 03:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was working on fryer (fryologist was my official title lol) so my workflow was 

do a maintenance task (dropping and prepping cinnamon twists)

when someone asked drop a special item, this has a 60-80 second wiggle room of stop what im doing and drop the item, 

rinse repeat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like youre very right. ive applied for an internship lab tech position at the vaccine research place near me. (Vaccines are my special interest!  and we all know about autism and vaccines! /j) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:53:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oops! i meant to put a not in front of it! ive known the head librarian since i was little so im going to talk to her and i think that will be a much better job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OOPS!!  i meant reasonable! i goofed big time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 20:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep! I even have the form from SSDI that says this person can work to full potential given these things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 19:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i dont know about you but my migraines fuck me every day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 16:07:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> blocked and reported </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 16:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just this april i no longer have to lie to turn off nsfw filters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 16:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> stardew valley and banished so uh just that one really dark sdv mod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 15:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have a scar on my wrist from trying to steal toothpick umbrellas. got excited and just jammed my whole arm into the bucket and got a deep cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 15:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ^^ i get silent migraines and this sounds exactly like what i feel! hard to talk and move. words sound like nonsense. 

my doc has me call if they last more than 10 mins bc im also predisposed to stroke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 02:54:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA this is creepy as hell and these stories are why i didnt even celebrate my 18th birthday let alone tell anyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 02:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got banned from a troop for a hell of a lot less. Didnt (in my case) change the behavior. 

(little 9 year old me thought it would be a good idea to scale the bathroom stall to hide in the ceiling to read bc i didnt want to go to recess bc i would get bullied) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 20:57:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> youve found my secret! :0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 02:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey! im late but i use they/them pronouns and a good tip is:

listen when youre corrected by them. they know their own pronouns best and the best way to be an ally is to listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 20:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey dude. i dont know if the science behind why male rape is real will help but here it is. 

there is a thing called a groinal response thats basically your body responding without your brain. its the exact same thing that happens in women. 

people who say that men cant be raped or dont matter are dead wrong. your trauma is real and valid. 

Please please seek out 1 on 1 psychiatric care PTSD is no joke and can manifest is all kinds of ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 17:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA big time. as a former 14 year old girl, my mom told a dude off once and it set it in my mind that dudes are supposed to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 05:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey! most kids are insanely lucky to grow up with 1 father who loves and cherishes them and your son landed two!! 
its a sign of a strong and emotionally mature man to be able to put a divorce aside because of his kid. 
your son is going to be a great man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 18:12:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh same hat! i was put on abilify when i was 10 and it permanently fucked my nervous system! i dont think medicine should Ever be used as a first line against bipolar bc ppl are either misdiagnosed or would respond to DBT/CBT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 16:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hi! another autistic person here! a good term is high medium or low support!! because the function labels are seen as a permanent thing 

where as i can say to someone who knows that

 oh! its a medium support day 

or

lets go to the movies! i dont need that much support today!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 02:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe not to you but id say from an outside perspective its pretty damn important!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 02:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think its a skill but also an easily practiced one! 

me and my S/O do a lot of non-sexual consent (can i complain a minute can i eat some of that would it be alright if i stood up while we talk?) 

it transfers wonderfully because its already in our day to day! 

so uh, thats a pro tip for ya! 

also note: it doesnt just extend to romantic/sexual! practice casual consent with: 

kids! (could i look at your drawings?) 

friends! (oo! could i have a taste of that!) 

coworkers! (im swamped would i be alright if i gave this report to you?) ((this one is great to follow with a treat like coffee or snack even a stress ball)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 16:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it means in this thread  have a wonderful day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 20:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hello! as other commenters have said going to another studio for a longer bar is the best choice. one thing to watch out for is if it becomes warm/hot. in that case you should make an appointment with a doctor or go to urgent if its really bad. hot means infection but swelling and red is your body adjusting and saying hm this less than ideal please help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 20:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh hell yea! :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 20:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it really isnt that deep! life is too short to forego doing things that make you happy in an effort to look more mature especially when its harmless :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 05:08:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me and my S/O are ending up most likely taking mine bc in his words its cool as shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 05:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> posts like this are why i love this sub! seeing people like me who are much older than me being confident in themselves reminds me that i dont stop existing after 20!

also i love your shorts!!! its  jorts season!!

thank you for posting!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 04:56:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yea! theres a difference between productive negativity (that dude said some real fucked up shit and made an ass of himself when i said hey dont ) and just catty mean bullshit (shes such a skank and dresses horribly) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 05:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey op, you are going through intense stress right now and crying in front of someone is a lot healthier than to break things and scream. 

You can not control your emotions but you can control how you display them. You went for a healthy cry in front of someone i trust You did nothing wrong.

 I think, like others have said, that if you feel like you want to address it its best to do it in a thank you than a im sorry 

My second thought is that, the best thing for my relationship was seeing my boyfriend openly and honestly express his emotions not just in front of me but other people. 

If for whatever reason she did find out, i dont believe she would see it as a negative. 

You can name and express your emotions in a way that doesnt hurt anyone which is a lot more than other people our age not just guys. Its a positive trait 



Source: im an 18yo girl whos been through a lot of emotional control therapy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 05:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 06:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> unpopular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 06:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! im going to give that a try! ive heard meal prep is good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 06:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if my jaw feels like staying in place(60% of the time) : Chicken breast, rice, mozzarella cheese 

when my jaw is painful and i cant chew(40% of the time: QUEST protein shakes, ramen, applesauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 06:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> popular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 06:25:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats a really good suggestion! i go to college full time so when im back in august i could use the one on campus! Thank you for the idea!! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 14:48:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA this is Not something that gets you in the news and is Not a once in a lifetime opportunity. I went to college at 15 and its fucked me up ever since. I get paranoid and freaked out at school and struggle to make friends. I never got to go to prom or walk at graduation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 20:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came into the thread ready for shes got 15 cats and crocheted her own furniture but this sounds like a bomb ass place to live! Shes 25 and living her best life! the gap between 25 and 30 is a Lot bigger in this aspect than one might think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 05:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it doesnt seem i can get it to work im sorry :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 05:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/user/subject9849/m/wholesome/?utm_source=share utm_medium=ios_app </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 05:26:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh oops lemme check it out and see if i can fix it for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 05:25:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey op! here is a multi-reddit of a ton of wholesome subs! i have bipolar and when im down these help me to stay in the green [link here](https://www.reddit.com/user/subject9849/m/wholesome/?utm_source=share utm_medium=ios_app) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 06:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yep! and those arent a deal breaker for you! so with the same logic, she wont think youre nasty at all youre just her S/O and she loves you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 05:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats perfectly normal! i have horrible cold sores that get nasty so i completely understand feeling gross from a common thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 05:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey! its going to be ok! its very scary right now but just stay in contact with your doctor! From a relationship stand point and a public health stand point my advice is to tell her! 

as for your health, your highest chance of staying healthy is from talking to your doctor A Lot! go in more often than anyone else you know. talk to your doc if anything feels off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 05:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Responding to my own comment but perhaps try to send a thinking of you text! or if she has a favorite food you can make/get easy bring it to her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 05:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EDIT: OOPS I DIDNT SEE WHERE YOU MENTIONED LOVE LANGUAGES 

hey OP! a great way to help smooth communication in any relationship romantic or not is to think about something called love languages!

There are so many ways to tell someone you care about them! The main ones (with examples) are 

Touch 
(holding hands, arm around shoulders)

Gifts 
(My BFF knows I love heart shaped rocks so when she sees one she gives it to me) 

Words 
(Poems or thinking of you texts) 

Quality Time 
(going for a walk, deep conversations, board games) 

Acts Of Service
(my mom saw my tires needed air so she did it for me)

if she isnt responding when you do one (like touch) maybe try another one (send her a kind text) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 05:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that makes a lot more sense! i think the effectiveness went up when i made behavior changes as well so that helped a lot! an anti-depression medication works better when you listen to Taylor Swift and not My Chemical Romance lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 05:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for taking the time to explain to me! i love to learn new stuff!! sorry i was trying to be a smartass in my first comment. have a nice night/day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 05:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i do think its a huge placebo as well bc even one day missed i get super tight in all my mussels and shake bad, even if i dont know i missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 04:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> copy of another comment i made but 

ive taken the same dose of my meds for 5ish years now and theyve only increased in effectiveness so i can confirm there are at least 3 that stay the same.  ((for reference its lamictal, zoloft and seroquel))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 04:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive taken the same dose of my meds for 5ish years now and theyve only increased in effectiveness so i can confirm there are at least 3 that stay the same.  ((for reference its lamictal, zoloft and seroquel))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 17:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [couldnt find one without any kind of name so heres a Best Friend one! ](https://youtu.be/-78vi_yDG3o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 04:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok so you remind me of that popular pretty girl with a heart of gold trope! also, if i was in a coffee shop i didnt feel safe in, you would be the stranger i sat down next to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-02 15:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> does he have an underbite? bc ive got one and i make that face A Lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 02:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i posted an update :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 02:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :D posted an update </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 02:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :D read the update its good news! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 02:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i posted an update :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 02:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i posted an update :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 02:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i posted an update :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 01:46:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i guess i kinda didnt think much bc shes a gold star so like i just kinda thought she wouldnt but also i have no reason to mistrust either of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 05:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is mild tangent but it goes for most disability tbh. I use a cane and people get all weird if i try to do anything for them. my friends who are in wheelchairs constantly have people who either talk only to standing ppl around them or hunch down to talk.

treat disabled people like you would anyone else unless asked! if you would make a fuss about another 18 y/o girl holding the door for you then and only then are you allowed to do it to me. 

however this obviously changes big time when you become close (like friendship). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 02:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well you make a comfy bed so for you to lie in it is a reward ! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 01:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good human  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 01:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well if thats dysphoria talking i have wonderful news! as per my post, you Are a girl 

if you mean like fake as it fake eyelashes and preppy clothes Not to love women on main but hnnnng youre pretty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 00:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> all jokes aside [listen to lizzo](https://open.spotify.com/artist/56oDRnqbIiwx4mymNEv7dS?si=-AMILrUVSkeCJwgEiZ5sPA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-19 07:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it was disorienting to see the reason it was redacted. like the personal privacy put my mind at ease and investigative tactics made me curious but ongoing investigation always made me OOF a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-19 00:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wish this was shopped. its from the Mueller report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 13:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> INFO do you do it around her? if so, youre the asshole, if not she is. i ask people im very close with (my 3 best friends and my bf) not to drink around me, in my case bc of PTSD, but im fine if they talk about it. people, especially ppl with mood disorders, can be finicky about drugs bc when youve got one its Super Tempting and easy to slip into using. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 17:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh nice. im already accepted to a seminary if i wanted to go lol. im not gonna bc i like to bang and i assume ill like drinking and weed (once im 21 im a good egg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 16:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> god i hate this bc thats my actual plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 22:12:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> disclaimer: that was written by paul not jesus but if anyone gives you shit for that remember that A) its accepted canon and B) Paul was writing filled with the holy spirit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 17:12:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry if this is weird but got confused about what sub i was on for a second thinking you were a character from a show bc you look Exactly like her! [a kady for reference ](https://hollywoodlife.com/pics/the-magicians-jade-tailor-photos/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 02:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey man you should write for r/scpdeclassified  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 07:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If youre hearing! Id recommend The Penumbra Podcast! I cant speak to Second Citadel but the Juno Steel stories are absolutely incredible in the way of nb rep! two canonical nb characters! (its also in a noir style!) 
-

One is Juno Steel (our leading lady) 

who uses he/him pronouns 

both him and ppl around him call him many versions of lady ex: you know how to treat a lady right 

wears dresses 

is seduced by a gnc gay man who takes on a masculine role in the relationship 



The other is the Mayor themself! 

uses a Mx honorific! 

badass as fuck 

has a renowned brand of murder high heels 

anecdotal but, Pilot empowered me to be open and badass abt my gender 

-

best part!? neither character is boiled down to their identity!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 00:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in every teen writing group ive been in sometimes its just Like That. its status quo really in my experience 

source: 6 years of teen writing group  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 15:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you look like God herself coming down to declare trans rights motherfucker and smite terfs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 04:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RemindMe! 1 week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 20:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> holy shit buddy youre an asshole. this is not only someone whos not in a healthy place but theyre a CHILD and you think its ok to be a piss baby because you no empathy? i dont know how to explain to you that you should care about other people!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 03:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you look like abby from NCIS!!!! i love the punk/goth aesthetic and you pull it off so well! Youre an amazing woman and it shows!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 00:08:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i mean this with like the most respect but you know in movies when theres that one pretty/popular/cheerleader girl whos always super sweet and has a heart of gold? you look like that girl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 02:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA youre experiencing grief and it comes in so many forms. 

your feelings are your own and you are entitled to feel whatever you need. 

feelings dont need morals, actions do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 02:15:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH ! keep the attitude but something that would help on the genuine-ness front is to be specific! its the good job vs great layup technique (i know nothing about basketball) its the difference of a good job on an essay and an underlined sentence with a amazing point ya feel?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 20:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA if the gender was reversed it would be Crystal Clear with no question. However, its still a Very Asshole thing to do to tell someone (esp a service worker) to smile. service workers cant tell your friend to hey dont but you can (and you did which is Very Good)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 17:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ooo! I've always loved the format on that one! The build up is incredible!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 04:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ooo! i love your handwriting!! this is so cool! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 04:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> these are human real live people ? why would you ship human people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 19:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i saw in a different comment that you are dealing with depression and a dog related tip from my therapist is that petting a dog and spend a few mins cuddling sends calming hormones through your body! its not a miracle cure but it is an excuse to pet your puppy!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 19:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats amazing! little gestures can mean the most!! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 19:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! i hope your day is going great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 15:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you look like that stereotypical pretty but emo girl in every high school set movie. (i mean this to be validating but lemme know if its not)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 04:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hi! im sure if i qualify for this survey!? I took it and i can give you the code if need be. I meet all the stated requirements but i suffer from psychotic bipolar. i dont know if this would disqualify my information  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-02 02:46:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> only answered 4 on owner influence bc my beabul (beagle bull dog) sleeps all day no matter what we do lol!!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-02 02:38:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> English Prof has open note tests and reads exam questions out loud the class before  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-02 02:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ^^^ im on nexplanon use condoms and rhythm method ((dont use rhythm alone)) and i Still have contingency plans if i get pregnant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 16:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shes a snack! im gonna munch! im gonna Crunch!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 16:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im just 18 and i was sex trafficked by a family member at this age and nobody helped me. Reading this reminds me that people care. I wish i had had a grandparent like you. I wish you and her the best. Thank you for caring about her it means more than you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-15 03:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im young dumb and broke so this might not apply as well 

but me and my bf love groupon. you can get anything on there but the activities are the best part. we went on a $500 paintball weekend thing for $30. its also really nice because you see things you wouldnt normally try and its so cheap you think might as well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-15 03:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey could you maybe add an other for who you live with? 

for non-conventional families? 

(((for instance my parent set that i live with is weird as fuck but theyre like all my parents (its my mom my grandma and a woman from our church) ))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-06 22:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> once you know one 3 keyed brass its so easy to learn all (plus trombone)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-04 00:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THE LACK OF HOG CRANKIN IS THE WORST PART AROO  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 06:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey! I know youve gotten the eyes are important already so maybe an alternative is contact lenses? I know a few brands that do red eyes and a lot more and are super comfy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 06:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think youre right, my judgement is clouded by my experience. Thank you for not being an asshole (even though I kinda was) I hope you have a good January  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 06:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont let falling out of the honeymoon phase mean allowing emotional emptyness. Your partner should always be making an effort  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 06:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You shouldnt be sexually active at age 14 no r j laws cover you until you are 15 if youre looking at a legal stand point. And also youre fucking CHILD at 14. I know my situation was extreme but being comfortable with sex at 14 led to me being kidnapped and sex trafficked. You should not and truly can not consent to sex at 14. I know the internet loves to think childhood is a sin but at 14 you have no prefrontal cortex. It is incredibly difficult to make educated and logical choices. You follow base desires. Theres a reason you have parents and its to stop shit like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 06:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dumb advice but watch or read about it first since she already has seen it and then you wont get distracted by it. Also as a girl, if she wants to watch a movie with you that shes already seen, BIG signal. Also just ask! Dont be afraid of ruining it. If it was a close friend thats different but if shit get awkward you can just either laugh it off or youve really lost nothing. BUT as I said shes sending big big signals  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 06:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get her parents involved. I did shit like this when I was 14 and it led to my boundaries becoming so broken I did shit Ill be in therapy forever for. Tell her parents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 06:00:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In todays world where saying the right things with the right words is everything it is easy for shitty person to been seen as good just because they know the lingo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-21 04:02:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh! same hat! When I went in for a cleaning they brought like 5 students in bc of my fucked lower jaw and then they started talking about TMJ and I got confused.  Turns out my mouth is really fucked. 

((Inb4 I go to a teaching dentist and they give me my care for free and sometimes pay me. Thats why the students. I have a class III occlusion my bottom jaw is out too far from my upper. Normally its very slight but mines is 1.02 inches of gap.))  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 20:23:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/subsithoughtifellfor
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 20:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome! I love your flair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 20:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got recruited for Sseko at 15 they have girls as young as 10 working for them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-20 20:10:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HELL YEA MFER IM THE OTHER WAY I GOT NO HOG BUT I WANT ONE. KEEP ON CRANKING MFER AROOOOOOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 20:11:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense to me. Im an AFAB agender and sometimes I wish I was AMAB bc I feel like it would be so much simpler ya know. I dunno its dumb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 21:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not even joking about this. Just raise kids the exact same way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 16:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yea thats a BIG mood  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 16:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to tell my doc but I dont want to go to suicide jail  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 04:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fixed it again!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 20:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I needed to see this sub! I lov it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 20:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its been changed!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 15:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey OP! Im the same age as you and had something similar happen. I fell asleep in the car on the way to a wedding, normally this would be ok but I talk in my sleep and said some buckwild shit. I was mortified but it turned out perfectly fine afterwards. It would show a good personality if you just apologized and laughed it off! I can promise you that they dont hate you!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 03:02:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw yea!! Rep!! Im in the same boat! Have a nice day!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-22 23:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im getting Nexplanon implant. Exact same hormone as depo, just different method  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-09 01:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre so pretty! I love your top!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-04 13:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-04 13:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> New York! I would say something positive but I live upstate and even that is shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-28 18:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im having mental health relapses and feel as though I cant tell anyone because when I have, people have been telling me that I dont feel like that and Im fine. Im very close to killing myself and nobody knows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 07:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im also a 54 enby!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-18 03:20:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> can comfirm


im on seroquel and ive got shit ass auditory processing from it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-30 06:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> iirc the white stripe is meant to represent non-binary trans individuals!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-27 02:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i cant feel the effects of opiate pain killers. it pairs nicely with my hyper-rare pain condition!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-15 04:39:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i use OpenMPT i recently got a 1.5 octave midi controller so thats exciting!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-15 04:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im on vacation so this is from like a year ago but im still fond of it 
[for the earth ](https://m.soundcloud.com/spacejace/for-the-earth)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-15 03:16:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i make em as well! nice to see it out and about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-12 04:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont know if you need anyone else but im here!! id love to!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-15 01:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello! I added you! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> sup </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 17:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> hehe! for an agender thot i sure have a lot of gender </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-10 19:59:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AITA for demanding unreasonable accommodation at work? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 20:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 18F and just got fired from my first job (taco bell) because i requested unreasonable accommodations. 

To preface I have autism. 
I asked for the following things

-Say my name before talking to me so i know that im being spoken to. something like (name) please drop 6 chalupas

-Give me specific instructions please clean this area vs it would be nice if this area was cleaner

- Understand that sometimes im not aware of my own body language. if im standing with my shoulders to my ears its not that im upset but that it just feels good. 

my boss as she was telling me i had to quit that it was because she felt that these would cause the workflow to be interrupted and were unreasonable. 

so AITA?

UPDATE:

ive decided im going to keep my head down but remember that these are not ridiculous requests for my next job. Ive been considering applying for a page job at my local library. i grew up doing programs there so the staff knows me well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> my beagle   old english mix Cookie enjoying her favorite pass time! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 18:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> old english   beagle mix for tongue out tuesday! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 17:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> nb transition goals </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 17:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Family/Friends] My mom made a small gesture and it meant so much to me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 18:03:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok so i was crying and super upset last week that ive never gotten to go to pride (talking to a friend in front of my mom) 

now, my mom is on the fence about the whole lgbt thing. she doesnt quite understand. 

so today she comes in and tells me that we are going to the ball game on tuesday next week. im like ok! cool!  

she tells me too look up the event (every night theres some promotion like 10 cent hot dogs or free ball cap) 

and its pride night. 

i tell her and she says i know. you seemed so sad and im your mom so i have to make you feel better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> lizzo said trans rights! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 00:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 'cmon guys we've been over this! This much black box is shitty writing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-19 00:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WIBTA if i offered to wash and style a friends natural (black) hair when im white? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 07:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend ive known from childhood for maybe 13-14 years now. Shes from a family that isnt neglectful but still doesnt pay much attention to her. 

Her dad is black but her mother is white and her mother never tried to help her with her hair. She normally wears it back because people like to try to touch it without asking. 

Shes the type of person who loves to be touched and cared for by friends but her hair is off limits to touch to most people but she doesnt mind when i play with it absently (the playing w/ hair is a teen girl thing i know) but her hair is kind of, well, unhealthy because she doesnt know how to care for it. 


Like most people I get into a youtube rabbit hole and when I was doing that a month ago I saw some women with hair like hers doing styles and curls by washing and wrapping it. 

The styles dont last more than a week so i was thinking of offering to style her hair because shes been struggling with mental health and i know that when i struggle new hair gets me out of a funk. 

 In the moments im not amazed watching the videos im aware of this its not for me feeling. The women in the videos tend to jokingly poke fun at white people hair tutorials and styles. I thought about the fact that that im a white person and i dont want to be presumptuous and come across like a racist asshole because i assumed that i knew what was best for her. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What SCPs would you consider capital "A" Art? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 17:38:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While all SCPs are art in that they are an expression of creativity there are some that go the extra mile and hit you hard and leave you thinking. What are some that hit those marks for you?

 #x200B;

Examples of art

* Twilight 
* Zentangle drawings 
* Harry Potter

Examples of "A" Art

* Dante's Inferno 
* "Saturn Devouring His Son" by Francisco Goya
* Fahrenheit 451 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> this image set was to cute not to make wholesome </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-15 03:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reverse porn effect? (Porn doesnt do it for me anymore?) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 05:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 18 and have had the same boyfriend for 3 years. For most of my time Ive been using porn and erotica to get off. Recently I just stopped being turned on by it. I still can have sex and cum with my bf but nothing else does it for me. Ive heard of the opposite happening? But not like this. I got nexplanon in October but it increased my sex drive if anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oof! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 20:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I got bullied into an MLM at 16. Im almost 18 now and still stuck. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 19:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shortly after my 16 birthday I went to a fashion show at a local college. The first important thing that makes me feel nasty is that it was a first major manic episode in my bipolar history. There was an MLM called Sseko there. They gave me the usual MLM garbage but being 16 and extremely manic I joined the start up fee was $300 and I was told that if I borrowed it from my mother she wouldnt miss it. 

I was in nowhere near a stable state. I was hospitalized 3 days after the purchase, and this is the second wild part, my big sis came to see me in the hospital. Being under 18 she lied and said she was my aunt. I had never seen this woman before in my life. I was extremely psychotic and detached from reality. She told me I could sell to the other teens in the ward with me. 

I was in the hospital for the next 8 months. I am finally out and stable. Im extremely stuck in this company and feel like shit. They call me on a regular basis and harass me through social media. moral of the story, FUCK MLMs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Happy Monday Morning! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 16:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Only Birth Control That Stops My Period Will Cause Noticeable Breast Growth </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-22 18:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To all transbians struggling with height dysphoria, remember that you can always give a girl this religious experience. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 05:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm making a radio drama style podcast and have a transwoman as a main character so i need a trans voice actor (More information inside) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-14 21:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm making a radio drama style podcast and have a transwoman as a main character so i need a trans voice actor (More information inside) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-14 21:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been working for almost a year now with the script for an fictional audio podcast. I have a transwoman as one of my lead character and would feel it's disrespectful to have her voiced by a ciswoman. I am trans myself (agender) and understand how important representation is. I have been informed that for the most part that, without voice training, voice pitch doesn't change so it doesnt matter if you are out or not, pretransition or fully. sorry if this is a ramble. 

TLDR: i need a transwoman voice actor PM if interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Offer] Niagara Falls! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-15 03:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i live close to the falls and have a season pass into the park that waves all of the fees and i would love to take those who would want to cross it off!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Best line/short monologues to quote ominously? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 22:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I often find myself lost for what to say in conversations, in an effort to become more conversational, Ive begun to acquire and memorize various phrases. 

Some of my favorites from non-Shakespeare for an idea of what Im looking for

As the prophecy foretold

If your left eye causes you to sin, gouge it out 

(( related to previous)) it is better for one part to die than the whole be damned to hell

Thank you for helping me! No curse of your name shall fall from my lips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What questions answer best humanizes another person? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 16:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> do i use bitmoji for my transition goals? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-01 18:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i heard transition goals were happening? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-01 18:39:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When someone misgenders my MTF friends </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-22 15:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-02 19:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is 10 times better than the original. thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> im a cripple with crippling dysphoria </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-02 18:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-28 23:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Coming from the perspective of a sexual abuse survivor, it could be entirely possible she has traumatic experiences that she may be denying or repressing. 

However, if her actions hurt you she is responsible. No matter if she is mentally ill or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 02:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i dont need a valentine when legion can fuck my brain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 02:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> legion is not back

2018 here i come  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-07 22:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i did this today and i have yet to recover the second key and i feel like ive done 10000 legal eagles at this point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-06 15:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's okay, i've had the flu since the update came out so i couldn't play bc of being so nauseous  i'm at 17 as well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> when your doctor sees you going into an episode </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-27 17:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-18 21:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it was around midnight on the way home from a concert and i looked at my best friend 

"there are two types of people in the world

those on this bus and those not on this bus"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-18 18:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i met my best friend's other friends and they were super nice and he was so happy for me to come further into his life!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-18 02:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jon makes a lot of mistakes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 21:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [me and a childhood best friend ](https://imgur.com/a/cMjfy) 

[me and a more recent friend ](https://imgur.com/a/nofzY)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 17:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my perception of reality is incredibly warped and i rely on other people way too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 17:42:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no, it's not. it's the definition of facetious disorder.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-15 17:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my best friend has a heart of gold. he is always looking to do something to make someone happy. he loves harmless pranks and loves to be an idiot with me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is your favorite thing about your best friend(s)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-15 17:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-15 16:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my mom did a really good job of teaching me about sex i feel. when i was young and would ask questions she would answer with what she felt was age appropriate. she was telling me about a conversation she and i had when i was 4. 

"how are babies made?"

"you know how chickens have eggs? girls have eggs in their bodies" 

"okay!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-15 16:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ugh i hate flat-time believers! it's a sphere get over it!! NASA has pictures and everything! just get off your high horse and wallow in self pity like the rest of us!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-14 17:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> call me half and half bc i'm 50% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 03:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's great to know me and my 2nd percentile working memory will always have a job somewhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 03:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got my gun 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 02:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this town is only big enough for one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 21:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm also irrationally over dramatic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 21:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i know, pal. i choked on a mini wheat when i was 10 and i am a grudge holder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 19:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CEREAL IS THE GROSSEST THING KNOW TO MAN. ITS RAW AND SOGGY 

edit, i have more to say: JACKING OFF ISNT THE REASON PEOPLE GO BLIND CEREAL IS. IT IS AN ABOMINATION AND NEEDS TO BE WIPED OFF THE FACE OF THE EARTH  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 17:14:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> put that thing back where it came from or so help me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 19:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is very comforting to hear. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 19:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brown vs The Board Of Education  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 19:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [ Romans 8:14 NIV] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 19:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. All of these comments have been very reassuring  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 17:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-01 04:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the only good option  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 18:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't seen this app but I just downloaded it and it seems great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 18:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got that too for the first few weeks

I would definitely talk to a doc if it persists because it could possibly be a more serious side effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 01:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Bi people always pick a side" 

Wow! It's amazing that they fall in love and marry someone!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 23:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a 1 which is predominantly straight only sometimes a lesbian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Someone mentioned the Kinsey Scale, so I'm curious how y'all fall! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 23:24:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 18:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live 20 mins south and yeah, exactly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can I get uhhhhhhhhhh </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-21 05:01:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-20 01:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I looked at the date for the launch of JUICE (the real one) and it's in 2022. Juice is a four year old! ((That is assuming robot development is akin to the human kind))  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 21:04:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope! I'm dead serious. I laughed a bit when my doctor told me that's what I experience bc it is a really amusing term but its legit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 20:46:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Word Soup

that's surprisingly accurate, the actual medical term is Word Salad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-07 21:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most likely it is tightening of the pelvic wall. Kegels help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-07 21:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [sbahjhehehe](/sbahjhehehe) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-07 21:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really didn't expect to be the only knight of heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm a local news star now </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-06 00:05:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-04 20:30:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bees! Every third bite you eat is thanks to a bee!!
[Relevant Image! ](http://imgur.com/a/nzEO5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-04 20:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NY has one where, once you are past compulsory schooling age (16), you can drop out and earn your diploma through a community college without it being marked as a GED. You also earn college credit for all your classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Serious] What's the best educational loop hole that you know of? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-04 20:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-04 18:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ability to follow objects with my eyes. My eyes shake and stutter whenever I try to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the fancy style! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's a second day look actually. it was like this 
http://imgur.com/a/MhYkH
but I brushed it out and it did that.
How i got it up like that in the first place is a hair dryer, gel and hair spray with my hair pointed down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:35:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's esp going to save me money because im going through a program for people between 14-17 so its only $55 a credit hour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice! I'm digging the sun glasses! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats pretty neat. I'm starting at a community college in the fall for an associates in Stat with endgame of masters in public health   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:26:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice. what are you going to study? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I congratulate you on your seemingly wonderful relationship. also on your ability to type with hands like those  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks. my hair is something i enjoy messing with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/UErsZ

Here i am!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Glow-up thread to distract from test result wait? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 20:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm waiting on a tumor biopsy test so let's see how ya'll have changed! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 01:39:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my class in 6th grade was reading a book about a piano player, i spoke with a slight slur and played it up when i got to the word "pianist" i told the story like it was the greatest thing for so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 01:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had been trying to convince myself that I only liked guys and then on a whim thinking she would say no, asked this really pretty girl who i was kind of friends with to sleep over on Halloween. It was gr8.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 01:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> never have i ever drank alcohol willingly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 01:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it really isnt that great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 01:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it was when i found out exactly how bi i am  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 00:52:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have bipolar disorder and was in a manic state. The guy hit on me and my girlfriend didn't even cross my mind till I saw her and thought she would be proud of me. She wasn't. She saw the emotional state I was in and understood, but, for some reason I broke up with her. I don't blame my disorder for my actions but I'm glad I got hospitalized shortly after.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>