<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject612</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>  so true imarite ??? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-08 19:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 14:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well i can tell you this story :) 
When I started the quivalent of highschool in my country, I'd decided that I didn't want to fall in love AT ALL. I had had too much heartbreak (for example: you're not thin enough to be my gf sorry). So well I started talling with this guy that was in my class and he was my bestfriend. Really I felt so good with him but remember, I didn't want any relationship so I decided that I wasn't in love. 
A couple months later, I was talking with his bestfriend (C), who became mine later, and she told my that he had told her that he really liked a girl in his class with whom he was talking a lot. I thought a bit about that and I realized I was the only girl in our class with who he was talking. 
A couple weeks after, I was still thinking about that and I realized that I was in total love with him. 
So, of course, I told my now bestfriend (C) something like "Fuck I think I am in love with him", to what she answered "Fuck, he is in love with you too" 
At this moment, she decided to tell him, so that he will have the guts to ask me out. 
He dared 
We are happily together for nearly 2 years 3
(sorry for the not so perfect english, i'm not a native speaker ^^') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 17:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the second one is true thought. they really had some "reproduction camps" where arian males had babies with arian females :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 11:52:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eh mais salut robin je vois qu'on regarde les meme trucs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 23:01:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *and a car. Don't you dare forgetting the car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 22:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes hello that's just being dumb im sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 22:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello. i AM a big potterhead irl and i genuinely (is that how you spell it ? English is not my first language oupsie) think Dumbledore was a reckless and manipulative cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 23:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Living in Switzerland, we love beaches and islands and anywere hotter than switzerland. Personnally, i still cant understand why you anericans love Paris so much ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 16:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EAT MY SHORTS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 15:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makes me think about a panic! At the disco song  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 15:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's an upvote for thinking about his/her dad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 10:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not the point... it's just that i know they were supposed to explain it to us but they never did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 19:35:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well at my school we had like 1h30 once a year about sex ed... I still never learned how to put a condom  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 13:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Soo that means it's not uninteresting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 13:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Salted with +butter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 13:34:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im eating popcorns  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 13:34:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So cute  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 13:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Talk with him/her... he/she might be not gappy because he/she likes her/his friends but if you dont like them, dont share time with them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 20:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Twenty one pilots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 01:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are total genuises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 01:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay so once i was in the traim and these two teenagers were im front of me (a guy and a girl). I think they hadn't seen eachother for a while. So the guy was like hey how are you doing blablabla and then he asks the girl "hey are you still witg your boyfriend btw ?"
Answer from the girl: "Oh no he cheated on me so i cheated on him with two guys... at the same time"

It makes everybody laugh so hard when i tell them about this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 10:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a mercy main, i felt fear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Redditors who work in a luxurious hotel, what was the craziest thing a client asked you to do ? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 00:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Academic] Internet addiction (people who are between 15 and 20 years old) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 20:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi ! I live in Switzerlnd and I'm in the equivalent of highschool.  We have something like an essay of 20pages about a problematic that we chose: i chose internet addiction in people that are between 15 and 2 years old.  I made a survey and I really need more people to answer to it. Thank you very much for answering to it if you are between 15 and 20 years old.  [https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1ORqz6pEA6rzPIXoyFR5s55EhR36y5GousUzdHYuaxPQ/edit](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1ORqz6pEA6rzPIXoyFR5s55EhR36y5GousUzdHYuaxPQ/edit) 

By the way, if you are a big internet addict or were and you are ok to be interviewed, just tell me. It would be great 

Thank you so much everone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I need visibility </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 14:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi everybody,

I need to fill this poll for school. If people that are aged between 15 and 20 years old could just answer these question i would be very grateful.  [https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1ORqz6pEA6rzPIXoyFR5s55EhR36y5GousUzdHYuaxPQ/edit](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1ORqz6pEA6rzPIXoyFR5s55EhR36y5GousUzdHYuaxPQ/edit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Academic paper or something like that </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 14:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 18:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To understand his french, you have to understand english  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>