<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject418</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 19:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 15:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not in this case; the poet's name is  (Su Shi), with  being the surname and  being his given name. Also, just an FYI to the commenter above, his name doesn't really sound like 'sushi'; the 'i' sound is a lot softer, so it sounds like 'sue shih' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 17:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its courtesy because youre not spreading your germs to everyone. of course theres dubious proof of whether it actually works, but everyone does it when theyre sick. well, not now though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 19:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The Shoebox Project](https://shoebox.lomara.org/shoebox-pdf-chapters/) : a fandom classic! Its Remus/Sirius but focuses on all four of the marauders equally. Awesome illustrations to go with the text. Very well written and funny, with moments that will make you cry as well.

linkao3(Astra Inclinant): this fic isnt very well known, but its seriously amazing. Future (non graphic) slash if that bothers you. Its a next gen fic that focuses on Harry, Draco Malfoy, and their respective sons. The quality is really consistent and the author updates every 2-3 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 19:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, okay. So sorry you lost your bookmarks, good luck with finding new fics to read :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 22:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry I dont have any recommendations, but are you talking about your bookmarks on AO3 by any chance? AO3s bookmark index is under maintenance for now, so all bookmarks arent currently visible, but theyll be back in a few days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 12:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe [When I Heard at the Close of the Day](https://www.poetryfoundation.org/poems/50509/when-i-heard-at-the-close-of-the-day) by Walt Whitman? Theres nature imagery that kind of matches your description </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 10:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> disagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> mwa </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 12:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 12:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats just weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 14:50:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the guy above noticed the word ; in simplified Chinese it does means feed, but its more often used as an exclamation in traditional Chinese. The preferred word in traditional Chinese is . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 15:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Umm....Hong Kong...? Just because we dont have costcos doesnt mean we dont have supermarkets at all lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 06:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not everyone is from the US where Im from, we dont have Walmarts or costcos. Perhaps you might find it a bit redundant or unnecessary, but I think its a pretty nice gesture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 07:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Traditional Chinese is used in Hong Kong, Macao, and Taiwan, while simplified Chinese is used in Mainland China. Traditional Chinese characters are basically ancient and retain their full meanings, so if youre looking for more symbolism, traditional Chinese would be the better choice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 07:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im Chinese and I think its hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 07:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 03:04:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, Im from Hong Kong haha. Just pointing it out because lot of people dont seem to know that China has its own version of Wikipedia, albeit heavily censored </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 15:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chinese people use Baidu Baike, which is kind of similar to Wikipedia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 19:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mostly English, although its not my mother tongue. I guess its because I mostly enjoy media in English and Im more used to the nuances of the language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 19:18:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a spaniel. He looks like a red panda with those weird dots over his eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 19:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 19:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stick googly eyes on all of their photos/paintings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 19:12:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 19:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sorry if this isnt allowed. 

How do I get this background? Ive tried looking at the love Nikki wiki galleries, but I cant find this background (or the suit it belongs to). Please help? This is the Taiwan/Hong Kong server, if thats of any relevance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where do I find this background? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 19:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 11:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, Ill be honest the jokes really arent that funny. Some of them have potential, such as the teachers hair one, but it isnt written clearly enough. Bear in mind that while juvenile humour can be funny, it needs to be in small doses. Overdoing it just makes it weird, and frankly quite cringey. 

I spot a lot of run on sentences (and just plain long sentences). Remember to vary sentence lengths and insert more punctuation. There are other major issues like spelling errors and incorrect tenses, which Im sure you can correct. 

The characters are fine enough, but theyre not really distinguishable. There are some weird descriptions why is there white liquid dripping from John Ngs arm? I understand that you wrote this for comedic purposes, but theres no real point to inserting random things like that. 

I think you certainly have a unique setting, but youll need to clean up your draft a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 11:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, I dont have much time, so I only read a bit of it. 


Your writing style is good enough. The dialogue is fine, though it could be a bit more natural. 
Ive noticed that you tend to use the same sentence structure when describing an environment. Try to vary your sentence structures more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 18:42:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $69 for one bottle? You gotta be kidding me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 16:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> heres a hug (**) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 17:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 760163
edit: sorry, apparently its 212412 now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 05:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Close! Hong Kong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 04:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worlds most expensive city and highest property prices  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 02:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 21:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an aspiring artist, I feel you! 

Practice helps a lot. Copy people in photos, objects, go out and draw your local neighbourhood. This will eventually build up your drawing skills. If youre short on time, even five minutes a day will pay off in the long run.

Know that its okay if you mess up this time. You havent wasted any time working on your current project, youve only trained yourself and subconsciously improved. As long as you know what youre realistically aiming for,  you can always try again in the future when you feel that youve become more skilled. Good luck, Im sure that itll turn out great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 10:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trying to sit on my dog as if I was riding a horse when I was 2  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 15:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zenobia, queen of the Palmyrene Empire. She was a warrior and well educated, fluent in several languages. After her husband was murdered, she became regent of her son. She seized control of territories in the east, conquered Egypt, and built a powerful empire. Later, she was captured after a Roman siege and executed. She is known as a heroic queen and a freedom fighter who inspired Catherine the Great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 06:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bored on a tour bus for a school trip to singapore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 17:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And God only knows what you are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 05:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nude Florida man burns himself while dancing in flames, chanting gibberish- June 22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 04:10:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They played this song six times in a row at my high school. Wanted to kill myself at that point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 13:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His Christmas songs are amazing. I love Barcarola too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 08:14:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We made in preparation for our school fair! Just start with a simple recipe and make a small batch, go for it! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 02:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 11:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks! Yeah, its like an oasis in the middle of the city, so nice and quiet :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 10:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like the effect! Looks magical  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 05:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Joanna Newsoms album, Divers, is the same begins with the word  sending and ends with trans-, creating the word transcending when you loop the album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 01:27:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-04 18:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its the instax mini airmail film! I just got it from a local store, so I dont really know where its available. Maybe try checking on Amazon? :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chi Lin Nunnery, Hong Kong Instax mini 90 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-04 15:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chi Lin Nunnery, Hong Kong Instax mini 90 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-04 14:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-04 06:16:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Talula Does the Hula from Hawaii
(yes this is real) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 18:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grammarly. Its useless anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 18:18:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, just cows milk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 17:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We just didnt know that milk soap would smell weird during saponification. After a few weeks of curing, it smells perfectly fine now :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 14:50:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The batch on the left is coffee, the batch on the right is milk and honey. We had a bit of a problem with the fragrance but it turned out fine in the end :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our first ever batches of cold process soap! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 11:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-16 11:31:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can anyone link to a source? Searching formaldehyde shark only returns news about the shark going viral online but nothing about the tank being broken 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-13 07:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus Christ thats horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-07 14:26:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I havent read YA in a while, but Aristotle and Dante Discover the Secrets of the Universe is one of my favourites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 20:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Words that sound like... well, sounds. For example buzz, boom, and pop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 07:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dumb as fuck, but kinda cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 07:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe not inarguably, but I love raspberry cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 05:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i love frank!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 03:33:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Late afternoon, when the streets are golden with sunlight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 03:28:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stinky tofu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 06:16:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh my gooooooood  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 03:27:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That Napoleon was short </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 02:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jello </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Legit] Scitsofrenia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 02:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 01:58:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i saw the title and was immediately reminded of sufjan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 21:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Swedish, I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-01 19:11:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-01 18:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no shame in that. Those books are great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt save the link; I dont want to see it again lol. I think I found it by typing mp4 (random date) into the search bar, because someone said pedophiles lurk around webcam videos uploaded by kids who forget to change the title of their video. I was just curious to see if it was real, and got that instead. So please, dont try that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 06:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The number of professors at Hogwarts. Surely their schedules would clash if there were only one professor for each subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 06:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found a video of a girl being raped on YouTube  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 06:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> During the middle of an exam  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 19:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 18:12:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> happy cake day! I find that nosleep has dropped in quality recently, but occasionally there are still some good stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 18:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a common Reddit sentiment. 
I dont hate facebook, its just not useful for me. All of my peers have migrated to other platforms. And personally speaking, I wouldnt like anyone selling my data, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 13:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An old man helping his (presumably) grandson pee into a plastic bottle at a restaurant, then putting the bottle into his bag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-08 14:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit is forum-based and anonymous, so its definitely different from other social media sites. Cant say if its better though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-08 14:34:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Procrastinate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-25 19:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can someone tell me why Ive been seeing so many reposts from the top talent subreddit and this particular user? Nice art btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-18 16:39:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The Light Rail line](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Light_Rail_(MTR)), serves a part of Hong Kong (New Territories) that is more spread out than the rest of the city. Source: am hongkonger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 19:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Butterflies. I just hate flying insects in general, no idea why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 17:01:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! but for some reason it says doesnt ship to Hong Kong... huh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 16:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 16:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> okay, thank you so much for the tips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 16:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! Ill just try to look around for cheap stick blenders, I guess :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 16:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Hong Kong, we dont have Walmart :( The cheapest I can find in this local chain store is 50usd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 16:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for the in-depth answer! 

Ive heard that splashing might be an issue. Do you know of any possible solutions? Im ruling out using a whisk as were probably making multiple batches. Unfortunately, there arent much thrift stores near my area, so Ill have to rule out that option too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Newbie question about stick blenders </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 15:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, Im thinking of trying out soap making for a school project. I dont have a stick blender on hand. Will a regular hand mixer work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 14:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love all dogs, but Cavalier King Charles Spaniels, because I have one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 14:10:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im from Hong Kong too! her handwriting is adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 07:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly my sentiment. I live in Hong Kong, where people dont usually tip unless theyre eating at a luxury restaurant/have actually received excellent service. All workers get a reasonable minimum wage they can live on. Im not against tipping, which is great when you want to show your appreciation, but making it compulsory is hard on both the customers and the workers. Tipping has become more of a necessity than an act of gratitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 06:21:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not too sure about the lomo instant, but [this site](https://instantcamerablog.com/comparisons/instax-mini-9-vs-70/) can probably help you with comparing the mini 9 and mini 70! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 05:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was this reddit comment that said typing a random date into YouTube would get you videos whose file names hadnt been changed. I tried it out of curiosity and found a video of a girl being raped... never again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 05:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tipping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 05:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was riding my bike at night with my friend. Saw a slope and thought it would be fun to ride down it, so we did. Fell down and dragged my chin against the concrete, hurt like hell and I looked like Id been attacked by a feral cat. We were stupid kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-28 19:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-28 17:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Replying with this to someone elses comment when you have nothing to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-28 17:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hea! Its a slang term in Cantonese that roughly translates to laziness and not putting effort into something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 20:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really, really need to sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 20:35:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read a dumb ass article and am still slightly pissed off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 09:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He likes falling asleep on my stomach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 20:05:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deleting Chrome tabs after finishing an assignment. Pure euphoria </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 19:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We read excerpts of Anne Franks diary in sixth grade English class (Hong Kong). Hong Kong was not really involved in the Holocaust so we were only taught an overview of the war and how kids coped. Sorry if this doesnt help much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 19:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need to stop looking down upon other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 18:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before I enter another room to do something else. I forget everything as soon as I reach the doorway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 17:55:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol thanks. I just took this with my phone camera. Dont know why the quality seems so high, all my other photos look shitty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 17:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its okay, I appreciate that youre being so polite :) Have a nice day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 17:39:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Japanese uses kanji, yes, but in a different way. Speakers of the language are able to differentiate. The characters on the package are , which means I like you. AFAIK, the same expression in Japanese does not use these characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 17:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im from Hong Kong. Native Chinese speaker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [I ate] Japanese bacon pancakes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 16:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 16:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> glad youre doing fine!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 15:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its so pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 15:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thats awful :(  dont feel too bad, he doesnt deserve you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 14:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hygiene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 13:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats Chinese on the box, not Japanese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 15:35:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 15:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who blast their music in public.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 15:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 21:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> noticed that too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 20:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> N </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 16:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can spot two letters on the right, . This is the name of a son of Toyotomi Hideyoshi, a famous Japanese warlord. However I cant read the letters on the left, do you think you could take a clearer photo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-18 08:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just checked, cant access it too (Im in Hong Kong)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-23 10:19:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was required reading at my elementary school. Glad you enjoyed it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need to see otayuri become a real thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-27 14:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YURIOOOOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-25 12:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe an interaction with a parallel universe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-25 08:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you noticed any other changes? This is really creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>