<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8336</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 05:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who has the burden of proof and how much proof is required are two different questions. But the fact is that you were not asserting the null hypothesis but a model for how it works. Which needs to disprove the null hypothesis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 04:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really do think i am ORIGINAL POSTER. Don't you? I AM NOT. The original poster is not me and i am not the original poster. That is why i asked you if you thought i was was the O.P. Please don't call me son,son.  I also mentioned that i was not making a point. I did not create this post. I am not claiming there is fairy magic  because i am a different person to the other person you were speaking to.

I simply stated that you had not substantiated your claims and you linked me to a website. This conversation has gone on to long.

Edit: sometimes i hate the way Reddit is designed. But then again it can be good to talk to the same person with a new perspective every time. It can be quite interesting. But it sucks if you are a regular to a sub Reddit as you can end up having the same conversation with the same person over and over again without knowing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 04:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No you have the burden of proof. If you make an assertion you bring the evidence. If you do assert something you prove it. I can assert it is not true and attempt to assert otherwise but the burden of proof is not on me its not on you. Even if the view is the standard. There is no point telling me to prove your point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 04:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would like to point out that tests done on out of body experience as far as i know showed that these people who experienced them did not in fact notice cards that were placed in the room except out of the view of patients and doctors. But the sample size was too small, with only nine people actually experiencing it. And anecdotal evidence usually isn't useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 04:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you mistaking me for OP? I am making no statement about the mechanisms of consciousness. And i am a cheap fuck, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 04:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never said it was a good reason to believe in a sky daddy. Just that its an unenjoyable strat to try to beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 04:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well i could see someone arguing that a lack of belief is a belief its just not a useful statement to make. Like i don't believe in some 'meaningless statement', could be considered true it would be a belief i held if confronted. The burden of proof may not apply, but it may be defined as a belief, and possibly somewhat reasonably. Its the use that may be a bad thing.

More a statement about a statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 04:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You seem to suppose that i am responding to your entire statement which i am not. I was talking about a single question which i found to be loaded which i addressed, which i in fact clarified. I was pointing out how specifically i found the question is there purpose to be a malformed question. Why am i obliged to argue your whole point anyway?

I was not specifically talking about inherit human values. That was just a rebuttal to a possible objection.  Maybe infallible was the wrong word but you did take a position that appeared to assume that they are someone who 'knows what they are reading' which assumes a higher position.

Fine.

None of your points actually supported the idea that there is some kind of objective reality. Not to deny it its a useful assumption but you could bury your head in the sand and deny everything based on the fact that all of your reason and senses cannot be independently verified if they are in fact fallible consistently it wouldn't be possible to know. Secondly Your assertion that you need to remove your ego, i assume it is the common definition meaning a persons self importance, hasn't been demonstrated well in my opinion apart from some statements about how you believe.

You could argue that i am giving good evidence for you conclusion about letting go of the human-centric view that we have objective morals and that our assignment of meaning is confusing our own assignment of purpose to the world and the inherent assignment of value.

All these points do assume that you are trying to strongly demonstrate your point and find the truth, which i think is a reasonable assumption based on your implied goal of finding the truth. And i do acknowledged it was a rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 03:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are making a positive assertion here. Mind showing a little evidence to substantiate your claim? Because as far as i know not much is known about consciousness apart from an apparent brain region that evidently may control it. Thought that could be a misremembering on my part or simply false. Not to imply i believe in a soul just that you have a burden of proof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 03:41:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um. Yes energy as far as it is known cannot be created or destroyed similarly to information, technical term not literally ideas unable to be destroyed ect. But you seem to be using an equivocation fallacy energy as in the property of particles and energy as in the new age soul thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 03:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing to do with randomness or determinism and certainly not about naturalism. Its a straw man. I was making a point  about certain fallacious reasoning and how i feel there is good reason to believe that there are no higher beings or an objective morality.  And was not making a point about your incoherent post, simply about one vague question you ask with some heavy connotations in bedded.

Also i may be misrepresenting you, but are you saying you are infallible? Or at least something similar by implying that you know what you are reading? Because if true that seems unfounded and also an unhealthy attitude to take for understanding. Also not very good reasoning for discrediting my proposed ideas if that is what you are attempting to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 03:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? That is kind of incoherent or more accurately i don't understand exactly what you are saying. I will attempt to answer what i think you are saying. Which is you are asking why i separate my value judgement from some inherit property of the world.

I separate my value judgement from objective reality, not that they can't be objectively measured, because they have been shown to be inconsistent between individuals. To a high degree which suggests the fact that it is not in fact based on the object but the entity which is interpreting it. For example with a rock i may add meaning to it based on the fact i think it looks useful to bludgeon people with it whereas another person may see it as useful to eat.

Sure it may be based on inherit properties of the object for example the reason a person may want to eat the rock may be because of its sharpness as it is a stupid thing to do if you want to survive and i may wan't to use it because it is sharp and good at cracking skulls but the deviation is explained by the individual differences in the people. And i see no reason to assume because i assign meaning that every other individual assigns the value in the same way and that an individual must have necessarily created it for the purpose of being sharp. Further if any deviations in axiomatic goal are possible which they conceivably are then it is not possible to show as a universal/objective fact one meaning is better or more absolute than any other then it means that any assumption that ones own added meaning cannot be objective nor reasonably applied to the universal/objective facts.

As for a higher being my problem with that as a concept is relevant to my prior point. Being that to assign a being as higher one must, based on my definition and based on my interpretation of the evidence,  must use a subjective judgement to determine if a being is higher or not.

Now for practical purposes we can say that for humans things are right or wrong or for one meaning or another but there is no inherit reason that this should apply to anything else as to do so applies a value judgement making it subjective.

Thus it is disconnected from facts of what a things purpose or use is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 02:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The question of whether existence is pointless to me seems a malformed one.  Not inherently but the way it is usually used. I think defining meaning in this context would be useful. A good definition of meaning may be when a subject applies context to a situation. This may be a pretty bad definition but it emphasizes the fact that the subject is doing something to convey/understand something with context to a purpose. Now my problem with this question is it appears to imply that because you add meaning to something that there must be some higher being that is adding meaning to things, Which funnily enough for something to be higher you must apply your own subjective value judgement to this being to in any way show that it is higher.

It seems to use a false dichotomy. Either i can apply meaning to things and there is a deity that gives things meaning or i can't apply meaning to things and there is no deity. If this is true then there must be a deity/higher being but i don't think it is. I would say the questions are independent of each other, you can apply meaning to a thing or not and it will have no effect on the existence of a higher being.

For example, there is a useful rock thus either it was created for me or it was not a useful rock.

Its conflating the fact that we add meaning to something and the idea that something inherently has meaning. Which i see no evidence for and it does not also does not inherently logically follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 01:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pls Nerf argument from personal experience no fun O.P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 12:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really i thought anti theism was just about being against theism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 12:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Undermining religeon and being respectful don't seem mutually exclusive. I say if an idea is bad it should ideally be critisied. I feel like you are unduely conflating respecting a person and respecting a persons ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 11:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nigger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 11:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 02:54:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok. That's good i wouldn't want that.

My best argument for god goes like this.

If the empirical evidence accurately matches the predictions made about a god and its the most efficient way of describing the details. Then this god exists.

Simple. If a deity passes the said test then it is practically real, if not then for all practical purposes it is in fact incorrect. And i can tell you now that i have found no holly books claims that have passed this test satisfactorily. As of now god is not needed to explain things, and things that aren't needed to explain things do not for all practical and real purposes do not in fact exist. As to claim to work outside of this framework leads to major issues like not being able to discern any kind of evidence from any other type as things are now all equally supportable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 00:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't talk for most people but the reason I am not religious is because near all the arguments for god have blatant logical fallacies. Relying on appeals to ignorance, emotional appeals and very strong personal convictions. Which not everyone can verify and share. And honestly don't make for good evidence.

To be honest the most reliable way to get people in general to believe something is to get them young. When they are unquestioning. As well as this the emotionally vulnerable are another group who are easier to convince. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 05:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its completely pointless and tangential but that is a tactic Scientologists use. Attempting to harass people and make the own up to their crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 05:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its also a false dichotomy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 05:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The way i think about it. If there is no evidence of hell then don't act as if it exists. Because if you do end up acting on something that there is no evidence and consider it valid to worry about then you in theory should be worried about all possibilities that can ever exist. For example what if the other religions are in fact correct? What if there is a microscopic person who tells you how to act and hates you. What about the opposite what if this microscopic person doesn't care? 

If you assert bad evidence as good then all arguments with bad evidence can now be realistically considered, all contradictory options every single one of the same evidence. Anything you do may in fact be wrong. Everything you do may be in fact right.

Its kind of pointless, working outside of the constraints of reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 04:23:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is this article telling people anything new?

Even if people do act more 'moral' when feeling watched, that doesn't mean the benefits of believing in a god are worth it. And it doesn't mean a deity is required to make people act this way. Thinking about religions being watched and encouraged to do immoral things may also have a similar effects. And some other articles claiming that god informs morality are misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 03:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it may be a false dichotomy doesn't mean the two ideas aren't fundamentally opposed. And to claim that theism can predict the "why" better than just base science is simply untrue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 10:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um people are in lots of non specific comunity groups that give meaning. Like people who play sports are part of clubs. Its not specifically atheist but who would think it would be a good idea to base your 'church' or community group on the lack of some idenifiable quality rather than the presences of it? There are lots of groups but they are not mutualy exclusive with going to church. There are secular charity groups that help people who need it ect. What about libraries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 03:26:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Well the same goes for the opposite. People who avoid mentally demanding tasks because they hurt. It doesn't actually matter why people avoid these things your missing out on things. If you don't kill people you miss out on that experience. You haven't had your skin burnt off before, your missing out on that experience. Does it mean people should do it? I'm not saying that doing physical activities is a bad idea. But its not really a point someone can counter and its not a very useful statement due to its encompassing nature </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 12:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a few issues with this.

To start off, who cares if there are contradictory studies. You can find dubius studies that commonly contradict the mainstream opinion doesn't in fact make them any more correct. Also there is a thng called a meta analysis where they get a bunch of studies and put them together to get a larger sample and a better picture. The advantage is that statistical quirks and dodgy research technique yes like p hacking dissapear over a larger data set. Also these are independent studies not just a bunch of studies from the same people. There are controdictory studeis on every subject why should it matter here.

Secondly and more importantly i have issue with your burden of evidence. I think you should be at least thinking about hitchens razor.

What can be asserted without evidence can also be dismissed without evidence. Hitchens Razor. 

I have a question why do you believe what you do? It's quite a useful question. What makes good evidence? For example how do you know that there is not in fact an angry infinatesmially small manlet making you act differently to how you usually do who makes you act irrationaly? You don't i have designed it so that for all practical reasons you can't disporve my hypothesis. 

If you do in fact wan't to learn the truth, does it not seem agreeable to build a highrachy of evidence with the more likely at the top and least likey at the bottom. We need to assess likelyhoods to be able to practically know things. If we accept this then how do we determine what is actually true? Well one idea is to falsify things. Because we cannot ever know if the sun won't come up with 100 percent certanty we must simply assume with good evidence that it will continue to do so. We can't ever show it correct, but instead we can prove it wrong. By multiple methods. Generally, you can make a model of reality and test what effects it could have in a system and show the predictions are useful and valid via satistics or you could simply demonstriat a statistical relationship between the two variables. Generally a model and statistics are preferable as it alows you to understand the underlying reasons but its not always practically possible for medical science. This you might consider higher on a highrachy of evidence. This also implies that a model devoid from reality is useless as it makes no real claims about it. 

Now hitchens razor applies to situations where there is little/no evidence for a statement. When there is no evidence you have a problem if you wan't to assert something as fact it means that all evidence is on an equal footing making it meaningless. And this is one of the problems i see with your claim they have very little evidence backing them up and even if i did bring up evidence there would still be no way of convincing you of the contrary. As no matter what i say your belief system permits you to simply dismiss any claim i make by virtue of my sucking off authorities overbearing cock. It's not based on evidence.

And the evidence you do present i would regard as weak. Its a complete non sequitor. If there have been unethical experiments in the past, then all the things i list as being dangerous for you are the results of these unethical experiments. I don't deny that its possible. But so is the priorly mentioned, angry infinatesmially small manlet making you act differently to how you usually do who makes you act irrationaly. Or any of the other controdictory ideas that cannot be reasonably disproven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 01:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro different energy levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 12:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wasn't very clear on what i said. I am not a postmoderist and do believe in an objective reality due to sheer nessesity. My point was that ideas like an apple being a thing or a brick being a thing are not in fact objective and are subjective. I did word it badly but, i think the fact i mentioned that i was talking about platonic realism is kind of a hint to what i was specifically talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 00:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If god makes no testable predictions then the god concept isn't going to make any practical differences in life. For example god of the gaps, being a god that doesn't have any predictions that is in the gaps of evidence. 

If we wan't to know the truth,

And the best way of finding it is using evidence and reasoning

And god has no testable function derived from reasoning and evidence

Then god is irrelevant to knowing the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 00:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well they don't seem that bad, sure they did purposely or not misinterpret their statement. I don't think everyone agreeing is a good idea and i see no reason why biosphere03 should not criticize [0fiuco](https://www.reddit.com/u/0fiuco/)'s ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 00:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but why should it be axiomatic that walls,bricks and clay are discrete objects and not just a product of our mind. It does to me seem disprovable so it really isn't a good axiom. Its doesn't seem to be an assumption that is useful either. Apart from the fact that it is not a necessary assumption, it seems to me it has nothing to do with the nature of causality and more to do with the intuition that such abstract objects had to be created by a god with extra word salad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 07:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well if we are posting shower thoughts. What does it mean your god to be inside you? Thats just perverted. Is it cheating if god is inside everyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 03:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um what if discrete objects don't exist. At the very least they may be simply a product of the mind. Why do we have to accept platonic realism? It seems to me that the experience of these abstract objects can be well explained by subjective experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 02:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be a false memory, It's possible even likely due to how long ago the event was.

When recalling the group can you remember any external factors when recalling this, for example external information being suggested and integrated into your recollection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 06:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This argument appears to be similar to pascals wager. And the same rebuttal applies. What if the rocks derive sexual pleasure from being broken into small pieces what if they like getting destroyed. Its a false dichotomy. Its not rocks are not conscious or your thoughts about what they are conscious of is true. There are an unending number of un-falsifiable variations that you are not considering. So it is usually best to stick with the idea that your particular non evidence based proposition is wrong and so are all the others.

I do think environmentalism can be beneficial to society but it can also lead to immense suffering. If we are for example talking about new age spiritual beliefs can get in the way of say for example medicine promoting natural remedies that work no better than the placebo. And harm people by making them think they are cured. Or not investing in industry to fix issues that people have already created. It all depends on what you think the consciousnesses of nature wan't/will do. Which may tend to be beneficial to society but these ideas can mutate, if you will. And Change into less useful ideas. 

I never stated that say respecting the natural world is necessarily bad just that asserting things without evidence is a better assumption for truthfulness to not make assertions based on no evidence. And possibly a better assumption for a stable society. As you have to make predictions about the world, the truth or the closest thing to it is quite useful and isn't liable to make complete 360's in doctrine/belief as it is more stable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 04:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say that a negative assertion is generally more useful than an a positive assertion based on no evidence because one is not making any predictions about the world about the world one is not doing so. And to assert something positively without evidence means that all ideas are on an equal footing. So in general it is useful to act as if we are not in a simulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 00:42:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of the existence of religious experience does not actually prove the existence of any form of deity. You can induce "fake" religious experiences in people, meaning it doesn't need a deity. In these cases there was no god being proposed. I suppose you could say that the god itself is causing the experience invariant of the person invoking the experience or the ideas present but then how do you know that there are different gods. If there is no distinction. Or of course you could just arbitrarily state that some of them are fake and others real but then you run into the problem of not knowing which are real. But none of this actually matters because you have asserted the existence of god/gods without evidence of the existence. If things can be asserted without evidence then no evidence can be held to a higher regard which is completely disastrous for actually determining what is true and what isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 06:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fine i can imagine an infinite spaghetti meatball monster. Doe that mean a flying spaghetti meatball monster exists. 

or an incorporeal all encompassing superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 04:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better eat it before hungry niggerians get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 01:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would just like to point out that the big bang theory says nothing about what happened before it.  It says nothing about creation of something from nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 01:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People can have false memories, it has been demonstrated that you can induce them through suggestion. 

Similarly finding patterns in things is also easy. People see animals, holy symbols household objects when looking at clouds. This is more on the other end interpreting these occurrences. 

Another explanation is due to the survivors bias. People who think they are resurrected other people and don't have similar hand writing won't be shown. Similarly people who simply aren't convincing won't convince their apparent former family so they are not shown.

How many cases are there of this? Because there are about seven and a half billion people on the planet, you should expect thousands of people, maybe millions of people to have insane stories that are simply coincidences. 

As well as this anecdotal evidence isn't very good due to the abysmal sample size. Being extremely prone to random fluctuations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 01:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes and anything asserted on no evidence can be refuted without any evidence. If you don't then all facts are on an even level and any predictive ability is gone as you can't distinguish between all possible possibilities.

Doesn't mean you can't be interested/fascinated by these problems, just not assert their truthfulness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 00:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please if you are going to quote an article without first looking at the research it's based on, quote a reputable science magazine.

Second of all, i don't think it is productive to say people are getting smarter because there are less Christians. Even if they truly do believe in a non existent, apparently benevolent sky daddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 02:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God done it.

 #x200B;

Obviosly.

Edit: spelling too good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 02:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have observed people with that general attitude you describe and they are hypocrites. I don't know if it is a thing that many people believe. We are using different definitions of it being a thing. And i could easily simply deny your claim fruitlessly. But all this is besides the point. 

People are pointing out that your claims or your mannerisms are not good for productive discourse, whether it be earned or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because you've heard it doesn't mean its a thing.

Move on now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WHAT IS A HIGHER BEING.

I say god isn't a useful assumption, as a base line assumption, IF you wan't to know the truth. I would be happy to accept there is a god if it somehow emerged later on. But as a primary assumption, he doesn't pack predictive power or accuracy that may be useful to find the truth. I have a question does god existing do anything change the laws of thermodynamics? Does it change the fundamental forces or the way biology works? 

I like learning, and making assumptions based on  what you wan't to be true doesn't have a great track record for being correct. And in turn learn about the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok.

What about it. One is a useful assumption based on some evidence one is not a useful assumption based on bad evidence. You still haven't clarified this HIGHER BEING thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What line of thinking? I don't understand? I still don't know what greatest being actually means. Does it mean most able to change things physical does it mean how cool they apparently "objectively" are? Are we having the same conversation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And? What about it? We don't know if things will continue tomorrow. We also don't know if the universe was created last Thursday.

That is why we use assumptions. Good assumptions. Ones that allow us to predict things. 

For example we don't know if our perceptions of reality actually represent reality. For example how do you know that a chair is a chair or that anything we perceive actually physically exists do we live in a simulation? We can't know by definition doesn't matter if what we do perceive is physically real or not we have no way of proving it with certainty, so that is why we assume that our experience represents reality its productive if you want to understand things. 

Same with reason. If we assume the world is self consistent and we can apply logic to it then we can predict the laws of physics. We can say with some certainty that the sun will come up as we have deduced to a reasonable degree the mechanisms that cause it to appear to rise. It could spontaneously disappear but it could do any number of un-falsifiable things. There is no practical reason to believe it. So it is for all practical reasons it is considered false. 

On another note that is one hell of a non sequitur. We don't know if tomorrow will exist thus lesser being means higher beings. I also don't understand what you mean by a lesser being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 00:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure what you have described is what the new atheist movement really stands for. I'm pretty sure it's not about living without meaning and general being cynical about the world. But more about promoting secularism and Naturalism. 

Its definitely not about rejecting any moral principles because they are subjective. For example Sam Harris often talks about building an objective morality off the amount of suffering the world, or at least the closest thing to it. Rejecting anything positive in your life? I also doubt that is actually part of the movement. 

I wouldn't say it's necessarily about completely destroying group identity and meaning in peoples lives. But simply about promoting the truth due to its sheer usefulness to a world view. As well as this to stop religion getting in the way of science and useful values for maintaining a prosperous stable society like freedom of speech. For example not being allowed to insult everyone from Allah to Big red. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 00:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are useful assumptions. Possibly the minimum amount of assumptions needed to make a working world view. They are much more useful than any "higher" being in making a method for finding some ideal concept called truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 06:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not saying that it's a good idea to not use math in physics that would be dishonest. As well as that it would be extremely stupid. I am simply point out that it depends on your definition of math to whether it is TECHNICALLY needed. I AGREE with your point about the usefulness of math in physics. Please don't lecture me about the usefulness of math in science and physics specifically i didn't say it wasn't useful. Its a straw man.

I have made a claim that there are many different views on what mathematics is. And you have simply stated that I am incorrect without any proof. I am not making an assertion, that an assumption made is actually unfounded, and all you have done is gone:

NAA Math isn't philosophy.

I did NOT in fact say that math was philosophy no more than the fact that physics is mathematics. I simply stated that math may be argued to be applied philosophy. Sure not a very useful statement, due to me putting forth no evidence and not even considering the definition of philosophy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 06:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 06:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I'm not sure. I also don't think that my personal belief has anything to do with it. I'm not particularly knowledgeable of the authorship or the bible. I am simply putting the burden of proof onto you to prove your point. That these accepted effects are unlikely to have been occurring. You should disprove the null hypothesis. Otherwise, everyone you or anyone else debates would have to prove you wrong to a sufficient degree which honestly isn't a good use of time, assuming you wan't to find out the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 06:14:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, i thought your statement entailed

First the assumption that the book had unreliable sources.

Then the statement that further research should be done.

If this is what you are saying and you have already researched enough and the burden of proof is on the pro religious to show it is different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 06:02:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. Except for the last part. I don't see a reason to investigate the sources of a religion further, assuming that we are looking for the truth. As the fact it comes from a bad source means that it can be refuted without much consideration, for practical reasons. As anything asserted without good evidence can be refuted with the same amount of evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 05:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do admit that my first point didn't really address your point.

Ok. The second point. 

I am assuming you believe that if a lot of people at one time witness something then its unlikely to be incorrect. But with this you are not stating the likelihood of a single person being incorrect. From what you have said i would assume you would agree that single people can be wrong. And several independent testimonies are not very reliable. 

My second point was about knowing if this mass revelation actually occurred. If you assume that single people can be incorrect and these single people spread an idea then it is likely to be changed as it moves along. I am supposing that your premise that a mass revelation actually occurred may in fact be incorrect.

You only need to examine folk lore and common stories about the past to see ideas changing. To see how ideas change radically in a short period of time. For example changes if we are talking about a text, you can get ideas lost in translation, or possibly lost in interpretation of a translation. Even in the same language if we were to compare say middle English with modern English it would be near unreadable. 

As well as this if an idea is transmitted orally then it is easy for one person to be wrong or embellish a story a little and the next lot cannot consult the original source. Like for example common myths that prevail in society today like the idea that people consume spiders in their sleep. I forget the claimed number, though it does vary. Or that Salieri Killed Mozart. 

Another possible mechanism for this changes in an idea would be false memory. Researchers have been able to induce false memories in patients and get people to describe certain elements about this false memory. 

None of this is to say this didn't happen. Simply that it's in fact possible, i see it as likely but that is irrelevant, that there was no mass revelation. And your first assumption is incorrect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 05:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If one religion is 100% false then yes. But i don't think that is a useful assumption. Its a different question if we are talking about the likelihood of some idea being correct. 

If we assume that the likelihood of an idea being correct is based on the method of attainment. \[Insert rant about the scientific method here and why its basal assumptions are useful for predictive power because I'm lazy and don't feel like writing about it now\]. \[insert section about how the current method of attainment is not very useful.\] Thus this religion is unlikely to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 05:03:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If i go ahead and assume you are correct and Judaism is in fact correct, then it seems very possible that false ideas can still spread like the plague as the other religions are false. Do you also believe that alien sightings are correct due to the mass belief in it?

Even if we do accept that the mass belief in something in a short time makes it correct does that actually mean that this event did occur? If one person can be wrong but many in a short time can't then holy books can then by the same logic be incorrect assuming that any person in the history between the event was also correct. People could be wrong in the long term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 04:52:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And mathematics is applied philosophy arguably. Doesn't mean you need it to use it. Say you don't actually wan't to quantify forces and simply convey a nonspecific, and very easily arguably useless manner, you could.

It all comes down to your definition of mathematics.  You may subscribe to mathematical logic-ism. So physics doesn't have to be a part of mathematics if you don't apply any. Or you could believe that mathematics is simply a set of symbols that denote certain things, so physics in this view can very much be done without mathematics. Or Mathematical Intuitionism so physics is math in this view even if conveyed non specifically and verbally Ect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 04:36:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That argument also assumes that causes cannot be cyclical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 04:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For all practical purposes no. 

There is no practical explanatory reason to say that a god exists at the movement. If you don't care about the ability of an idea to predict things then, who knows?

From your statement it seems to me that you wan't to know if the existence of god is a fact.  A fact being defined as a belief that is overlapped with the truth. I would be inclined to say no its not a fact as so far no one has demonstrated a gods existence to my standard of proof. 

And if your view of god makes no testable predictions we have no idea if it is a fact or a incorrect belief. So i tend to assume that this god does not exist because it makes no impact on the world and to assume this kind of idea is correct breaks  any kind of justification for any idea. As now all ideas are on an equal footing meaning that you can't actually distinguish fact from fiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 01:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could also argue that statement is a straw man. Or at the very least a generalization without any evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 01:14:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either that or they deny the science. Like some creationists claiming that fossils sort by intelligence, density ect. And other claims including the global water canopy. And the denial of carbon dating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 13:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You make a statment of fact based on no evidence i ignore it. Should i take a different aproach? Is believing it better? Or is sitting around pondering all the possible realities that are also based off nothing whatsoever a good aplication of your time?

Sure physics is wierd. Some spiritual beliefs are also weird. But I prefere the one that makes acurate predictions. And i don't wan't another conversation with you about your cone with finite volume and infinite surface area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 10:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Firstly the reason i siad "need" is becuase predictive power is what matters when making models as far as i know. If you don't need special relativety to do rocketry then don't use it. Its just pointless, you don't need to understand all of physics to be a chemist. Quantum theory only applies to systems that have two conjugate variables whose uncertanty are equal h bar over 2.

About senses,  I do know their is evidence that for example tests done with fruit flies could smell the difference between duterium and hydrogen 1 when the organic molecule are made of it. And would prefere the lighter one.

[https://www.newscientist.com/article/dn20130-fly-sniffs-molecules-quantum-vibrations/](https://www.newscientist.com/article/dn20130-fly-sniffs-molecules-quantum-vibrations/)

I couldn't find anything more credible as open access jurnals are prone to many issues.

There is also evidence if i remember correctly that the sense of direction in sea birds possibly due to entangled particles interacting with the earths magnetic field.

It was hard to find a credible source on this one. This one seems a bit scetchy.

I didn't say that quantum phenomona do not occur life/the brian or something like that. That i admit is an intereseting field of inquirey but it still isn't really evidence for your deepak chopra stuff.

I can't explain conciousness, I'm not sure anyone has done so with much success, but you have been equivocating conciousness with decisions. Conciousness i would argue is the experience of existing being aware ect. This is not about decision making. Things that affect decision making are known. In basic phycology class students learn about the different cortexs and how they effect behaviour.

If we are talking biochemically then i would try and hide the fact i know very little about neorscience as well as simple psychology and point out that scientists know about neorotransmitters and neorons ect. You know, how your endocrine system effects your behaviour, agression, lustfulness ect..

Quantum theory is not needed to explain seeming randomness of the brain either, chaos theory is an example of an area that studies deterministic systems that have hypersensitivity to initial condition. This is a physical mechanism for why choice seems random when in fact it may not be. Due to the brains chaotic nature. And here i am disregarding certain interpritations of QM that are in fact determinisitic. So if you accept many worlds or piolet wave, which there is no real reason to, then its not technically random.

Also no disbelief is superior to bind belief in the absence of evidence. As i am not maing physical claims, you are. I am not asserting things in the absence of evidence and saying but you can't disprove it.

Ha, its gotten to the point in the conversation where you choose to disbelieve in my light speed hypotmous. Just because you think your more intelegent for not believing in it. MMMM.

Wow i didn't even mean to misspell intelligent.

Ok that was childish but i think it demonstrates my point from before. Not that i believe the thought experiement you have proposed is that absurd.

One last point it's not double standards if i actually have evidence and you don't. And for safe measure i will reract the first statement and change it to, As far as i know the currecnt explanations are doing quite well compared to your new one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 08:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you may be arrested for saying the opposite. 6M is a tad low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 08:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Assuming i can't falsify your suggestion. I can still dismiss your claim on those exact grounds, if i can't there is no point. Its not needed to describe the brain. You can get chaotic behaviour in completely deterministic systems, you don't need quantum theory to explain the way the brain works. Also you haven't actually come up with a coherent physical mechanism for this actually happening. 

You call the observer can be anything bullshit but don't actually show how it can be. You simply attempt to demonstrate that their may be many variables effecting a quantum system and have not disproved the idea that polarising light is an observation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 02:32:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never said my experience of reality is not subjective. By definition it is. But my point was simply that if you follow the assumption that their is a knowable objective reality that assuming other aren't any other the infinite unfalsifiable realities like everyone being philosophical zombies or your a Boltzmann brain. Which are very safe assumptions, if you wan't to attempt to understand things. I see no reason to assume that time and space are subjective, just your experience of it.  I am claiming that time and space cannot be changed in such a way by any subjective experience of it. Simply that your use of it as a metaphor for the subjective view of what heaven is undue at best.

Also I don't really understand what my point has to do with mathematical Platonism i don't know why you have brought it up. Am i claiming that abstract concepts like geometric objects and numbers are physical things. 

Um are you kind of linking the observer effect with consciousness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 00:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone is going on about how they know someone smart but stupid. Or any bloody definition. Nothing is actually being said apart from, insert predicatively useless wisdom here, this was more about most of the comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 00:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um. Time and space are relative to the reference frame... Not exactly subjective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 00:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This reeks of half ass definitions. Come on. Is anyone actually talking about the same idea at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 00:35:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That smells of an equivocation fallacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 00:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some studies claim their is a statistically significant difference between peoples precognition and it when guessing erotic images. Have you tried looking at a meta analysis on the subject? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 02:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Checkmate theists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 05:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two words. 

Empirical examination. Look at the literature. Also evil is kind of vague. Maybe too vague to make any predictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 05:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know what logic actually is?

Logic is simply put a set of rules that dictate how reason should be conducted for validity. Without empirical examination of the world logic is really quite useless.

Here is some logic that is flawless.

Cars are People.

The sky is a car.

Thus the sky is a person.

It follows logical rules, its premise is wrong, due to simple empirical examination you could tell me that the premises is incorrect. But LOGIC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 05:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bow down to the mighty spaggett and all the meatballs in heaven. Receive the love of the mighty dish and come to the true prophet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 05:18:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The magic spaghetti monster disapproves of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 05:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Untested atheism... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 04:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, the ghost cheeks strikes again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 04:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 02:15:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That doesn't seem to prove objective ethics wrong. I think you mean that morals are subject to circumstance.

You kind of need to define what ethics is. Defined as a set of moral principles that governs a persons behavior. From here its possible to already see the issue with objective morality it by definition is subjective. Its about what people tend to believe. And there is variation in what people believe. Its subjective because it is by definition not based on truth but on what people tend to judge is the correct way to act. Something that increases the amount of prosperity for both the self and the community.

Besides this if objective morals existed, the objective morals would be the best, as they are somehow correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 00:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> False dichotomy. Do neither. Just because, lets assume its possible to be unquestionably proven wrong this does not in fact make the other correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 02:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry but science if we are talking about it does not deal with absolute truths simply usable models of reality. So if we are equivocating atheism with rationalism, which there is no good reason to, then your statement about athiests having faith is kind of wrong. Its more about having the minimum possible faith. Science works with things that can actually be known and predicted, i don't see how any kind of religeon or other philosophy can do any better. They are not two sides of the same coin as i see it. I have reason to believe my car is going to work, i can't be 100 percent sure as skepticism can always be applied. But any idea no matter what can be questioned including faith. I have good enough evidence that thermodynamics will work as well today as yesterday, as the opposite assumption is that we can't know anything.

That is why scientists assume that their senses give outputs that are representative of reality, that reasoning and empirical examination can show things about the way the universe works and that better predictive models are more correct. Tell me how can unprovable, nonspecific ideas be useful for prediction, over predictively powerful ones like evolution, Relativity and quantum mechanics. These theories are far more useful than GOD did it, which explains everything but fails to actually predict anything before the fact. 

Gravity will stay constant. If you assume otherwise you might as well assume there is no history and the universe appeared in the current state last thursday, its unprovable and not very useful. Also no wave like properties has nothing to do with the consistency of gravity. You probably didn't know that you have a wave length, matter acts as a wave. Should we then conclude that we can't be sure matter exists? It has been tested up to bucky balls, about 60 carbon atoms in them. The thing is that that you as a person's energy levels or momentum together aren't small enough when timesed together to be equal to the h bar over 2 nor the same with energy and time.

Faith can be dangerous as i said. Not is inherently, but i also don't see science and coping with reality as a dichotomy. I seem to live without an invisible alpha male who tells me I'm loved and must love back. And for humanity in general, i see religeon as being very unhealthy. As its a mass dilusion that gets in the way of the truth wich is very useful for manipulating reality as to not be in poverty or to be free of disease. 

As i see it for finding the truth faith is useless. Science rejects the super natural for good reason and thats not going to change just because alot of people fear their own mortality and wan't to spend all their time in hellish heavan praising god unendingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Faith is usually defined as belief without evidence. Being divorce from realitity can lead to issues when interacting with it. There that is why faith can be dangerous. So how is faith knowing better period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 16:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still doesn't make it correct.

Edit: also i don't think the other poster was denying the abrahamic background more that that reddit as a single entity doen't understand nor like the abrahamic religions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 15:42:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure. The point was the asserter, has the burden of proof.

But if one actually wanted to know, they would do a survey. Or even look one up, i didn't find one. r/SampleSize seems a good sub for collecting data or r/dataisbeautiful. Or even this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 15:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about we get the data on this. Use the empirical evidence to decide who is correct instead of this pissing contest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 15:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The concept of global skepticism. You can never be certain of anything as the are always concievabe alternatives that could be true. There is always basis to doubt everything. But a helpful method is to decrease the amount of unfounded assumptions, only the bare minimum required to make a workable world veiw. Those as i see it being 1. the world is knowable 2. reason can be used to know things about the world. To be able to efficiently predict things that have and will occur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 15:16:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well maybe you can illicit such feeling from other sources that you don't have to delude yourself into believing in, with any good evidence. Though i do have to admit churchs are very good at this type of emotional arousal, a bit like facism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Believe in the unbeivable or the unbelieveable will come around to your house and genocide your people, because he wanted an exuse for himself, to kill some people. Welcome back to the dark ages. 

Everything god does will be glorified. Nice. Define yourself as all good and your ready to go on bootleg zuese style. You know the type, turn into a swan for a bit of buggery , that kind of stuff. At least zeus didn't define himself as all good as far as i know.

Good luck with stone age II. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because the authors didn't like the fags, too gay apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 14:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No its more like trying to not figure out chemistry and praying for your incorporeal alpha to smite your enemies instead of working hard to understand what the hell is actually happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 07:55:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And this is a meaningful statement, how? This applies to many different definitions, usually for abstract concepts, like for example a car. Well what is a car? Nearly all definitions of a car will have some issues as car's are not tangible physical object it's just an idea that has certain variations. You are saying that making generalisations can be inaccurate, and vaguely that "most" statements are not absolute is kind of meaningless.

Its specifically a non statement, how am i supposed to add anything meaningful. Because you can simply retroactively state what you think in vague terms about what is and isn't a correct absolute statement, about relgion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 07:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok. Why is faith good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 05:56:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 05:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The problem is your first assumption is god exists. I don't think this is a very useful assumtion. As it means you have no evidence of its existance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 09:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When i say see i mean observe. Also no naturalism out right rejects the immarterial by definition, its super natural, as if it exists it has no effect on the universe. If science can't do it how can a less efficent faith based assertion prove the apparently unprovable. If science can't do it how can a less efficent faith based assertion prove the apparently unprovable. How does it bypass universal sketicism? A solution that involves a second adgent that is interviening that is similarly effect by this issue along side the normal scepticism that come anout in everyday reality.

My arguement against prophesy is the predictive power and novelty of them. If i went around saying that a natural disaster was going to happen soon. I would probably be right. Its not novel. When is soon and where is the disaster, what qualifies it as a disaster, no specifics, like the order of magnitude ect. those might actually be useful. Its also easy to simply not look at the data. For example survivors bias, you don't often hear about failed celebrities or from the people who are dead thus skewing the results. Same thing with prophets, failed ones could easily have been swept under the rug where as by random chance someone getting something vaugely correct is remembed as it is memorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 02:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If god is unsaleable that means you can't really falsify the idea making it simply a waste of time to actually test. Also meaning there is no reason to assert his existence. And if you can't assert the existence then there shouldn't be a god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 01:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does not. First off i call b.s on your first statement. How does it predict quantum mechanics. Does it specially tell us that there are discrete energy levels in the universe and that all matter acts as if it is governed by a probability distribution? Does it predict entanglement? Does it predict wave function collapse or the behavior of bose-einstien condensates? What about vacuum energy?

Or does it simply state the existence of super position which has been a phenomena in classical physics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 05:38:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Entropy is not that. Depends on the definition of it. The original definition was simply the unavailability of energy to do mechanical work. At thermal equilibrium you cant do work so its high entropy. After the advent of statistical mechanics it became defined by micro states and macro states. A high entropy system is a system where there are a high number of micro states to a macro state is a high entropy system. So say a pressure gradient exists that is a low entropy system as energy can be transferred as the system will go towards thermal equilibrium as there are the most micro states to that macro state. It has nothing to do with how complex a system may look to a human simply the probability of a system trending towards the state, which happens to be thermal equilibrium.

Unless you are using a less physics use of the word simply meaning disorder.

Also no life does not in fact violate the second law of thermodynamics. Life on a local level does in fact decrease entropy but on a global scale actually will tend to increase it. For example if we look at the energy coming from the sun, it will come in high energy wave lengths. And eventually is released at lower energy levels. As it has been dispersed being used to make biological reactions occur.

As i see it the cancer would like all biological tissue decrease entropy at a local level and increase it in the wider universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 04:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sub: But what about ChRiStIaNs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 03:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait for steam to download it and try to save again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 03:45:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The way humans formed it is not exactly known. But the point is that you simply can't just assert that because we don't certainly know that it was an unlikely event that we must assume the opposite. There are several explanations including the less likely now but still interesting panspermia, or life coming from deep sea vent.  Some more likely than others. And it may only be random in the sense that its an emergent property which in a sense is random.

Also that trumpet is cherry picking. You can find a relation between almost anything given enough data points. Its not novel to say that certain structures recur throughout nature. Would you be amazed that hills drain water much like the roof of a house or that a double helix looks like a vine. This is Illuminati confirmed level, obscure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 03:14:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The usual question first. 

Have you validated the game files? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 03:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He wants us to buy the latest edition of his book series and need something to drive sales.

Good business model buy the anthology or suffer eternal damnation. A bit like Disney, except you get eternal damnation to the uncanny valley either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 02:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can't prove the existence of god, then you can't then prove how he decides when someone is born. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 02:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only fact i think matters in this debate is the merit of the idea of a god. As i see it, to understand my view you need to first accept a few premises, for good reason. So the important question is how someone goes about deciding the merit of an idea. First premise, the nature of reality can be known to some extent. This is first off because if you accept the opposing view you are being self contradictory as the statement there is no truth, is a paradox. 

 Secondly, assuming that there is some form of objective reality that it is most likely that the most efficient explanation is true. This is to make sure any hypothesis made is not unnecessarily complicated, as such a thing would be by its own definition unfounded. 

So if we accept these ideas and look at the concept of god. What do we see. Well what is the purpose of god in an explanatory system. If it is to simply explain the physical laws of the universe? Well what evidence is there for the causes for the physical laws. There honestly is none so here a god would be an unfounded assumption unless already proven. What about for morality. Well that is something that can be objectively measured and has been. Morality can be explained easily by evolution, for which there is overwhelming evidence. For example incest is thought to be generally wrong because it decreases genetic diversity and leads to all kinds of issues, even if this explanation is wrong morality does not actually prove or disprove god. But we don't need to invoke a hyper specific character that has specific difficult to prove that doesn't like 'certain' aspects of your relationships. What about creation of the universe? Once again scientists are unsure over the nature of the universe before 10 to the negative 43 seconds after the big bang. Its open to interpretation also meaning  there is nothing close to certainty, which is in it self not possible to reasonable get to. 

None of this disproves any religion but i don't need to disprove all religious claims with certainty, simply demonstrate that a god is not a useful explanatory concept for explaining the universe making it on the current evidence extremely unlikely that a god exists. Or simply the fact that whatever it may be assuming that it does exists, which is a pointless assumption, it doesn't matter at all as we know nothing about it. Which is indistinguishable from it not existing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 02:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Later maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 02:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up a time series graph of average temperature, actually collect that data yourself and come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 02:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Na the truth isn't a good basis for a philosophy. Lets just speculate on end until the truth is almost completely obscured. But muh communism but muh acceleration, but muh anarcho-capitalism. A belief in an objective reality is a very useful lifestyle choice, it allows you to actually change things instead of flander around in post-structural bliss, with their African and christian "science". Because the alternative is adopting a view that their is no truth, which as a statement is self contradictory and not useful even if our current reality isn't representative of the entirety of reality. And we truly are brains in vats or Boltzmann brain/brains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 01:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do what you will. But remember self delusion can be very dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 04:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spoilers, mods can fuck people over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 01:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't be a redditcuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 04:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For physics and chemistry. Usually both.

Thunderfoot

King Crocoduck

PBS space time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 03:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a black box. You know what goes in to some extent and what goes out to some extent. I'm not advocating determinism or a probabilistic universe. This has nothing to do with what someone describes as the constraints on them.

I am simply stating that assuming you have no constraints what ever that actually means, is absurd. The  brain to some extent has been mapped. And parts have been identified. Its not reasonable to assume that actions can be predicted due to the inherent chaos involved in organisms. But that doesn't mean the mind has no constraints. Just you cant completely accurately predict them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 02:45:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If we are talking about proof, it would be better to not make unfounded assertions, in this case free will has no evidence. Its a semantic argument to hide the fact that people wan't to feel special. You can safely assume it is not a thing, just like assuming their is no god due to a complete lack of evidence of any predicted deity, is a reasonable assumption. Most people do not deal with certainties, they only exist in conceptual frameworks. Like mathematics or philosophy.

Edit: Its the minimum faith needed. It is not a faith based argument. Look up Karl popper. 

He is not asserting that there are black swans without evidence he is asserting there are no black swans on the fact that there is no evidence of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 01:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They weren't there, during the battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 05:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bastard children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 02:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably us of us haven't actually read the paper as you can only view the abstract without actually paying money. Could easily be badly misquoted/manipulated. And since we can't really tell if it methodologically flawed so i don't see the point in arguing about it.

Edit: Remember that about 80% of research published in sociology, psychology, economics and medical science are blatantly wrong. There is a lot of bad research out due to an ongoing replication crisis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 07:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, I'm pretty sure it occurs in plants. Due to anaerobic resperation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 06:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you don't need a god to avoid existential dread. Could be a biological issue or physiological issue. I generally opt for fixing issues or finding a vice that doesn't change my view of reality itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 06:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't tell if this is satire.

Still i like it, either way this is gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me it kind of looks like you are using an equivocation fallacy here. 

Light was never supposed to have a deep personal philosophy i would say, but he was supposed to be deep. They are too different meanings of the word. One being that the character is a nuanced portrayal of a person and the other the character is thoughtful, insightful ect. 

Light is not thoughtful, he is on a mission to rid the world of criminals according to his moral code and he isn't going to analyse the effects of his actions ect. But he is an interesting character because of L. L is his counterpart, he exploits lights arrogance, one of his main character flaws to find out where in the world he is and is constantly prodding at light to drive the plot, be it turning up at his entrance exams and constantly trying to trap light. Light also fills this role with L forcing him into situations by responding and attempting to find out his identity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like hating america has more to do with its international politics than anything else, it being a world power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My problem with light is that is ideology is not rooted in reality. His judgment is based on his singular opinion of a person, he is all powerful and completely fallible. He doesn't follow due process and hasn't even seen the evidence against people commit crimes. He also isn't interested in preventing crime judging him purely by his actions. Sure he is killing criminals and that is decreasing the crime rate, but he has shown that he is interested in keeping alive good productive people. 

For example in a segment were the news is playing in the background light notes that it is too soon to be promising to kill the lazy as his spokesperson, forgot her name, said. Which isn't a very productive attitude, similar to the attitude in Stalinist Russia, where it was considered industrial sabotage to not meet your work quota. 

Likewise he is interested in justice and not a decreased crime rate specifically. Crime does go down when Kira is killing but it by no means does it disappear. He most likely stops repeat offences and people who likely have committed crimes in the past but there was little evidence.  But he isn't fixing reprehensible behaviors. People are still beating each others heads over with blunt objects. 

In the first episode he considers killing some bullies, light ponders about if anyone would miss them if they were to die. 

He on many occasions demonstrates black and white thinking to justify his actions. These people are evil, rotten ect. Subscribing to a completely unnuanced world view, which i don't see as representative of reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 02:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No love can be physically quantified. Neurotransmitters can be measured. Facial expressions can be quantified. You can't be 100 sure everyone else isn't a philosophical zombie but in life nothing can be proven to this degree.

Also the good thing about science is that they change their mind. This is how the process occurs. Also string theory hasn't been proven so scientists will tend to disagree.

Why can't you build your life philosophy around the truth, seems perfectly reasonable to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 02:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really. How did Islam predict cosmic inflation or the red shift of galaxies? What about the CMB? Also there is little evidence that we will be having a big crunch scenario. Its much more likely that the big rip or heat death will occur.

Also all of these examples are not actually scientific theories. The big bang theory is. Big crunch or multiverse haven't been elevated to that level of evidence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 01:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats next feminist algebra? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 05:38:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is that going to do?

The wavelength of the signals is most likely a few orders of magnitude too large for the signals to be ionizing. I'm pretty sure any studies that have been done on the effect of long non ionizing radiation on people in the long term haven't been conclusive. But if we are talking about chances of catching cancer, i find it likely that there may be a random correlation between the two variables.  If only due to lifestyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 03:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 04:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the issue is that religious people are not arguing from sophism. The reason people don't accept the religious books is because if you start assuming the most possible thinks aren't real then go from there. The reason religious texts aren't considered real isn't for cherry picking but instead is the result from the fact that no one yet has found these properties emerge from any other view point other than the book being correct as one of your axioms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 04:50:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a sense agnostic. In practice atheistic. Your entire argument comes from the idea that there is such thing as mathematical proof in real life and not simply near impossibly likely, as you don't know all the properties of your conceptual framework and never will. One is extremely likely, one is extremely unlikely, simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 03:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is it that politics, religion and art cant be in the domain of science? To me it seems it would be mighty useful to use empirical evidence to see if certain political actions will actually work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 04:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> has it? For me its still there when searching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 05:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why have i not experienced this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 05:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't experienced this, either its fake, on mobile or fixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 04:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 03:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Facts and logic. Destroys libtard.

But seriously it is a fact that you think china is horrible. And it may be a fact that a large number of people believe this. But china horrible. That is a subjective opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 03:50:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes will no longer have to marry a potato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 06:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly I've never seen a point in correcting natural language. Natural language changes it happens. Its not as if OP is going about using formal language incorrectly like certain postmodernist philosophers who like to using mathematical and scientific languages as "metaphors".

For example weight used in nontechnical aspects, like loosing weight. When really it would be more correct to say loosing mass as we aren't measuring force applied to an object. Should i go around nagging people that it's mass they are loosing. And there is consequentially less weight. Because they are using it wrong?

Please explain how the word is being used incorrectly. According to a few definitions i have found on the internet it means in this context, that the language is being used to persuade in a particular style. And that is their style. Or that the talk is apparently meaningless or empty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 06:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Put it a different way one that isn't coloured by too much emotion. 

Would you complain that Mozart in Amadeus or in the musical it was based on was that much of an ass hole. Or that Salieri murdered Mozart despite there being no evidence for that being so. It's biased and it makes a good story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 07:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Numbers are abstract concepts" anonymous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 06:08:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depending on the pic it may have violated the rules. As irrelevant titles are not allowed. But those comment graveyards...

F for the brave commentators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just a wholesome image </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 05:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 05:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 04:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watch you language

Nargos if one wishes to speak more formally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 07:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure the quality of a school has very little effect on the outcomes of the students. I'm not sure if there was no statistically significant difference or a very weak correlation. Even with a correlation a causal link really hasn't been established. The generally quoted reason for prestigious schools having higher scores, is the exclusivity. Smart people can get into good schools, as they are exclusive. Another fact is that expensive schools can afford to kick out dropkick students before they start their exams as to not decrease the average score of the school. That is presuming the information content or access is the same. ie. standardized curriculum or access to a library.

But yes that does seems to suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 07:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly you could interpret it how you like. Either way, seems plausible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 06:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't know which r/atheism you've been on. There is some shredding on Christianity, but there is a lot of stuff about all kinds of topics from pointing out logical fallacies, talking about laws regarding religion, some of its just mundane, conversation. But it is a pain in the ass when you get a discussion about another religion and you get those idiots who go what about Christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 06:06:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By cheap grain from swadia when its at peace and sell it for around to 30 fold profit. At another kingdom, say the kingdom of veigers. 

Usually can get 10 or so bags of grain from villages. Around dhirim for 2-3 denars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 04:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like people who don't want to do math </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 01:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doom eternal end of 2019 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 01:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well fearing death sucks but is useful in motivating yourself to not want to die. Weather it. Change your diet, exercise ect. not that i follow my own advice but these kind of issues can be biological.

Honestly i wouldn't recommend deluding yourself into believing in something insane. It simply makes it hard to cope with being wrong as you've invested a lot in them. And they wont don't fix other issues in life. For example, faith healing is no more effective than a placebo.

Existential issues?

Personally I've found that religion is no more inherently meaningful than another activity. If you are looking for that. If not, have you tried any other kinds of community? Do you know what you want from life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 05:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 02:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That as far as i know is not actually the definition of materialism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 02:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can't show proof that 100% lots of things don't exist. Like most other gods ever conceived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 02:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Simple answers are usually good. 

A Creator isn't necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 02:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you are going to make some new age "quantum healing" can you at least have some quantum phenomena involved l It's kind of boring when you get these quacks who don't even know how to make a legible falsehood.   Come on, if you do plan to run around with magic crystals you could at least make it interesting. Sure efficient light bulbs and computing are results of the quantum revolution in the 1920's but they just aren't that mystical. I guess the issue is that you need high energies for anything particularly interesting to happen. Of course you have to use many world interpretation. But wouldn't the Copenhagen interpretation be validly mysterious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 01:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe those qualities aren't actually christian. By definition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 01:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is an interesting concept of faith. From everywhere i have read the term simply means trust and confidence in someone or believing something without good evidence. If we use this definition of faith you have rebutted nothing. But you've made your own definition of faith. This definition as i see it  postulates that mental state can change reality.

 I'm not denying that faith is an abstract concept doesn't make it any better at changing objective reality. Just because it isn't a specific molecule, which it self is an abstract concept as a molecule, is a region of space with specific fluctuations in specific fields. Which is simply a construct to describe reality not reality itself. 

I see no evidence that these ideas manifest themselves themselves in reality.

And to claim there is no truth is a truth statement, which then can't be tested by this view as everyone sees or changes reality according to your concept of reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 06:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He doesn't usually look like a fly. Expect when he going incognito mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 06:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> National socialism.

 #x200B;

 #x200B;

Happy Hitler noises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 05:59:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My question is what is your explanation for faith being good. Faith being belief in things based not on proof but on spiritual conviction.

Unless its an axiom of the religion then why is this fact considered self evident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 05:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My question is then why is faith a virtue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 05:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being an atheist. I would like to say that i have never loved sin. I simply have not seen compelling evidence that cannot be explained more eloquently than by the natural laws. Compared to a supernatural entity.

Caveat, that is not to imply that i have not or do not continue to indulge in things that may be considered sinful, just that i don't need to invoke a lack of god to feel as if i may do so. As the issue is with evidence. You would be more of a self loathing and delusional theist than an atheist. Which implies that theists aren't already self delusional but that's a matter of opinion that has little to do with the point. Gotta throw some shade every so often... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 05:37:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By any chance was you gf, Christian and wanted to get married. Because you said you had already been seeking god before the 'super natural' indecent. Another question why Christianity, i know you said that you were getting into Christianity but the board never actually mentioned Christianity specifically, assuming your transcript is correct.

I would also like to point out the clear survivor bias that is present in this thread. I doubt you would be proclaiming things a miracle if your mysterious illness didn't go away and you died. And what about all those times that you can barely remember where nothing interesting occurs what so ever. What about all those people who had an 'almost miracle'.

About the diseases, there have been many cases of many diseases going dormant for years and re emerging years later. It may well be that the disease did go away and there was a correlation between going to a church and being cured of the disease this may be a result of factors like the lifestyle you are recommended to live out. Or you changed your lifestyle and it only happened to correlate with your coming to Christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 05:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to a semantic black hole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 03:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ben Shapiro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 07:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a bit cynical. Possibly has some truth to it. But my question was more about the philosophy of what mathematics actually is. Formalism, structuralism, logicism. That kind of stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Orthodox Philosophy of mathematics? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 07:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was just curious to what is considered the orthodox philosophy of mathematics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 07:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obviously. Do you really need to point that out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 05:45:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Half life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 05:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> f

Maybe it needs to be a bit more specific. But then again it does kind of emphasis the more important qualities of what we consider life. Without adding too many specific categories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 04:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like a more physics orientated definition. That life is a self reproducing low entropy system that create more entropy in the universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 03:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No its not atheism has no tenants or a rule book. Islam does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 11:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On purpose.

Lets start from a baseline for the sake of clarity.

What is purpose, simply put its reason that something is done. The next question is what reasons are there for something to be done, evidence would suggest that survival is the meaning of our lives. Why is survival good then? A reasonable question. Because we want it. Fundamentally you can't really choose to wan't to live you just do. So finding a purpose beyond that seems meaningless. So the question from there is what do you do about this fact. Well its quite convenient to build a morality and a purpose around. 

Define the worst possible state of affairs and the best as maximum and minimum amounts of suffering, for conscious entities. This way you have an objective measure of how good things are. This also means that some moralities are better or worse than others. There are obvious nuances but the idea stands. There is no inherent reason why this is good its just you can maximise your own and in turn others happiness. 

Adding a god really doesn't fix the fundamental issue. You can implement a system of rewards and punishment but it still doesn't change the fact that there is no inherent reason to respect any form of deity nor any other set of rules when talking about the subject in a vacuum . If this statement is correct then either you have to accept this premise and work on this level or deny it.

If you end up accepting that there will be no more fundamental purpose, then you can make your own purpose on the level of what. Not that there was anything stopping you from doing this in the first place.

One reads a book because of the pleasure derived from it, in the short term or in the long term if you are thinking about the future 'good' it may do to learn things from it. 

I don't know you so i don't really know what your goals are. But i would assume that you have some kind of goals in life.

This probably still doesn't fix your problems honestly. Especially because i have absolutely no expertise in the topic at all. But i don't see religion as the only meaningful avenue that a person could  pursue. Not all of these examples are ideal or good long term strategies in the pursuit of fulfilment. 

Ideology devoid of religion.

The study of a particular field. To understand the philosophy of different religions, you said you have had an obsession with them. There are perfectly good reasons to do so, like wanting to understand influence, psychology or simply the enjoyment of the subject. 

The pursuit of pleasure.

 #x200B;

They all seem to be valid purposes to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 10:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Certainty is to an extent an illusion. You can never 100 percent know reality but. But that doesn't mean you can get as close as possible using empirical examination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 10:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Criticism is part of discussion.

I make a point and you defend or you make a point and i defend. And ideally the truth or something close to it is agreed upon. Which happens rarely in my experience but that just an anecdote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 10:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ritual can be separate from what you believe. And i would say you don't really need a religion to give you a routine either. If you wan't to engage in these social activities without a religion there are plenty of communities you can join devoted to many different ideals. And in a sense there is an element of spirituality or at least the feeling that accompanies it. I'm not telling you to give up on learning about religion but if you don't believe it, why have one at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 08:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfection?
Explain vestigial structures, organs that serve no apparent purpose to an organism.
For example the appendix, wisdom teeth ect.

Who said that these structures occurred due to pure randomness, or out of nothing as you put it? Could it be due to a specific set of variables than make it likely to occur. The tree exists due to the process of evolutionary biology that has slowly over many lifespans, adapted somewhat well to its environment. But to the mortal eye it may look or be describes as perfect.
The reason i invoke naturalism, is because it works. Here is the justification for the view of the world, lacking in some detail.

Let us say that we assume that most/all of our knowledge may be wrong. What can be known about the universe? First off we know there at least has to be something what the nature of this is doesn't matter at this point. Well what can we know about this world?
Nothing for certain, as we have a barrier to observing this world, a conceptional one but a barrier none the less. As how do we know that our cognitive faculties or senses at all can give us a picture of what objective reality is. We can approach this one of two ways as i see it. You can Say well that's that we can't know anything, or you can take a practical approach and say if we assume that our senses and cognitive faculties can represent the world whatever it may be. Or more precisely what we are observing.
So if we make these assumptions, and if we don't then reasoning doesn't work at all as any reasoning done is self defeating. How can you prove there is no truth to any extent if there is no truth in that statement.
Then we can observe, and test what our models of reality would entail if they are all explained by the natural as how can you prove anything supernatural, if you could then it would be natural.
The next step is to try and figure out how best to figure out things.
Its the only practical way to view the world and a shoe horned in creator without evince i do not see as a practical insert into a model of reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 07:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly its probably a fundamentally flawed study. 

There is a thing called p hacking. Statistical significance is measured in a p value, which represents the chance that a given effect is completely by chance and is written as a proportion of 1. So 0.05 p value means that there is only a five percent chance that a given effect is merely by chance. P hacking is when researchers purposely manipulate data to get a certain statistical significance.

There are some methods for doing this. One is to collect data until you get enough of a p value and stop when you have. Another method is to test as many response variables as possible. Post analysis dropping or merging certain treatment groups.

As well as this statistical significance does not mean causality nor does it imply the strength of a correlation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 07:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why does everything need a creator?

Also about logic.

Logic is a formalized language that is used to remove ambiguity and to come to necessary conclusions  from an initial conditions. Think mathematics as a great example.

Nothing about my statement is illogical. It may contradict your belief that a universe needs a creator but i make no such assumption.

It could be completely self contained and to say something has a creator is meaningless.

 If you don't buy that time is special and is simply like another spacial dimension. Causality seems to come about do to emergent properties of statistically governed system.  On a quantum scale the past and future are meaningless concepts just like pointing to a region of space and saying it was before another. What if space had an asymmetry and you lived though it temporally. Would you then conclude that this space had to start somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 06:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure a painting without a painter would not know it's painters intentions either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 02:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First off your claim that the fbi can't be wrong or dishonest or their leader is an appeal to authority.

Second alot of the ideas that you put forth involve a world view that presumes that group identity is the ultimate factor that determines a person. I see this as a problems when the group identity used is not representative of their ideology. For example it is true that females are as a rule more neurotic and generally higher in agreeability.  Its a spectrum that means that the most disagreeable woman will be more agreeable than the most disagreeable man. So there is a difference between these groups psychologically but it isn't as definitive as you make it sound. But this seems to generally manifest itself in pay, one explanation of the gender pay gap that doesn't involve the patriarchy, and interest in certain fields. Ok if we assume gender does not work then we may have to use another metric. Lets say, class. Is class a good indicator of a persons character?  I would say no.

Its still unspecific. With a large distribution of beliefs. Not a useful category to put people into definitively.

You assume that a black person can't represent a white person and a male can't represent a female. Based off this same first view. 

Approximately 70 percent of Americans are white. So about 35 percent of them are white men. Does this mean that 70 percent of government positions should be filled with white people and 35 filled with white men when the numbers of people who are competent are not directly correlated to these numbers due to normal variation and simply interest in a certain field? 

Yes people of minorities have felt disenfranchised, but that still doesn't excuse your aggressive attack on white males. 

Claiming that white men in history has little to do with today's demographic. Using it as a tactic to shame an entire group throughout history. Or to give victim-hood, is irrelevant to what is happening now. 

And then you wonder why emo teens who feel thrown out from the world go out and take their hate out on everyone. I'm not claiming this is the only or even primary cause, i simply claim that the view is not constructive. Look at the subsets of these groups as well.

Just to point out, I'm not pro-trump. I'm not american so i don't feel so strongly about him,  but i do see the issue of his scientific illiteracy, his denial of climate change ect. But to make a large easy scapegoat isn't a constructive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 06:19:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You forget non local hidden variables. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 05:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm certainly not promoting defeatism and cursing genetics or society ect. And not claiming to be accused of it either. Something that appears self evident to me is that that hard work is a trait, you don't earn the ability to work hard, it is simply exists. 

I do see the practical application of telling people to get their act together, it may, or may not help but in theory promotes people to change. But i certainly disagree wit the point that getting people into action is more important than what is right or wrong. 

To start my objections about this premises i will have to see if we agree on some fundamental premises.

 First that there is an objective reality and that this can be known, As if we do not accept this premise then  we must conclude that truth does not exist, which in of itself is a truth statement. Even if reality didn't reflect what we observe it is useful to presume that the world has been self consistent and real through time otherwise nothing can be known with any amount of certainty at all. 

Second concept that morality can be objective. It can be objectively measured using an indicator, for this we can use suffering. The maximum possible suffering for all conscious  entities  is considered the worst possible state and the minimum possible suffering for all concision entities is the best possible state. This doesn't mean that any life goal is inherently better or worse than any other. This is to give a measure of effect of actions, otherwise talking about the issue becomes almost meaningless.

If there is an objective morality then that means that there are better approaches than others to achieving good. I would say that being good hearted is not necessarily the road to good. As If your view of reality is deluded, then your judgment of reality must also be. And your actions reflect this fact.   

I will give an example. 

Religion.  I'll use Australia as a case study from the 2016 census. Not the best type of data but it will do to prove a point.

 [https://www.abs.gov.au/AUSSTATS/abs@.nsf/mediareleasesbyReleaseDate/7E65A144540551D7CA258148000E2B85](https://www.abs.gov.au/AUSSTATS/abs@.nsf/mediareleasesbyReleaseDate/7E65A144540551D7CA258148000E2B85)  

Approximately 50% of the population is of a christian denomination. 30% report not identifying with a religious belief the rest are made up of  other religions making up the rest like Islam, Buddhism and Hinduism.

Let us assume that most of these people are good people, lets define this as the want to do good in the world. If morality is objective which stems from the idea that there is an objective reality then one must assume that by the presence of other ideas half or more of them must by definition be wrong, this is assuming that each theistic group or atheistic group agrees internally as a whole which is near certainly wrong.

If we accept this then we can take it further and look at the effects of people's beliefs that are objectively wrong and their moral consequences. 

For instance look at the deniall of evolutionary theory. Which on the face of it seems an amoral topic, but if you want to have people live in prosperity which as a rule for humans does increase happiness to a baseline level. These evolution denialists probably believe that they are combating stupid beliefs, that are corrupting the education system.  This specific issue manifest itself in the USSR and Maoist as the idea of evolution and natural selection were not good for propaganda as it sounds much better to say that there will be an increase in productivity next year instead of ten years time. There were also claims that evolution was capitalist propaganda, these ideas lead to further starvation and more pain.  Denial of the truth in this case in the short term at least has been shown to be immoral.

 [https://www.cell.com/current-biology/comments/S0960-9822(17)30949-1](https://www.cell.com/current-biology/comments/S0960-9822(17)30949-1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 02:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe fault isn't the word. They are equally morally culpable by your original premise, if you follow the logic of the statements, which is they are not. 
I'm not promoting full on egalitarian ideas. Simply that a more practical approach should be used when talking about these matters. 

And  secondly that the proposed concept of a great man is not a particularly useful one, if you are attempting to make a distinction between high achieving individuals and most other people, the ability to change yourself also mean you can change yourself for the worse and remove 'free will', if you believe in it at all.

In a later comment i attempted to put forth evidence that there is no physical evidence to believe in this divide and that a better predictor success in society is needed, and used. Like psychological traits, that lead to success like openness, conscientiousness, neuroticism ect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 01:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was a point.

If it is in a great man's nature to control or reshape them-self and people can't be be faulted for how they are, then a great man cannot be faulted for being great. And further, if you use this concept then a great man can become a normal person, but not the other way around.

It was an attempt to undermine the gap in moral culpability between those who had unfortunate circumstances and are given leeway and people who achieve great things. As its not a geniuses fault by your prior definition that they have reshaped them self and achieved great things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 01:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As i see it you are admitting that the predictive power of your arguments is limited due to it being solely based on anecdotal evidence. You are basically admitting that your advice may be bad. Or at the very least not generally applicable.

I never said that mathematicians, philosophers or physicists sit around and think. A lot of being a physicist is sitting around and waiting for a computer to compile. I am saying that abstraction is an important skill that should not be waved over as useless. Unless you can accept idea's like relativity in time and inherit uncertainty and different geometries of space time, even vacuum energy. 

 Apart from the fact that 'living in your head' as you call it is enjoyable is a factor in wanting to do it, you assume that no one can enjoy doing it and live a so called balanced life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 05:45:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe their influence is not evenly distributed. All highly speculative... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 05:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless you want to become a philosopher, physicist or a mathematician. Anything that involves abstraction at all. Hell even, social scientists.

Thanks for the life advice cunt.

Can't make a good case so lets just tell them that they are wasting their time debating me. That's obvious now, isn't it?

You're either a Normie fagot or Bait, either way go fuck yourself, with your psudo-philosophical life advice and vapid quotes. I can't speak for everyone but i say your dogma is insufferable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 04:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Survivor bias.

People who try to be noteworthy but fail miserably, you don't talk about those people. Not to dissuade people from trying to do anything, but it is a bias that manifests itself.

But this is a divergence from the original point which you still refuse to acknowledge which is that trying hard is not someones fault, i refuse to unevenly distributed culpability. A criminal who does something wrong, is no less culpable for his actions than a person who changes the world is. You seem to think that trying hard is this undefined force that differentiated great people from those who are not so great.

I refuse to give working hard a free pass. The same as someones physical strength nor their intelligence. All of these can be explained by external and internal factors satisfactorily. Without using some ambiguous and needless un-predictive free will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 04:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But what he does is determined by what he is, its not independent of their nature. And also from chance.

You are simply stating that noteworthy people are noteworthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 04:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A human is a highly complicated system that is adaptive. Peanut butter is not. 

Also You didn't answer my question.

I'll put my point differently.

I'll use your example of a  "great man".  If a great man can't be faulted how he is. And his ability to change himself is part of how he is and not some supernatural distinction between a great man and an ordinary person. Then we must conclude his ability to change his defined nature is also not his fault. Furthermore this should also mean that a great man should be able to redefine himself into a not so great man.

I don't believe in such a distinction between a great man and an ordinary man. Due to a lack of evidence for such a claim. there have been no such distinction that have been obvious between so called "geniuses" and rob who does your plumbing. There has never been such a distinct difference observed. From dissections of brains there have been no clear structural differences between proclaimed genius and the everyday person. Similarly no such un-nuanced distinctions have been proven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 03:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the shaping of one's own existence is already determined by their own existence. So how can someone be faulted for not changing their existence because of their existence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 03:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does the Heisenberg uncertainty principle violate determinism?

As far as i know only certain interpretations of quantum physics loose quantum information. It is simply a result of adding of waves. And is the fundamental limit to the know-ability if the system.

I would argue that none of this actually matters to the argument at hand. I would say that free will and the argument for or against it has no need to be brought into the physical. I see the problem as the assignment of culpability. If a process is random or not has little baring on the quality of culpability of a person, free will is simply an ambiguous concept that is used to allows people to assign guilt status to people, be it emergent from biochemistry or not. 

Call it a black box where free will is the process and actions are the result if it were random, if that's even possible or not, it is still attributed to the person. If it is defined still attributed to that person. 

Example, if a rock were thrown, is it it's own fault?

If it there is randomness involved then does it now have it's own free will? If not does that actually change how you treat the rock?

Is a consciousness a defining factor of free will? If so how does being able to experience one's actions change how they play out? 

If it does change the way they occur haven't you just pushed the problem back a level? How do we know your consciousness is control of it's actions? What ever control actually mean, maybe its simply just an experience.

I would say this is a bad question. Do we have free will? A better question would be how we should act given the nature of the brain, with some underlying goal in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 02:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good thing government mechanics have been confirmed.  You can now implement basic policies, like giving more power to your lords in distributing land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 02:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They can recruit in towns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 02:29:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Using this you can as easily conclude that good things are also not the products of one's worth. If you accept this then it all comes down to practicality. I don't see a distinction between people knowing what most people see as wrong and right and not caring as it is just as much of a product of circumstances as the other. I say don't stop empathizing with people with people at any point, but instead do what is practically needed to make thing acceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 07:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> f </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 07:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP is saying that people he doesn't like should have a heart attack?

# RACIST </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 06:50:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think he's asking for the numbers. Not a personal anecdote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 03:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If we are talking about justice, we probably should be talking practically. If you can show that light is changing thing for the general better, and not our own personal idea of what is right and wrong. But societies as a whole. I would argue that lights 'justice' doesn't meet the scientific rigor required to prove that what is being done is effective.

Sure crime rates are down, but there may be several reasons for this and not directly because light has been killing criminals. Obviously its an anime but historically harsh punishment has not been an adequate deterrent for criminal activity, one interpretation of this is that people who commit crimes don't do so out of a rational frame of mind. Be it from substance abuse, a mental disorder or simply a lack of empathy. If this is so, I would be curious to know the effect of Kira's purges on repeat offences, which i could plausibly see as going down significantly, to around zero i might say.  But i personally find it hard to believe light has decreased the amount of beating your wife over the head with a golf trophy type crime or of desperate person stealing.

Also lights regime has some resemblance of ideas in Stalinist Russia. As mikami has their spokesman say, forgot her name, they wanted to punish the lazy and unproductive, and light comments that it is too early for that. In Russia it was considered industrial sabotage to fall behind your wonk quota when working in a factory. As far as i know light hasn't by the end of the manga/anime implemented any pro-ideology pseudoscience like that of the soviet union and Maoist china, with agricultural science being completely backwards due to Lysenkoism. But he does share an authoritarian approach to the truth, him being the infallible judge of those who have been even accused of a crime.

Yet I can also see the appeal in his world view, with a justice system that seems to value ad hawk rationalizations of evidence to prove a persons innocence or guilt and of two people being payed to try to change the truth, and have a vested interest in winning as apposed to finding the truth, but a god of death, one who clearly doesn't actually investigate who is guilty or innocent and simply kills without restraint, doesn't seem a solution to this systemic issue.

It also does not permit any kind of nuance, which is bad if you want the truth. Which gives people more tools to manipulate reality and make the world a better place.

I don't think there is anything wrong with you, I think there is a problem with kira's ideology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 09:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was being inconsistent. I first stated what method i believed OP was using. Then answered the second question without the context of the first.

We were not using the same standard.

My answer would be lack of attention. It would be more correct to say i wasn't answering your question.

 #x200B;

I would say that most people like the products of existing. Not the act of existence itself. Non existence is simply the absence of experience thus it is amoral. Like existence. Existing requires someone to have priorly existed meaning they can have tenancies, and people tend to like to exist, so the act of going from existing to not can be considered bad. Not the simple act of not existing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 11:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say the standard deviation of what people want is fairly large. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 08:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on the system. There is ambiguity here. In an ideal world parenthesis would explain every part but they don't, so you have to follow an order of operations. Without this system this would be a horrible equation. It still is. Because people are getting it wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 08:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We should conclude that most people think so. If this statement is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 07:17:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would guess that they are going from baseline human tenancies. What most people would agree about. Not wanting to suffer. Doing as your desires mandate how you act. Most people don't derive pleasure from being stabbed so then being stabbed is bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 07:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its also very possible that a great being is sadistic and created us for that purpose. Or that no great being did anything ever. What does a great being who "loves us" have to do with the fact that suffering still exists. I don't feel obliged to think about this being purpose for me, and its definitely not a rebuttal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 07:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of the evidence is correlational. There is a statistically significant link between social media use and self reported mental heath problems. The correlation is moderate but no causal relationship has thus far been shown between the  use of Facebook or twitter and other social media platforms and mental health issues. So it can be interpreted either way, as being a coping mechanism or actually causing mental health problems. I would say Its most likely both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 06:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> usually play hos first. Blood and wine raps up everything well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 06:15:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope it gets better later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 05:38:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good ending? What good ending? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 05:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you tried most of the obvious fixes?

Validating game files updating graphics card drivers, going into files and messing with the in game settings. Re-installing it, usually not very useful.

edit: its kind of unclear the exact issues in the photo, you may wish to clarify. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 05:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also it not the final fight. There are about 10 more main story quests to do. Some of them are parts of another main story quest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 05:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a cat herding SIM, mid- late game anyway. Want to go on a campaign? Nope, king Harlaus is feasting. Want to manage a fief? Nope, entire enemy faction are raiding your village, have come from the other side of the map, just for you. And still feasting. AI is basic at best retarded at worst. Easy to cheese, tactics and strategy once you actually have money. Still a great game, and end game is bearable with mods. Banner lord on the other hand, you'll be waiting a very long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 05:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure they said they planned to release on pc. Then think about console later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 03:52:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus the fact that Germany had basically no oil so had to heavily rely on other sources for domestic use, like hydro-electric. Definitely a climate change hero. Unlike the evil communists who burnt oil for the hell of it near Stalingrad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 03:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A good story, horrible science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 03:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The enclave are the good guys. If you think killing everything on site is a good thing. Done. Rectum protected, you argument is redirected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 06:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They can be handled well. Like in the original doom, with the shotgun soldiers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 04:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have fun in the absence of any experience after death.  

Or have fun in Hel with the ice cold.

Or have fun being a beetle in your next life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 04:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A good ideology if you value the truth should be as simple as possible and have the highest predictive power for that simplicity. This way you cut down on unfounded assumptions meaning you can be closer to the truth.  I personally value the truth, or as close as one can possibly get to it as it allows one to predict and control one's environment which from a human perspective, is usually useful and sometimes uncomfortable. To rate a view of the world on how much you need to work to explain out of thin air, seems counterproductive if you assume that people wan't to prosper.

Naturalism, or the lack of belief in the supernatural and belief in the natural laws, so far has had enormous power. if we accept this philosophy and assume that the laws of physics apply to the past as well as the future then it is not possible for many religions claims to be true, or they are impossible to disprove on account of their ambiguity. for example Noah's arks proportions would not actually work. If you decide to take a "non literal" approach then how can anyone disprove your claim that there is some being somewhere that we can't satisfactorily test the existence, you really can't. Or for example horoscopes that tell you that something good will happen to you some time, any prediction can be interpreted as a positive. I'm sure if there were a hyper specific prediction which has proven to be correct, but its hard to rule out chance in these cases as so many hyper specific predictions have been made that its highly likely that one will have been near correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 03:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you wan't to be an engineer having a high iq is a useful property. To work in healthcare is a different story. Emotional intelligence is a buzzword. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 03:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who said anything about Copenhagen interpretation, there are equally valid others like many worlds or pilot waves. Unsatisfactory results doesn't mean your right, just means your uncomfortable with some of the results. 

Also what do you mean by a hard line atheist? 

Do you mean no deity of any description can ever exist? 

Proving something is impossible. You can get 100 correct but you still can't be sure your right, always room for skepticism. As far as i can see it its extremely unlikely that any form of deity exists but i can't prove that none exist only that their are inconsistencies in certain beliefs, especially if you are being ambiguous about your concept of deity and i have nothing to disprove. 

If this is your description of a hard line atheist you don't need quantum physics to see the issues with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 01:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough. My point was that asking if something is normal and caring what is normal are two different affairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 07:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who said anything about normal? 

And what make "reality" so important? Apart from the fact it can fuck you over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 07:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That implies some inherit moral structure. I say to hell with it. The guy can spend his time how he likes and can define what important is. But one intends to min max one's time on total war focus at work and eating well will probably be better in the long run as dying is a bit of a handy cap.  Same with the sleep. Emotions are another thing to take into consideration as if you intend to optimize being irrational and tire aren't a great plan, not sure if dumping "that hoe" is the right strategy. Have to consider the long run as well as the short term. You may have to be prepared for unforeseen consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 03:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't mine at night minecraft gf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 06:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can never reach the speed of light as inertial mass is the property defined as the resistance to movement and is a property that emerges from energy. No such thing as 100% efficient, other than an matter anti matter annihilation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 05:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Galilean transformation is wrong. The closer you get to the speed of light the more energy is needed to increase the speed. The object would still loose energy, from radiation due to the statistical nature of objects and the inherit uncertainty quantified by the Heisenberg uncertainty principle, means matter will create radiation. and loose energy from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 05:47:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 939 annoying to play or play against. I personally think 939 isn't the most enjoyable scp to play as but is useful as it's tracking ability alows hypothetically for  teamwork to occur, for example flanking the other team, and the speaking ability is great for the memes. He is more of a support scp than anything. 

I think to truly evaluate the quality of the scp you can't judge it in a vacuum, so when played with team mate it can work well with almost all of the other scps. Being a bit less useful when with 079 who already has tracking abilities.

Playing against 939, is my favorite quality, you need to employ stealth to beat him, as shooting 939 increases their speed, meaning you have to play it smart and respect the power role of the game, the scps, that is unless you are part of an mtf or chaos mob on surface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 06:27:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Invade them

 #x200B;

 #x200B;

 #x200B;

Seriously if you intend to improve relations you can simply join another faction that is at war with them then instantly leave it. If i remember correctly this should default your relation with the faction. I don't think you even need to join a Waring faction. If you want to increase relations with the towns or villages then do the boring quests. Honestly though i don't know why you would bother improving relations with them.

I don't know much about it i usually don't find raiding enemies worth it, long term. Relations with villages in the region you want to recruit troops from is what matters relations wise. Otherwise become Honorable. And get those free relations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 04:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't forget about having bastard children. That would be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 02:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Give them all differently aged children so anytime they die they have children who are nearly old enough to become a lord. Not too many but enough so if you go on a killing spree they have replacements. Would also be interested to see if there are characters without children who you would wan't to inherit their land. Probably go to big old king though. Maybe if they are still dying off, the AI could recruit mercs like you to minor noble positions. To fill in the vacancies.

 #x200B;

If clans are your family then minor members of clans who have no land could be promoted to the position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 06:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm frugal i probably would wait a year in agony anyway for a good sale Epic store or no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 04:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Evidence?

My anecdote won't change it but i would just like to claim that i like the crusades because it is an interesting dynamic. Historically anyway. The geopolitical motivations, the internal rivalries and of course the peoples crusade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 04:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah its still an anecdote with very little predictive power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 04:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The problem with these types of debates, or should i call them shit shows, is that nothing is quantified, without numbers and a view on the actual scale of the proposed issue nothing useful gets said. You can say there is a lot of players have one opinion or probably not many but it won't make any conclusion. Anecdotes and other low level evidence won't fix the issue. You can find an idiot with most kinds of opinions, across the whole spectrum of possible ideas. Then at least we can bitterly argue and possibly just misunderstand each other with horrible sample sizes, correlation connections, digging for correlations over several variables and good old conflicts of interest.

Because i don't know the truth can be abstract. It can go against our confirmation bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 04:16:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> with mods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 03:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shameful periods seem  to me have interesting dynamics. Political upheaval, war, possible genocide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 03:47:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not as if you don't have westerners who wan't to white wash history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 03:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Objectively? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 03:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They confirmed this would be a feature i don't remember when. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 04:46:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The tutorials are part of the game play. Would you advocate removing any content between the start of a level and a boss battle because the concepts can be explained by a pop up tutorial. Because the game designers could be spending their time doing the more important stuff. We don't need to test the player mastery of each game  mechanic lets just throw them strait into a boss rush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 04:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The game already runs like ass... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-03 11:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think light cares about being pragmatic. His morality only makes sense with some arbitrary concept like free will to justify the punishment. I Don't believe anything is justified and i don't think lights methods would even be effective at crime prevention so he is just a killer. Kira states that he forgives people who never meant to kill, are genuinely sorry ect. If i remember correctly which shows that he puts the responsibility on the people. As it was either not their decision or they were not themselves. Which to me seems stupid as no one chooses to be be born the way they are virtuous or not.

I also do not believe in the concept of good or evil in a metamoral sense. I am not against killing people, inherently but it is a tool like any tool is to be used when necessary. Honestly the most i think light would actually end up doing would be destabilising the world, both economically and politically, and kill a lot of people. He is clearly a threat to political figures. And has killed board members of the yotsuba corporation and from the public's perspective kira followers on the TV show kira's kingdom. It would suffice to say this would not be good for business. Not to mention radical cults who worship kira are also a problem.  He hasn't irradiated crime either, sure he killed off clearly guilty members of the mafia but like L mentions, he hasn't irradiated 'professional' criminals. Deterrent for being caught historically hasn't stopped people from committing crimes, people  who aren't in their right mind, tired, drunk, hungry aren't going to stop to think of the consequences, they can't, their prefrontal cortex has effectively shut down.

I could also image kira getting to the point were he ends up killing people like African warlords and the like. Which would just create more of a power vacuum. In places of present instability.  

I do not see him as evil inherently, no one is in my eyes not Hitler, Stalin, Mau, Mussolini, genghis khan ect.  but i think his actions are not helping the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 01:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> we need a sub dedicated to simply bannerlord when </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-27 01:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's why you get there early. If you know mtf are spawning head to spawn before they get down the elevator, or wait in heavy. You don't have to be constantly moving, you are disadvantaged when doing it.

A buff would be nice i agree with that but it wouldn't be gameplay wise very interesting, a difficult counter play is basically a Nerf but really a buff other classes which is different from a nerf it's different not necessarily much worse for peanut but is better for say facility guards who at the moment, to me at least, are one of the least interesting classes in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-24 05:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Peanut is really good at playing stealth. You can sneak behind enemy lines and attack your unsuspecting prey from behind. I don't think the NUT is the best SCP but if played right you can case significant damage to an enemy team. Much like larry if misused is almost useless. I don't think it would make peanuts main advantage worse which would be devastating it would just make a 'frontal assault' less advisable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-24 05:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would give him more gameplay variety. But probably make him a bit harder.

But then again a bit easier as if MTF were insensitived enough to bring the nut to surface zone then it gives you a second chance. Instead of just being mobbed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-24 05:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Three words light containment decontamination. I don't see how this would work better than a containment cage.

There would be basically no way to get peanut to go back into his room and be trapped. How is the Peanut incentivised to go back to its containment cell? How does it benefit game play? Larry is incentives to play more cautiously and check back up at his containment cell.106 has additional conditions he has to be mindful of and can actually use it to his own advantage by setting up an ambush for players trying to recontain him. Personally i think there should be a higher barrier for recontainment, like a parkour challenge or something. There is no incentive for peanut to hang around the spawning area and if you could lock 173 in its own room it would be nearly no different from locking the NUT in somewhere like the armory before decontamination. If there were some reason that peanut would stay near its room , probably the gun that sometimes spawns, and follow a player in it may have a chance of working but I'm guessing people would simply ignore the opportunity.

With the containment cage Peanut is already incentivised to hunt down players so a trap would add an interesting gameplay element and give player a reason to not just simply run from the SCP but actively try to capture them and then bring them to the surface. And also give the player a bonus objective of protecting their room if say the cage was found in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 13:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SCP secret laboratory

Can't think how it is any way like mount and blade but a fun game if your into asymmetrical horror games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 03:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bumping the cage could work a bit like in Dead by Daylight's struggling mechanic when a survivor has been captured by the killer. Obviously not a bar to fill before being able to escape but being able to push the cage into walls. Possibly also hurt people standing too close to the cage and break a hole in it over time. For example every time people blink or if unsupervised quite quickly.  Maybe the cage being bumped could make an obvious sound and it hitting the wall could make more noise. Possibly could damage escorts with the cage trying to run into them. And other scps could free them by holding e for a certain amount of time while looking at it, idk 20 seconds or something. Maybe the cage could be acquired from peanuts holding cell with a containment engineer card possibly something lower as Light containment decontaminates after 10 minutes. So peanut could protect it like larry and his holding cell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 03:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think difficult re containment would make the game much more interesting as it increasingly incentives conflict with the SCPs. Instead of just running away and hiding from SCPs players might actively track them down. If they did this they could buff the SCPs not with more health but with more functionality, like for example make 106 be able to make more than one 'portal' for lack of any lore friendly words, to balance it. I also think if re containment was added for 173 it would have to be difficult to pull off if no buff happens. For example having to set up the cage before hand and turn your back to lure the SCP in. Or maybe you have to slowly drag the cage at it while a friend looks at and shoots at peanut.

But i agree the dev's probably won't add in this functionality unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 01:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you better be ready to wait a very long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 12:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Larry isn't that effective of a killer if they change the pocket dimension he should be less lethal. So a buff like no slowing through doors, a buff that would probably be boring, wouldn't be too bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 05:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think that would work. The whole point of the doctors illusions are to show were the survivors are. Not to make the survivor think the killer is near them. In a confined space like the facility it just wouldn't work.

The only way i could see it working would be if an illusion would spawn far away so it may be hard to tell if it's an AI or a player and have it leave you vision quickly.  But not last long and have the sound of it continue on.

Region specific sounds could play, for example if the 'illusion' is near a Tesla gate you can hear and see it go off. And door sounds should play in the time it takes to get to a door but have some random variation in the times between sounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 05:38:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They did say they didn't plan on doing it any time soon. So i would say some time after the pc release if at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 04:56:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> now nearly 3 an hour later...

 #x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It would be nice if the class choice was less random to make it feel more random </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-23 09:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate ending up as D class 15 times in a row </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-12 22:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe just make it more difficult to get into larries chamber like adding parcore or tesla gates. Just to kill off a few sacrifices to make the decision harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-12 22:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can recruit top teir troops from villages its just unlikely. You mave to increase relations alot though and you get less of them than other troops. I just built a school on my feif and left it. This is after investing in many dyeworks to have enough money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-03 23:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Run, don't die. Try to follow other players unless they have a gun. That's if you are a D boi. If you are chaos insurgency or Mobile task force/facility guard shoot everyone you see. Go to heavy containment and get killed instantly by SCPs. Or just form a firing squad as chaos. As SCP find all targets and kill them except for chaos. Don't get lured into the upgrader room or any armories you cant escape them as SCP.

Edit: or just play ear rape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-20 01:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being a no mike sucks. usually when i try to help new players they don't trust me and get killed. Either that or i get endless lectures about how to play but at least there's good will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-19 00:28:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say he wants to stay on campaign but can't due to lowering relations. Or maybe the count has transcended his prior form to become a godly Butterlord who forces the peers of the realm alike to join him in festivities, Ad Infintium. And like the cheating ai he is has infinite money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-13 23:04:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happens to me often. I just continue to attempt to reconnect until it works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 23:08:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doggos better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 04:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What timezone is the update going to release on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Halloween update when? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 03:40:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard they released the April fools update on the day, if they are with the Halloween update what timezone are they in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 01:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really depends how i feel. But usually SCP. 

Out of the armed groups definitely chaos. 

And D class out of the unarmed groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 04:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also the lockers are dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 01:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then what killed TF2 for its hellish Dev time or all the valve games for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 11:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely flight of the valkyries  


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 03:34:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would not say that they would seriously corrode the experience. Merely that it would be different, the words being used having very little positive nor negative connotation. Having a single player mode or mod wouldn't or isn't the point of the game but is something useful and more worthwhile than not, in my humble opinion. 

I would (or may) give it a go if i manage to feel bothered to do so and I am inclined to believe others possible a few may feel so as well. Be this conclusion from bias born of rigorous self delusion or there actually being a minority or unrepresented group of people of notable size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 04:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would be inclined to disagree with that statement, playing multi player games without people just bots isn't the same but it doesn't mean that its entirely worthless. Especially if you can't manage to make yourself play containment breach being a punishing game for noobs. Not have internet were you are at some time and not wanting to play CB for aforementioned reasons is a situation. Wanting to play the game with no restrictions just playing around with mechanics at your leisure without having to wait around to re-spawn. Practicing with weapons. Just shooting stupid D Class because.

It could be useful like bot servers in some games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 02:20:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just your average day in the laboratory </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 08:42:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just think how bring your kids to work day would go. If you thought D Class were annoying...

https://preview.redd.it/o5ok197193t11.jpg?width=1920 format=pjpg auto=webp s=86383db44aa53bea3a53a7f168a7ee13bca50877 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 03:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SCP's and teamwork in a sentence are a joke.

And no a conga line doesn't count.

Also SPS's are lazy and don't get easy kills from checking airlocks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 09:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No that is not entirely correct, it is 'ripped' from Containment breach but it was based off the g mod game mode. But in general want to swap out assets to distinguish themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anti cheat a bit too active </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 08:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Larry always wins

https://preview.redd.it/i6uvj4n72ws11.jpg?width=1920 format=pjpg auto=webp s=c0c0f8a89fceb798211d0f46aa9fde7c4ff25c3c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 01:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> only on certain servers. Also it still goes to help chaos if you do that as NTF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 01:03:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like it but.

You may wan't to add another colour to balance out the general design. Probably at the another end of the colour wheel like a dark blue Or even a light grey blue like on the foundation site. I can tell you are trying to mimic the foundation and you can do that but you could use creative liberties to make your site look better with the same overall feel or colour pallet as the SCP foundation website.

Also you could add a background to your website or add some more colour to it. You may also wish to add some borders to some of the elements on your web site.

I have some other suggestions that may work but would only be easy to implement if using CSS as well as HTML, PHP ect. Which if this is a first project is probably just on HTML, speaking from experience.

You could also spend some time perfecting the distances between sections of your page.

On another note you need a section dedicated to peanut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 03:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not always, with a quick wit and a good quality microphone can get you a way. No mic's are usually the first to die. 

On a friendly fire server people can enact vengeance for you dead comrades or for war crimes committed by over zealous guards. A mic is even more important for these servers.

 #x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 01:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheating is too my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 01:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One person didn't know that you can trigger him by looking from behind. Well at least no one would know, as they were averting they eyes from the unearthly presence before them, distracted by nothingness before their untimely departure. Don't worry he were fated for the Tesla gate, there is truly karma no matter how slow it may be. Whether it be in the form of probability or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 00:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Simple hide. "i just kept crawling and it just kept working"- Jerry. 

SCP's just walk past you if you hide in the airlock door things. They just wait for you to come to them. SCP's shouldn't be so easy but people don't seem to look very hard. 

Closing doors isn't the best idea all the time, sometimes not closing doors and leaving it ambiguous to which direction you are headed in. Closing doors just leaves a trail strait towards you. Its called mind games. Closing doors can be advantageous but you limit your options as well as the SCP's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 00:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not one to hate on try hards nor friendlies, people generally aren't one or the other. Also there is a solution, a server with friendly fire. A solutions none the less just a costly one. And people don't grenade spam too often on these servers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 09:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Khergits can choose their battles due to quick map movement speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-04 04:16:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy wars!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 04:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also that happened to me. It would skip the unity menu and just jump into the game. I did nothing and it fixed itself, maybe it was a patch. The game would start after a wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 04:06:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not your screen size. It fits the specs.

And i have no idea what you actually mean by your C++ wrong. When all else fails blame windows and update graphics card drivers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 01:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do think part of the shooting D-class/Scientists is ignorance, as people don't realize that you can bring them back to join your team, as the game simply tells you to terminate everyone except your extraction target. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 01:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that breakable props could add to the game's feel. Except for the 12 year olds going round shooting them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 05:09:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be an operating system update but i doubt it.

You could try updating your Graphics card drivers.

I also doubt it could be fixed by waiting a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 09:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://pcgamingwiki.com/wiki/SCP:\_Secret\_Laboratory](https://pcgamingwiki.com/wiki/SCP:_Secret_Laboratory)

It tells you the compatibility of the game including the screen resolution

I doubt its res or your hardware i know someone who has a gt 720 and runs the game barely on lowest graphics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 08:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this was after downloading the game? No settings touched?

What is the resolution of your screen?

More context please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 06:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you tried going into task manager closing the game from there and restarting the game. I have had a problem were steam games refuse to appear on screen yet they are running. And restarting the steam and opening the game doesn't work. That's what it sounds like you are describing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 02:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If its removed then its removed its it was a bad idea or badly implemented, it can be reverted.

I'm not asking for absolute proof. I'm asking to see this proof. Your proof seems biased. For instance the survivors bias may apply to this situation. The people who complain are more likely to be taken into account than people who do not. How could you listen to non existent comments? 
This phenomena is commonly applied to old buildings. Some people think that old architecture is more useful, more reliable and more beautiful but the thing is all the ugly useless stuff has already rotted over time. Celebrities. (This one is quite ironic) I had an English teacher in school who would often quote how all the the people who advocated change were shot, JFK, john Lennon ect. After readying the book I AM MALALA. He failed to recognize all the advocates for change who had not been shot or even received gregarious bodily harm. Who had lived relatively un sensational lives and had since been forgotten being a boring story. The ones who died were remembered, the product of the survivorship bias. I prefer the nearly get killed and write a semi autobiographical book and naturally make a shit load of cash.
 
It's not a class picker. You choose preferences. A set spawn and preferences. Possibly could be a combination of both reverse and preference system. I don't know if it will work, I have no illusions to such a thing. Using similar empirical evidence to yours there are an unrepresented group of people playing the who obviously aren't vocal or alternatively who ignored who do enjoy playing classes other than d who do main killer in games and would do so as SCP:SL. 

I doubt the system will do nothing, just in the hypothetical situation that you had added, it will have done no harm to the game with maybe a possible amount of dissatisfaction with the system. If there are people who are contrarian which will almost always exist. The statistically unlikely will be likely to happen in a large enough data set this is simply based on statistics.
It will have done something. Meaning someone will get their first choice and someone else won't get their last choice. A win win situation for both parties involved. More than two parties as if one person wants to play one, say SCP, if everyone else doesn't want to play it they won't end up playing it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 03:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does that mean it shouldn't be tried.
It would achieve higher player satisfaction than now. Giving a small amount of agency to the player. Not everyone will be happy. 
It could of course be a reverse preferential system. Meaning you may not expect the class you really wan't to play as but you can clearly get not get the ones you don't wan't.

 I for one wouldn't wan't to play D Class every single game or scientist. 
I know some people who would most likely try to only play SCP being killer in other games like Death Garden and Dead by daylight.

The game will still vary. It is designed to do that. The facility is randomized and spawn counts and types are varied. So players can't stay on the same team every single round of the game. If everyone had the same choice nothing will change. People may just complain more that they didn't get their choice. But if someone does want something different they will get it. 

Also UNIVERSALLY DISLIKED. You haven't proved that. There are a lot of I think. You do not know this, you have no evidence to support this idea. This is purely the grounds of hypothetical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 01:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's called the wonderful world of modern medicine...

I mean optimization.  We can only hope.

 #x200B;

On a serious note, games can have large servers. Even optimization messes the likes of SCP:SL. Mount and blade Warband (a great game), in its Napoleonic wars DLC, has 100 v 100 battles and that game is an indie game that somewhat badly optimized.  It handles them quite well. There is hope in time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-28 05:19:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A preference system would mean that you had preferred class or SCP it doesn't mean you will get to play as them its just a preference to who you play the game still chooses what teams spawn. And what type. It could be the fact that you choose if you are CI, MTF, D class, Scientist or SCP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 07:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We need to declare a holy war. Against those heretics of the Church of Shrek. Or maybe a smaller church that we can purge easily to get some publicity and holly knowledge. Time to steal some memes from their holly vaults. And some holly relics from their merchandise stores. 

If that is too risky we may wan't to begin an inquisition. May be a bit difficult for the church. Too polarizing so i suggest a holy war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 05:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let me guess SCP 096 or Guard with Micro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 04:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Inspired by true events.



A D class. Was in 914 as any good escape story begins. Fled the exit being camped by dog. Fled through air lock doors and hid with fellow scientist in side section. Dog waltzed in. Tension was high. Dramatic utterances were let loose in parting with my scientist friend as i Leroy Jenkinsed my way out, closing the door on dog's face and fled with my key card to the exit gate. The chase was afoot, the veracious mutant following in suit.  I got through the exit doors nearly getting myself eaten. All the wile screeching like the 9 year old I am into my non existent mike, pleas for my life and for a suitable arrangement were i live and my pursuer gains nothing but no return on their investment and a whole lot of nothing sandwich. The elevators were in sight, one was open. I leaped in a semi dramatic manner and slammed the small red button as i had never before, that game. I panted, a pool of sweat slowly building up on my broken, cheap but all american chair. The tension eased with imaginary elevator music lightly humming in my head.  The doors opened re inviting me to the real world once more. I Strolled out in the best manner any D class can hope to achieve. And was invited into the loving embrace of an self respecting Facility Guard. The honest Yankees' trusty bullet.

Truly a Greek tragedy. A story of hope, ambition and all appropriate antonyms to these terms.

The only escape i had received was death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 04:36:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would advocate for larger servers and spawns. The facility seems as if it can hold it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 04:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it really that bad to not win.



In my experience the MTF do half your job for you killing D bois on site sometimes. Chaos kill scientists. Let the factions in fight.

I do believe SCPs should be far more powerful than everyone else. But decreasing spawn size, not really.

What would their role be? Decrease MTF, CI, D Class and scientist only leaves SPCs More SCPs. Who will you kill. More D bois more targets and screams from your prey how can you hate it. It only sucks on small servers were there are very few of everything then hunting becomes a pain. When you are the only SCP anyway. With two you can harness the magical quality of team work. Even in a casual game team work is a concept that exists people, like making alliances and hunting in packs we are heard animals, its natural.

I feel it only honestly sucks when they rush the gate and get into heavy containment. That sucks for all teams. NO challenge, thrill of the escape ect.  Some times it one person escaping sometimes its all of them.  One person escaping isn't that bad as they will probably be mopped up by chaos. I usually call it as my fault if this happens to me as an SCP. If i haven't figured the lay out roughly and got down to light containment quick its my fault. Even if they got extra lucky. I gotta adapt. I find it always more enjoyable to hunt packs more kills. Unless CI or MTF. Then you have to play the thing called "STEALTH" and not run strait into their guns.

SCPs seem to win quite often. I'm going to have to say it. Get good. Change how you play. I try to, I'm not implying i am in a state of 'good' more getting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 01:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The whole point of me mentioning that I'm annoyed about them removing 079. Is because i don't particularly trust people who say it wasn't enjoyable. And it may have been blown out of proportion and have been not as bad as it was eluded to. We are just throwing second had accounts of 079 and have never played him. I would like to have a opinion on it. A preference system would be a feature that would fix this. So they don't have to remove the SCP every time something goes wrong. If it actually does go wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 01:14:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And you could still disregard the 'instruction manual' and do it yourself there is nothing forcing you to learn how to play the game. I played it without a tutorial. And have enjoyed learning the game myself. But it doesn't mean a convenient option shouldn't be added. It does turn some people off and its not like they designed the game not to have a tutorial. I heard they just removed it because it was completely broken. I joined after it was removed. I probably wouldn't have read it if there were one though. But it doesn't mean I won't look into it in the future or go on the wiki. A tutorial is usually preferable to the wiki. And is usually a given.

 #x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 06:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Unless they had a preference system for who you wan't to play as. That seems very much needed. If people didn't want to play him they wouldn't have to.

It could be the fact that the SCP could just take time to understand and enjoy. And quitting early is just the fault of the user and the Devs for having no tutorial. As well as being a completely different game style.

Also the basis was that it may not have been as bad as people make out it to be. If there aren't player statistics you don't really how many people hated playing him. It could be a very vocal minority complaining about 079. And not as bad as it was made out.

Edit: For instance people always complain about hackers and cheater, maybe i just play on well moderated servers, maybe I'm not looking for them, but i have not seen a single hacker. I don't think its the servers i play on as there is rampant mic spamming and the lot. It could be that hacking and cheating is an order of magnitude more important that an ass with a mike and will get you banned on well maintained server. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 00:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To clarify my clarification, one  could be alot more unduely sceptical of the game. This is followed by a dig at no mans sky as it is a useful case study as its is well known and also it did turn out to be a lie. I then clarify that i have made a simmilar extrapolation as you and am not going go full conspiracy theorist as it was meerly a ill choice of words. I honestly don't  want this to become an arguement over semantics. I agree with what you have said. I have watched the specific interview and gameplay footage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 09:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The camel war from the Swadians down under. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 09:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That and the fact that the community has a good wealth of content to meme. That in it's nature is memeish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 09:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you know the mid to late game *exists.* Some companies make separate versions of their game for events like E3. For instance ...



Cough cough

no mans sky

cough cough



For the record, I'm not that much of a cynic, i still have some faith in humanity, i am physical able to put aside my conspiracy theory level scepticism to be able to consider the concept that the game may actually exist. at all. Date. 

 #x200B;

It was merely a bad choice of words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 09:20:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is entirely subject to point of view. Finishing up the game may not necessarily mean that they are going to release it. It could be they have finished the core game play, it could be they have been finishing up the game and then going onto polishing it and it could be they are just holding back to taunt us in this meaningless and empty life. Robbing us of the one meaning left in our hearts, mostly due to a small build up of nostalgia surrounding the game. The one shining star in our dreams, beautiful and serine  sitting there forever in a perpetual state of euphoric bliss. An image of perfection. A radiant being covered in the promise of more. That which must and can never be, yet that which we yearn for so. An amalgamation of all our hopes and dream spontaneous com-busting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 08:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's called people devoid of musicality or musical taste combined with a microphone and an abnormally "youthful" voice, friend. That's what is truly in the game.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 08:46:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would be why they removed it from the game not just updated it. My question is why did they outright remove SCPs and not just rework them and then update them? I joined after 079 was removed and I am curious how boring and confusing it actually was. It seems a bit stupid to just remove it unless it was game breaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 08:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not if you play mind games with your 'prey'. Its really enjoyable then. A bit like playing hag in Dead By Daylight. You get the satisfaction of the surprise motherfucker moment. As you come up from behind them when they are camping the room you just entered. Chasing as 106 seems a bad idea. It doesn't seem the ideal way to play him. So don't play him that way. The only problem with playing Larry like this you are open to being contained while you are not paying attention. But its always a risk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 06:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He also said they had completely polished early game and were going to do that for mid to late game. Either that or mid to late game doesn't exist or exist in a playable state. I believe it is the prior.

Which is hopefully early 2019 release, entirely speculation no substance to that claim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 03:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 982, I am infatuated by the concept of an omniscient jade turtle that tells you what you should have done after the fact and usually at an inconvenient point in time, 6 minutes later. Also may be useful for new players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 03:28:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would guess  they are intending to revamp it in the next few updates. Like the removal SCP 079. Why they couldn't leave it and just update it next time is beyond me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 06:07:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to do it go ahead re-post this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 05:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like it but i feel like it would be a bit like the spy in TF2. Everyone would become paranoid and begin shooting all their team mates as there is no friendly fire (They do this anyway). This would be punished because of limited ammunition as going kill crazy would mean you would have no ammo to kill other teams and SCPs. You wouldn't really be able to insight a witch hunt against any other player like in Trouble in Terrorist town as there is no friendly fire. To re add friendly fire would be hellish, people just love throwing grenades in elevators as it's apparently very amusing without friendly fire. I do see this decreasing as everyone will hate you if you do this but a lone troll could do a "lotta damage".

I see SCP 236 Being most enjoyable if a partial friendly fire system being implemented like in Left For Dead. People generally play by the rules and are usually nice some times people get salty that you friendly fire but if you do carry intentions ill your team mates can kill you. Also it will most likely mean that players will be slightly more careful when setting up a firing line when fighting an SCP. And that a look first shoot second mentality can be better implemented as it could be a team mate down that corridor.

On that note the game needs an item giving and player healing system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ideas for a in game tutorial </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 05:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The game kind of needs a tutorial to ease new players in. SCP 698 (critical turtle) would be a good candidate for this role. Its purpose being to give advice about the objectively correct decision after five minutes of the choice occurring as long as the chooser has stayed in the vicinity of the SCP. This SCP could be giving to a new player or any player as an item that tells them what they should have done. Being part of the game you could naturally throw it away or put it in a lore related sound proof box. It would be very non intrusive.

It may be helpful also for more experienced players who don't know certain specific game mechanics. For instance some lots of players shoot d bois on site despite the fact that if the NTF or FG were to bring them back to span they spawn as the NTF. And I'm relatively sure vice versa. Another example is Larry'c chamber which for the first 16 hours of the game i personally had no idea what it did and just enjoyed watching people kill themselves to it. Mostly captured b bois. Now i just do it for the fun entirely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 03:59:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinking of 939 and got the number confused with 698. Also I'm fairly new to the fandom and still don't really know the names of the SCPs that well.

I'm fascinated by the idea of a patronizing carved turtle. That tells you what you should have done. It would also make an interesting game mechanic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> SCP's Healing rework suggestion </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-20 09:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SCP's seem like they need some form of healing and a skillful manner in which they can heal. I'm not advocating modern war shooter healing with passive healing that removes the stealthy play where you run around looking for health but allows for a come back if they manage to survive their latest encounter. I do not believe that SCP's are overpowered nor should they be under powered the entire thrill of the game is hunting down weaker players or surviving against the odd's, the game is casual and as long as it isn't insanely broken it shouldn't pose too much of an issue.

SCP106

Heals when people take damage in the pocket dimension the longer you linger the more health Larry gets incensing players to move quickly, at maybe a 2 to 1 ratio of healing after the fifty percent damage.

SCP Edit: 939

Can eat dead people, having a maximum amount of people over a period of time, healing a small amount of health every time. Maybe be able to eat 3 people for 40 health per five minutes heals over 5 seconds. It might take time to stop it happening in the heat of battle. Maybe 5 seconds to enact.

SCP049

Heals a small amount when he turns corpses into zombies. Same time as it takes to make a zombie, gains more health than 982 as he can do it less frequently but not much more as his weakness is lack of health. Maybe 50 health regain.

SCP096

Health regeneration on kill for 096 may work. If you have health over time for kills, so that it can't be endlessly spammed. To prolong your life on low health and it should be minimal health maybe 10 health. The main problem is shy guy is played so that you have prolonged periods of nothing punctuated by short periods of rapid action, were you get several kills. I can see it becoming redundant as when you need the health you will get gunned down before you can do anything either facing a large group or versing a single person wise enough to not look at you and shoot you every so often as to not enrage.

Healing over time with a cap might also work. Meaning you heal an amount over time when out of view to a capped amount of health.  But that isn't skill based or particularly enjoyable.

SPC173

Not really sure about peanut. But i do know it sucks to be caught by the chaos insurgency or nine tail fox on low health. You be punished if you run off like an idiot as the peanut and run strait into the firing line but if you escape you should have a chance to recuperate and ambush your enemies.

I'm really not sure about the numbers. Its more about the ideas.

Edit: For non SCP characters the use of a med kit should take a short amount of time maybe two seconds to add a decision between shooting more and healing. As well as this you should be allowed to give items to other players directly and heal other players like in Left for Dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-17 01:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could kind of do this in with fire and sword. You could customize your troops equipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-16 01:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably play as the empire or valandia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-15 02:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first time i played i started off as in the kingdom of nords. Had heard of the game via word of mouth and realy had no idea how to play. I got attacked by sea raiders i think, I quit for some time after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scp 698 concept </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 06:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 04:04:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This has a whole new meaning now.

edit: he really wants his butterlord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-18 10:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Count regas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-07 13:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Join a server, get your ass thrashed, rage quit and go back to single player tail between legs. I do that every time. Then you play Napoleonic wars and play on tropical island server and complain when you get murdered wile playing overly dramatic baroque music for the occasion.

Edit, also GET GOOD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-07 13:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just can't choose any faction but Sturgia can never be bothered with Nords in Warband despite their perks in offensive siege battles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-07 13:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't bother with save and exit it is easily broken, just close the game before leaving an area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 10:27:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For easy doe.

Take quests and rob the quest giver. for instance transporting cattle for the guild master is an easy quest to make money kill the cattle go to the nearest town and sell the meat. The same with a tax collecting quest for a lord, take the money and run. If you don't mind losing relations with lots of NPC's of course.

You could just loot villages early game and ask for a pardon if your relations with the faction are not very low \-3 or so. Just find a border village in a distressed kingdom, most likely Swadia, near Dirhim is a good spot. Or near Halmar after an early game war. Don't bother stealing from villagers. Just loot and burn them if your at the level were you can grind sea raiders. 

If you wan't enjoyment and money don't bother with productive enterprises, they break the game. especially when you have a dye work in every town, you have so much money it's hard to get rid of unless you own a town or castle and an insane garrison and army. It not very enjoyable mid game. And trade is just boring. If you are unaligned and have a reasonably large party bandits wont bother you and you can make easy profit buying from villages and selling at the towns of other factions. As long your not buying meat or expensive goods it easy profit. Grain from Swadia for 3 to 53 or so in the kingdom of Vaegirs. It is most likely only worth it if your in the shit and need money fast. A war has ended and you have an army you don't want to get rid of, trade. I wouldn't spend my time doing it though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-03 08:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just waiting for the Warband graphics and game play overhaul for Bannerlord.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-03 08:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It hasn't gotten that bad yet.  No one had started talking about a battle royal mode. Give it a bit of time and the mount and blade community will eventually emerge from its trance like state of morning and come forth into the world to observe more outdated memes to then un\-intuitively, copy then paste bannerlord onto. Time moves slowly in niche communities so i put my bet right about when this radiant comment graces this corrupted, aids filled thread and in turn this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>