<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6426</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 22:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SP7 has a huge impact on my life too. I watched all of it through and was so sad to see it come to an end but it was a great thing. Thanks for sharing with us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 13:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, good sir or madam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 13:40:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you bob, very cool ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 13:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 13:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 05:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really dig this idea! You wear it so well. The line work is great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 05:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started doing yoga! Ive always like yoga but never committed to actually taking classes. Its doing me wonders, physically and emotionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 05:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More accurately would be running to do all the chores you were supposed to do before she got home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 05:01:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nafenzer, 
We are all here for you. You matter. I dont know your situation at all, and I cant imagine what youre going through, but you are important. You are here for a reason, and I want you to be here. I hope you can find some peace and I hope you pull through this tough time. I hope you are okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 04:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A good idea might might be to have a conversation with her about what both of your intentions are. It might have been unclear to her that since you guys arent dating officially, that what she did was crossing a boundary. If you really like this girl, tell her how you feel and be direct if you want to make things official. Lines can be misconstrued if you dont let your boundaries or wants/needs be known. 

I wish you the best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 20:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> James makes a killer Agent Cooper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jumping on the graduation cap bandwagon. Be nice, I put this together 20 minutes before leaving for graduation. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 06:02:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 09:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second this. Eriksons 8 stages might help you with writing this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Iceberg piece done today by Davey Spataro at Okami Tattoo, Newfoundland NJ </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 04:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 13:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wanting to be as safe as possible does not make this your fault in any way. Seems like she has some issues regarding STDs that she needs to or hasnt worked out yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 12:31:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there anything you can specifically think of that made her turned off by sex with you? I have a feeling that shes just saying that to avoid getting intimate with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 19:00:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you Jakob, very cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 01:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read the title as applesauce ensues. I was confused for a minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 12:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it doesnt pay well at all here in New Jersey either. But its very rewarding :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 02:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im currently a psych undergrad student working in a group home for adults with developmental and intellectual disabilities. You dont need any sort of degree to work in a group home. I basically handle the day-to-day routine stuff with them like showers, meds, meals, etc. If this is what youre looking for, feel free to PM me! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 17:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is amazing. Great job, OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-09 06:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Such an underrated song, I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-01 19:14:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, thats your opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-01 18:17:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt like I was the only one who felt this way! I love Shane and Andrew and his little group. They all have great personalities and will always look forward to anything they post. I havent seen a single person being appreciative about Shane since his new video was uploaded, besides you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 18:45:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 12:11:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was honestly about to say that he hadnt uploaded in a hot minute but then we got BLESSED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 03:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We all know James dyed his hair blonde so he could become the next Slim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 02:24:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alec and I are the same age and I literally look like a 9 year old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 02:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who is this cute little lesbian and why does she remind me of JonTron? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-26 16:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for your input!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-26 16:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats so great to hear. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-26 15:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is very helpful! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Graduate school+ and visible tattoos? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-26 15:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a dumb question, but a serious question. Will having visible tattoos effect someones chances of getting to a grad school program? I have a few that are very easy to hide depending on outfits, but have always planned on getting more. For context, I live in the United States and was hoping to go into clinical psychology. Im about to earn my associates from a two year school and Ill be moving on to a four year university for the next step.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-24 22:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As much as I respect her decision and know that she needs to do whats best for her, I feel like there will be a big piece missing. Autumn is one of my role models and Im so glad to have seen her work and grow like she has. We love you Autumn, never forget that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 13:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theyre super vibrant, I love them too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-22 16:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love all of the songs on b b but my absolute favorites are Stay, Paranoid, Rich and Sad, and 92 Explorer. They all make me feel some type of way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-22 04:38:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I was nearly as awesome and beautiful as Hila is! But thank you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-21 21:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive been told I resemble her except for the eye color! Thank you, thats a great compliment :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My beanie game will never be as good as Ethans, but it was worth a shot. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-21 21:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 20:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, Behind Closed Doors by B. A. Paris had me gripped from start to finish. It dumbfounded me how Jack was always one step ahead of the game. It made me even more paranoid of people than I already am.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 14:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe suggest taking a break? Not totally breaking up but having time apart might help you to see what it is you truly need right now in your life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 04:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ouch!! I hope James takes it easy until its healed up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 04:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RemindMe! 3 days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 15:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh shoot, I meant offensive, sorry about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 15:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, anyone is free to correct me if Im wrong because I could be wrong, Ive been picking up bits n pieces of the story. I think the reason he doesnt want to be on camera anymore is because people were saying really offensive stuff and he was tired of it. He still works there, he just doesnt want to be on camera in bits anymore. 

Edit: offensive, not defensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 14:43:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jakob is one of the funniest guys ever, I miss him being in bits but I understand why he isnt anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 02:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The bottom one is actually Poppy Harlow, get it right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 18:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-10 04:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im getting the black long sleeve cow skull one in the mail on a few days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-07 01:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a psych major right now about to start studying at a 4 year college. My dad keeps urging me to choose a different path as well. I assume its because there is a lot of school that it takes to  get to a career. Theres not much you can do with less than a masters degree. But I think if you really like psychology, go through with it. Thats what Im doing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-04 06:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess for example I always invite friends out because I want them to feel included, but then Ill go on snapchat and see all of them hanging out without me. Dumb stuff I guess. I just want to feel as included as I try to make everyone else feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-04 06:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is what I needed to hear. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-04 06:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why wouldnt someone disappoint me? I guess I just have high skewed expectations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-04 06:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel quite the opposite, as though I need to prove my worth to people in order to feel valid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-02 00:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for your comment, that puts things into a better perspective to me. I dont know why I cant be real with him. Ill be sure to voice my concerns since it wont help either of us if I dont.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-02 00:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to know Im not alone in that sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 03:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what I was searching for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-26 14:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why isnt this on the PewDiePie subreddit? All of his fans are 9 year olds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 11:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 04:39:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know what you mean, and Im really sorry it ended up that way for you. I used to be like that, I had the whole no one would care if I stopped making the efforts first. It weeded out A LOT of people but I have the only people who matter in my life right now. I guess my insignificance feelings are more towards the world/universe as a whole, for example what is the purpose of all of our efforts? I hope things get better for you though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 03:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt mean for that to sound sarcastic at the end  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 03:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im only going to a community college for right now but Im soon transferring to a university, Im scared that thats gonna intensify what Im feeling. Thanks for sharing with me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 14:55:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-16 05:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sounds absolutely traumatic. Im so sorry you had to go through something like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-16 01:02:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Couldnt have said it better myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-13 21:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell him that if he doesnt clean up his act and start treating you like an actual friend and not just a person to borrow stuff from, then you cant be friends with him. This one-sided relationship is toxic and unfair to you. You can find better friends, although it may be tough since you said so yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-10 18:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those PLUMP LIPS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-30 16:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive always just wanted a redo, like if I could just be born again and do things differently. Same circumstances, different choices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 01:10:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So glad I won sprem race </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 01:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scotts Tots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-27 23:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope they do too. If anything, remember even if you have no clue who I am, Im rooting for you to get better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-27 23:54:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think youre being ridiculous, the thugs youre feeling are just. I just think that things can get better if you tell the truth. Youll get the help youre looking for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-27 23:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She wont judge you, this is what shes there for. Shes there to help you get better. And if she does judge you, shes not a fit therapist and you should find a new one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-27 23:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell your therapist. They are trained to make the call whether or not you are a threat to yourself and withholding that information is counter productive to the reason why you are there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-27 12:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend recently got a tattoo with that bandaging on it, I have quite a few tattoos but have never been given that. Id say just trust you artist, they know best.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-26 13:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope this is a joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Watched Christmas with the Kranks at work today. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-25 23:45:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Made me miss the days when Jon still uploaded videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-23 06:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont really know what I was expecting to see after scrolling through that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-20 14:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go for it! He seems interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-07 17:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cursed_Toilet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-06 01:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the exact same way, but I also feel like if I delete these apps Ill be out of the loop with my actual friends. My boyfriend also tags me in a lot of stuff and gets on my case if I dont respond to them. I feel pretty stuck when it comes to social media.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-04 14:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eating disorders and depression are horrible mental illnesses. It is extremely hard for the person with these disorders to just snap out of it and often need psychological intervention. I think the best you can do is support her and try to help as much as you can for now. If and when she gets better, she might realize that she had such a great support system with her this whole time. But these things really do take time. Good luck with everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-01 15:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely think you should keep your eye on her. Maybe help her find hobbies she enjoys to take her mind off some things? But therapy is definitely needed. I hope all goes well for you and her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 13:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good for you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 23:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely think you should ask her out on a date, but I also think you should seek some help for the issues youve listed. Maybe talking to a professional could help you get a clearer mind, and Im sure shed love to go on a date with you from the way youve explained your encounters with her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 12:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely see what youre saying and agree. I think there is fault on both ends, and his actions really do say a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 11:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont really see the need to block him? Just stop answering. If he really wants to continue your friendship and not be weird about it, he will try. Doesnt sound like a good idea to let your romantic feelings for him to continue though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 11:27:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time you have sex there is a small percentage that the woman will get pregnant. Man up to your shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 11:23:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People are allowed to go out and not be on their phones the whole time. Personally, I hate being tethered to my phone when Im out with friends I havent seen in a long time. It sounds like he got annoyed that you were blowing up his phone and said somethings out of drunken spite. Im sure things will be fine but you gotta give your dude some space when its due.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 11:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Office maybe? Sounds like a Michael Scott thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 13:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id love to see her face when no one shows up to her wedding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 23:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 06:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister did that with her SO around the same time, 6-8 months of being together, and theyre doing great. But every situation is different, whats great for someone might be hell for someone else, so its hard to really bank on other peoples experiences with this one. Wish you the best of luck though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 19:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably both honestly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 17:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drop him. Dont take shit from a man, theres someone out there who wont make fun of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 17:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plenty of women wear all the fancy lingerie just for themselves. Theres confidence in feeling sexy. Also many women where things because they dont show underwear lines when wearing certain pants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 17:44:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once you leave high school, all the people that claim to be your friends will never speak to you again. The ones that make the effort after high school will probably be lifelong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 17:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is rough, Id probably be screaming out of anger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 15:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get out of there. Dont stay in a relationship where he thinks its okay for him to look at other women sexually. If you want to swap pictures with other people that arent the person youre in a relationship, then you clearly dont want to be in that relationship in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 14:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you made him feel like this was something he HAD to do, even if he wasnt ready yet. He probably loves you a lot, but even though youre ready for that next step in the relationship, he might not be ready yet and it sounds like you just guilted him into being engaged. Try apologizing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 14:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My best friend went through this same exact thing. Her ex kept telling her that he thought he fell in love with other girls but was never sure. She put up with this for a year until she got fed up of feeling second best to every other girl. I believe you can find someone that will treat you like their #1. You can find something better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>