<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9967</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 23:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Robin Lane Fox's Alexander the Great is really readable and entertaining, if at this stage a bit old. Plutarch's Paralell Lives are fun, though obviously don't take them at face value. And again a bit old but MM Austin's sourcebook onthr Hellenistic world from Alexander to the Roman Conquest is one I'd highly recommend.

I've heard good things about Stephanie Dalley's work with regards to Mesopotamian cultures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 13:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If people want to know more about medieval Africa I highly recommend The Golden Rhinoceros by Franois-Xavier Fauvelle. Readable and easy to parse, with a brief overview of the period told through a series of vignettes around specific documents or objects. Really interesting stuff. Available in French or English </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 10:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In modern Irish royal is "roga" and fist is also "dorn". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 00:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  

1. Julia Lovell - The Opium War
2. Leeanna Keith - The Colfax Massacre
3. Kyle Harper - The Fate of Rome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-23 11:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sign me up lads! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 13:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tis Scotland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 16:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> UK remains Ireland's largest trading partner, and UK leaving EU will have a massive impact economically, as well as on border security, if they also leave the Customs Union and Single Market. However, Ireland's economy is not as reliant on the UK as it was in the 60s and 70s. 

Ireland and the UK joined the EEC on the same day in 1973, and remains a massive link for Irish agricultural trade, which have a very powerful lobbying body compared to industries with greater links to the rest of the EU like pharmaceuticals, electronics or financial services.

There is a lot of worry in the Irish media around a no deal Brexit - but broad support across parties and the public for the government's stance and policy on Brexit. Indeed it could be argued that its the only thing keeping them in power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 14:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, I'm always a bit skeptical of that when it comes to UK political maps, things can hang on a knife edge and you wouldn't be able to tell that from how they are shown.

I just thought the inclusion of Rockall was funny as theres nowt on it but cormerants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 12:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean NI uses a different voting system than the rUK for European elections so kinda makes sense - as it would be difficult to have a consistent visual. Including Rockall is gass though - how did the kittiwakes vote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-28 17:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mary Beard has given a lecture on whiteness and its application to the classical world. I can see this ruffling feathers/rustling jimmies 

https://giffordsedinburgh.com/2019/05/07/lecture-two-whiteness/amp/?__twitter_impression=true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 11:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoever put Cider as their favourite hot drink is a monster and should be called out as such </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-10 14:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the best resources I've found for ww1 photos is https://www.europeana.eu/portal/en/collections/world-war-I

Great mix of archival material and public engagement from  almost all European participants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 16:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Free France </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-17 17:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a big fan of Art Deco as a total art style -the architecture, sculpture, painting its all class. [Autoportrait](https://api.culture.pl/sites/default/files/styles/420_auto/public/images/imported/sztuki%20wizualne/galeria/gl%20lempicka%20tamara%20prace/galeria/lempicka%20tamara%20prace%205_6828863.jpg?itok=xGoPIIYW) by Tamara de Lempicka is so cool.

For an individual artist Harry Clarke can never get enough attention - his [stain-glass](https://wordsandimagesbycynthia.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/mdsorrows1.jpg?w=500) as well as [illustrations](http://www.bpib.com/illustrat/clarke8.gif) are just phenomenal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 12:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 15:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He knowingly fought for a side that had the perpetuation of slavery as a clear war aim and reason for secession. Grant being a dickbag doesn't change that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 17:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bohernabreena has some nice wooded parts, especially at the upper reservoir. 65b, 75, 49 go to Old Bawn - about 20 mins walk for the entrance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 14:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "We raped and pillaged the city" is what a sack is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 13:00:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R/ireland has gotten pretty rabid about it, and ISF on facebook is almost as bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 19:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eurocentrism, I've been trying to expand my knowledge of African and Native American history to help combat it, but I'm not sure its taken yet. Also, I cannot help but take a combative stance towards 19th century Liberalism, particularly English Liberalism. I went to too many Great Famine related things as a teen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 18:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Home Rule is Rome Rule! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 20:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit has yet to move on from Max Weber  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-25 15:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have access to a public library? quite a few have access to jstor on the library PCs. Good way to get journals without paying through the nose  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 17:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bit further south then where you are thinking but 'Italy in the Age of the Renaissance' is a pretty good collection of essays edited by John Najemy covering various aspects of Italian society during the period you're  looking at. Not really much military or political stuff but loads of material for fleshing out the world of your game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 12:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In this case ellipsis = /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-22 19:26:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cult of Collins tends to overshadow his achievements I'll admit, leaving him in popular history with only his faults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-21 13:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So here in Ireland we're coming towards the end of a decade of centenaries, and into the more contraversial aspects of it with the War of Independence and the Civil War. If anybody here sees any particularly egregious takes, be they handwringing revisionist or rabid nationalist, do let me know so that I can smite them down with Ferriter in my right hand and Townshend in my left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-21 12:53:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't even want to think about your poor imaginary liver </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 10:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say trying to filter out the question/discussion/request posts and redirecting them to the weekly stickies. That'd mean that the majority of the posts are actual badhistory posts, meaning a more casual redditor would be more likely to understand the main purpose of the sub.

Also more shitposting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 15:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to discourage anybody from writing a response but a similar question was answered quite well here: https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/8otw7p/was_the_treaty_of_versailles_too_harsh/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-14 11:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Presentation is a key element of education </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 14:29:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This LPT brought to you by Marcus Aurelius iin the 2nd century AD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-07 15:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bartlett is a fantastic medievalist! If you're interested in another book of his that deals with the thinking of medieval peoples I'd recommend The Natural and the Supernatural in the Middle Ages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-07 15:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well anybody looking for stories dealing with faeries can't go wrong with thebdigital material published by the National Folklore Collection. This link leads to a collection of school children's essays about Irish folklore from the 30s: https://www.duchas.ie/en/cbes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Irish Times Inside Politics Podcast: The Transformative Election of 1918 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-14 18:01:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-14 16:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The voice of God </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-11 01:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IllumanatiRex's obscure media review on [WWI Allied submarines](https://www.reddit.com/r/badhistory/comments/9tdot8/the_obscure_history_of_allied_submarines_in_world/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-11 01:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I nominate /u/YRUasking \- **Urban II started the crusades to prop up the petrodollar**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-11 00:48:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This two parter on a blogger's Belgian Congo apologetics](https://www.reddit.com/r/badhistory/comments/7svvbo/altright_blogger_does_some_questionable_number/). [Its quite something](https://www.reddit.com/r/badhistory/comments/7t40ok/more_congo_free_state_apologetics/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-27 09:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are also amendments from pro choice TDs who feel that the proposed government legislation doesn't do enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Boat built 5,000 years ago found by men on River Boyne near Newgrange </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-23 14:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-20 16:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any situation where Aerys would win requires Aerys to not be Aerys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-16 14:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats more frustrating is people who bring up Pearl Harbour and the bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki in a comparative sense, ignoring the entire conduct and floeof the rest of the war and the historical context to get a gotcha moment on the opening and closing of hostilities between America and Japan, like the person in the linked thread did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 12:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should have gotten the alternative vote when ye had the chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-01 20:23:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is a contemporary report on how King Leopold ran the Congo (be warned it makes for very grim reading): [https://archive.org/details/CasementReport/page/n1](https://archive.org/details/CasementReport/page/n1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 16:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More anti-UK than profacsist, its pretty left wing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 13:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If that happens without a trade deal, like Norway's for example, both EU and UK will have to answer to the WTO for violating most favoured nation rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 14:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'Sure, one off housing is less efficient than building an estate, but for many of us, we don't want to live in an identikit house with no garden to grow anything of their own etc' - living instead in an identikit house out of bungalow bliss,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 17:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ban books, they make you lazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 18:15:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am the punishment of God... Pilgrim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 18:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was a thread in r/ europe yesterday about Eamon de Valera's response to Churchill's VE speech. Couldn't help but think of this scene https://youtu.be/ulHR8C4ZZes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 14:13:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 14:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does CK2 have a start date in 4th or 5th century? Because if not that doesn't make a lick of sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 10:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, you're thinking of Cavan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 17:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the abobe poster was basing it on WWI gasmasks and extrapolating that for modern usage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 12:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually can't stop on the bike area at the front because theres a car in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 18:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tudor plantation in Ireland was mostly in the south, notably Laois and Offaly (Kings County and Queens County) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 15:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Direct rule has not been implemented. The civil service are running things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 12:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blirn Baloidis (Folklore Snippets/Tidbits). Its a podcast on Irish Folklore from the National Folklore Collection in UCD. They go over some really interesting topics, and I find the archive material they break out facinating https://m.soundcloud.com/folklore_podcast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 13:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> East sounds more foreign though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 11:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ye picked up on that but not 'Tirty'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 14:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A number of my contemporaries absolutely pulled this kind of shit in flats in Dublin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 09:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Denmark is Scandinavian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 14:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The mandate on which their constituents elected them, and an oath of loyalty to the crown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 14:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stefan Molyneux is where they got it from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FF should back Government for an extra budget, Calleary says </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-18 11:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-17 13:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The animal is usually stunned before slaughter anyway so won't feel the pain. its cut in major arteries on the neck and tend to bleed out pretty quickly. Halal only allows for individual killing so you don't have animals getting distressed from the line to slaughterhouse if animal welfare is your concern.

And there is another religious group who practice a similar ritual slaughter in this country that you aren't complaining about: shehitah for kosher meat in Judaism. 

Addendum: I take issue with your characterisation that most new films are politically motivated, which is a gross exaggeration. And with the implication that a film with a political message is solely politically motivated - that a film that tries to be about something is devalued because of that. But again this link and story has little to nothing to do with politics in Ireland

Edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-17 12:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Halal is less ethical then other ways of animal slaughter how exactly? Unless you are talking for the banning of animal slaughter in its entirety I'm not exactly sure what your trying to say here. Or why your posting news on a film on the politics sub (Though I do have a sneaking suspicion) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-15 08:26:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That second line seems edited in after the like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 20:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I looked up the guy he quotes near the beginning, Alan Brown, whose definition of socialism seems to mean any form of collectivisim, including nationalism. He claims to be a senior lecturer in history, though doesn't state where, and that he got his PhD from a Teacher Training College which closed after having its accreditation revoked in the 1990s when it failed an academic validation inspection. He has three books published, the one quoted that seems more like an essay and is self published, and two on Allied airforces, neither through academic publishers. Doesn't seem to have anything in academic journals. Good first reference TIK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 23:47:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd want to as well, however this whole retributive attitude where any wrong doing (we have no idea how hard the child was hit, if at all) leads to excessive shows of force, or that retribution should be expected is not right either. Black lad may be a scummer outside the instance of this video, I don't know. I just know that the other lads are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 18:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Repercussions up to and including having the threat of your legs being blown off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 12:25:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barbarian Migrations and the Roman West 376-568 by Guy Halsall might be of use. Don't know of any monographs dealing specifically with Hispania but I'm sure there's plenty of relevent material on Jstor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 19:16:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say that there tends to be a lot of bad history and out of date grand narrative construction out of the fall of the Western Roman Empire. A couple of books that I think help to clear that up would be:  


 *The Fall of Rome: And the End of Civilizatio*n - Bryan Ward-Parkins

*Empire and Barbarians: The Fall of Rome and the Birth of Europe* \- Peter Heather

*Rome and the Barbarians, 100 B.C.  400 A. D.* \- Thomas S. Burns

*Barbarian Migrations and the Roman West 376-568* \-  Guy Halsall

*The Later Roman Empire* \- Averil Cameron

*The Historians of Late Antiquity*  \- David Rorhbacher (This is an overview of the primary sources from the time, and to try and foster a better understanding and critical engagement with them) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-26 18:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All their replies are being downvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-17 11:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This map shows geographic proximity to nearest grounds, not a real measure of where supporters are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-16 16:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Terry Pratchett </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 15:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do agree that he shouldn't have been convicted, however I think using the pug to point out the obsurtity of the law when it wasn't the reason for his conviction is disineguous. Though I can understand why that caught on, makes for a better story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 12:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is that allowed so close to those buildings? Thats insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 12:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm fairly sure him saying gas the Jews did more for his conviction than a Nazi saluting pug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-12 11:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A visual representation of the French losses during the invasion of Russia: https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/29/Minard.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 17:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha! I see you've fallen for my trap card!: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irish_Confederate_Wars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 15:18:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats because the BBC is actual news not entertainment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 11:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does minority religions include Methodists and CoI as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 10:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are the Confederates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 17:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And how rigorously they check that you are fit is very much dependent on the GP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-06 17:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'Tis Cyprus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-05 18:26:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mayo's GAA team curse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-04 18:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last day prior to it going to a vote in Parliament urgency might compell more people to actually do it. if it passes by all means keep at them to try and reverse it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-03 15:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I liked it, funny at times and really captures the mindset of parts of that subset of Dublin life. but I feel some of the dialogue, and especially the internal monologue, suited the stage play better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-02 17:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Source: Man in the High Castle by Philip K. Dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-02 12:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currently reading George Bulls translation of Castiglione's Il Cortengiano. Finding it interesting, if a bit of a slog. In the market for a more acessible translation if anybody knows one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-30 00:15:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://books.google.ie/books?id=ZHD4Asj0FagC pg=PR36 dq=Dai+viet hl=en sa=X ved=0ahUKEwia4-6c8vnbAhVMD8AKHeLEBsYQ6AEISDAH#v=onepage q f=false there is a reference title you might find useful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-29 22:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pick up some linen ones! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-29 22:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might want to look at narrowing search terms or implementing " symbol; as in "Vietnam under France" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-29 12:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two that I listen to:

Hawthorne Radio - a curated playlist of funk and soul that changes every two weeks https://open.spotify.com/user/mayerhawthorneofficial/playlist/00J3fzBVxXoTl3OIVZQJ9D?si=ngXh1i9LTP2K9eZXAbX0mw 


I'm cyborg but thats ok - playlist for youtube channel of the same name that makes music videos for lo-fi and indie music using classic films https://open.spotify.com/user/mxba75plqvbtv2ynx2d6cnhfl/playlist/6doFYo0Wk6DHvGZUBmhqnG?si=U6SIma4eT6yAvELCIctnKg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-27 18:28:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://medievalarchive.weebly.com/uploads/2/4/7/9/24791478/vikingsireland795-873_2.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-26 12:53:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a shared flat yes, for a shared room unlikely,  I've seen 100 a week for a shared room, but I doubt it goes much higher than that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-21 15:03:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> German mobile bank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-21 08:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There were some good topics in the discursive section, especially for leaving cert level. Would be interesting to see the marking scheme and guidelines for examiners </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-14 17:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uncritical (if any) use of sources? Check!

Perpetuation of clash of civilisations grand narrative? Check!

Western and Southern Europe only areas of value? Check!

Nazis greatest ever, despite losing after only 12 years in power? Check! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-14 10:27:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1000s exempted while taking a seperate foreign language, which is ridiculous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-12 12:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be more worried about proposed EU online copyright regulation if I were you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 12:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its washing up from river systems here and waste fishing equipment internationally, not tourists causing it. Though tourism may be effecting the govs response, and seeming lack of concern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-07 19:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've found one here for ya, its his armoured skeptic response: [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VVSLr1S6hFg](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VVSLr1S6hFg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-07 13:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats like 15 sargons long! We can't be expected to subject ourselves to that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-06 16:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'm blind. Nil points for reading comprehension </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-06 14:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Dead Zoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-31 17:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Faking his death wasn't necessary for him not to get assassinated, though it could be argued that it was necessary to catch at least one of the people who ordered the assasination </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 13:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That link leads to the wikipedia entry on the Frankfurt School where the only references to Cultural Marxism are under the subheading Cultural Marxism conspiracy theory. Its not a thing, at least not in modern academic usage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 11:46:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cultural Marxism isn't a thing, he uses Critical Theory.

Edit: He could also be using Marxist Theory, but that isn't Cultural Marxism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-29 19:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But this is about referals not the procedure itself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 16:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I know a few, they tend not to advertise the fact that they are Travellers due to reactions like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-22 16:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tyger Tyget not by Blake? I'd like to see the version anyway! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 21:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I do. I think he was a very interesting and innovative playwright. *Whistle in the Dark* and *The Gigli Concert* were both very engaging plays, and his work with Druid helped put them on the map as one of the great production companies.

Michael D seems to have given a shite as well: http://www.president.ie/en/media-library/news-releases/statement-by-president-higgins-on-the-death-of-tom-murphy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 18:10:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope they are looking forward to their potential fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Playwright Tom Murphy dead at age of 83 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 08:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 14:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was a diplomat not the ambassador, just to clarify </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-11 08:45:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See You at the Pillar I think

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=O9jU196ZYpE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 01:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to clarify, I wasn't the poster who called your OP nonsense. I do agree that there is a self serving nature to the ignoring of the antisemetic aspects of Irish history.

In terms of Irish denial of Jewish refugees I would say that it was right in line with what the Allies did prior to the war. For example there is the MS St Louis and its Voyage of the Damned in 1939 where 900 German Jewish refugees were denied entry to both the US and Canada, as well as Cuba, and were forced to return to Europe, where about 250 would die in the Holocaust. 

I would disagree with your point that denying Jewish refugees entry was an act supporting the Final Solution. It is presentist to assume that Irish callousness towards Jewish refugees was informed by this given that the Final Solution wasn't formed when the refugees were denied entry before and during the early stages of the war. (I'm very tired, so my point may get a bit muddled here. I will likely get back to you tomorrow) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 01:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the fact that you're saying that Ireland wasn't at least partially skewed towards the allies during the Second World War is the nonsense part, not the Irish response to Jewish refugees. In terms of concrete help afforded to the Allies by the Irish Government you can look to Richard Hayes' codebreaking of Nazi messages which was shared with OSS and MI5. Further to this was sharing of weather reports, key to logistics around shipping and flying. As well as the laxer attitude towards downed Allied airmen, as opposed to their German counterparts which you referred to.

For more information on the unbalanced nature of Irish neutrality during the war I would like to refer you to *In Time of War* by Robert Fisk and *Behind the Green Curtain* by T. Ryle Dwyer.

Regarding your point on anti-semitism: I would hesitate to use the instances of anti-Semitism as the reason for why the book of condolences were signed, more it was Dev's rigid adherence to international protocol at the death of a head of state, foolish and unfeeling as that action may have been. I'd like to refer you to this article: https://www.historyireland.com/20th-century-contemporary-history/de-valera-hitler-the-visit-of-condolence-may-1945/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-01 14:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like somebody's had too much fluoride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 18:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the 50s and 60s there was a movement by the government to standardise and simplify spelling and to allow for easier communication between the diferent dialects, could be in reference to that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 17:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was in the 1860s though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 11:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I put my park anywhere lights on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-24 19:08:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Article text:

 Apple will start paying 13bn in back taxes to the Irish government from May in a move that comes 19 months after Brussels ruled that the tech giant received a quarter-century of illegal aid from Dublin through a tax scheme unavailable to other groups.

The start of the tax repayments follows an agreement between the Irish government and Apple to set up an escrow account to hold the money pending their appeals in Europes highest court against the ruling from Margrethe Vestager, EU competition commissioner.

This is a very, very significant day now in terms of dealing with this issue, said Paschal Donohoe, Irish finance minister. Mr Donohoe told reporters he will sign a legal agreement today with Apple to set up the escrow. The full recovery will be completed by the end of September, he said.

This is the largest recovery fund of its kind ever to be established and, due to the complexity of such, together with our duty to comply with EU procurement rules, it has taken some time to get to this point.
Frustrated at delays in collecting the money after its ruling in August 2016, the commission took Dublin to court October to force recovery of the money from Apple. Mr Donohoe said he spoke on Tuesday with Ms Vestager about the agreement with Apple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Irish government and Apple reach deal on back taxes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-24 17:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 15:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one this year was particularly bad, some of the strains were resistant to the vaccine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 09:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't the flu outbreak have had a massive impact on that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 13:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And would ya look at that! Speak of the divils and they do appear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-19 15:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lads what are yiz at? Who downvotes the fucking article text?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-18 23:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whigish disinvolvement and Malthusian fears </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-17 09:39:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A satirical news site needs to be topical to get those clicks, its not about the morality of their respective actions, but the visibility to the public of their actions and reactions *right now*. When I say there's more things to have a go at with Varadkar I don't mean his past, but his present actions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-16 19:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's the Taoiseach, there's more things to have a go at him for than any of the opposition leaders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 14:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> David Anthony's book, The Horse the Wheel and Language, does an excellent job covering the origins of the Indo-European language group using a mix of archaeological and linguistic methodologies. He also briefly summarizes the older theories surrounding the Aryans which have now been dismissed and debunked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Good Friday agreement is so much more than a shibboleth | Fintan OToole | Opinion </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 01:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 17:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like you to read that thought over again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-05 18:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Irish news: Times, Examiner

Broader: Spectator, Economist, Guardian, New Statesman,  Politico (EU), Financiaal Times

I've recently signed up to a newsletter which gives you artivlrs that run counter your biases.

https://getdevilsadvocate.com

Its a bit US centric, but interesting nonetheless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-04 22:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All the lads who think the daily commute is a good opportunity to pretend they're doing the North West 200 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-02 20:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could get a larger restricted engine model, but in order to use it unrestricted, after upgrading your license, you'd have to do the IBT again if I read the NDLS website correctly. Do correct me if I'm wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-28 16:33:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not disagreeing with the verdict of the case based on the evidence. Just disagreeing that the girls version of events should be discounted due to inconsistencies when it was all inconsistent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-28 16:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everybodys story in this case was all over the place. The account of events from PJ SO and BM were wildly inconcistent with each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-28 15:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd agree with you there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-28 14:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you're confusing charged with found guilty. The whole point of a jury trial is to establish that. Why would we need to if it was already 100% certain? How can certainty br assertained without someone being charged an a trial held? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-28 12:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has to be Fangclub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-27 15:00:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have previously expelled an Israeli diplomat, in 2010, and another Russian one in 2011, both over false passports </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-27 12:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would still say that Ireland's neutrality both during the second world war and now is skewed towards the UK and the US, from shared weather reports, and turning more of a blind eye to downed Allied airmen hopping back over the border, to sharing codebreaking info and sending support and relief during the bombing of Belfast.

And to say the Irish army was doing nothing kind of belies the point that there was a potential threat of invasion from two sides. Robert Fisk does a pretty good job of outlining these in hus book, In Time of War, which really hammers home just how precarious the Irish situation was at the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-27 10:58:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who deserted the Irish army to do so were prosecuted. Not all those who volunteered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-27 10:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its fully: Trinity College, University of Dublin. But its the only constituent college of the University </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-26 09:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 137,000 that was given to Amnesty Ireland? That Amnesty would be very foolish to use because its currently involved with a challenge around it in the High Court? A challenge that they're fighting because SIPO ordered them to give it back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-23 14:29:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Further down the same paragrah: However, many businesses and politicians use methods that owe more to the underworld than to legal practice. The state hires hackers and arms gangsters to fight its wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-23 11:18:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I reckon a lot of the seqiences from the book that were cut worked well because of the medium, the long discriptions of how the biologist is experiencing the shimmer would not translate well to the visual media, and cutting them in favour of focusing on imagery and sound was the right choice, even if it loses some of the cosmic horror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-22 08:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really. Opinions shouldn't be sourced. Original ideas don't need to be sourced. Your own stories don't need to be sourced. Somebody elses content should. You just brought us the topic that is up for discussion. You should source it.

Also I didn't see your previous post so no its not because of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-21 17:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because we are coming up to a very devisive referendum where emotions are going to run very high. When emotions run high misinformation moves faster than it already does. Which is why if we want to keep an informed debate and reduce the possibilty of a game of chinese whispers we ahould provide the source of our information.

I had heard of Sheila Hodgers before your post, but not the full details that you go into. How am I to know that everything you've said is true, or not framed in a certain light? You haven't provided a link or even the name of the source your taking it from, and in doing so provide an opportunity for an attempt to undermine your point that is completly unnecessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-21 12:25:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you not link one then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-17 11:10:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you read his Confessio? He was a miserable cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-14 15:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You say that as if white South Africans weren't always in a minority. With that being said I think that Australia is making a smart move here by seeking to import skilled labour, and the ANC's constitutional change is going to send the agriculture of RSA the way of Zimbabwe, all to cover up corruption and mismanagement in the land claims commission </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-13 14:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That tattoo appears slowly throughout the film, she thinks its a bruise at first after the crocodile attack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 10:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A reference to the current BBC drama on the seige of Troy where the actor playing Achilles is black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-09 11:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That seems like pretty standard satirical turnaround on the bigotry towards travellers here. You might not agree with it but its hardly loony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 19:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both. 3.2billion from UK out of 85b pakage from IMF/EU. A lot of which has been paid back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 16:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cases for assessment for fatal foetal abnomalities or risk to mother's health would be after the 12 week limit, before that they would be unrestricted and would not require the medical assessment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 15:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Likely birth certificates, but you might have more difficulty figuring out if a child is the father's first child or if they had a child in another relationship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 14:05:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably easier to compile statistics for age of mother than that of the father </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 12:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nord Stream 2 - a planned natural gas pipeline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-07 19:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [**HamsandwicH** - *BODIES*](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oGMmJcOMnLA) (Indie Rock) "One thing I really like is a band with a boy and a girl singer and this is one of them" - Littlefinger

"Lisa Hannigan hasn't released anything in allotted time. Sad. These guys will do" u/subject9967 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-06 15:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've my issues with globalism, its exploitation, its uneveness in equality, and lack of oversight for multinationals. 

But an appeal to an imagined past utopia as opposed to actual critiques of globalism irks me no end </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-06 15:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When was this? Before the curent globalist system we had, among other things, fucking mercantilism. 

Trade duties and tariffs between peoples have existed at least since the ancient egyptians so the period of international free trade, unless you can give me a more recent example, is prehistoric </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-06 14:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There isn't a single country on this earth without some level of government regulation on internal markets. 

If you think that doesn't apply doubly on the international stage, you would be sorely mistaken. The free trade between EEA members is the deepest and most complex arrangement of international trade there is. 

Libertarian ideas of complete government disinvolvement do not apply and if you are genuinely interested in getting engaging answers please do try to post more than single sentences putting the onus those you're talking to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-06 14:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody wants a hard border. But leaving the customs union and single market means that  there will be discrepecies between the EU and UK on the quality and structures around goods, and this willl be the case unless their is an incredibly close FTA, which looks unlikely given how negotiations have been going so far. So in order fir these goods to be processed and any potential duties to be paid, and to clamp down on the likely increase in existing smuggling, some form of border infrastructure will be needed.

A hard border is difficult, expensive, political suicide, and likely to lead to an uptick in paramilitary activity. But it is completely necessary, for both the EU as a whole and for the UK unless negotiations move quickly and smoothly to a deal which allows for the free movement of goods, something that will keep the UK at least tangentally attached to the EU

Edit: corrected spelling mistakes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-06 14:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flann Campbell's The Dissenting Voice does a pretty good job covering this aspect I think if anybodys interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-05 09:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MISSUS BANFIELD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-26 15:00:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The way your original comment was framed it seemed as though RTE had made the allegation against Kehoe, as opposed to a guest making allegations which were mostly back pedalled during the programme.

And the jury did find that Costelloe was liable for 6,500 in damages for making the idiotic and libellous statement which won't be paid because he wasn't a named party in the suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-26 14:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RTE didn't make the allegation though, Joe Costelloe did. And he didn't even name Kehoe, that was SF TD Eoin  Broin. No point in suing Costelloe though, cos he's got no cash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-23 09:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't say Harris was either. O'Reilly and McGrath were acting like children and the Ceann Comhairle rsally doesn't seem to be in control of the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-22 13:11:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No grummles? Blizz plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How did the US government react to the United Fruit Company's activities in South and Central America? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-21 21:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Specifically: Did UFC monopolies gel well with US foreign policy? How did it interact with the Munroe Doctrine? Did the United Fruit Company have support in Washington? Did having banana republics in Central America benefit the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-20 11:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100 nearly twenty years ago. Its worth over 1000 now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-20 11:06:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't have a lot but:

30% in 3 year savings bonds (would not recommend now, interest rates have gone through the floor)

10% in forestry (in middle of a growth cycle atm, expect return on investment in 5 years or so, when forest is harvested.)

Rest in credit union and bank, cos I really don't have the time or interest to get too active

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-19 16:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you'll have another 2 years with a different beautiful yellow vest, so don'r go wishing it away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-19 15:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd get used to riding on the 400 first anyway. Your instructor may be able to provide you with a 600 to do the IBT module on, and maybe for your full license test as well. 

I believe the 6 months is related to your learner permit not IBT, so shouldn't effect when you can take your test </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-19 15:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, its a bit of a bitch. I'd say if you're thinking of going up a size, to do it before going for full license, save you from doing it twice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-19 14:56:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to clarify, you still have to do your Initial Basic Training, to be road legal, and you can only use bikes up to the engine size you did your IBT on. If you want to go up an engine size, you have to do it again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 16:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, absolutely I's say thats acceptable! I've had brief conversations with a cousin that speaks Gaidhlig, and the level of interaction always surprises me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 15:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The word for the language family to avoid confusion and misplaced annoyance is Goidelic. I suppose the confusion here has arisen because /r/ireland thinks you meant Irish Gaeilge, while you referring the the language grouping of Gealic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-14 17:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really doesn't, it gives more prominance within the party and DUP base to the MPs, who are actually doing stuff, and reduces the influence of the MLAs including herself, never good for a party leader

Edit: I have ten thumbs and no index finger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-14 16:13:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Foiled again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-14 14:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're hiring atm if anybodys interested: http://www.cartoonsaloon.ie/positions/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-14 12:23:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shes an independent from the new batch from 2016. In order to keep constituents aware that they exist, and to be seen to be doing something independents and backbenchers make these attention grabbing statments. Shes obviously not getting anything from beating the dead horse that is the Labour Party anymore, so shes trying something else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-14 11:34:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two syllables though, can't be having that when your trying to get a self satisfied snappy barb onto the news </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-13 15:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure I'd agree with that, but I think it should affect public school places for those without vaccines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-12 19:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats a nice quick summary. You have to ask though, why has it been allowed to go on for 13 months by Westminister, how come a second round of elections weren't called, or direct rule imposed to tide things over while SF and DUP sort themselves out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 14:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 'Charts' have started taking youtube views and spotify plays into their calculations, so I would argue that they aren't entirely inaccurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-09 22:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a couple on Parnell street iirc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 18:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's a music producer and composer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 16:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 2 top voted comments when you posted this were disputing the title, and saying the blame on McSharry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 16:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen Dee, further Anglisised maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 12:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One story that I don't think is particularly well known is the Voyage of Bran, where Bran Mac Febail goes on a journey around the Atlantic, encountering strange lands and people, after hearing a poem about a silver tree branch. Lots of comparrison with the Odyessy and some of the Viking Sagas

If you're looking for more Irish Folkloric stuff I woukd highly recomend the podcast Blirn Baloidis, which has lota of archival material and intersting tidbits.

https://m.soundcloud.com/folklore_podcast


Didn't know Ireland was idealised in that way. Any idea why? Has that changed in the last while? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Irish Times: Civilised debate vital to discussion about abortion referendum </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 10:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-27 12:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would have said that it had to be Robinson, although minus points for not completing her term in office, so I might have to go with McAleese. 

I would add though, American have those polls because the President has a very active role in the governance of the country, and a more pertinent question could be, which are Ireland's favourite Taoisigh, in which case I'd go for Lemass or Fitzgerald </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-26 15:29:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus Christ. Casement Report don't real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-24 19:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Based on this: http://www.imff.ie/pricing.cfm
450

Edit: Should add, that that is minimum costing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-24 10:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its prohibitivly expensive and can take up to 3 weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-18 13:02:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has that not been put into escrow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-17 10:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quicker to mature than broadleaf and provide good amount of timber relative to land usage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 21:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We've had nearly 90 years of self rule to go for a reforestation project, that isn't profit orientated non-native conifers, and we haven't, because there isn't the political appetite for it here, its not all the Brits fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 13:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh sorry, misread context of comment chain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 13:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also not what Finto is getting at....Its a satirical piece on the baptism barrier is schools </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fintan O'Toole: A Baptism barrier would solve our hospital crisis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 11:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-15 09:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed it is. Which is why the Public Spending Commission is telling them to give it back, and why whenever an article relating to this story is posted the majoeity of the upvoted comments are against Amnesty in this instance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Former Fine Gael TD Paddy Harte has died aged 86 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 19:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 17:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm talking about acts during the Civil War which featured a massive upsurge in violence against non-combatants compared with WOI.

Gemma Clark's book covers it fairly well, summary and review can be found here:

http://www.historyireland.com/book-reviews/everyday-violence-irish-civil-war/

If you are counting unofficial executions as part of Free State war crimes, but justify executions of suspected informers as simply being part of IRA policy, when both sides consider themselves to be the legitimate authority of the country are they not both committing the same war crime? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 16:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plenty of attacks on Protestants, which would be considered attacks on civilian population, no? 

Also I'm not saying that Free Staters had not previously engaged in these activities, I take umbridge with the statement that Free State war crimes vastly outweighed those by anti-Treaty forces </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 13:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Arson on houses ofsuspected informers, for the Free State, as well as on Protestants was pretty common during the civil war. Gemma Clark has done some extensive research into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 17:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd try out **The Extraordinary Adventures of Baron Munchausen** it is basically a rp version of **Just a Minute** and is great fun. Heartily recommended </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 13:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thought Prisoners of Geography was a great read, made a very compelling argument. I did feel, however, that in elevating geography he diminished the importance of other factors on international politics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-07 11:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Non-Fiction: The Horse, The Wheel, and Language - David Anthony

Fiction: Valis - Philip K. Dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 13:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's the miracleofsound chap. Has he moved abroad as well? 

I think that as English speakers primarily, moving to where support for online creators is more prevelent, like the UK and US is easier. We don't have the population or the resources to compete with that. 

Do Youtube not have a creator programme here? If not thats a bit ridiculous considering their EMEA HQ is here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-04 12:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There seems to be a fair bit of critique for the poppy every year.

And I wouldn't say that this t-shirt is exactly an Easter Lilly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-28 13:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An interest in satirical humour, and a complaint about how horrible other people can be? Sounds a lot like /r/ireland to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-22 21:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idle Wild on Fade Street. The Long Stone. Doyles. Underdog, below Brogans on Cork Hill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-21 23:46:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you say we should recognise Jerusalem as Israel's capital. 

Should we do the same for Palestine? That seems a pretty unworkable situation, in as much as the entire situation is unworkable. Which is why not recognising either claim until the peace process is completed keeps a lid on the situation, a peace process which is looking increasingly unlikely to ever be concluded.

Quick edit: finished a sentence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-21 22:21:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except that Jerusalem is the capital of Palestine. Just because you dont like them doesnt change that their government has decided that its their capital. Besides both exist as post WWI entities, but with long histories of cultural, ethnic, and religious presence in the area. Israel as modern political entity has existed since the 1940s, although the process began in the 1920s, while an autonomous Palestinian state has been sought by the Arab population there for roughly the same amount of time. A 1:1 placing of Ireland as either Israel or Palestine is oversimplistic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-14 13:15:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would just like to note that this fairly upvoted comment is calling on the forced sterilisation of all travellers.

wtf. Do we not consider them to be human anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-07 17:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd agree that its certainly a line that requires the full context of the bit.  But I don't think lack of comedic poise necessitates near instant downvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-07 16:05:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very few Stewart Lee fans on this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-07 13:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also to say that in general criticising the Brits would energize the FG base is a bit laughable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-06 15:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Death of Stalin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-05 18:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They wouldn't give Arthur Griffith a telephone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-04 13:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'Greedy pig'
'Runts of the litter'

Plenty of relevant idioms about pigs in English </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-01 10:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The proposal is an extension for Presidential vote to both NI residents and those who have left for elsewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-01 10:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't vote in them either I'm afraid. Residents from the UK can vote for Oireachtas elections though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 21:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Preconditions on the trade negotiations were already set when May and Hammond both stated in July that the UK would be leaving the customs union and the single market as well as the EU. 

Having some commitments on their only land border with the EU, and to uphold both the CTA and the GFA, is not an unreasonable thing to ask, and the only reason we are at the current juncture is that the proverbial 'Irish question' was considered the least important of the three issues in the first round of negotiations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 20:03:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actual paper found here: http://www.britishirishchamber.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/Big-Principles-Final.pdf

Major issue with it is that its unlikely to be accepted by hardline Tories, as the UK would still be subject to EU trade deals
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> British Irish Chamber of Commerce outlines 'borderless' trade plan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 19:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 00:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well Australia, is a fair bit different to Ireland in that it is a federal system, and therefore has further layers of local and state government tanking on parts of legislation that would be done in the Oireachtas in Ireland.

It also does not have proportional representation, all their districts have a single MP, so they have 150 separate districts, compared to our 40 multi-seat districts.

An argument could be made for Ireland to switch to Single Member Seats, using STV, but to simply say that we should, under our current system, simply reduce representation of districts with increasing populations, is not a particularly good or democratic idea.

Edit: added a quite important 'not' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-24 14:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say a fair few of the Independent Alliance are gonners, and it'll be the final nail in the coffin for Labour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-24 12:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If FG don't back her then they are further beholden to FF and even less will be done in this minority gov.

The fact that they are using this opportunity, as oppossed to myriad others that have come before, many with more legitimate cause, shows that this is not about the good of the country. 

I'm fairly sure it will work out for them though, and we'll have a FF/SF coalition in January </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-24 11:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The smear campaign of Maurice McCabe by An Garda Siochana is not a non issue, and neither is corruption within the Guards

The email to Fitzgerald detailing the Guard's aggressive legal strategy. In an ongoing tribunal the minister couldn't interfere with the legal strategy being pursued and the Fitzgerald's decision to not interfere is backed up by the attorney general. The mess of timelines and Dail corrections is embarrassing for FG, and Varadkar, but I don't think are strong enough reasons to call for resignation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-24 11:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot SF and FF for forcing a general election, on the non issue of an email Fitzgerald couldn't have done anything with, for their own short term political gains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-23 14:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nearly got hit on my scooter by some clown who didn't realise this at a T junction If I hand't taken a lifesaver check I would have been sent flying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-23 14:00:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Possibly due to both rugby and soccer being in English leagues, as oppossed to having their own ones, like with SPL and the NIFL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-23 13:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are Roscoff or Chereburg well equipped or positioned to take an influx of trucks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-17 13:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be the Christian symbolism that GFA wraps it in, as opposed to the more secular Belfast Agreement. Same kinda deal with Easter Rising </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-10 11:44:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like Bertie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-09 14:18:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've a direct debit with oxfam. In the last year I've given to BirdwatchIreland for their wetland restoration scheme and bits on the street to SVP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-07 19:54:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Charity that looks after war graves, and support for vets. Money for poppies here goes to the Irish branch of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-07 00:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. Which is why every government has been centre right since thre formation of the state! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-31 14:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well its being used as a counter to the much more popular thread about how awful Irish society is. A bit of pride has to go somewhere, no? Can't be moaning all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-15 20:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its for loose leaf tea. Adding the milk first means that the leaves stay at the bottom, and don't float about the cup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 15:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He followed them down the street after he was attacked and then stabbed one of them. That isn't self defence, that isn't in the heat of the moment. You shouldn't attack people in the street no, but you also shouldn't be carrying a knife around the streets either, and you cab absolutly be fully be held acountable for knowingly carrying a knife and then following someone with intent to use it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 15:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Downvoted for not advocating premeditated murder. Whats the story here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 11:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has two joint heads: The President of France, and the Bishop of Urgell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-09 22:51:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's about the goals of the organisations, whereas what /u/TotesThrowawayEire is getting at, if i'm not misreading him,is not that ISIS = IRA, but the reaction of the general public who are affected by the actions of these terrorist groups is to lump in all members of the same cultural/ethnic/religious groupings as the terrorist organisations with them. 

The goals and ideologies of the terrorist organisations is not what is being questioned here, but the reaction/fear/hate to other members of the societies from which they come.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-09 21:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  because of how ~~Irish~~ ~~Mayo~~ ~~Dublin~~ *Cavan* people say the word book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-09 17:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres like 10% forest coverage of land in Ireland, we've barely any and those we do have a mostly commercial forests with non-native pines. Until 16th-17th century there were plenty, all deforested for farmland or for shipbuilding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 21:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, its kinda hard to tell, cos OP has't provided where he's getting any of his data from/ methodology used. But generally speaking, most houses are timber framed, whereas there may be a higher concentration of stone thatch-roofed cottages in the Galway-Mayo area, but bugger if I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 17:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was a great interview. They do have 4-5 active podcasts all uploading around once a week, so I wouldn't say they are too infrequent. Obviously not on the same output as a radio station but theres a good level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 15:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its close to my heart. I'd also recommend something from the Cork band FRED who had the best live set I've seen (Running is a tune) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 14:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not going to be popular but some key artists are missing because of their inherent naffness:
Gilbert O'Sullivan - Alone Again (Naturally)

The Nolan Sisters - I'm in the mood for Dancing

Chris de Burgh - Spanish Train

Johnny Logan - Hold Me Now

Dana - All kinds of Everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 10:53:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stone houses in the Wesht as theres less timber basically </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 19:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you not drop the register of electors a line to clarify the situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 15:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clubs and Societies. Find something you are interested in, see if theres a group for it in your college and start going to their events, the only way I made any mates while in university </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 12:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd well believe its a tricky system, I know I wouldn't be arsed to do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 10:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just having ar read through the thread from when they were disabled. Thats one of the reasons given </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 10:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quoth baz: The were disabled because not enough people used them and they were an eyesore. The addition of the flair was a pain in the ring and has only lead to a lot of whinging from users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 10:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So they got rid of them because the flags were wrong and mods weren't arsed replacing them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-04 19:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh, she just refers to it as a popular tradition in "Potatoes, providence and philanthropy" in 1997, new evidence must have come to light, I stand corrected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-04 08:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't find an unsourced opinion piece in the examiner from a novelist to be good enough evidence. I don't have time to go through and do some more sleuthing around the myth right now, as I have to go to work, but I will come back to it this evening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-04 00:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the myth I'm referring to. I can't find any citation to say that this is true that he ever tried to give that amount, only that it was a story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-03 23:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not saying that what she gave couldn't have been greater, but 2000 was a heck of a lot of money. The only person I can find who there is even suggestion of wanting to donate more is the Ottoman Sultan, who is supposed to have initially offered 10,000. This doesn't seem to have actually happened, just another popular myth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-03 22:24:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Famine Queen thing is largely based on the myth that Victoria gave only 5 to the famine relief fund. She did in fact give 2000, which the Bank of England puts at 213,958.76 in today's money (using 1846 as start point) and was a patron of a charity dedicated to relief efforts, the British Relief Association, who she wrote appeal letters for which raised an additional 200,000 from the rest of the UK, Australia and the USA (over 21m today). 

As monarch, she wasn't head of government and didn't really have a lot of influence over policy, which can more appropriately placed at the feet of Lord Travelyon and Sir John Russell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-30 18:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They would want to rejoin the EU to be sure, but Spain would just veto any attempt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-29 21:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you don't like swearing then why fake it or obfuscate it? Why not say 'Sounds like a deeply unpleasant man' instead of comparing him to a 10th century Norse King?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-28 19:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> showed people a picture of his recently born niece I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-28 12:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the Grauniad bit. Even though I'm a subscriber I find that a lot of their Ireland content is absolutely woeful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-20 16:01:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well if she immigrates and obtains citizenship shes been living here for between 5-9 years, having been employed and living without state support for at least the last 3 years of that period. This suggests a necessity for a level of engagement with Irish society from non EEA nationals seeking Irish citizenship, which would include both you and this hypothetical Nigerian woman. And if she was accepted as a citizen through these criteria by the state and you weren't then yes she would be more Irish than you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-20 11:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well it also has a list of all TD attendences if anybody is interested in their own TDs record </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-08 16:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goes nowhere near tallaght. That'd be drunnk students affecting stops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-07 18:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Benefits of PPR STV you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-31 18:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was always nice to go to the bottom of a thread and see what he had written  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-30 10:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well since it seema like a lot of users here already contend both statistics, Iwouldnt call it having it both ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-30 10:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Net population drop doesn't necessarily mean that there are no nonIrish speakers moving to the areas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-23 19:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The seperate water is because traditionally hot water was stored in the house in a cistern, while the cold tap is drinkable water from the mains system. Thats still the case in my house at any rate, though I'm sure newer builds don't have it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 15:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A four foot box, a foot for every year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-14 15:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That aul lad is definitely being ironic. He's one of the few in that doc that seemed to make any steps to assimilation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-14 13:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Population density. S/E England is much more densly populated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 14:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say its more to do with the self-awarness of cultural quirks today that makes it seem more pervasive. 

Its also not just something for phone calls, as I can attest to spending half an hour at the door woth more than one slow leaver of a party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 19:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know a couple of lads who did it out of Weston who were pretty happy with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 18:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't it not make sense timeline bookwise though? The Others appear thousands of years after the Pact with tCotF and at the end of the Age of Heroes? Thats a hell of a long time to leave a superweapon just lying around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 17:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He also had the man he made the bargain with killed horribly. We should be watching our backs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 16:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Time passing can be made clear in a multitude of ways, through dialogue, especially during military manouvers,which can definitely be seen during the early seasons, or editing your scenes so we don't hop between two locations four or five times, which can make some character seem to be standing around doing nothing while others are hopping around the globe

Instead info is just withheld for a gotcha moment - the books do this too on occassion, but it gets very frustrating after a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 15:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or a failure of making the non-linear structure clear to audiences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-02 17:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, I always bring self healers and/or secondary healers to keep everbody afloat as insurance. 

He's great in a marking party for single action bosses as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-01 00:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well algorithms for online sections and social media links are  designed in such a way to show you content similar to what you've already engaged in, in order to generate more click-through. Which is why the most divisive or hyperbolic headlines tend to come to the fore, as those are the ones that are clicked through. What you are presented with on the internet is reflective of content you've already engaged in.

The Irish Times has not, to my knowledge, published unverified, uncorroborated hearsay, under the grounds that it is their journalistic duty, in a literal case of [fake news](https://www.buzzfeed.com/kenbensinger/these-reports-allege-trump-has-deep-ties-to-russia?utm_term=.yqknz2XY9P#.ic89ME1Dyq) like Buzzfeed has done in the past. That is what I mean when I do not put them on the same level.

I find that the Irish Times from the headlines, to the ledes, to the meat of the articles present information in a factual and cogent way, and opinion pieces is where that critique comes in, which is why they will have two or three articles on a single subject if it is large; the presentation of the facts in the main paper, with the opinion pieces further in the paper, these are the ones that gain more traction on social media - because they have the more subjective and clickable headlines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 22:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But that is exactly my point! No newspaper can be possibly be objective, so a variety of sources is necessary. My purpose with this was not to state that the Irish Times is some sort of paragon of virtue, but that there are degrees of bias, and Buzzfeed is far more egregious in this than IT. 

By the way, I've found that the political staff in the Irish Times, especially Pat Leahy tend to be quite critical of the far left, Solidarity in particular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 20:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you found the Irish Times to be intentionally spreading false information? What prejudice has the Irish Times, as opposed to its opinion columnists, perpetuated? What news source would you say provides a completely objective viewpoint?

On that, I'm going to disagree with the assessment that news is supposed to be unbiased. Bias does not equal dishonesty, If there was no bias in how any media outlet chose to show the news it would be a stream of information without context which would be confusing or overwhelming. What a newspaper chooses to lets say, place on the front page, or give an op-ed to, is a sign of bias; based on what they think is the most important issue of the day, which is something that another paper might disagree with.

I would say that the US's problem with media has more to do with its 24hr news cycle than bias, and the fact that each of the main media outlets have to constantly emphisise the importance of what is happening *right now* to retain viewership and that sweet, sweet, ad revenue. Partisanship also plays a major role in this but that shouldn't be equated with bias </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-30 22:20:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having a left leaning editorial staff =/= Irish Buzzfeed.
The Irish times has its issues but its not a sensationalist or histrionic paper in its coverage, at least outside of the opinions section, and even then it has histrionics from all walks of life and political leaning, including Breda O'Brien and Nicholas Pell, who are far from bleeding-hearted liberals.

If your interpretation of what true journalism means is so rigid that the Irish Times is voided entirely means that your going to have a hard time finding any news source, regardless of the political leaning of its editors, that would match your rigorous standards.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-28 16:55:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Redditors can't understand irony without a /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 14:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Large sugarcane plantations mayhaps?
Gin and Hennssy being luxury items and therfore desirable?
Abundance of fruit plantations in southern usa and carribean?
Sugar tastes good which is why everybody likes it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 14:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because they also have access to sugary based drinks. If you look at one of the links I posted further up beer has a huge market in west africa, and I can personally attest to the popularity of beer in south africa and swaziland. I would say the popularity of fruit based drinks among black people in the states is cultural, as in African American culture more so than some inherent trait, and even this ignores the popularity of malt whiskey amomg African Americans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 14:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cider, a heavily sugary drink, is popular in southern UK and northern France

Buckfast tonic wine is popular in Ireland and Scotland. 

Schnapps is famous in Southern Germany and Austria.

Its almost as of people regardless of the colour of their skin, or the culture in which they were raised, enjoy alcoholic beverages of whatever base they can get their hands on. 

I'm not saying that black people don't like sugary drinks, sugar is an addictive substance that effects everbody. 

I'm not downvoting you or calling you a racist, but mate, the whole thesis ignores the complexities of available crops, soil, and differing societal make up in an over 20million km2 area for one set of peoples (subsaharan africans). While waving off a similar approach to another group (southern europeans). Does that not seem a bit off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 01:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I've done some digging around, and while agricultural technology in precolonial Africa is not as advanced as in other parts of the world, it did, in fact exist, with written evidence from European explorers in 16th century, with high yields of millet. www.jstor.org/stable/3601888
Millet having been cultivated in Africa since at least around 2500 BC
https://www.thoughtco.com/pearl-millet-domestication-170647

Dr Schaer institute puts a higher percentage population with celiac's disease in Western Sahara, compared to USA and Germany, however I would not extrapolate that to cover the whole of Subsaharan africa, which would have a huge diversity in child nutrition and intestinal flora, which would also be factors. http://www.drschaer-institute.com/us/professional-articles/a-global-map-of-celiac-disease-1229.html

They don't prefer wine, they like beer too, it's just that land was better for grape so that became their culture

Cereal beers are popular in subsaharan africa btw, with massive brewing operations for domestic and export in Ghana and Nigeria. 
http://www.vanguardngr.com/2017/06/breweries-battle-increase-beer-market-share/

All this is bearing in mind that the original conjecture, that Africans choose to drink Hennessy because it is fruitbased, as they all come from hunter-gather societies, which ignores the agriculture that has existed in Africa for thousands of years, and therefore don't like cereal based drinks. All on a reddit post, about a twitter joke comparing gangster rappers to grannies in Killmallock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 00:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll take the bait. First off, by the logic employed here all southern European countries are hunter-gatherer in nature because they prefer wine. 
Secondly, there is evidence of cereal based agriculture in parts of Africa from about 5000BC, with plenty of cereal crops originating there, like millet or sorghum. To keep an image of the entire continent of Africa from a lifestyle similar to the bushmen of the Kalahri would be like basing your understanding of all European agriculture on the traditional herding of the Sami people. Geography dictates what is the smart choice of food to eat, not inherent bias from somebody's race </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 17:35:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Higgins is, but he wouldn't be representative of Labour's parliamentary leadership, which is much more centerist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 17:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Camp claude - Hero </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-19 23:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-19 13:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, but it doesn't make it any less either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-18 15:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did History and Classics and am now working as a database admin. Final year knocked any ideas of a career in academia right out of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-18 13:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quare can mean very, or it can be strange and out of the ordinary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 19:47:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose its a confusion between myself and others over a condemnation of scumbag loyalists in general, and a condemnation of scumbag loyalists in this specific instance, ie attacking firemen. I find a lot about loyalism abhorrent, but a holier than thou attitude about how idiotic, violent, or self-destructive people can be on both sides of the border is unhelpful. But whatever, down vote don't communicate, the traditional reddit way; its part of the culture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 17:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mud's a pretty practical building material in subsaharan Africa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 14:50:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.irishtimes.com/news/ireland/irish-news/firefighters-attacked-during-halloween-call-outs-1.2412164?mode=amp

Drunken idiots will be drunken idiots, regardless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-09 21:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope he has more screentime than Djimon Hounsou did in Guardians of the Galaxy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 14:30:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lede </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-25 20:49:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stand corrected! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-25 19:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or Coptic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-20 14:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A couple of factors are at play here. One is that a large portion of the SNP's voter base would be rightleaning/conservative, and as the party has switched to more leftist policy positions those voters are naturally migrating back to the Tories. It would be a bit much to see it as a rejection of independence,  but to a rejection of any idea of holding a second referendum so soon after the last one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-20 13:47:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This boggles my mind too. Cycle lane on my route is elevated, new and well maintained, covers a long stretch, with plenty of opportunities to get onto it from cyclists joining from a junction and I only ever see aul lads and school kids on it. Everybody else just uses the road </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-15 09:04:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think I've ever heard reporters say Bundeskanzler though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-09 14:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up the ulster plantations and ulster unionism. TLDR Northern Irish doesn't always equal Irish (In how one identifies oneself) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-08 12:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bit late to register though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-05 23:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He didn't ask for her to resign, the interview put the question to him, and he could hardly say he was confident in her leadership could he? Its a bit of a shot across the bows, and the independent, rag that it is, gets those juicy juicy clicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-02 00:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's fair. I would argue that human development will in the long term be helped by action to reduce the impacts of climate change, but I have a fairly comfortable living situation, so perhaps I've blinders to the effects on lower skilled labour (although I feel the implimentation of some form of universal basic income could help alleviate this).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-01 23:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slightly further down:
*Narendra Modis government has promised to get 40% of  its electricity from non-fossil sources (renewable and nuclear) by 2030, with finance and technology sharing from wealthier countries. The CEA proposal would mean the non-fossil share would increase to 53% as early as 2027, up from 31% today, without relying on international support.*

India's moving away from reliance on coal usage, and towards renewable energy sources, or at least the intention of it is to be applauded.

For the record, while only 15% of american power is in coal, 37% is from oil, and a further 29% is natural gas, making fossil fuel usage 81%, while India's total fossil fuel usage, by percentage is only 67%

https://www.eia.gov/EnergyExplained/?page=us_energy_home

http://cea.nic.in/reports/monthly/installedcapacity/2017/installed_capacity-04.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-01 22:40:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You must have missed this one
http://www.climatechangenews.com/2016/12/16/india-to-halt-building-new-coal-plants-in-2022/http://www.climatechangenews.com/2016/12/16/india-to-halt-building-new-coal-plants-in-2022/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-01 17:43:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh sorry, I get you now. Way sentence and quote were framed I thoght you thought rte had gotten the number of years sentenced wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-01 17:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats his dad, who was also invovled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-31 01:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah stop codding, Seal's an attractive man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-29 18:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'm going to preface my next statement by saying that I don't agree with a lot of the comments in this thread. A lot of class snobbery going on.

However, things gain more traction when you yourself court the public eye, which Conor obviously does. He revels in it, and uses it to help further his career, and more power to him. And again I'll reiterate taking a boat in between the bouys isn't nice no matter who you are. I could be taking this to heart a bit, was a big Kirsty MacColl fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-29 15:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Using jetskis and power boats in water designated for swimming isn't nice either, regardless of who you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-12 09:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They'd be shitting bricks in Montrose if they thought we might actually win, safer and cheaper to do it this way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A solicitor is a weird person to go for MP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:38:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is Irish in quotation marks there OP? There's nothing in the article that suggests he isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the new album... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Stagecoach woes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi guys, just coming towards the end of my first run, one boss to go and then on t the DD. My problem is that I only seem to be getting new recruits from the same 4 or 5 classes: Vestal, Houndmaster, Hellion, Occultist, and Graverobber. No matter how many weeks go by these are the only ones that appear. I'd like to have at least one BH on the roster before going for the DD, any info on how to get a more diverse stagecoach? Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rush </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well thats a move towards federalisation. While it does empower the people of Europe as a whole, it removes power from national governments, which would be seen as an erosion of national soverignty. No government wants to reduce its own powerbase, and many in the citizenry don't want it either. Which leaves us with a half measure that in order to ensure the soverignty of the member states the people are pretty much removed from power, as the European Parliament have no real legislative power. This in part leads to the high level of apathy you see across the EU, with only about 40% voting in EU elections. Even in Ireland where the EU has quite broad support but few people vote in MEP elections, because the electorate is so far removed. Personally I would be in favour of either having the the EU Commissioner directly elected, and they then choose their commissioners, or all of the Commissioners forming out of the MEPs, power to the people etc. I do howecer understand why others would disagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the The Elder Dragon version. It kinda goes into the tradition of divine justice and retribution for not respecting guest right, in the vein of Greek and Norse mythology (and in many other cultures I'm sure) of respect for the host and for the guest.  It might help remind the murderhobos that they're living in a world and a society that exists outside of the adventuring sphere. If that's what the group is going for anyway, otherwise murderhobo to one's heart's content! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? Guards at my local station signed mine no bother, and I don't know a soul nearby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:32:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I would suppose in many ways we are in agreement, and our disagreement is one of terminology. Voyagers to the West by Bernard Bailyn sheds some serious light on how appaling it was for English and Scottish indentured servants if you're interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Never said indentured servitude wasn't bad or inhumane
2. An indentured servamt never lost their legal personhood, so they could retain persobal property, and take cases against mistreatment, which they sometimes won. These are not things that happen to a chattel slave that is not a person but property
3. My point was not that the Irish have never had it as bad, but that the messaging of the linked post is to further the belief that the Irish have had it the worst, and uses this to justify an anti-welfare state position because they have worked hard, and others supposedly have not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which isn't in the West Indies. The slave trade of the Barbary Pirates was a seperate horrible trade network. The point isn't that  no Irish person ever was a slave, but that this line of thinking that the irish indentured servants in the West Indies were in  the same position as African slaves or worse is just plan wrong. And the implication in the facebook post is that the Irish have bettered their position by the has work that the black community has not shown, and coming from a worse position. Which is simply not true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How are the translations? Is it just text and barks pr naration as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As opposed to the massive amount of excessive drinking they'll see, which will be formative  and character building </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. There is a separate test for Motorbikes, the AM, with some of the questions being the same as the car one, rules of the road etc. It does have some motorbike specific questions - personal safety equipment, motorbike specs and the like.
2. Separate test for Car provisional unfortunately
3. From [my reading](http://www.rsa.ie/en/RSA/Learner-Drivers/Motorcyclists/The-Motorcycle-Test/) it doesn't seem like it, just need to hold learner permit for 6 months
4. Go for the basic training, I did and I was much more confident as a road user for it
5. Same booklet for cars and motorcycles, just with separate sections, can be found online, or most bookshops I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:08:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A problem shared is a problem halved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Contextualise might have been a better word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IF they weren't thinking about it and making plans now, and it did come to pass in two years time, people would be giving out about their lack of cop on and preparedness. Having a plan doesn't mean they are going to implement it unless they have to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tu quoque! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still at committee stage. Won't be out until March, and it'll be shite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stand corrected! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just back from a ski trip there, at a lovely spot outside of Salzburg. The Austrians are incredibly friendly and inviting.

For current affairs if you've been keeping up, the greens won the presidential election on the third try after a couple of fuckups with postal voters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody shows up to anything on time, if they show up at all... even after you said you were going the night before, Amy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-21 14:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Powers with a drop of water. Wouldn't be a regular drink for me though, more of a Smithwicks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-17 00:26:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well they'd have to rebrand Six One News </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP was complaining that the clearly xenophobic rasits weren't our clearly xenophoic rasists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The process takes a while, a few months. I applied for one at the end of June, notice after second round wasn't until October. I'd still go for it if I were you, but I wouldn't be relying on them to get employed in the immediate term </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While I can't say if its due to the ads, as opposed to safer cars/roads, more education, or enforcement(ala penalty points, speed traps), the trend in road deaths in Ireland is actually going down, and has done so pretty consistently, apart from a slight rise in 2013-2014.

Links:

* Death and Injury stats 1961-2007: http://www.garda.ie/Controller.aspx?Page=10717 Lang=1

* Deaths 2008-2013: http://www.garda.ie/Documents/User/Fatalities%202008-2013.pdf

* Traffic stats 2014: http://www.garda.ie/Controller.aspx?Page=12511 Lang=1

* Traffic stats 2015: http://www.garda.ie/Controller.aspx?Page=14573 Lang=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-29 12:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Judging from the exit poll for the GE done on the sub this year I wouldn"t say thats the case

https://docs.google.com/forms/d/164Tg1hp55K_P-6Eg-Hk32ld7Y8qzfUAt2NdwJTmowwI/viewanalytics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think there's an argument to be made for 'economic migrants' outside of the 1840s-50s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The contraction in that case is for had
 
We had noticed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That artwork seriously reminds me of mike mignola </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing on the scale of the O'Shea scandal that I've seen. Most of the works I've read have been very dry political ones though, Terence de Vere White's 'the Road to Excess' is supposed to be a more personal one, and the title suggests some sordid details, but haven't looked at it myself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-26 21:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, he's pretty overshadowed by Parnell, I only heard about him because I happened to be in Ballybofey a few years ago and saw a bust </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you're right, apologies! I may have confused it with the federal system, which Butt proposed as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ceased to exist following the Act of Union 1800,  its been single United Kingdom since. Isaac Butt mooted a dual monarchy as an idea in the 1870s, but pretty much off the agenda since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-29 11:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did mine on the Rape of Nanking,  particularly on the Nanking Safety Zone. My advise would be to get a mix of sources, primary and secondary, around 6-10 will do ya. A few journal articles would be a plus if you can get them, but books will do just fine. Try to be aware of where your sources are coming from in how they are constructing their narratives, a few comments on why one historian argues a particular point, and a another disagrees pads out your wordcount and shows you are engaging with the material.

Pick a topic that you find interesting, so it won't be too much of a strain to write a long essay about and do some research on, and delvong onto the particulars. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-16 13:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Overconfidence is a slow and insideous killer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If they are going through a junction where you have a green light, or are on the larger road at a junction, then no they do not have right of way, a horse and trap has to follow the rules of the road. However, you really do have to be careful driving around them, a horse can spook easily, and being in the right is poor consolation if there's an accident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-29 14:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the comprehensive list! I'll be sure to check them out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking to learn Irish with limited free time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-28 21:35:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I was thinking about having another stab at learning Irish, I'm out of school six years now and I'd like to give it a go, but I don't have much free time to go to conversation classes. Has anybody used an Irish language learning app like Rosetta Stone or Duolingo? Are they any use? Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The eu would be looser than us national government. There are federalists who would like a much closer europe, and without a largley euroskeptic UK membership, the federalists are likely to have a stronger position in Parliament. As to how the EU works, it is very complicated, which is what happens when you try to get so many nations to agree on anything. CGP Grey has a good stab at explaining it: https://youtu.be/O37yJBFRrfg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:46:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi not exactly an expert but I'll try to help! This will have amassive effect on world relations from Britain's percpective. A lot of trade agreements with the rest of the world were negotiated through the EU. This means that Britain will need to renegotiatw all of these deals, disentangle itself from the EU, abd then establish a trade deal with the EU.

To answer your second question the EU is kind of both. It a political and economic union of 26 soverign nations, some of which share a single currency. There is a central European Parliament which votes on laws, however these laws don't cover every aspect of the law of the member nations, and there are still national governments. TheUK leaving is a very complicated issue, how much eu law will no longer be in effect, how it will interact with the reat of the eu, will therebe a manned border between th uk and roi? These sort of things are likely to keep eu law experts in pocket for the nect few years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-23 00:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone needs a lozenge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Given the general make-up of the poll being men under thirty, not to mention redditors, I think this won't be particularly representative of the national vote. However, if people keep with these voting patterns it'd be interesting to see if the political landscape shifts in the next 10 years or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-20 22:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is reciprocated in the Republic as well, with UK citizens getting to vote on elections that other EU citizens can't, such as general elections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-13 23:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Connolly also wasn't a member of the IRB, him and the ICA were only brought in after the other Rising leaders caught wind that he was planning a separate rebellion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-30 17:21:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really in Europe; in fact many knights would engage in banditry and raiding themselves in peace times, and would attack the peasantry. One of the reasons that the First Crusade was called was so that Pope Urban II could give the Frankish nobility a target to stop them fighting and killing each other and innocents.

The literary tradition of the chivalric code of the knight protecting the innocent and saving damsels in distress was much more prominent in the literary tradition of medieval Europe, in the *chasons de geste* and romantic poetry, than in reality. this romantic idealism of knights continues today through the works of Walter Scott and other 19th century romantic writers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-30 02:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A short answer would be yes, there were knightly organisations that helped the poor. The powerful knightly orders, such as the Hospitallers and the Templars were formed to protect pilgrims on their travels and provide shelter. 

Both of these organisations were founded following the First Crusade, providing armed escorts for pilgrims travelling through the Holy Lands to protect them against brigands, and setting up hospitals and hospices. As time went on they became more powerful, gaining land and wealth. 

The Templars in particular were given some extraordinary rights by the Papacy, such as in *Omne Datum Optimum*, 'every perfect gift' which exempted the order from taxes and tithes. This made them a powerful financial institution and they engaged in moneylending, this moneylending is probably why Philip IV had many of the Templars in France tried for heresy and burned at the stake in 1314. So to answer your question the knightly orders became powerful factions out of their position of helping pilgrims.

Sources:

Barber, Malcolm   Bate, A. K. *The Templars: Selected Sources*. Manchester, 2002.

Hindley, Geoffrey. *A Brief History of the Crusades: Islam and Christianity in the Struggle for World Supremacy*. London, 2003.

Edit: Formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>