<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7517</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 22:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the wording currently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 19:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both Jailor and mafioso claimed Jailor D1 and fought about it a ton.

Janitor cleans Jailor N1

Another maf claims to be med and says he was [important town role]

Maf was really lucky RT/TS didnt have a red or real med </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 19:06:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The role list would confirm. Its like escort and consort (minus sheriff inv results) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> XP Farm Me 4447 2551 4433 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 05:27:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I open gifts daily. Just in it for the xp. I send gifts when I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 02:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. They really miscast Alaska from the southern, curvy, charming portion. Havent seen it yet, but in the book her thing is sex appeal, particularly in her body type </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 07:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to assume that the video is informative in nature and regards arms sales. 

 #x200B;

1) Identify the arguments that you find yourself drawn to in the video - do they tell a story? If so, what is that story?

2) Break down the "story" into 1AC contentions. Inherency, plan, solvency, \[framing\]

3) Take each contention, and figure out the arguments that comprise it. 

4) Find a card for each argument. 

5) Figure out what arguments are missing and fill them in (does it look like a typical aff?)

6) Because you're a novice, take other's 2AC blocks and modify them so they make sense to both you and your aff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 07:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For just warming up? My usual routine is do a 1AC/Typical 1NC slowly, then top speed, then average speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 07:18:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like the concept, but I think a few factors are missing. The ones I caught were: religion raised, sexual orientation, and location </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 06:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awwww it's okay love. There's always room to learn, even if those in your game were harsh. Jsyk, psychic is meh hard to fake (think LO, tracker, crusader), so the worst you can do is get lynched and reveal a couple confirmed evils in your will through visions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> XP Farm Me 3 (4447 2551 4433) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 06:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 17:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I. Interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 02:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not editing this, just throwing together my thoughts. 

Diction - [Strangles](https://politics.theonion.com/gop-lawmakers-watch-silently-as-trump-strangles-each-of-1838885386), emphasis on how much trump sucks

Diction - wait-and-see approach, refers to actual politics, thus why the onion is emulating real political websites

Metaphor (extended) - strangled all their loved ones to death.

You could do some irony thing with how the president's role is to protect their citizens. 

Hyperbole - ometimes a bit outside the ordinary

Diction - ommander-in-chief asphyxiated

Allusion - barbed wire (likely to the wall or another barrier of some sort) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 04:23:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oof, I was wondering if we had the same course program </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 02:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ShmilyLin1

Oh, me too! Did you by any chance have summer homework with 3(?) essays and a book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 02:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't taken AP spanish yet, but I think that the majority of the class is understanding what the AP test wants from you (but what else is new). As long as you have a decent idea of conjugation and know your vocab, you should be good to just take a few practice tests and have a native speaker or teacher review it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 02:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AP students, homie. Have a bit of academic integrity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 00:49:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Palmer's great. Would recommend giving it a read. Even if it's just once and like, 24 hours before the AP test, it's a really great, "brief" overview of everything you need to know. It's also less fluff-filled than other Euro textbooks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 00:39:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yooo same here. The teacher had summer hw which I obviously wasn't in the loop for. Shoutout to staying after school with the teacher for 1/2 an hour then going home and working for another 2 hours. (fr though my teacher is the best) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 21:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I helped write the umich 1033 aff. Hmu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 04:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My AP lit class focuses heavily on essays after the first few tests to try and ease us into the question format of the AP test. I'm currently trying to develop a good writing strategy (quick and concise) to be more efficient. Idk if it's the best idea, but it's the one I'm using </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 04:27:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do they purposely make the problems harder so that it takes more time/thinking to figure it out? Also you're crazy lucky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 03:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 03:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're looking in the wrong place, love. People here are high school aged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 02:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If your altering isn't the cause of it, you can "paste without formatting" to remove any potential places in which the website's data might look like a tag to verbatim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 14:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll keep that in mind. My teacher has always said that you can pretty much do whatever as long as you have a key. Do you have any idea about how it's represented on the test? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 06:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're actually kinda asinine, but think of it this way

4|20

4 is the stem

20 is the leaf

 #x200B;

So, first you look at the stem, which usually indicates the largest digit value. Then, the leaves are placed directly beside the stem to create data points. Commas afterward are used to separate numbers. 

They're usually used to look at the rough shape of a set of data, but you shouldn't come across it too much aside from the "familiarise yourself with visualised data" unit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 06:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck bro. It's 11 where I'm from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Daily Player - 4447 2551 4433 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 02:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I open gifts daily. I try my best to send gifts to highest friendship level friends. I'm basically a free xp farm if anybody's interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 02:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you okay with a person who only opens gifts? The nearest pokestop is really far away from me :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 04:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completed this, but I'm not sure if it matters because I'm under the age of 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 04:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, it technically is. Comparative to other AP classes, it's one of the easier ones in terms of concepts. However, the majority of it is just being extremely cautious with explanations. It's one of those classes that allows for \*creative freedom\* as in there's like, 3 ways to be correct but 5000 ways to fuck them up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 19:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should probably explain how you got to the outliers that you identified. The AP test will accept a variety of answers (within reason) as long as you explain your thought process with either an equation or actual words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 19:43:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Psych isn't that bad. I just had to read over the textbook once or twice. Would recommend taking notes on \*SOME\*, but the majority of it is common sense and previous knowledge from other AP classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 19:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, it's just so much work over in my class. Thank god I have the most passionate teacher ever. 

 #x200B;

We just started our normal curves unit and half of the class was my teacher drawing bad bell curves and yelling "NO" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help a rural student out 4447 2551 4433 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 06:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 23:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tabroom is your friend. Octofinals results are in. Quarters just ended </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 16:15:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to stutter really badly from nerves, but tbh when I got fast enough I really zeroed in on reading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 19:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 21:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's your trick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-23 03:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started with reading sim and sim. I didnt find it particularly helpful with debate but it did help with reading other K lit because I started with a more upper level book. I dont think many books are good for debate, but it was quite fun and interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 17:52:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its the dermis. It looks like styrofoam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 22:21:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here! Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 00:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Three. Days. Grace. Good shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 03:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8:16? Seems like youre already doing the majority of it already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 03:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the dialogue but if youve seen the anime already, itll ruin the mystery. However, you get to know the characters a hell of a lot better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 03:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have notes from the mich one. Dm email (use a throwaway if you dont wanna share irl names) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 07:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 20:47:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough. Sorry idk much about that quest line since I just evolved the Dratini </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 20:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. I dont know but the quest prior to evolving a Dratini gives you a Dratini 

2. Perhaps you should just not evolve unless necessary for gyms or raids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I send gifts and do things </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 16:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4447 2551 4433
Lol I just need to finish the special research </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-10 00:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Based on ahoge, kibo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 20:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's entirely effects T. The effects of the plan lead to a net decrease in immigration. However, the plan does not meet

Reducing restrictions on legal immigration

Most teams focused their research around visas for immigration rather than the immigration system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 20:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currently, the affs that are slightly obscure revolve around a specific type of arm being restricted. Those typically access soft left impacts. I'd look to Umich's Mexico small arms aff as an example. However, I wouldn't recommend it because the cards lack specificity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 01:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah thats some satanic shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> R/pokemongo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-08 17:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 18:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shane Dawsons jefree star clip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 17:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My go-to, but pretty bad for learning how to do proper impact calc work. It gets you really good at framing/knowing your aff, but your team will suffer when reading a hard right impact vs a hard right aff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 21:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You a real hydrohomie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 16:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on what you work on. For me, its breathing. I do

A normal spread of an 8 min speech
Overenunciation of the same speech
Normal spread of 8m speech
Backwards drill until I get cross eyed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-01 15:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a different account. The only benefit reaped is help in raids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 23:18:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rip. Guess I dont have that problem because my dad (who requested the cam) is in a different country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 23:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My security cam keeps falling over. 10/10 would recommend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 16:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol you might be in my lab. Debate camp helps everybody to the extent that they want to be helped. Just remember that once lab is done for the day, people go to the dorms and start prepping like, immediately. What you see in lab is not necessarily a reflection of how much people work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 16:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't say it's "inspiring" per say, but it did help non ED people understand eating disorders a bit more. It's really well made, but Hollywood really likes its tricks and camera angles to make everybody SO SKINNY. My god, it's like thinspo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 19:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> W A T E R </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hydration boiiiiis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 19:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 22:26:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Icy hot is my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 14:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend with hypoglycaemia. She sometimes skips meals but keeps energy gels (for runners) if shes feeling woozy. I havent seen her skip more than two meals, so depending on how you deal maybe consider IF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 14:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Start with shorter fasts to see where your threshold is. Then, start pushing it. I recommend looking into techniques the moment you feel unwell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 17:21:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Part of PTSD is forgetting small bits of info regarding trauma. For most, this manifests itself in the world's most confusing flashbacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 17:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makeup gains too! I'm proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 17:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thigh gap babyyyyyy!!! Looks so good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Medical ID questions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 17:09:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've started having crippling flashbacks in public. My flashbacks generally involve me being unresponsive, in the fetal position, hyperventilating. Friends of mine have confirmed that if they did not know about my condition, they would've called an ambulance.

 #x200B;

Thus, I've been considering a medical ID bracelet that lists conditions, symptoms, and a request for people not to call an ambo. What should be written on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 16:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google [campname] [year] google sites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 22:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive gotten to fat, but it wasnt very enjoyable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thinspo Reddits? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 18:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 17:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The starter packs for camp should be mostly out. I recommend an hour for looking over the formatting, but start cutting cards ASAP. The first few might not be too good, but itll help familiarize you with the topic. Also, t cards are best for analyzing the structure of the res which should make research easier for you if you start there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 03:00:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anemia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 18:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro, it doesnt matter how you get the PTSD. Were here to empathise no matter what. Were all together in this fight. Dont feel like ur experiences are lesser or anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 17:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adrenaline is powerful shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 03:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 03:04:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clothing. Casts are a last resort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 01:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SUBTELY discourage Ed related behaviour. Something along the lines of did you wanna finish those crisps? Or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 01:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big mood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 21:13:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neosporin doesn't help, but it does prevent any potential worsenings. Perhaps a clothing cover-up or some high quality foundation would be better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 17:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If its blood sugar, maybe ease off the aspartame for a bit. It triggers your system into thinking its real sugar, which leads it into fake processing the cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>