<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject331</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Answers don't match the questions. College education has no gender as far as I know. But my income could well be "no". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 20:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is once a year the lowest possible amount to visit a health professional in a year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 10:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mark Williams was ranked 16th in 1997 and I think he had never qualified before that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-07 12:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would specialize in birds, reptiles and insects. As it's way too cold here, it would either be mainly inside plus nice pastures during summer or I would have to move to a warmer country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-07 11:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The goth is here to stay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-07 11:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I won a summer job at a tech competition. Sadly the job turned out to be marketing and as I am a young woman they wanted me to do social media stuff and marketing emails etc which I'm totally clueless about. Fair to say I was pretty mad and also totally useless. IT department then rescued me as it was a small company and everyone knew eachother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 10:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Women who drink and dress provocatively deserve what they get." What am I supposed to answer here? If they get compliments, a nice pet, a raise or find a partner sure they deserve it, but if this is  implying  harassment then absolutely not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 15:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Iceland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 15:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alfred J. Kwak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 17:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lovely! So many sighthounds, I was certainly lucky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 14:09:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 12  per hour or 50  a month for unlimited play at the local club. At least the tables are amazing and the club is near my apartment so no additional travelling costs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-13 11:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why nearsighted and farsighted are the only options? I'm neither, but wear glasses for astigmatism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-09 16:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty funny questions for a maths student </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-07 22:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lost it when I chose to do statistics on top of pure maths. Now I just want to become a peacock farmer and forget everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-06 12:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no option to take no medication for a headache </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-31 20:23:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paying for composting? I probably would if it wasn't a free service and now I'm confused and realized it might not be free everywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-08 01:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wearing glasses. Retrospectively thinking that should be pretty obvious. I rarely need my glasses for everyday activities but there's enough astigmatism to throw off depth and angles. Who would have thought that might impact my game...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 15:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't really know how to feel about physical contact. It doesn't bother me at all, but I definitely wouldn't say I like it. Luckily showing affection is not a big deal in my culture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-02 16:24:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, but the following questions don't make any sense if your family is indeed totally non-religious. Some sort of NaN option would maybe solve the issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-02 11:01:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only people with religious family and upbringing can answer this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 16:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love darkness, but hate everything else about winter. October and November are perfect as long as snow stays away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 20:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He would solve 90% of Europe's problems ...or wait was it less than 10% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 13:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It felt like finding an easy and obvious answer to a really complex question. Also the way I viewed relationships pretty much immediately changed. It wasn't some annoying must do thing that the society had cursed upon everyone after all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 21:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's possible to use more than one operating system, so I couldn't answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-11 19:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Potted yellow along the cushion almost the whole lenght of the table and from a pretty bad position to begin with, but I had a nice lead and decided to go for it anyway. I was so excited I missed the next easy green by a mile...

Highest break is 15 but I'm getting better (hopefully) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 14:36:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have experienced that weird rib thingy. I can feel one of my lower ribs shift and move when wearing a corset and quite often without a corset too. My lower ribs flare out a bit and are quite flexible which could probably cause the odd movements.

About the sore back, I remember my Orchard corset having a very straight and stiff back and it took some extra work to slightly bend it to my natural curve. Maybe the fit just isn't quite right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 13:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Switzerland (French speaking part)

How unorganized can you be, seriously? Also heavily armed police always frightens me and I start to worry about why they are needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 19:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After sauna I jumped naked into snow. The snow had a really sharp crust, almost like glass. Cut both my shins pretty badly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 16:02:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Star Wars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 15:42:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. It would take nearly an hour by bike now that I checked some possible routes. There's absolutely nothing but swamps, two motorways, a gigantic cemetary and an aiport between my home and the campus. The bus uses the motorway so it's really quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 15:30:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Russian, Python, embroidery and snooker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 14:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10 minutes by bus and that's literally my only option to get to the campus. Walking is not an option as there is a motorway and an airport blocking my way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>