<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7866</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 21:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! It's not that I don't love the shoes, it took me a while to get used to them so I \*know\* they're perfectly normal but it's the area between my knees and ankles that looks weird. I think the jeans might be a little too tight, especially around my calves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 21:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also think it's the pants. I KNOW the shoes are okay, so the weird feeling must come from the pants. I've gotten a bit fed up with skinny jeans, so I tried straight-legged ones and they're not ideal either. I wish there was something in between! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 18:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those sleeves! \*heart-eyes emoji\*

(I also like your other outfits!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 18:13:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 35 / rural France / high school teacher

Trying to dress my age while being a bit more daring than what I used to wear (t-shirt, sweaters and jeans). I have to do with being 5'10" and having wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not super fashion conscious and I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/8bWFSlA): For a very long day of teaching.

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/yuz44tz): For a very short day of teaching ^(\^\^)

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/2TIlmp3): No teaching on Wednesday, just grocery shopping, various errands and meeting up with a friend.

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/tW0Anq7): I've had these derbies for years and they're cute and comfortable, but I simply don't know how to wear them with pants. They look okay with skirts and black tights, but I felt super weird uncomfortable all day long with these skinny jeans (and I don't know why). I loved the top part of my outfit, though. 

[Friday](https://imgur.com/M2nNZbA): Same outfit as last Monday. My car broke down and I had a hellish day but at least I looked cute and I was comfortable enough to run around and try to find another car while mine was getting towed (a coworker ended up lending me hers, phew!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 18:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's okay for fall and winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 16:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely agree with the slimmer pants option. I don't know why I forgot the very simple rule "loose at the top, tight at the bottom"!

I don't wear pencil skirts because they make my wide hips look even wider, but I wonder if the batwing sleeves would divert the attention from the bottom to the top part of my silhouette... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 15:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is something I will have to try next year. Right now, the cold and rainy season is starting so I will only be able to wear boots for the next six months (\*sigh\*)

English is not my native language, would you mind explaining to me the difference between mules and slides? I googled "slides" but all I get is... flip-flops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 20:23:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I check your comment every Sunday and I *really* love how you manage to rotate the same pieces and yet create an entirely different outfit every time. That pink blazer is amazing, love the length. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 20:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That green sweater is amazing. Still a huge fan of your outfits! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 20:05:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a s'utilise en Alsace aussi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 18:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 35 / rural France / high school teacher

Trying to dress my age while being a bit more daring than what I used to wear (t-shirt, sweaters and jeans). I have to do with being 5'10" and having wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not super fashion conscious and I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/xy5TBTJ): The photo was taken before the sun rose so colors are a bit off. It's my usual black skirt with a forest green sweater.

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/FJhoyBc): I really love batwing sweaters. I feel that this was not a good pants or shoes choice though.

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/1QbTu6f): I was all set to return this skirt which highlighted my hips in ways I didn't like, but wearing it with thicker tights and a sweater somehow made it look okay?

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/fEdOvyK): The knit kimono is homemade and I'm super proud of it, even though I'm having difficulty finding what to pair it with.

[Friday](https://imgur.com/9JlvyKW): If you've seen my posts in the last month, you must have seen this skirt half a dozen times because I'm wearing it at least once a week.

Unfortunately, I think this was the last week I wore heels for a while... What started as a mildly uncomfortable feeling in my feet when school started again has turned into excruciating pain whenever I wear heels even for an hour. Dr Google told me I might have metatarsalgia or capsulitis so until I see a podiatrist in a week, I give up on heels and solemnly promise to only wear flat shoes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 20:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> French teacher here. There are several ways of becoming a teacher in my country, which correspond to your #2 (closed application). 

The first is the "concours": competitive exams that determine if you can become a teacher or not (only the top XXX candidates make the cut  the number changes every year and is different in all subjects). To take the exam, you need to have validated the first year of a Master's Degree, and you will need to complete the second year during your first year as a student-teacher. 

Another way is to be a contract worker. These teachers did not take or pass the aforementioned exams but apply to the local teaching authorities who decide to give them a job or not. AFAIK, the requirements are to have completed at least 2 years of college studies. The selection is much less strict but contract workers make less money than tenured teachers. 

Contract workers are still a minority (10% of all teachers) but the number keeps growing for various reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 20:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I crocheted a blanket last year and had a double-page chart in my bujo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 19:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love your skirt and dress outfits! They look so elegant and comfy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 19:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 35 / rural France / high school teacher

Trying to dress my age while being a bit more daring than what I used to wear (t-shirt, sweaters and jeans). I have to do with being 5'10" and having wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not super fashion conscious and I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/9txGW4B): For a long day at work and two trips on foot under the rain.

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/czv3A5e): This was the last time I wore ballet flats and cuffed pants. It's now way too cold (close to freezing) in the early morning.

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/c4GlO3p): Trying to find the energy to go grocery shopping under pouring rain.

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/yiDmRPr): I like flared jeans but they always look so weird in photos!

[Friday](https://imgur.com/e03TeuV): The heating system in my school broke down and I was super cold all day long. I guess I can say goodbye to shorter sleeves as well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 12:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Pire", je l'entends beaucoup dans le Haut-Doubs (zone frontalire). Je confirme que "fin" est normment utilis ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 19:29:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Toi au moins, ils savent ( peu prs) o il est. Le dernier recommand que l'on m'a envoy, ils ont trouv le moyen de me le PERDRE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 20:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is so sweet, thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 19:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the skirt and the first two outfits :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 18:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 35 / rural France / high school teacher

Trying to dress my age while being a bit more daring than what I used to wear (t-shirt, sweaters and jeans). I have to do with being 5'10" and having wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not super fashion conscious and I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

This was not a particularly good week for me, fashion-wise. I was super tired and not too inspired which led to some frnakly "bleh" outfits... But now that I actually see them from a different perspective (than in a mirror), it makes me want to make some extra efforts.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/k8g6lpM): I loved this outfit! I am more and more drawn to skirts and the silhouette they give me. One of my seniors told me that she loved my outfit and that I looked wonderful. \\\_()\_/

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/BL2fJUQ): Starting from this week, I only have one hour of class on Tuesdays, which is making me feel a bit lazy in terms of choosing clothes.

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/b9tfwmu): Photo was taken around 6am so everything looks bad, but I did follow last week's CC and wore the skirt higher, closer to my natural waist. The entire outfit was so comfy...

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/7xlHIn7): Thursday was breast cancer awareness day at my school and everybody was strongly encouraged to wear pink. I don't have a lot of pink clothing, especially for warm fall days, so here is what I came up with. I'm not convinced. 

[Friday](https://imgur.com/tmTrKzd): Another classic for me, but I just adore this shirt. I also found a way to do my hair that I actually like, yay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 18:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess I will find out soon enough! I have just dumped all the concerned PJs in the washing machine and as soon as they're dry, I will put them away in my chest of drawers and see if the smell comes back.  

My wardrobe is also IKEA but the smell is not chemical. I don't know if it's mildewy because I have never smelled mildew, but it is kind of sour and... acrid? I have already tried lavender sachets, cedar blocks and essential oils on clay diffusers, to no avail :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 17:51:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok, not really fashion advice but garment care advice, I hope this is allowed.

So, I have a weird issue that has been going on for years. Some of my clothes (only my PJs, actually) smell bad after spending some time in my wardrobe. Literally ALL of my other clothes (pants, sweaters, underwear, towels...) smell great after having been washed, and they still smell good after weeks or even months on a wardrobe shelf. I never leave wet clothes in my washing machine, and I always make sure everything is completely dry before putting it away. 

The problem started in my old wardrobe, where all my PJs were in the same part of the closet. I don't understand where the smell initially came from. The air where I live is dry and there is very little humidity. I have never seen mold or mildew anywhere, and I regularly clean shelves and cupboards. I changed wardrobes a year ago, I thoroughly cleaned the new one after putting it together but the PJ problem persists. I'm at my wits' end! I sometimes add vinegar to my laundry and the PJs will smell okay at first, but if they sit on the shelf for a month without me using them, they'll start smelling bad again. I really don't understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 12:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose you're the same person who posted a similar survey yesterday... without a link to the actual survey... and who apparently also forgot to add the link today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 20:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You forgot the link... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 08:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a huge compliment coming from you! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 08:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I agree that looking at the picture, it does look like it could sit a bit higher, even if it didn't feel that way when I was wearing it. I will keep it in mind the next time I wear it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 08:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, I will try to wear the skirt a bit higher. 

 #x200B;

The sleeve cuffing makes it look very cool and contemporary 

I will tell you a secret... I initially didn't cuff the sleeves of that particular blazer to look cool but because I have very long arms and after a dozen washes, the sleeves had started to shrink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 18:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 35 / rural France / high school teacher

Trying to dress my age while being a bit more daring than what I used to wear (t-shirt, sweaters and jeans). I have to do with being 5'10" and having wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not super fashion conscious and I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

I paid attention to the CC I received in previous posts and tried to apply it: more tucking, more cuffing, more fitting.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/eAyNpO7): For a long day of classes. We had a bit of an Indian summer here, it's very rare for me to be able to wear a sleeveless top in mid-September.

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/gEwAFcF): Shirt and pants were for teaching, then it was so hot when I got home that I changed into something lighter to run a few errands (that is to say the dress I wore for most of my vacation.)

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/I6QQIxo): I'm a high school teacher but I occasionally give seminars in college, for which I tend to dress a bit more smartly. I had to get up at 5am because said college is a 1hr+ drive away which explains the bleary eyes and grainy picture but at least I felt super stylish.

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/AcX7VKa): I've already posted this outfit here. I switched shoes in the middle of the day because my feet hurt. I wonder why it's taking so long for me to get used to heels again this year. Maybe I'm just getting old \^\^

[Friday](https://imgur.com/gJqmUys): I need CC on the length of this skirt. It's much longer than what I usually wear, but I'm tall so I guess it doesn't make me look too much shorter? Also, it has pockets!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 08:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's in the old town of Rdesheim-am-Rhein, this specific street is the [Drosselgasse](https://www.google.fr/maps/place/Drosselgasse,+65385+Rdesheim+am+Rhein,+Allemagne/@49.9783886,7.9201239,359m/data=!3m2!1e3!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x47bdef3f6b66a3ed:0x36d57d124e884cc3!8m2!3d49.9783876!4d7.9207746). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 20:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! The scarf and jacket were just to walk to work (it was 6C in the morning, brrr), I didn't wear them at all during the day because it was extremely hot in my classroom. I will have to think about wearing black. I got sort of interested in color theory last year and apparently, I'm a warm spring that needs bright colors to look my best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 19:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still adore your style and I'm happy you're now showing us your shoes as well ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 19:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for taking the time to write such a detailed and constructive comment! I have to admit I laughed at the image of your pump going its own little way during a job interview. My students and I had a good laugh and I put the blame on it being a Monday morning! 

Pants have always been problematic for me. I have long legs, wide hips and a narrow waist, so it's quite difficult for me to find pants that fit everywhere unless I order them online. I only started very recently to buy pants that are not cheap and therefore crappy. The latest jeans I purchased area bit more high-waisted ([here](https://imgur.com/tEMdF1W) and [here](https://imgur.com/WFT8PNN)), I don't know if that's what you had in mind in terms of fit? I also have truly high-waisted pants ([here](https://imgur.com/qU0Syjt)) that I adore and I know it's a style that suits me. Concerning bagginess, up until last year I was wearing lots of skinny jeans ([here](https://imgur.com/cMJZsim) and [here](https://imgur.com/65BcogT)) but I grew tired of them and thought they were a bit too tight. 

Concerning Tuesday's pants, I actually started cuffing them, but I wasn't sure about how it looked with the blouse and since it was quite chilly on that morning, I decided to leave them uncuffed. 

Again, thanks for your criticism and recommendations. I love how kind and wholesome this sub is :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 18:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 35 / rural France / high school teacher

Trying to dress my age while being a bit more daring than what I used to wear (t-shirt, sweaters and jeans). I have to do with being 5'10" and having wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not super fashion conscious and I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/xUfJxe5): I was wearing these new heels that are a bit higher than what I usually wear and I rolled my ankle and faceplanted in class, in front of 30 seniors. Now they probably think I drink between classes \^\_\^ 

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/YyKkub1): I really love this blouse and got several compliments on it, but I will have to try tucking it in because I'm not satisfied with the outfit's general silhouette.

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/0P0b9ls): No classes, only grocery shopping. Trying to distract from my messy flattened bed hair with a crimson lip.

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/2J1xp6d): I walk a lot on Thursdays so I prefer to wear flats, even if it makes my ankles look a bit thick.

[Friday](https://imgur.com/vEhfl5s): Not my usual style at all (a coworker told me she did a double-take to make sure it was me, but another trendy colleague said it was a nice outfit and that she wished she were as tall as me) but I quite like that outfit and I didn't feel self-conscious for one second even if it does feel a bit early 2000s country music video to me. I don't know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 19:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need an honest (or brutal) opinion concerning [this skirt](https://imgur.com/hBJRCwR). I ordered it because it looked more flared on the model and while I like its general shape, the only thing I see is my dip hips. Should I return it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 20:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the way you tied your top on Tuesday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 09:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also I love your haircut!

Thank you so much! I'm growing out my hair from a pixie and I recently decided to give myself bangs. I was not too sure of my choice so an outside opinion is precious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 19:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Merci ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 07:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 35 / rural France / high school teacher

Trying to dress my age while being a bit more daring than what I used to wear (t-shirt, sweaters and jeans). I have to do with being 5'10" and having wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not super fashion conscious and I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

I wore heels on Monday and Tuesday after three months of sandals and sneakers and I basically destroyed my feet. So back to flat footwear it was.

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/ZUPpUum): I opted for a relaxed outfit because I only had two hours of class. But my classroom was so stifling and hot that I changed t-shirts in the middle of the day. I now realize that these striped shirts are not flattering at all and unnecessarily widen my stomach/belly area. Oops.

[Friday](https://imgur.com/qU0Syjt): This is one of my favorite combinations. Polished but so, so comfortable. The only thing that bothered me is that it was a bit cold in the morning and since I go to work on foot, I would have felt warmer with a light coat. However, I always face the same problem: how do I combine a blazer (or a thick cardigan) AND a coat? Am I supposed to look like the Michelin man? Should I buy coats two sizes too big? Put my blazer in a bag and switch once I'm at work? How do people do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 08:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! 

Your comment about the dark t-shirt makes so much sense, I don't know how I didn't realize that myself. Thanks for pointing it out :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 20:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been following the WAYWT threads for more than a year and I'm glad that you're finally showing us your face :) 

I like all three outfits, with a preference for the second one. The colors really work well with your skin tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 19:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Today's shirt is so cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 19:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love love love your style. Is it an intentional choice not to include shoes in your pictures? I would love to see how you match your footwear to your outfits! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 18:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 35 / rural France / high school teacher

Trying to dress my age while being a bit more daring than what I used to wear (t-shirt, sweaters and jeans). I have to do with being 5'10" and having wide hips. CC and advice is more than welcome because I'm not super fashion conscious and I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Last Friday](https://imgur.com/fzbbo9A): back to school without the students for a day of staff meetings. [Phone version](https://imgur.com/Ggw3Xtk) to see a different angle.

[Monday:](https://imgur.com/tEMdF1W) back to school, in front of pupils this time. It's a repeat of Friday's outfit with a different t-shirt and shoes.

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/WFT8PNN): the weather got sunny and nice again so I opted for this cute mustard/dark denim association.

[Today](https://imgur.com/JFJ1aER): I don't have classes on Wednesdays so I put on something simple to go grocery shopping and run a few errands. 

Three of these outfits are really similar but the weather is supposed to get much colder in the next few days so I will have to be a bit more creative! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 18:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your sign says the street is in Beaucourt-sur-l'Ancre, a village in Somme... which is in the complete opposite direction from Bordeaux :D  Maybe someone from the North of France will be able to help you.

Edit: [found the sign](https://www.google.com/maps/@50.0797491,2.6863613,3a,75y,334.26h,88.67t/data=!3m6!1e1!3m4!1srP5-xagfpW8J7nMa_P-FFQ!2e0!7i13312!8i6656). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 11:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5. do you prefer bars with high protein or high fiber?  
Yes  
No  
Maybe

Hmm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 09:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's beautiful and so very useful! I will definitely steal that idea in my 2020 journal :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 19:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In France, I guess it's ham and [pasta](https://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coquillette) with butter or fries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 14:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. Makes for a bitchin' phone background. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 08:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I reported it to the police and filed a complaint, and while they took me very seriously, they told me that it had already happened in my neighborhood, that they knew why it was happening (a delivery person had lost their keys, including the master key for all the mailboxes) but that they could not do anything if nobody knew the thief's identity, and that the postal service didn't care either because "once it's in your mailbox, it's not our responsibility anymore". For more than two years, I've been having all my parcels delivered either to pick-up points or to my parents' (who live 3 hrs away) when it's not possible. I recently tried a home delivery again, just to see, and it was stolen. So the person is still doing it after all this time! 

Ugh, sorry for the rant. It just annoys me so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 20:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never had problems in my previous building. Then I moved 500m away and into the range of a mailbox thief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 19:30:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A 3,75 la bouteille, y a des chances... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 19:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is utterly inconceivable for me. I've had parcels stolen from my locked mailbox, I can't imagine leaving one like that in the open... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 12:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hehe, I am from this region so every little opportunity counts to promote it :)   
If you have the occasion to visit Alsace, don't hesitate. I may be biased but it's truly a beautiful place! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 13:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once again in Alsace, France, in a lovely little town called Bergheim :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 09:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the coldest winter

Yeah, not really... I'm Alsatian but I moved to Franche-Comt for work and trust me, Alsatian winters are laughable compared to what you get in the Doubs. 40 cm of snow, -15C on the reg... It's not called Little Siberia for nothing :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 13:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aprs, **l'ge et** le sexe jouent

Je n'ai pas dit que a n'arrivait jamais aux hommes, juste que d'exprience, tre une femme \*et\* avoir dpass la trentaine, c'est la porte ouverte  toutes les remarques  la con des gens qui pensent tout savoir mieux que les autres. Dans mon quipe au boulot on est deux  ne pas avoir d'enfant, lui un homme plus g et moi une femme dans la trentaine, et bien la diffrence de traitement est hallucinante. Y a rien qu' voir les quelques commentaires dans ce thread, les remarques faites aux femmes sont en gnral quand mme nettement plus agressives... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 08:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aprs, l'ge et le sexe jouent

Bingo. Je suis une femme et plus ge et les gens ne se gnent pas pour donner leur avis. Un homme qui ne veut pas d'enfant, il profite de la vie, c'est un solitaire, il se concentre sur sa carrire, c'est normal, c'est pas grave, etc. Une femme qui ne veut pas d'enfant, ce n'est manifestement pas une vraie femme, elle n'a juste pas encore trouv le bon, elle doit avoir un problme psychologique, elle est tellement goste, elle est encore immature et va changer d'avis, et j'en passe. 

Le lieu joue aussi, par contre la classe sociale, moins que ce que je pensais. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 19:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Je ne sais pas si c'est tabou, mais beaucoup de gens concerns hsitent  en parler. Parce qu'il y aura forcment des remarques dsobligeantes voire insultantes et des jugements htifs et infonds. L'article le dit, 95% des gens souhaitent des enfants, c'est une majorit crasante et on touche  quelque chose de trs "traditionnel" et attendu donc ne pas en vouloir suscite la curiosit ou la perplexit. Le problme, c'est que certaines personnes ont un avis tranch et zro tact, donc souvent, on prfre ne rien dire si a peut viter d'interminables discussions striles (si j'ose dire !) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-02 15:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your bangs are really cute and suit your face. I love the volume they add at the top. Good luck with your CG journey :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-02 15:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After about 15 years of various pixie cuts and very short bobs, I grew out my hair to my shoulders. After a spectacularly bad haircut (not really, but I sincerely hated it), I decided to go back to my good old trustworthy pixie cut. It lasted four months before I grew utterly bored with it and regretted my longer hair immensely. So here I am again, growing it out for the 265324789545th time in my life...

Last week, there was a terrible heatwave which made me stop using hot styling tools on my hair and I discovered that I could wear it curly again without looking ridiculous (the shorter my hair is, the least curly it is).

My aim is now something a bit shorter than the first photo, because as good as it looks, it was a pain in the butt to manage. Either a medium-length shag or a chin-length inverted bob.

My routine is pretty basic for the moment: I use Ultra Doux low-poo or Aleppo soap to wash my hair, Balea Locken Power Spray (a German curl-enhancing spray) or mousse, and Vivelle Dop gel (French brand) with praying hands. Then, I plop with a microfiber towel and diffuse. None of these products apart from the gel are CG-approved so I'm waiting for an order of Cantu products to arrive to really start a better, healthier routine.

I'd appreciate any type of advice, comments or constructive criticism. Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> At last I can wear my hair curly again! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-02 15:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-02 11:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to like coffee, now I can't stand the taste :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-17 19:43:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you look really good in picture #5 of your collage (bottom middle). Both the cut and the color! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-17 17:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much for the id and the recommendations :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two indoors plants (+ are they hard to care for?) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-17 09:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 14:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Moi aussi j'ai test, et je n'ai pas t convaincue. C'est certes super joli mais ce n'est pas trs pratique en main, c'est beaucoup plus fin qu'une ponge, a ne mousse pas et surtout, c'est compltement dgueu et dsagrable si on a des rsidus de bouffe  rcurer. Je trouvais galement que a mettait plus de temps  scher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 21:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, "Mountie look", thanks for making me laugh! I'm going to return them. The fit around the calves was perfect but I definitely need a straighter leg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 20:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right, I'm going to return them. Thanks for the advice and recs :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 17:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, it's me again with my silly questions about jeans. I'm getting tired of skinny jeans so I've bought my first pair of boyfriend jeans. I think they might be too wide/baggy, especially in the butt area, [what do you think](https://imgur.com/JqmhWlB)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 17:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are actually heels but the angle of the photo does make them look like flats. I'm not too sure about cuffing with flats either, they probably look too "delicate" as opposed to the sneakers that bring some width and balance in relation to the cuff (if that makes sense!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 17:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for your detailed answer and explanation. That cuff was actually 2.5-fingers wide but the general consensus is for it to be wider so that's what I'll try :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 17:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, I will definitely try a longer fold!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 16:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been experimenting with cuffing wider-legged jeans than my usual skinnies. Can you tell me if [I'm doing it right](https://imgur.com/coHX9i5)? I'm not exactly sure where the cuffed part is supposed to fall, and if it's not too bulky. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 08:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to have one in my 2018 journal, but when I started my 2019 one, I realized that I wasn't really getting any use of it. I'm almost always happy or tired anyway, and it was taking so much time just to draw these pages that I decided not to continue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 19:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a ne marchera pas forcment, j'ai tent une livraison chez moi aprs deux ans  tout faire livrer ailleurs, le voleur continue  faire la tourne des botes et  piquer tout ce qui ressemble  un colis de valeur. Ces mecs ne redoutent rien... :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 19:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Je compatis vraiment puisqu'il m'arrive la mme chose depuis deux ans. Aprs m'tre fait voler plusieurs colis, j'ai port plainte. Plainte videmment classe sans suite, mais j'ai quand mme appris par le gendarme qui m'a reue que 1) je ne suis pas la seule  qui a arrive, 2) une factrice a perdu son passe il y a quelques annes, 3) la poste n'en a rien  carrer. La seule solution que j'ai trouve, c'est la livraison en relais ou chez des parents/amis qui ne sont pas dans la mme ville.

J'ai d me faire livrer chez moi le mois dernier car le site ne proposait aucune livraison en relais, je me suis dit que j'allais tenter. Depuis deux ans, srieux, le mec a bien d se trouver un nouveau hobby ? Eh ben non, 80 balles de matos disparus. J'ai tellement les nerfs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 12:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... unless you have curly hair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 10:53:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I like poop paper. 

A familiar but very common way to say it in French is "ass paper". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 21:02:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Prof agrge en lyce, 9 ans d'anciennet, 2 200/mois sans les heures sup, indemnits et vacations (autour de 2500 avec les bonnes annes). Je suis en province, en zone frontalire donc tout est nettement plus cher mais je vis confortablement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 17:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hehe, that's a sensitive topic for me. I use my native language (French) exclusively. I'm fluent in English but I don't see the use of mixing the two languages in my bujo. I just prefer things to match, even down to the language :)

I often browse French-speaking bujo groups and it honestly bothers me to see English phrases being mangled by people who don't speak a lick of English and who are just copying titles off Pinterest, sometimes without even knowing what they mean (while we have perfectly good equivalents in French).

I don't know, I really love English but I'm weirdly protective of my own native tongue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 15:45:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had the exact same problem. I don't know if it's done on purpose to get quick, gut-instinct answers but it's incredibly annoying and I didn't finish it either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 10:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look amazing on pictures 4 and 5.

(So I think that's a yes!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-16 19:15:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I chose the same image for my January page and calendar too :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Those of you who track weather and temperature in 1x1 squares, which temperature do you choose to represent the day? Highest? Lowest? Specific time? Average? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-16 19:06:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-09 14:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started my first bullet journal on January 1, 2018. I was probably a bit too enthusiastic and I had trackers for basically everything, which ended up being a pain to fill in every day or every week. In my 2019 journal, I'm only keeping a weather and temperature tracker because it's the only thing that's interesting to look back on. I realized pretty quickly that I don't care about how much I slept three months ago or what my mood was on some random March day. I am of course keeping my collections (books read, films watched, etc.) and useful trackers (birthdays, periods, car maintenance, etc.) I even made them much prettier :) 

 #x200B;

I used to make colorful and elaborate weeklies ([1](https://imgur.com/U3w6vdi)) but on very busy weeks, I simply didn't have the time to draw 12653 boxes and titles so I ended up adopting a much simpler layout ([1](https://imgur.com/82R6SRf) [2](https://imgur.com/IxUWIi4)), using washi tape to add a bit of color and creativity.  The only pages I'm still going full on are the month pages and calendars. 

 #x200B;

I also changed notebooks. I used to have a Rhodia Goalbook and I picked a Quo Vadis Life Journal for 2019. They're basically the same except the LJ has white paper instead of cream. All in all, I'm pretty impatient to start my 2019 bujo :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 12:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Je ne pense pas qu'on puisse appliquer la rgle habituelle de la dtermination zro  un pronom... Si on prend l'exemple "Some French people thought they were superior to Germans; others disagreed". Mon "others" ici, c'est bien "d(es) autres", pas "les autres"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 08:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a dpend comment la question a t pose dans chaque pays, mais en anglais, "superior to others", ce serait plutt "suprieure  d'autres". Pour "suprieure aux autres", on dirait "superior to the others". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 18:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 34 / France / High school teacher

Only four outfits this week because two others were repeats I've already posted.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/dbwzece): Extremely basic but I love the color of the top and the lacy panel on the sleeves.

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/HzBlt36): Don't be too hard on that one :) I knit the kimono-inspired cardigan and I really love it. Looking at this outfit now, I should probably have left the shirt hem outside of my pants...

[Friday](https://imgur.com/nMRQKiR): New boots! They're the most expensive I've ever had and I can see they're going to last much longer than my old ones (which were synthetic leather). Only downside is that they hurt my instep a lot so I will have to suffer and break them in for a few days... weeks? 

[Sunday](https://imgur.com/cMJZsim): Mid-term break at last! Dressing comfy for the 3-hour drive to see my family. I love the lace in the back of the top but also how soft and warm it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 20:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Je n'y connais pas grand chose en sculpture, mais j'ai pu visiter le Muse du Prado l'anne dernire et j'ai vu un magnifique [buste de Torreggiani](https://i.pinimg.com/originals/2c/7d/ea/2c7dea72b6bb73353e7e2d7c642c1681.jpg). J'tais merveille par la beaut de la sculpture et l'impression que c'tait rellement un voile de tissu d'une finesse incroyable qui tait pos sur le visage de la reine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 07:32:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Yes, I'm really happy that I'll be able to wear it even in colder weather :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 16:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww, thank you! For me, it's essential to look neat, even if I'm not super trendy. I've experience first-hand how cruel kids can be when you look different, so I'm trying to not give them any reason to make fun of me. 

This week will be different, though (it's the last week before mid-term break here). I'm exhausted and very tempted to grab whatever's clean from my closet just before leaving for work :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 15:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for your input :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 15:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I wouldn't wear this skirt with flats. It would be very unflattering with my calves. I'm wondering whether it would look good with ankle booties...

A pair of boots I had had my eye on for weeks were finally back in stock this morning so I ordered them. I think they're more red-toned than the old tatty boots I'm wearing in the photo, I can't wait to get them! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 15:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 15:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you thinking you'd rather it hit just below the knee?

Yes, that's pretty much what I was thinking. It's a more usual skirt length for me. I have no idea if there is any distortion, but then again I'm quite tall (5'10") and this is a regular-sized skirt so... I think it might just be me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 18:44:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That blue is indeed so lovely on you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 18:43:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 34 / France / High school teacher

Trying to dress my age, to be a bit more daring than jeans and a sweater while remaining comfortable, to add a bit of color in my neutral wardrobe and to divert attention from my wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not very stylish or fashion conscious so I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/S7U6J5c): For a normal day of teaching. It was still fairly hot outside so I went for a knit t-shirt. 

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/pP4U4FX): For a morning of classes followed by an afternoon of staff meetings. The skirt was bought after seeing u/bikinikills wearing it in one of these posts. Still wondering if it's not a tiny bit too long? 

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/qzaKBWH): It's a cute top (I love polka dots and bows) but too flimsy for the season. I was so cold during my morning classes! 

[Friday](https://imgur.com/5WFZPxG): I'm pretty sure this would have looked better if the boots had been more orange-toned, but I love the sweater and the skirt together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 12:29:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Malheureusement, je confirme. Je me suis fait voler plusieurs colis dans ma bote aux lettres et quand je suis alle au bureau de poste, on m'a dit que 1) je devais passer par le service de rclamations officiel parce que les guichetiers ne peuvent strictement rien faire pour nous et 2)  partir du moment o le colis est dans notre bote, ce n'est plus la responsabilit de la poste. 

Pour moi (et quelques voisins), a s'est quand mme fini avec un dpt de plainte  la gendarmerie, o j'ai appris qu'une factrice avait perdu son trousseau de passes, qui avait trs certainement t rcupr par quelqu'un qui faisait depuis la tourne des botes aux lettres du quartier en se servant allgrement au passage. Les gendarmes l'ont signal au directeur local de la poste qui leur a dit "bah qu'est-ce que vous voulez qu'on y fasse ? on ne va quand mme pas changer toutes les serrures, vous imaginez ce que a nous coterait ?"

tldr: En gros, c'est mort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 22:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Tuesday pants are fairly snug, I took them in at the waist like I do with all my pants, but the legs are indeed a bit loose (they're sailor pants so they're supposed to be like that, but they sometimes look a bit too big)... I think the shirt was sneaking out because I was moving around too much, lifting my arms to write on the board, etc. All outfits are not adequate for teaching! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 21:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I actually wore Monday's blazer with Tuesday's outfit but I chose to take the photo without it. 

I only took this one photo on Friday but I'll try to remember to take photos with and without blazers and cardigans for future pics!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 19:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 34 / France / High school teacher

Trying to dress my age, to be a bit more daring than jeans and a sweater while remaining comfortable, to add a bit of color in my neutral wardrobe and to divert attention from my wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not very stylish or fashion conscious so I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/6id5xp5): My "Wednesday Adams going to a job interview" oufit. 

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/AJ3Kct5): That shirt drove my crazy trying to escape my pants all day long, but looking back on it now, I think it may have been worth the hassle. 

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/l7gUT9G): Still my favorite pants. They're stylish (I think), super comfy and they flatter my figure. 

[Friday](https://imgur.com/J60A95N): I listened to the advice I got here and started tucking my shirts in! (If I look exhausted, that's because I am. Two weeks left before mid-term break, oof!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 18:55:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Religion wasn't included in my "other reasons", since civil servants are prohibited from wearing any distinctive religious sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-03 11:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an English teacher who has welcomed quite a few language assistants: do take off your hat. With a few exceptions (shops, supermarkets, etc.), it's considered extremely rude to keep a hat on indoors. Doing it at school would be a very bad idea. Some teachers might understand the cultural difference and not mind it or tell you nicely, but a lot of people would think you're rude. 

Unless you really need to wear a hat for other reasons. I had a student once who had lost a patch of hair because of a disease, and he was allowed to keep a cap on at all times. Same for a girl who had alopecia and who wore a headband to hide it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 22:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh wait, I just remembered that I did wear my top tucked into my pants once [last week](https://imgur.com/hk7qh1k) (with the same blazer). The ratio pants/top still looked a bit off but that might be the photo angle, as you said. 

Yeah, those paper bag pants do wonders for my silhouette :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 20:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A longer top, definitely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 20:18:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, that may be it... I've always heard that if you wear tight pants, you have to balance them out with a looser top and vice versa, but it might not actually be the case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 20:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a bit more expensive in France (28) but I was weak and ordered it. I'm tall but bought it in "normal" because I don't want it to be too long. You'll definitely see it in one of my future WAYWT posts ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 20:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am probably on the taller side (1,78 m / 5'10") and my main issue is that I have normal shoulders, smallish boobs, a narrow waist and super wide hips. Defining my waist sometimes makes my hips stand out, depending on what I'm wearing (it's gonna be fine with an a-line skirt, much less with skinny jeans!) 

I'll probably have to experiment with each outfit and post the variations here to get some feedback. I've actually tried to tuck several times, but I chickened out every single time and put the hem outside again :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 19:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I LOVE that first skirt and as soon as I have posted this comment, I'll head to the ASOS website and check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 19:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had missed your posts! The "stripes on stripes" outfit is just fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 18:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 34 / France / High school teacher

Trying to dress my age, to be a bit more daring than jeans and a sweater while remaining comfortable, to add a bit of color in my neutral wardrobe and to divert attention from my wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not very stylish or fashion conscious so I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/fmBps2A): CC needed on the footwear. I've been trying to get into flat Oxfords, but I don't know if I'm convinced. I do notice now, looking at that outfit, that the top doesn't go with the pants (the hem hits at the wrong part of my hips). 

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/6lf5V31): Dresses and boots are so comfortable. Those boots have seen better days though, I'll probably have to replace them soon. They are brighter and similar to the belt in color, but the sun had just started to rise and the bottom part of my body was still in the shadow. 

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/Yoq85UC): I love this new shirt but I'm wondering if the jeans aren't too tight... (I fixed my hair after taking the picture as well.) 

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/drwrAyI): I had to walk to and back from school twice in that day so I wanted to be comfortable. There is a delicate gold thread in the yarn of the sweater that you can't see in this picture. 

[Friday](https://imgur.com/YaofSgu): The pants are a very recent purchase and I'm in love with them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 13:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bah non. Si + imparfait, conditionnel dans la 2e proposition.

Si \[...\] existait  imparfait  
chacun pourrait  conditionnel

Donc u/sphks a raison. [Voil](https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3MIfk0dsAWyveHA4JJRgpdyuHtFTGJbTFgQJLsBuOBKtYfqfL7Dr2g0doY5zavzfv-W9eQ=s0).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 20:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every week, I impatiently wait for your comment. My favorite outfits of yours are today's one and the midi skirt. You wear those colors so well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 20:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those Wednesday jeans look amazing on you. The entire outfit is great, actually! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 19:48:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I ended up going with the peach one because it brought a bit of contrast to the rest of the outfit. 

Besides, with the nice weather, I knew that I would end up not wearing it much and I was right since I walked around in shirtsleeves all day long!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 19:46:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no, you're quite right! It might be simplifying things but there is definitely some truth to it. Some kids do pay attention and I (as well as another colleague who enjoys dressing well) have already been complimented on my shoes, on a nice watch, on a nice knit sweater... 

It's silly, really, but I think that I just don't like to draw attention to myself too much, even though I love looking neat. It sounds strangely self-contradictory, doesn't it? Last year, a math teacher told me "Oh wow, you look so beautiful today" completely out of the blue and I felt horribly self-conscious all day long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 18:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 34 / France / High school teacher

Trying to dress my age, to be a bit more daring than jeans and a sweater while remaining comfortable, to add a bit of color in my neutral wardrobe and to divert attention from my wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not very stylish or fashion conscious so I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

I apologize for the grainy quality of some of these pictures. Late September means that it's starting to be night still when I get dressed!

 #x200B;

[Monday](https://imgur.com/hEBG2KB): I only had four hours of class in the morning, including a challenging one, so I wanted to be comfortable. 

[Tuesday 1](https://imgur.com/nzOznSi) / [Tuesday 2](https://imgur.com/0lvlZsB): Small hesitation with the jacket. I'd be curious to know which one you'd have chosen! As a side note: I was super comfortable the entire day long, but I felt very overdressed compared to my colleagues. I live and work in a rural mountain town and most of the female teachers wear jeans and t-shirts or dresses over leggings and birkenstocks (I don't mind the first outfit but the latter is more backyard attire for me!) So every so often, I feel a bit silly in my heels and skirts and tailored jackets. Do you ever feel that way too? 

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/wA8JecF): Grocery shopping and various errands. Boring outfit, I don't know if I should keep including them. 

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/FdUNFi1): Had an important staff meeting with some higher-ups. Same outfit as last week except with sandals because it was hot. Some people definitely came in leggings and birkenstocks though...

[Friday](https://imgur.com/hk7qh1k): I don't know if it's the angle of the photo making me look stumpy, but I am 5'10" so I don't really care ! I wore a black blazer on top but it's so hot in the classrooms that I quickly took it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 11:52:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I finished knitting [a sweater](https://imgur.com/RP2P4to). It's way too warm to wear it now but winter comes very fast where I live so I should have to wait for long :p

I have since then started knitting a kimono-looking cardi in teal. Lacy pattern, my fingers hurt and it's going to take a while!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 12:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't notice yourt boobs or even your "slight curviness", as you put it, before reading the rest of your comment. Your colleague sounds like an awful person, who the hell thinks it's okay to say things like that? The red sweater looks good on you, especially with the half tuck. 

I think my favorite outfits are the second one (striped shirt and jeans) and the fourth one ("running errands"). They looks effortlessly cool :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 18:15:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 34 / France / High school teacher

Trying to dress my age, to be a bit more daring than jeans and a sweater while remaining comfortable, to add a bit of color in my neutral wardrobe and to divert attention from my super wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not very stylish or fashion conscious so I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Monday](https://imgur.com/7E4TiH6): A normal teaching day. It felt like summer again, it was so pleasant!

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/RYh68jZ): A bit frumpy but I had FOUR blisters the sizes of small moons so I just wanted to be comfortable. I wore low-heeled sandals and straight-legged jeans to hide the multiple band-aids and blister dressings :( I think I won't wear these jeans with flat shoes again though, it just doesn't look good.

[Wednesday](https://imgur.com/f2AzhTe): No classes, just a few errands to run.

[Thursday](https://imgur.com/8Bd1dai): The top looks weirdly boxy on this picture. It's more flowy and flattering IRL... The angle of the photo doesn't help either!

[Friday](https://imgur.com/vynZKcG): A day of classes followed by three hours of driving to visit my mom in the hospital. Those are my favorite pumps but I did switch them for flats when I got in the car :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-15 12:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :)

I agree that big hair can definitely overpower a face! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-15 11:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knoooowwww...  I have yet to find a way to have both the pixie and the curls. For the moment, when I try without styling my hair, I just look like a wet poodle :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-15 11:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I posted on r/hair when I was still hesitating about cutting it, and someone told me that longer hair made me look in my 40s. I definitely am not in my 40s so looking younger is a good argument :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-13 22:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm no stranger to pixie-short hair... I've had it throughout my 20s and then I decided to grow it out a few years ago. Then, I got tired of the inconveniences of longer curly hair. It always looked great on the day I washed my hair, but as soon as I slept on it, it looked bad. Showers took ages, there was hair everywhere in my apartment, my hairstylist didn't know how to cut it, it was all very frustrating so I decided to go back to short.

I'm not saying I don't miss my long hair  looking at the before picture kinda makes me regret cutting it  but I know that it looks good **and** is practical, so I'll keep my hair short for the moment. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Went for the big chop... again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-13 22:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-11 17:04:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! It's a new purchase and I love it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-11 17:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mixing colors has always been my difficulty. Especially with reds. I used to believe that I couldn't really wear shades of red because it might clash with my hair, but it's absolutely not true. So here I am, at 34, starting to wear reds and oranges and bright pinks :) That's why adding another color is still a bit too daunting for me! 

The flats are more like a cheapie knock-off (no idea if it was intentional, there's only so much variation in flats) that I got for 10% of the price of a Repetto pair. They're very comfy though! 

Thanks for your nice comments :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-11 16:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a French (?) brand called Tamaris, I checked their website and they don't carry it anymore, which isn't too surprising since I bought them more than a year ago... I'm sure they exist in other brands though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-09 20:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? Thank you so much!

(I spent a large part of my life being picked on for the way I look so you have no idea of how much your comment  and the general kindness and wholesomeness of people here  means to me )

I will definitely try to post more, especially since it forces me to put my outfits together with more care than I used to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-09 19:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hehe, nope, it's actually charcoal! I don't have anything in dark green but you're right, it's an interesting color association. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-09 19:27:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! 

I agree with your point on round toe shoes. I hadn't really put a lot of thought into it, I had to walk a lot on that day so I chose flats, and I thought that the color went well with the rest. I'll definitely pay more attention to such little details, even if I'm okay with a slight modcloth/youthful touch :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-09 18:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First time posting!

34 / France / High school teacher

Trying to dress my age, to be a bit more daring than jeans and a sweater while remaining comfortable, to add a bit of color in my neutral wardrobe and to divert attention from my wide hips. CC is more than welcome because I'm not very stylish or fashion conscious so I'm not always sure of what I'm doing.

[Last Friday](https://imgur.com/GI4iEB9): back to school without the students for a day of staff meetings. 

[Monday](https://imgur.com/hyEjGh2): I didn't have any lessons but I needed to go to the school for paperwork so I dressed fairly casually. 

[Tuesday](https://imgur.com/65BcogT): First real day of classes. Classic with a pop of color? 

[Thursday 1](https://imgur.com/w6zqnfQ)/[Thursday 2](https://imgur.com/DaKbAMS): I hesitated a lot between the two cardigans and ended up going with the beige one. 

[Friday1](https://imgur.com/cCuaXic)/[Thursday 2](https://imgur.com/Qp6ZjJS): Sailor pants and a sailor shirt. Maybe a bit too much? Added a cardi because mornings are starting to get cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 20:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dix ans d'anciennet... Agrge, trois heures sup, prof principale, formatrice  l'ESPE et j'arrive  2500. Ce qui est trs trs confortable, je m'en rends bien compte, mais on est loin des 4000 ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 19:08:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Prof agrg avec deux ou trois heures sups dans les collges  ct ton salaire commence certainement par un 4.

Oui, alors, comment te dire... certainement pas. Et crois-moi, je sais de quoi je parle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-02 20:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I'll definitely try :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-02 19:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We almost have the same hair! :)

I love Monday's and Saturday's outfits. 

What is that elastic trick you're speaking of? (from someone who never manages to have the perfectly scrunched sleeves) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 18:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as hair is concerned, if your bob isn't too short, you should flip out the ends of your hair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-26 09:04:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with the other commenter! It brings out your face and you look more polished. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-25 17:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As well as France, Belgium, Switzerland, and Germany.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-25 17:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because it is!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-25 16:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I'm a high school teacher and my style is relatively classic. Think casual chic with lots of nice tops and blazers, jeans and heels or dressy flats, etc.

I walk to school (~10 minutes), I have [a briefcase](https://i.imgur.com/sP9tKUb.jpg) for big days and [a shoulder bag](https://www.paulmarius.fr/femme/sac-a-main-cuir/lerive-gauche-m-naturel) for shorter ones. The problem is that I also bring my lunch almost every day, and I sometimes need my own laptop as well. Until now, I used a tote bag but it's not super comfortable (especially shoulder bag + tote bag) nor steady (I live in a place where sidewalks are snow-covered and icy 5 months out of the year).

I don't want to stop using these two bags because they really work for me and they were rather expensive. I thought of a nice, smallish backpack to carry my extra stuff, that I would leave in the staff room during the day. Briefcase + backpack could work, shoulder bag + backpack will definitely look stupid, BUT the shoulder bag comes with an extra strap to turn it into a messenger bag. Would that work and not look completely awful? 

Oooor if you have any other ideas to help me lug around all my crap... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 17:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. I once considered dress clips for a top that was too boxy, but they didn't suit my general style so I ended up chucking the shirt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 10:54:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, this will definitely help! Thanks for taking the time to do this. The colors chosen are lovely and I will try to keep them in mind when I dress :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 10:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think so, autumn is either warm, deep or soft. I think it's my eye color that makes me a spring, but the autumn tones might make it a warm spring?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 19:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 16:20:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm the opposite! When I was younger, I dreamed of wearing a pencil skirt. It's only when I found the perfect one in a store and tried it on that I realized that my hips are way too wide for a pencil skirt to look good on me. I then very reasonably turned to a-line skirts :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 15:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oui, je pense que si tu ne mets pas de migaine, il faut un peu plus serrer les mirabelles (en les mettant un petit peu sur le cot, en les superposant  demi par exemple, en plus a fait joli.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 19:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of those awful Orangina commercials with sexualized animals, those gave me so much second-hand embarrassment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-11 18:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh, great! 
Have you tried r/SampleSize? You can specify in the title which demographic you're after, it might help you target those last few places you're still missing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-11 11:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will you post the results? I'm definitely interested in reading them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-09 20:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Il y a la LELE et la LVA qui permettent vraiment de s'clater en sortant un peu des sentiers battus (et la section europenne, mais l je ne peux pas dire, je vais dcouvrir en septembre) mais dans de nombreux lyces, les sections L sont le moyen peinard d'avoir un bac gnral pour des lves franchement pas bons, et je sais que j'ai franchement galr les dernires annes en LELE parce que certains L ne comprennent vraiment que dalle  ce qu'on leur raconte, alors de la littrature, tu penses... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-09 20:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Je suis prof d'anglais en lyce et d'accord avec tout ce que tu as dit, mais surtout a : 

 Ne te lance pas dans un CAPES+titularisation sans avoir dj une exprience du mtier, c'est bte. Si tu as un master et de bonnes comptences en anglais, tu peux dj tre contractuelle. 

OP, tu as l'air d'avoir une vision trs idalise du mtier (ce n'est pas un reproche, beaucoup d'entre nous ont commenc de la mme manire,  rver de parler de littrature avant de se rendre compte que de bons lves de terminale ne savent toujours pas former une phrase interrogative correctement) donc je pense que passer par ce statut intermdiaire permettrait de se mettre face  la ralit du mtier sans prendre trop de risques. 

J'ajouterais galement qu'une fois le CAPES obtenu, il faut ~~se farcir~~ valider l'anne  l'ESPE qui selon les acadmies, pse de plus en plus lourd sur l'emploi du temps et le moral des stagiaires. J'ai malheureusement connu d'excellents jeunes collgues qui avaient travaill d'arrache-pied pour obtenir le CAPES et qui ont finalement abandonn devant la montagne de travail pas toujours trs pertinent qu'on leur demandait. Il faut vraiment tre solide pour rsister aux premires annes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-09 20:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> C'est exact : le bonus de points d'agrgation ne s'applique qu'en intra-acadmique, et non inter-acadmique. 

Il me semble aussi qu'il existe(ait?) des bonus diffrents selon le type de voeu (acadmie/dpartement/tablissement) mais je ne me souviens plus des dtails. Juste que plus le voeu tait large, plus les points taient levs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-09 20:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus ou moins, mais il faut faire preuve de stratgie et bien se renseigner sur les besoins des diffrentes acadmies. Quand j'ai d faire mes voeux de mutation  la fin de mon anne de stage, avec mes 75 pauvres points, j'avais le choix entre la rgion parisienne et des rgions plus rurales et moins demandes : Franche-Comt, Bourgogne, Limousin, Auvergne... J'ai choisi une de celles-ci pas trop loin de chez moi, je l'ai eue, et je suis tombe dans un lyce super sympa o je suis encore 8 ans aprs. Mes copines de promo ont toutes mis sur notre rgion d'origine, aucune ne l'a eue, elles ont fini en rgion parisienne et ce n'tait pas joyeux pour toutes. 

Pour ce qui est du choix du dpartement, c'est assez compliqu (tout comme le systme de mutation, d'ailleurs). a va dpendre de tes points mais aussi des dparts, qui sont parfois annoncs, parfois non...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-09 20:05:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  L'avantage c'est qu'on passe moins de temps  faire de la gestion de classe.

Pour avoir discut avec une collgue du suprieur rcemment, c'est en train de changer, a... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-09 18:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like it too, the colors are great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-09 09:21:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I used to buy a new pair of high heels every few months, the I realized my feet hate them.

Same here. Society + female colleagues who look down on anyone who doesn't wear towering heels and IG-worthy outfits. I'm currently on vacation at my parents' but as soon as I get back home, I'm selling or donating all these pairs of heels that I've worn once. I'm keeping a few (I've somehow managed to find 3 or 4 pairs that don't put my feet in excruciating pain after a few hours) but all of the others must go. I have ordered cute, dressy flats that will be just as pretty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 18:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for your very reassuring opinion! You can't really see it on the photo but those are also navy and leather. They should be quite comfortable as well :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 18:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love late spring and early fall. 

Where I live, November to March is (cold) winter and while I love snow, I'm quickly fed up with the cold. March and April are often rainy and windy, which I really dislike. Late spring is when the weather gets pleasant and when I can start wearing something else than sweaters and boots. It's also the season in which you can assemble outfits with interesting layers (later, in July and August, it gets too hot).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 17:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I Google Image'd "Ferragamo Varas" and saw lots of nice outfits with rolled-up jeans and colorful ankle pants... I might have to turn my original idea around and wear real, flat flats with dress pants and those heeled flats with trendier pieces. Can you see how much of a fashion noob I am? Eeesh.

I am a frequent wearer of midi skirts and striped tops so thank you for the idea. 

I laughed so much at your Queen comment :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 16:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's kind of my style too... I was mostly planning on wearing them with wide-legged pants that would sort of hide the back and just show the cute front with the bow and patent leather. 

Since it's your style, what would you wear it with?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 16:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oops, yeah, I found them in the "flats" part of the website, labeled "heeled flats" so I didn't think twice. 

The problem is that I love patent leather and bows :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 16:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, you're right, but they are sold as "heeled flats" in the "flats" category so I didn't really think about the name. 

Thanks for the brands recs, I will have to see if they're sold where I live.

Can I ask what you wear your Varas with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 16:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I walk to work, I often spend the entire day on my feet and I'm having more and more trouble wearing heels all day long so I went looking for some cute flats. 

I think that [this pair](https://imgur.com/MXRxsaK) is pretty cute but how do I make sure it's trendy and not something my grandma would wear? 

I was planning on wearing them with dress pants, sailor pants or dark chinos... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 11:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The eye color argument makes a lot of sense. 

I have read so many webpages about color theory that I'm a bit lost now. How can I differentiate clear spring from warm spring?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 11:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! Thank you for your detailed answer! People here seem to agree on clear spring. I'm a bit surprised because I have always been drawn to rich, warm autumn colors. But now that I've cut my hair and gone back to a pixie, I think that my face looks "brighter" than in my first photo, so it matches everybody's impression of a clear spring.  

 Are there any colors you hate to see yourself in? Anything you put on and think "I really can't pull this off"?

I try to stay away from white, light colors and pastels because they wash me out (except pale yellow which looks okay for summer tops, and off-white for chunky knit sweaters). I think that beige/tan/cream are also bad choices clothing-wise. I don't have a lot of red in my wardrobe because I used to think it might clash with my hair, but now I'm not so sure. I have a few black tops which may not be the best color for me, they don't really bring anything out. 

Concerning lipstick, anything that is orange doesn't look good. Anything pale or nude isn't great either, especially since I have naturally pigmented lips. I generally revolve around raspberry red, dark rose or cherry pink. 

I'm on holiday at my parents' for the moment so I don't have access to all of my clothes and makeup, but I'll make sure to try more combinations when I go back home!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 10:47:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Mais a tend  disparatre, notamment au profit des rond-points.

Je trouve au contraire (et malheureusement) que les priorits  droite fleurissent, du moins l o j'habite (Nord-Est)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 10:38:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pas partout :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can you help me find out my season? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 09:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! 

I've tried rather unsuccessfully to determine my color season. I thought I was a typical warm autumn (red hair, yellowish undertones, blue-green eyes, etc.) but some websites classify me as a clear spring.  

 nbsp;
  
A few notes: 

 I think that gold jewelry looks better on me than silver.

 I'm having a hard time determining my undertones. I would have said yellow, but looking at my veins, I see green as much as I see blue. 

 I don't feel like posting makeup-free pictures but the makeup I wear is fairly minimal. Face photo #3 is rather old and blurry but the closest I have to no makeup :)  

 nbsp;

Face photos: https://imgur.com/rbjbTUq / https://imgur.com/EHf5d0v / https://imgur.com/e0GoFiv

Eye photo: https://imgur.com/sDNGTm0

Veins photos: https://imgur.com/gjHLihB / https://imgur.com/hJin4D0

 nbsp;

Thanks a lot!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-15 17:20:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is what I did on mine: https://imgur.com/9EkTVU5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-17 06:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh hi, I saw you on r/hair :) I'm glad you made the decision to cut it! I personally prefer the two styles on the left, I think you look extra adorable with a little bit of bangs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 19:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look lovely with both, but the short hair is so pretty, it definitely makes you stand out :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 21:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahaha, oh, boy, I should definitely go for the pixie then! I'm actually 33 (and on the short-haired photo, I was 30). I do admit that I've been quite tired and swamped with work lately so I feel haggard most of the time. Don't feel bad about it though, your answer made me burst out laughing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 19:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get your idea, but straightening my hair when it's short doesn't take a lot of time... I spend so much time on my hair at the moment that spending an additional half hour straightening it just doesn't appeal to me :(
But thank you for your suggestion :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 18:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, what age would you give me based on the first, long-haired picture?
Thank you for your nice comment :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 18:56:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh dear, no, you're telling me that in addition to all the things I already do, I would have to straighten it for like 30 minutes after I shower? Yeah, that's not my idea of making things easier ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 18:55:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately, Deva stylists and products don't exist in my country. So it's trial and error until I find a product that works for me... until it's discontinued! 

I'm not too keen on straightening, it would definitely take a long time and I'm not sure it wouldn't damage my hair. I used to do it when I had a jaw-length inverted bob and my arms were happy when I was finally able to stop having to do it :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 18:52:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I plop after I shower but I had never thought of doing it overnight. I'll definitely try though, thank you for the tip :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 17:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi r/hair! 

I'm posting here for advice. As you may have guessed from the title, I'm currently fighting the urge to go back to the pixie cut I had a few years ago. 

I know that my hair is beautiful when it's long  it's red, and curly, and shiny and everything, but it brings me so many inconveniences in my daily life! I can only shower in the morning because it takes ages to dry, it looks crappy after I've slept on it, ponytails are mandatory after day 2, showers take ages because of all the hair I have to pick up if I don't want to clog the drain... I'm kinda wondering why I'm doing all of that just to look pretty one day out of three. I know that a pixie requires maintenance, especially on my curly hair, but I've done it for ten years so I know what it's like. I basically need to blow dry it for a few minutes with a bristle brush, then use a straightening iron, but my hair is pretty easy to style. 

On the other hand, I know that I'm partly frustrated because my stylist messed up my hair at my last appointment. My hair was getting long and I asked her for an inverted bob to take some thickness off the back, but she cut my hair in a straight line all around AND much shorter than what I asked. I can't even do a proper ponytail without using bobby pins. And now I'm all grumpy every time I do my hair. 

So I'd love to have your opinions. Should I persevere and grow it out, or do I look better with short hair? Thank you for any input.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To chop or not to chop? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 17:18:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 14:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, I know that if I think about it reasonably, it's a nice cut, but I'm frustrated because it's not what I asked for and she cut 5 cm / 2" that I had so patiently been growing for months :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-22 16:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's okay :)

No Deva stylists but I know a few other curly-haired peeps so for lack of a website, I'll have to rely on recommendations!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-22 16:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck to you too! Fingers crossed for more 2C days!

(Ugh, that thing about curly hair in colorguard makes me so angry! But weren't we all totally awkward in 8th grade? :D) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-22 16:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for all the technical details, I'll make sure I'll remember them next time I ask for something else than a bob (and ask beforehand if the stylist can do it...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 18:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, we're already here :) 

Unfortunately, there are no Deva salons in my country, and people typically don't leave reviews online for hairstylists, so I have to rely on word of mouth or personal research... or trial and error, in my case \\\_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 16:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww thank you, that's really sweet :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 16:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I thought too. Do you have a precise idea of what I could ask for in a "style" only test?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 16:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I think she only knows how to do it that way... and maybe she didn't want to bother trying to do it differently. I think it's safer for me to find a new stylist now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 16:26:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes, it's definitely not my first bad haircut either :D 

I've been to this salon many times and she's never messed up my hair before... but it's the first time I ask for something a bit more complicated than a trim and layers. I should also add that I spent the last ten years with a pixie haircut which makes me think she just doesn't know how to cut curly hair. And she's the most experienced stylist in this salon, so I don't think there's any use in going back. 

I'm just going to wait for my hair to grow a bit, and look for other salons in the area! One of my curly-haired colleagues tells me that her stylist always wants to give her an inverted bob while she doesn't want one, so I might have a lead already :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 12:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My hair was down to below my collarbone. I was very happy with the length but willing to trim the dead ends a little bit. I mostly wanted to get rid of the back which was super thick and heavy. 

I asked the stylist for a moderate inverted bob and she warned me that she couldn't do a "real" one because she would have to use a razor which would break the curl pattern. Okay, fine, a smaller angle would be okay since I didn't want anything too angled anyway. (I was aiming at [something like this](https://i.pinimg.com/564x/55/83/1a/55831a561e5ef83a0f1d000f5f3e4e74.jpg).)

Well, she ended up not taking a lot off the back and she trimmed the front way too much, so now I have a basic shoulder-grazing bob that's the same length all around and worse, which is the same length it was at Christmas. Ugh. 

My hair is still a bit frizzy from the salon shampoo and hair-drying, but here's my (usual) routine:

* Condition with a low-poo gentle cleanser

* Scrunch mousse into hair while it's still wet

* Spritz with curl enhancing spray

* Plop with a microfiber towel

* And blow-dry on the lowest setting using a diffuser until hair is about 80% dry

No brands given because they're obscure French and German brands :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hair was down to below my collarbone. Asked the stylist for an inverted bob. Walked out with this. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 12:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-03 20:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't the 100-500 price range missing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-02 19:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was a fun survey :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-01 20:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is the pitch perception test reliable? I got 91.7% and I've never played an instrument. Maybe I should have tried :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-01 09:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The shading on the clovers is amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-23 20:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm willing to help as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-21 20:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't either, but then again I discovered bullet journaling in December, I actually started a personal bujo on January 1, and I don't see myself starting a school bujo in March :) 

I do have a planner in which I write what I do in class every day + homework/assignments/etc., but I'm not using the bujo system. It would be pretty easy to adapt it, though. 

It would definitely be interesting to think about it during the summer holidays and see what other teachers here are doing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-15 12:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, a macaron recipe, of course! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-14 15:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My habit tracker is in that place, but on the opposite page :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What would you put in a small empty space? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-14 13:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After two months and a half, I've finally found the PERFECT weekly layout for me. There's just a tiny little box with which I have no idea what to do. 
(https://imgur.com/x0vVTfp)

I already have trackers for everything I need, to-do/shopping lists, notes, a calendar. I track books/movies/series/meals/exercise/mood on other pages, it's too small for a quote, I don't want to put a doodle or tape here, I'm not into gratitude logs or tracking achievements or memories (yeah, I do realize I'm picky!) and I can't think of any other domain in which I could track things. 

What I've thought of: important things in the coming week / something related to astronomy / new words learnt (English is my second language) / progress in my current book. What do you think? Do you have other ideas?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-03 13:52:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found a few things on Pinterest, if you search for "capsule closet bullet journal" you should find some ideas. It's a pretty interesting concept, make sure you post your results if you ever decide to go for it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 19:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I might be in love with your handwriting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-17 20:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's adorable, and you have a very nice handwriting!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-17 18:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's lovely! I drew daffodils for my March page too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-17 08:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, I just did that. I hope they're nice because it's a really ordinary project compared to what some of the others post!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [No pattern] I made a sleeve to protect my bullet journal while traveling. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-17 08:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Going on a small trip next week so I made a sleeve for my journal :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 17:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 16:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks really nice and clean, and I love those little pandas!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 15:34:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> European here so it's always been Monday for me. 
I'd have a very hard time cutting the weekend in two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-01 08:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, that's not depressing, it's already 6 more than me :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 12:40:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [There you go] (https://imgur.com/t4hz3Dm) :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> February page and moods </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 09:39:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 09:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have 8 in mine: happy/energetic, proud/satisfied, good/normal day, tired, sad, frustrated/angry, stressed, sick. 
At first, I realized that I had more negative moods than positive ones, but I have much more good days than bad ones so it balances out. I mostly use "good/normal day" and "tired", at the moment anyway! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 09:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I drew them... If you want, I can take a closer picture so you know exactly how to do them in relation to the dots?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-22 19:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I'm not that talented :) I rubbed a pencil over the outlines on the back side f the paper, and then I traced the outlines on the front to transfer the graphite. It's like... ghetto carbon paper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-21 20:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's beautiful! So soft and calming... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-21 18:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found the idea here, and since I wear nail polish pretty much all of the time, I thought it was amazing. It's going to look great at the end of the year, and it will definitely help me to choose colors when I don't know what to wear :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I started bullet journaling three weeks ago, with A LOT of inspiration from here. Here is the result :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-21 16:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-21 11:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's okay. I don't like Thursdays either. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-19 15:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do, but [mine]  (https://i.imgur.com/wmFCs5N.jpg) just covers Europe because I've only been in the rest of the world twice, and it was a long time ago. 
I love the little stickers that you put all around yours :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-19 08:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, it was the same thing for me. I thought about that January/February split for days, and then I just decided to do what felt right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-18 20:51:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I answered a similar question earlier today, you might find an answer in [this thread] (https://www.reddit.com/r/bulletjournal/comments/7r0x1h/when_do_you_guys_switch_months/) :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-17 15:50:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I put that week after the January/February division, simply because there are more days in February in it (T F S S) than in January (M T W). 

If I take the last week of May, there will be four days in May and three in June, so I will start the first June weekly on the 4th. 

I'm not entirely sure that this is entirely clear anywhere else than in my head but for me it makes sense :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-14 11:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, me too. In my country, simply opening the plastic wrap it comes in would mean you couldn't return it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-13 09:29:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is brilliant. I am SO stealing this idea! Thanks for the inspiration :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-01 17:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love your "Goal by numbers" page :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-01 11:54:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-01 11:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not the OP but I have the same sleeve for my laptop, the brand is Lisen and I found it on Amazon. As far as I know, it exists in different sizes. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-31 18:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, that's French! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-31 10:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It still hadn't been shipped yesterday night so I changed the delivery address to my place. The only problem is that there is (was?) a mailbox thief in my neighborhood so I really don't like having Amazon packages delivered to my mailbox. It should arrive on the 4th or 5th so I will have to run down to the entrance hall every couple of hours to check if my package has arrived! (Luckily I'm off work until the 8th!)

It's my own fault though, I can't really blame them. I should have ordered sooner and with the holidays, everything takes a longer time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-30 08:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm also new to bullet journaling and anxiously waiting for my Amazon order. It was supposed to be delivered on January 2nd and I was okay with it (I have also sketched pages outlines on normal paper to be ready when it arrives)... except the order status has been on "not yet shipped" for two days and I'm wondering by what happy miracle it will be there on Tuesday if it wasn't sent yesterday at the latest! And the worst is that I'm currently spending the holidays at my parents' and I'm supposed to leave on the 4th, so if it's super late, I won't have it before the end of January :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-20 11:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a hazel tree. Those things are catkins and they're full of pollen (and they make my life hell in the spring). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-15 20:03:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I don't remember often seeing the diagonal line without the horizontal line.

Where are you from? I'd say that in Europe, most people write their 1s without the bottom horizontal line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Repost][Academic] British people's opinions on Brexit (UK inhabitants + expats, esp. racial minorities) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-11 17:11:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Academic] British people's opinions on Brexit (UK inhabitants + expats) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-04 16:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-26 18:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of my co-workers once said that only children don't get enough affection in their childhoods and always end up with psychological problems. The majority of people she was talking to are only children... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-17 19:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Il y a peu de franais sur le forum mais tu as trouv une alsacienne :)
Malheureusement, je ne peux pas t'aider dans ta recherche, n'ayant jamais trouv de coiffeur spcialis quand j'habitais encore en Alsace. Je crois qu'une telle spcialisation n'est pas encore arrive jusque dans nos contres :(  Peut-tre peux-tu te tourner vers les salons de coiffure afro ?
(Sinon, une rapide recherche Google semble indiquer que des gens boucls ont t satisfaits chez Minelle Coiffure  la Krutenau.)
Bon courage, et fais-moi signe si tu trouves quelqu'un ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-10 18:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a CF high school teacher :)

But I chose teaching in high school for a reason. I absolutely couldn't work with young children, even middle school would be very difficult for me. People are surprised when I say this, but I actually prefer teenagers to children. At least they are autonomous and I can have interesting conversations with them. 

I should add that where I teach, it's quite uncommon to be CF. Rural region, quite conservative... Most of my colleagues have at least two kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-06 14:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same for me, exact same version except on Windows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-19 19:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I fucking hate Thenns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-24 18:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oooh, I hadn't thought of that, thanks for bringing it up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-24 18:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :) Grey was actually my second choice and it would look good, but I already have grey floors in the hallway (PVC tiles), the dining room and the living room (laminated wood). Such a difficult choice!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-24 18:57:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! And it would indeed look very Scandinavian. I like the lime wax idea... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help: Kitchen floor color </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-22 12:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi everyone! A year and a half ago, I bought an apartment from the '70s and as you can see [here](http://imgur.com/a/BqTVr), the kitchen hadn't changed since then. I renovated it as best as I could, and I absolutely [love it](http://imgur.com/a/XveuJ). The only negative point is the floor. It's tiling and while it's sturdy and super easy to clean, I don't like the color or style, and it's scratched and cracked in places. 

I would like to install PVC flooring (planks that snap together  sorry for the vague descriptions, English is not my first language and the more technical terms elude me!), probably in wood, but I'm not sure of the color I should choose. I'm leaning towards a light wood similar to the countertops, but I'm starting to wonder if it wouldn't be too much of the same tone. 

Can you tell me what you think? Which colors would suit this room better? Many thanks in advance :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, you worked in France? Can I be nosy and ask where? 

I'm reading so many things in this thread that are completely new to me. I knew that the American healthcare system was nothing like the French one and that being sick could be really expensive, but to skimp on maternity/sick leave? That's appalling!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for clarifying that for me. It sounds so crazy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:42:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, thank you, I had no idea. I knew that the healthcare system was quite absurd, especially compared to ours, but I didn't know it was that strict. Now I understand the downvotes ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair, this attitude is not only seen in mommies. Three years ago, I needed surgery in May but I chose to wait until July because I didn't want to drop everything and everybody (my students who had exams, my colleagues who would have had to correct my share of exams, etc.  I needed a good month and a half to recover) and many people were shocked that I chose to finish my school year instead of going on sick leave two months before. Different work ethics, I guess. 

I already asked someone else in this thread, but could you very briefly explain the current state of maternity leave in the US to me? It seems to be completely different from what my country provides, that's why my rant may appear unjustified to some.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-03 09:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, I suppose you're talking about the American system? Would you mind explaining to me the "maternity leave through union contracts" thing, because I'm not sure I get it? I'm French and in France, everything is covered by universal healthcare. All mothers can get from 8 to 16 weeks of maternity leave and all mothers and fathers get benefits. 

That's why I thought the woman's request was a bit entitled. I don't see why a teacher should get 16 weeks of paid leave in addition to the 8 weeks of summer holidays, while someone working in a private company wouldn't. It sounds a bit unfair, doesn't it? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Teachers can be entitled just like any other parents </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a teacher, and I frequently browse a Facebook group reserved for teachers but for lighter discussions or practical questions. A woman posted today because she had a question. She's pregnant and due in early August. She very seriously asked if her maternity leave could be postponed to September since she will "lose" it by giving birth during the holidays. Some commenters answered that she was asking a bit too much since we already have several weeks of holidays throughout the year, but many moms came to her defense and complained that having a baby during the summer holidays was definitely being cheated out of paid vacation. What?!

Next time I have the flu during the holidays, I'm going to ask the principal if my sick leave can be postponed to after the break. This should go over well!

ETA: To clarify, this took place in France, where new mothers automatically get 8 to 16 weeks of paid maternity leave, since everything is covered by universal healthcare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really is. I'm starting to believe it's cultural (I'm French), especially after having read a lot of stories on this sub. We do have some mombies, but half of the crap American or British mombies try to pull wouldn't fly here :) I live in a very rural region (so Catholic people who have tons of kids), with many cross-border workers (who are super wealthy and can afford tons of kids) and a medium-sized Muslim community (so families who have tons of kids) and NO ONE cares about what I choose to do with my uterus. I've had some surprised reactions ("Oh, really, you don't want kids ?") but it was healthy curiosity and it was never followed by a negative remark. The coworker who half-bingoed me is awfully catty and mean with everyone so I didn't take it personally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Co-workers' kids... (rant and rave!) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:45:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I've never posted here but I've been reading your posts for a few months. Here are two anecdotes that deal with colleagues' children that happened in the past week. 

The first one took place on open house day in the high school I work at. A former colleague popped by to have a little chat with us in the classroom we were using to greet parents and pupils. We remained friends after she left so I see her from time to time and I know that she has a 3-year-old son who is cute, I admit it, but so noisy! Not only did she bring him with her, she also brought his toys... such a bad idea, if you ask me. While she was talking to us, she let him play with a toy backhoe in the classroom. He started running it on a row of desks on which we had placed posters made by pupils, and the shovel part of his backhoe got caught under the photos and we had to intervene before he ripped half of them off. His mother was completely oblivious to what he was doing but after our intervention, she told him to play somewhere else. 

So he went to the back of the room and started running his toy on another row of desks... and letting it crash to the floor at the end of the last desk. Over and over again. His mother was not reacting at all, she was merrily chatting with one of her friends. I was explaining important things to parents and it was starting to be embarrassing to have such a racket in the room. I could see that some visitors did not really appreciate it and two other colleagues were starting to exchange angry glances. Then, after a solid five minutes of incessant crashing noises, mother and son finally left and it was calm again. One of the two angry colleagues, who knows I'm friends with the mom, asked me whether she ever said anything to her child, wondered how she could stand so much noise all the time, and assured me that she had never let her children act like that. I personally wonder how my friend could not see that it was inappropriate to let her kid make such a ruckus in a professional setting (even if open house at my school is a pretty laid-back affair). I guess that she is so used to the noise that she doesn't notice it any more. 

Now for the rave part: on Tuesday, I was invited for dinner at another colleague's... who has three kids, aged 2-5. I was pretty apprehensive but it turned out to be a great evening. Her children were well-behaved, ate with us at the table, talked between themselves at a normal volume level, played calmly in another room when they were done eating, and they all went to bed at a reasonable hour so we could enjoy our meal between adults. It was a very pleasant surprise and I had a lovely time. 

Another rave would be that even though I'm a teacher, surrounded by kids all day long and by colleagues who have a minimum of two children each, discussions never revolve around their children. I've never been bingoed (apart from the time when I was told that I should be the one in our department who stays for evening meetings since I don't have kids) and my closest co-workers know about my stance on children and respect it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. Nothing wrong with you. I would personally love to have the confidence to go make-up free :)

And apart from that, I wear a bit of make-up and my bathroom certainly doesn't look like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could almost say the same thing! I bought a huge flat (just for myself  it was cheap because it's old and I spent an entire year renovating it) in a building mostly inhabited by old people, and it's super calm. Except when the old lady in the flat above mine has her grandkids for the day. They are incredibly noisy, listen to music extremely loud and spend the afternoon yelling, running and jumping around, making big banging noises in my ceiling. It doesn't happen too often and it always stops at around 7pm so I've never complained, but it just reinforces my decision not to have kids of my own :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-02 13:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My downstairs neighbors have installed an electric extractor fan in their bathroom, and connected it to the natural ventilation ducts. The vents in my kitchen and toilet are okay because they're on different ducts, but I constantly get smells from the apartment downstairs in my laundry room and bathroom. When it's laundry detergent or cake it's okay, but most of the time it smells of grease, fried food, or cigarette smoke. I hate it. Or course, it's entirely illegal for them to do that but I haven't mustered enough courage to talk to them about it yet, and the management company doesn't seem to care. 

My upstairs neighbor is a sweet old lady with a dog that I didn't even know existed, but two or three times a month, she invites her grand-children who are the most noisy and boisterous kids I've ever heard. They listen to music extremely loud (very often the same song on repeat for 30 minutes to an hour) and run and jump everywhere for an hour or two. And then they leave. I'd never have thought that small kids could produce that much noise. But since it doesn't happen too often and it's never after 8pm, I just leave them alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally did a double take... I thought they were knitted toys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-09 15:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Photo #5 is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My employer hasn't but my coworkers certainly do. Whenever there's a late meeting only one in our team must attend, they guilt-trip me into going, because, "you know, there's the kids..." (All of them are married with parents or parents-in-law in the area, who I know can take care of their children.) 

The one who does it the most has a 14yo daughter who apparently can't come home from school or eat or do her homework alone. But only when there are meetings; if we all (our team) decide to go out and have dinner, she's a totally independent teenager.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whichever work I do on my lunch break, I don't have to bring home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was bullied a lot as a kid and teenager so now I have huge trust issues. It's too difficult for me to put myself out there, I guess I'm still scared of rejection. What's weird is that even though I'm reasonably attractive and try to look confident, I never get hit on. Men look at me, but they never come and talk to me. Except the crazies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My love life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Getting splashed by a huge bus as I was walking home from work. I was completely drenched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:36:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi all I'm trying my hand on her face to be in a while ago but never the case with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> French woman here, I was bullied a lot in middle school and high school because I'm a redhead (I was continually insulted, sometimes hit, sometimes spat on...) It wasn't a joke and certainly didn't feel like it. I have no idea why, but I can assure you it definitely exists. It even made the news a few years ago because a little red-haired boy committed suicide after years and years of harassment at school. I wouldn't say there's a historical reason since it's mostly middle-school kids who do the bullying, and they're generally not educated enough to be aware of this particular history. 

Thanksfully, the discrimination seems to stop after high school. I got insulted once or twice in the streets when I was in college (the insults were specifically directed at my hair) but it hasn't happened again. People are actually pretty envious of my hair now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:34:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Driving at a speed that "feels right" without checking the speedometer every ten seconds? Jeez, if you're that much in a hurry, just pass me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 20:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay so English is not my first language (but I've studied phonetics) and it took me some time to understand too, but I think that what BoldArch is getting at is the pronunciation of the last "a" in avail**a**ble. You should pronounce it like a short "uh", not like an "ay". Availuhble, not availayble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful castles like Neuschwanstein, Herrenchiemsee, Hohenschwangau, Linderhof... I visited them and would love to go back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well obviously it's going to depend on the context and on your personality, but I am a pretty chill and reasonable person who favours discussion over conflict and confrontation, so when someone attacks me, I think of myself as the bigger person and remind myself that not everyone can be as open-minded and sensible as me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been a teacher for 6 years in a relatively calm rural high school. We've never had a bullying problem; kids sometimes make fun of other kids but we always manage to nip it in the bud. For the most part, they're good, reasonable students with principles so they listen to reason.

However, it's a subject that really concerns me. I'm scared of not seeing it, and of not knowing how to react. I was bullied a lot when I was a teenager and only one teacher awkwardly acknowledged it. She did nothing concrete about it, but hearing her tell me I could always talk to her meant the world to me. Today, I'm the teacher and I would like to be able to do something if the need arises, but it's something we've only started talking about in my country. There is this huge campaign with phone numbers and stuff, but there are no training courses on bullying and harassment for example, even though I'd love to be more proactive in that domain. So if anyone has pointers, I'll gladly listen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the morning, take my medications.
In the evening, read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My "granny hobbies" (knitting, crocheting, coloring, painting, crosswords  I do enjoy other activities though). Most people are impressed by what I can do when I tell them "yeah, I made that ornate and delicate sweater", but I mentioned it once in front of some not very open-minded coworkers who laughed and added "oh wait, you were serious?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:12:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have recovered physically (my hair is seriously awesome and the envy of my friends, coworkers and hairstylists) but the years of bullying made me scarred on the inside :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:08:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a female redhead and I got bullied so much for my red hair, it was awful. I'm 32 and I still have a hard time trusting others because people were so gratuitously mean throughout middle and high school. I even got randomly insulted once or twice in college. I mean, wtf???

One of my red-haired male friends said that he never got any problem when he was a kid, but that it was indeed more difficult to approach girls when he was a bit older.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess I'm a frustrated scientist. I wanted to become an archaeologist, then an astrophysicist, then a science teacher... and somewhere after that, I decided that I really liked English, so I became an EFL teacher (majoring in literature). But I still like science a lot and even though I love my job, I wish I had been more encouraged in pursuing a career in astroanything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:44:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Radiohead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay so I googled that because I'm curious and... it looks like the game I used to play at a friend's house in middle school and whose name I haven't been able to remember for 15 years. Was there a point in the game where a screen with a city would appear, in which you could buy (?) buildings and they would gradually appear/fade in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:00:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's mine as well. In addition to what you said, I also loved the fact that it wasn't an easy movie, that there were real scientific theories in there and that it made me think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm French, and I'm always stumped when I have to translate "tartine" in a simple way. A tartine is a slice of buttered bread, typically covered in something sweet like jam, honey or chocolate spread. It's an essential part of the French breakfast. Every morning, I have coffee and tartines. 

There's also "n'importe quoi", which can be as polite as "whatever", "anything", but which in familiar speech can become "nonsense", "bullsh*t" (as in "dire n'importe quoi") or stupid actions ("faire n'importe quoi"). 

We also have two words for "owl". An owl with little ear tufts is a "hibou"; one without them is a "chouette". It's not just for bird-lovers, I'm pretty sure any 4-year-old could tell you the difference.

Same for "river". We have "fleuve", which is a river that flows into the sea or the ocean, while "rivire" is a tributary. It's kind of a big deal, any person with a basic education wouldn't mix the two.

I'm sure I could find others given enough time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-18 18:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like [this](http://imgur.com/a/EIGsu). It's been raining for three days straight :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To have someone fall in love with me, for a change. 

I know it's selfish, but dang, I'm so lonely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing is, many teachers would resent you for going over their head and meeting the principal directly. You might also make a bad impression on the principal if he hears that you didn't try discussing it with the teacher first. 

Your teacher doesn't seem like the most reasonable person, so I wouldn't take any risks. Try broaching the subject with him at the end of a class, but don't insist if you see that it's not going anywhere. You will have done your part of the job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-25 16:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. Exactly this. 

I'm a teacher and what this guy is doing is totally inappropriate. You should always try to approach your teacher first, and if you see that it's not changing anything, then you must go and talk with the principal. See if you can go with a friend who could back you up, if necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-17 16:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried University a few days ago. I sent my sim to college and held on for two days before sending her back home. I found everything extremely boring and frustrating. School performance was difficult to keep up, life in the dorms was terrible because roommates didn't take care of anything (rotting plates of food everywhere, stinky roomies that made my sim unhappy, etc.). Also, the "go to class" action is queued 1h30 before classes really start, which might sound ridiculous, but for some reason it takes a very long time to reach college buildings (bad routing). So in the end, there is very little time left in the day to eat, shower, have fun or study, which makes for very unhappy sims. Other players have reported glitches and crashes, I have avoided them so far.

I don't think I'm going to use the college town any time soon. I'll simply enjoy the clothes, furniture and decorative items that we got with this EP :)

(I don't have Island Paradise so I can't comment on it, although it looks pretty good and quite interesting.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-07 20:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a high school teacher. Last week, while I was waiting for the photocopy machine to finish printing, I had a look at a test paper a colleague from my subject had left lying around after having made copies for their class. My work BFF entered the room, I simply looked up and told her "holy crap, you have to see this, I don't know who made it and what they were on but it's packed with mistakes!" It was hers. I'm never making fun of random papers again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-13 13:06:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Non-native speaker here  what does "flank" mean in this context? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-11 20:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jean Martin (Marie Martin for a woman).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-03 11:12:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, that's actually the biggest compliment you could have made! 

I suppose that Chinese students have a very different way of working. I had a Taiwanese exchange student in my class last year and I do recall that she didn't approach assignments in the same was as the other pupils. Incidentally, she ended up leaving in the middle of the first trimester because she couldn't get used to our school/her host family/France. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-03 09:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, France too :) I'm French but I teach English to French high-schoolers. 

Is such a behavior typical of Chinese students? Because it's getting worse everywhere, I think. Kids have access to basically everything that's online and they don't even see the problem with plagiarizing. "But... I **researched** it."  Yup, but I'm a language teacher, so my job is to evaluate you on your linguistic skills, not on your capacity to google stuff and copy-paste it into Word... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-02 17:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Divorce. I keep pronouncing it with a diphthong, like "d**i**verse". And the worst is that this word comes from my own language, in which it's also pronounced with a short I sound. I really don't know why I'm making it extra difficult for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *she

And yeah, I do sometimes feel like throwing myself off a cliff but here, it was just formatting ignorance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:12:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, it seems like your teacher didn't quite know what plagiarism was. 

Was it the first or only grade of the year? Because I quite don't get how a teacher, who was supposed to know you, would accuse you of plagiarism if you were a straight-As student. Such words *are*  bit unexpected for a 15-year old, but not impossible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So "farther" for a real distance, "further" for an abstract one? Thanks, I learned something new today :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately, 95% of the papers I get are in handwritten form so that's not something I can use. However, since I teach a foreign language to teenagers, I can spot an adult or professional writing style pretty easily, and Google quickly takes me back to the source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-02 15:55:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, the contrary, actually: I'm French and I teach English as a second language.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-02 15:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> France.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-01 22:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I fixed it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-02-01 21:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A few days before a parent-teacher conference, a pupil handed in a paper that was completely plagiarized. She had a very poor grasp of the language and the homework was extremely well-written, in an adult style that obviously wasn't that of a teenager so I immediately understood and found the original article online. It wasn't the first time she tried to pass off someone else's writings as her own, so I gave her a big fat zero (a F, if you will). 

On parent-teacher night, after a completely cordial 5-minute conversation between her, her mother (a very put together, classy woman) and me about her results, how she could improve, the extra homework I could give her, etc., the mom tells me point blank "so, on the subject of that latest homework... why zero? She worked so, so hard on it!"

I start explaining that I can't accept plagiarism, that it's actually very serious and could potentially hurt her daughter's studies if she continued doi-- 

"She didn't plagiarize. And she worked, so, so hard on it, for several evenings!"

"I'm sorry, but she did plagiarize. I found the original webpage with the same content, word for word, the same presentation and even the same fonts..."

"Nonono, you don't get it. She just likes putting together lovely presentations. Besides, we did her homework together. No, really, that's not possible. "

"Well, if you did check what she had done, she must have changed it afterwards because what she gave me was... this". And at that point, I showed her the printed webpage, a photocopy of her homework, and all the common points highlighted (i.e. most of the document was bright yellow). 

"That's just... *[waves hand, implying "a coincidence", I suppose]*  No, I can assure you, we did that together. Well, we *did* use an online translator but all the ideas were her own."

"Ma'am... that's not possible. It's word for word the same thing. Even the spelling mistake here is the same."

"No. This is her homework, I swear that we did it together. Well, now it's your choice *[gee, thanks!]* but we explained ourselves. But I think you don't believe us. So... you won't change her grade?"

"I'm sorry, I won't." *(Pupil starts making a face.)*

"Well, that's unfair and disgusting! Oh yeah [pupil], you can cry, because this is downright shitty! Next time, you can cheat, since you'll get a bad grade anyway!"

"I guess we'll leave it at that, then."

She gets up and storms off in front of bemused colleagues and parents. 

That was four years ago and I still can't fathom how an educated adult would lie to a teacher with so much nerve about something so trivial as high school homework. A simple apology and a new paper would have gotten much farther and would actually have helped her daughter. 

And yes, the following papers were also partially plagiarized. \\_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-07 20:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me, not at all, but that's probably because I live in a remote rural area. 

I have family and friends in big cities that would be more at risk, but we're all pretty unfazed, tbh. We are aware of the fact that these major cities could definitely be the targets of attacks, but then we shrug it off and move on to something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tea is not good for people with iron deficiency. Drinking a lot of tea (especially close to meals) can decrease iron absorption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (There were other, more important problems in our friendship, but...)

When she spent a few days at my place and totally ruined everything she touched because of her poor hygiene. I thought it was so disrespectful of her not to care about anything (period blood all over the bed and sofa  I'm a girl too, I could have dealt with it, honestly; foundation and other make-up splattered everywhere in the bathroom, various food stains on my nice tablecloth, infrequent showering after hikes and long days out, etc.)

I spent four days getting everything clean again after she had left and it made me so angry. You wouldn't do that in your home, why do it at my place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-27 08:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, no, you misunderstood my post. I guess my wording was ambiguous in places, sorry  English is not my first language. 

My grandmother is fairly well and able, and quite independent. She just has trouble walking and doesn't drive, which means that my dad has to run errands for her, or drive her places. My dad, never my mom, who literally never needs to do anything for her. That's why I really don't understand where the resentment is coming from. She doesn't have more obligations than the normal amount an adult has. 

So yeah, it's probably something else, and the attitude towards my grandma is just another symptom, but I'd still like to help, even if it's just to comfort my father :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-27 07:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really tempted to try this. I could easily get some alone time with her, but I don't know how she would react to such a question. I've never seen my mom express her feelings! I've already tried asking her what was wrong between her and my grandmother (very tactfully of course) but I didn't manage to get more than a really evasive answer. So this might be tricky!

Anyway, thank you for your advice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>