<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3169</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 16:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly i kinda feel like I'm a kid too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 07:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I answered this based purely on my DnD experience but I was wondering whether other Pen Paper rpgs would be relevant too, because if I would have answered for my favourite character across all pen paper games (in my case that would have included Pathfinder and The dark eye) my answers would have been quite a bit different </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 22:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanna be in this picture and I don't like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 13:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh wow, that's gonna be interesting, I've not really told anyone I'm gay yet (mostly because people don't ask), I can totally see why that would get anooying and am really not looking forward to stuff like that, even though I generally enjoy sarcasm quite a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 13:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend who totally can't handle this too, so he almost always apologized right after making any sarcastic comment, and I kinda had to stop doing it around him cause he's always taking it that little bit personal but it's so hard cause he's always serving me the best "templates" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 17:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So basically: "Do you want to become Bose-Einstein Condensate with me" is a viable pickup line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (Hobby-) Astronomers/Physicists of Reddit, what are some of the most insane things that exist in our solar system (not on earth)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 00:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 23:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of this one time i followed a link like that, 12 minutes later i was arrested by the fbi for purchasing child porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 20:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wanna hear the story of how my brother stabbed me with a broomstick? Cause it really isn't that interesting.

Me and my brother were fighting with these broomsticks and at some point his just snapped in half (they were made of some hard plastic) and where it snapped it left a pretty sharp edge on both parts, so naturally we keep fighting, with him using both of his pieces now and obviously he would point the sharp ends in my direction. So naturally at some point i tried to block his attack and well he slid along my stick and right into my arm. At first i just stepped back and made it clear something had happened, because my brother didn't really notice what had happened but well within like 2 seconds blood was already streaming down my entire forearm from beneath my ellbow and that was the point at which i started running for my mum.

Other than that I only the have the scars of when I impaled myself on a fence and that time my brother hit me on the head with an axe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 22:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 09:50:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My insecurities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 10:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Law of Conservation of Energy, energy can never be lost, only transformed, any energy we create with solar panels will eventually be turned back into thermal energy (heat) through resistances in our cables and circuits or simply by manually changing it to heat with electric heaters and what not (although that's a pretty similar process a lot of the time) so theoretically all this would do is delay the heating up of the earth, which would then propably be compensated by what's been delayed before leaving everything about the same. The only change i could see would be in the position in which the electric energy is turned into thermal, but I also don't see that much of a problem with this since the energy we produce stays largely local.

Although I am only talking out of my (tech focused) highschool science ass, so I might forget some stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 08:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Self love.

That's propably not something you should be doing around other people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 02:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'm kind of having this moment right now, I'm doing this quite a lot and I know that some people take this a lot more personally than I mean it to be (which is not at all) but up until reading the comments under this, I didn't really ever think it was that bad... or well I guess it was more hoping that it wasn't that bad since it is pretty much the only way I ever make people laugh, reading some of the reactions here though I guess I really need to tone it down quite a bit, especially if the other person doesn't do the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 16:22:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All right, that clears things up, thanks a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 16:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2E

Still new to this all and I'm not quite sure how the universalist wizard works

Do I just get 1 extra first level wizard feat and a 1st level spell, is that what it's trying to convey to me (also is there any greater influence in later levels, other than the improved "drain bonded item", mostly asking this cause I'm actually in the process of doing my level up to 2 and I realized I forgot about the universalist stuff) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 02:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't know how this could possibly be a cultural thing. Sure playing "doctor" specifically, but the whole exploring each others bodies thing mostly comes from exactly NOT knowing about privacy and personal space stuff and is generally something I've never heard of being encouraged by the parents or other supervisers (at least not in the sense of trying to get kids to do it). When I did stuff like that as a child, I made it a very important point to hide it from my parents because I knew I "shouldn't" do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 10:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god, if just a single person I know finds my reddit account I'm done with life, I've written some stuff on this account, I don't even feel comfortable thinking to myself about (and I haven't even written that much yet)
Also my username is one pretty much all my friends should know so uh... I guess I'm propably fucked because quite a few of them do use reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 09:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THIS

So much, some peoples commitment to getting you to drink is astonishing and I didn't even think about the depression part and "drinking your problems away" (even though that's definitely true for me, especially right now) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 23:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8 years ago I was 11 in 4th grade and propably trying to get my best friend to kiss me (we were both boys btw) or maybe he was already trying to get me to kiss him (or well that's at least what was happening 2 months ago when op made in this post), both pursuits, even though we both knew we wanted it however came to an abrupt end with finishing 4th grade and switching schools. After which I was mostly just sad because I knew I propably wouldn't really see him after that... with which my till now first and only love story would end.

 #x200B;

Since then: Well I'm about as confused (propably quite a bit more actually) about my sexuality because I'm just not sure about anything. I propably actually found something I wanna do for a living and I'm about to get into my last year of highschool with actually surprisingly good grades (even though I actually always got pretty good to decent grades). Honestly I think I'm still just the little nerd who happened to be just likeable enough to get some of the cool kids to like him to make me not a complete outsider just that now I'm a lot more aware of this and all my shortcomings. I guess I at least learned to stay out of fights by now but in the grand scheme of things I really didn't change that much.

 #x200B;

(Also I know I'm a bit late to the party considering the lifetime of AskReddit posts but yeah I just kinda needed something to vent right now so thanks op for making this post, also I like your Pigeon "Buisness Coins") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 14:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it is not, it's a mix of high testosterone levels and bedtime brain activity, this is a myth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 13:51:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a myth, which btw is mentioned in op's source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I feel lost </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 23:11:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like I'm having a permanent existential crisis. I keep questioning my feelings, my motives. I don't know what makes me happy, what makes me sad, what drives me... like a little child that doesn't understand it's own feelings and I also don't feel like I've really changed that much since I was a child. Like deep down, everything basically always stayed the same.

I think I need help but I don't know who to ask, where to ask or how... 

 #x200B;

and I'm scared... of what will happen when I get help, what will change, how people see me and mostly... what I might find out about me

I want to know where I am in live, I want to know the future, whether it's gonna get better but now I just feel lost somewhere in my live ... in the dark... unable to see what's to come or what's behind, hoping for that glimmer of light somewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 01:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know, even though I'm totally aware of what it means and what we're doing here, reading it described like that really hit me with a reality check </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 01:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The last hug I got was from a random girl at a friends party on new years eve (family included) and well let's just say I don't wanna know how long it was before that

but who am I even fighting here, cause right now it seems to be my mental health </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 21:59:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A good portion of my thinking (at least 50% propably way more) goes on in english and honestly the part about love and deep feelings is something I can totally relate to. With english it all just has a different feel to it, in my mother language words like love feel almost unnatural for me to say. Maybe I'm more detached from them or maybe it's actually the opposite since most of my day is now happening in english (because most of my day is spent on the internet and in games which I almost always have set to english not because I live any english speaking country or anything). Maybe I'm actually even more used to hearing them in english especially since they are such a common topic in games, anime and movies. Honestly I don't really know but yeah I can totally relate to that (it'd be interesting to see whether another language has the same impact though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 21:14:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow except for the friends we're literally the same person, I have friends to do stuff with, thing is... I don't know  whenever I'm with them it feels like I'm just there for no reason, just tagging along. On the other hand, there really is no one I feel safe talking about everything with. But yeah since we're mostly stuck on the same things I guess I can't really help with anything, the friends I have are all mostly just from one friend I've known since childhood introducing me to his friends so can't really help with that either... I don't really know why I'm even writing this, I guess all I can do is just wish you the best of luck and hey if you feel like showing, I'd gladly watch some of the art you make </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 15:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbh I'm not sure if I can honestly claim there is a difference, but I see the difference in how I'm feeling about my life in general
For example: for this post i took a short break from watching videos and just thought about my life a bit and pretty much instantly i start feeling depressed and well thats the case for almost everything I do in life, once I stop doing random shit and what not and I start just thinking on the most fundamental level about my life, I just don't feel happy and well I don't think that thats how it's supposed to be so I'd propably call that distraction because at the end it doesn't really give me happiness in life it just gives me something to do to distract from the sadness even though I genuinely enjoy it and would propably still do it once I feel happy but as long as that's not the case, it's just another thing I do instead of trying to solve the root problem behind my sadness
But yeah I don't know honestly it's pretty much the same and I propably just needed another reason to confront my stupid little self to try and get me to change something in my life instead of just doing the same hoping my sadness goes away with time, or once i find the right job, or once i can finally draw as good as i want to or whatever else i use as an excuse next </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 17:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been carrying pocket knifes pretty much ever since I was 10 and everytime I bring it up to anyone new they almost always ask me what I need it for and why I would carry a weapon with me and go full on "you're dangerous" mode and what not yet whenever they have anything to cut or something they always come to me, still insisting on knives being so rarely usefull and me not needing to carry one.

My life would be so much more annoying without one, why can't people just accept that a knife doesn't have to be used to murder someone

(but hey that's still better than the people telling me I have to like violence because i draw weapons... thanks mom)

Edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 16:51:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the most annoying parts of my life right now is propably the fact that my door is basically a curtain. I've complained about the broken glass of the (except for the frame) basically glass door so many times already, but my mom basically just says that there is more important stuff she has to pay for right now and that every damn time.

Just because i can technically live with it, doesn't mean i like the fact that everyone can hear every single sound from my room by basically just being in the same floor as me or the fact that pretty much everyone that has ever been in this house, just walks in without ever knocking or anything and even if I could lock the door (which i can't) they just pull the curtain aside and walk in through the frame anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 16:33:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So i was permanently searching for why this comment triggered me so much, I was constantly searching for the times my mom has done this but could only find one instance of it, until i realised that what got me so mad wasn't my mom but my dad, who permanently tells everyone pretty much everything he knows about us (and occasionaly throws in his own made up stories, treating them as reality) and then never takes any complaints seriously treating us as if we didn't have a right for privacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 16:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Austrian with pretty much finished high school education here (actually it's called  a higher technical school, since that is our focus)

So far I have learned about the discovery of america, it's participation in world war 2 (and the following marshall plan to help europe rebuild itself, even though it was more portrayed as a shady tactic to profit off of the war even more) and the occupation of austria following WWII and then pretty much all the important cold war stuff (like kuba, korea, vietnam all that fun stuff) where America really doesn't get away from very nicely

basically America is portrayed as corrupt police trying to rule the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 14:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like MeIRL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 14:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That "made with depression" made this so much better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 22:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like me screaming like a little girl when I'm scared / drop something cause it gets me to laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What embarrassing thing do you do on purpose? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 22:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 20:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so I actually kinda really don't wanna tell this... at least not on my main account and I might actually delete this later but I think I've been silent about this long enough and maybe it helps talking about it to someone at least.

So what I'm actually trying to say here is that as a child (ages 5 to about 11) I regularly had sex with other boys about my age (and yes we all definitly did it consensually) and I'd argue that while it definitly fucked me over (cause I pretty much always just wish I could have had the innocent normal childhood others had in my pursuit to find something normal about me) I'd say that this definitly doesn't have to be the case for everyone and the reason for that is because I actually did some research on people having similar experiences (which weirded me out enough already cause I was basically searching for people having sex as children with other children... try explaining that to someone) because I'm really still not sure how to deal with this, especially since my best friend is one of the people I had sex with and he simply never talked about it after we stopped.

So I read a bit about people telling horrible abuse stories and what not and I don't know how, cause I tried finding these posts once because they would have been helpfull as a source and just couldn't do it anymore, but somehow I ended up on like 3 different sites, each of them about people having had sex as a child and either being proud of it or not caring at all and for example there was this one girl (who I actually think was planning on releasing a book about this) who regularly had sex with her uncle when she was like 8 to 10 or something and was sad when it stopped because she was so proud of being his "chosen one" and having done this "adult stuff" at such a young age and feeling so mature because of it. A few were very much encouraging each other in their proudness in some of these posts and, even though very few, some were actually forced to do it, but for the overwhelming majority, it was definitly more of an experimental thing that either involved other kids or adults

So yes I definitly think that this can happen without any negative consequences for the people involved and that it's great that it didn't have any negative impact on them but since I have also seen this argument made, people really need to watchout when it comes to the kids agreeing to it, because even if they like it at the time and really didn't have any problem with it, they can still suffer from it badly later on (like me)

Edit: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 17:29:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is just something about that "Sorry mom" that hits me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 22:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> China is on the frontier of renewable energy technologies having installed more solar panels in 2017 than the entire world in 2015, they are producing double the amount of renewable energy than the US, they invested 45% of all the money put into renewable energy in 2017Additionally China is the worlds largest producer, exporter and installer of solar panels, wind turbines, batteries and electric vehicles.  
China is still ridiculous in terms of their plans and current situation but so is that of the rest of the world, after all we need to be net zero by 2040 or were gonna have to deal with propably the largest immigration waves ever on this planet and many countries and cities sinking. China is still  a huge problem, but at least they are trying harder than most other countries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-03 16:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... now i kinda feel old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i wish something tragic happened to me, maybe i should just force it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 15:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (like some horrible accident or loosing someone in my family)

so I have a reason to be sad and something people give me attention for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 21:36:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of a problem i had with twitter,  i had apparently created my account 2 months before i was 13 and so had to lie about my age because 13 was the minimum age, changed it last year and they banned my account, they thankfully had a feature to correct this stuff and told me they just had to delete every info of me from before i was 13 and it would be fine and i could use my account again, in those two months i made just 3 posts in total, it took them until a few days ago to get this done... almost a whole year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 01:23:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you only know about this because of reading it on his cousins deviantart account... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-24 15:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So... more masturbation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:37:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that moment if you hear such stories and at the same time, got your first knife bought by your parents when you were like 10...
(a pocket knife obviously) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-27 23:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess there are many things i could talk about now, from breaking a window with my hand, to a fight in 4th grade where i actually went home with a bloody neck and yeah... other dumb things 

but i guess the riskiest thing was when i was chopping wood(my parents obviously not allowing us but you know how kids are) with 2 of my siblings at age around 5-7, my sister was about to lunge out and i wanted to walk through behind here, but i had to move directly under the axe because of some wood behind her, and right as i was under the axe my sister decided to lunge out just a little bit more, well i endet up getting the  tip of an axe right onto my head... lets just say it ended in a lot of blood streaming down my head and a lot crying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>