<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1009</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 01:37:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1273
I consider myself quite well informed about geopolitics, but man this made me feel stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-14 01:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Linguistics - where the hell the human language comes from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 04:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be honest, I've heard most of these utterances produced by native speakers rather than non-native... Especially the "expresso" one was driving me crazy (I used to work in a coffee shop). But maybe I've just met the wrong people haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-12 15:47:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my opinion, unless it would help you to get a better job or help you in any other way, there's no point in learning a language you don't like because you will have no motivation to do so. If you like the way Polish sounds and would like to speak it just because of that, go for it. If you think German is cool, go for it (this one could be actually pretty useful). I'm speaking from my own experience: I tried learning Japanese just because it's believed to be a useful language, but I didn't really have any other motivation, so I gave up. But then I picked Finnish, which I'll probably never use but damn, the language is sooo cool and I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-12 15:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I failed my first attempt because "my driving was too aggressive". I didn't make any mistake, just that. Later I learned that they needed to fail someone to meet the quota or whatever. On the second attempt, I got a commissar who is known for being a giant arsehole. He took me to the worst parts of the city, during the morning traffic, clearly wanting me to fail again, but I made it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 14:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sibling of the year
But honestly, I love this and I wish to have a younger sibling I could torture like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 03:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not even in my final year yet, but in first year I started buying the books I borrowed the most in the library or those that proven themselves to be very useful and which I plan to use for my dissertation so I can have a physical copy for my own library which I can access anytime I want. So far I've spent approx. 300, but I don't regret it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 01:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Czech "panna" means virgin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-10 03:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can confirm that 29 is 100% right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 21:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really sorry you had to stop visiting your family because of that. Politics these days is unfortunately something that causes quarrels within families which just isn't right. I don't know about you, but in my country you can't really watch a TV or browse the internet without seeing any political stuff, it's kinda everywhere. I'm really glad we agreed on not talking about it, bc otherwise we would be arguing constantly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 21:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We try not to talk about it, and if someone needs to vent their anger about the news or sth, we try our best not to comment on it. It works most of the time, except when we visit grandma, she just can't accept that someone has opposite views to hers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 21:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leather </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 21:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those who like pineapple on pizza and those who think it's a blasphemy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 17:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend's brother is a proctologist and he did it exactly because of that - sure, he wants to save lives and help people, but he also needs money, and he knew that if he becomes a proctologist, he wouldn't have a problem to get a well-paid job easily, unlike his classmates who chose to specialise in some more popular branch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 16:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well someone has to be the unique one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 15:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely agree with you. Majority of what the non-equestrian people see is horseracing and so it's natural that it is the one most talked about. But (probably) thanks to that, it became the most controlled one of the equestrian sports. There are still practices in other sports that are way more dangerous and cruel to horses than the whole horseracing itself, but people don't talk about it that much because they don't know about it. 
Once I was talking about dressage with my friend (who knows absolutely nothing about horses), and when I showed her one video, she got completely crazy about how unnatural it is for the horse and how he is suffering and how this should be banned. Ok, I get it that it might seem like this to some people, but... it's not THAT unnatural for the horse as it looks, and if everything is donr right (no rollkur and stuff), then the horse is not suffering at all. You just ride a horse, and based on what you do, you expect it to do certain things. And that's kinda the whole point of horseriding. Of course people can then argue how the horseriding itself is cruel and unnatural, but this seems to me like complete nonsense.
The horses that are used for sport are born for sport - they have it in their genes and most of them really like what they do (like the crazy racing horses). So as long as no harming or unethical practices are used, the animals are totally ok and happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 04:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This thing: r()
I'm not sure how to phonetically describe it, but it's a sound very typical for my native language (Czech) and very few speakers of other languages can pronounce it (actually even the Czechs have problems with it). Plus I think it sounds pretty cool if you know how to pronounce it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 18:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so cool man! Congrats on launching the game, deff gonna play it. Your grandma is so lucky to have you make her stories remembered, and you are lucky to have her share them with you. I recently got an idea about writing down and maybe publishing the stories from WW1 and WW2 my grandma used to tell me when I was a kid, either of what she experienced herself or what she heard from her relatives/friends, and honestly, some of it was pretty unbelievable stuff. However, since she it getting older, she starts forgetting things, including her memories. She still remebers a lot, but when I ask her to tell me one of the stories, I know there are some things just missing, but I can't teally tell which things. Or, once I asked her about a story she told me about our neighbour who fought in a battle quite important for my country, but she didn't recall the story at all. This makes me really sad and I wish I could travel back in time when I was a kid and tell myself to listen more carefully or to take notes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What would you do to a person you hate without them knowing it was you? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 20:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha I completely understand that, the professors can be really confusing sometimes. But from what you wrote I'd say that any language except the really big ones should be ok, 'cause they can't really expect you to study some completely undocumented language on an undergraduate level. Anyway, see what your prof will tell you and if you are interested in my languages, don't hesitate to message me:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What exactly do you mean by understudied language? I am native in Czech and Slovak and would love to help you (with either language), but I'm not sure if they really fall into your description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 00:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's really good question. I usually know if the person I'm texting with uses more Czech or English abbreviations, then it's quite easy to know which one it means, but otherwise I would have to figure it out of context, so there would be a chance of mixing those two up. But to be honest I can't think of any of my Czech friends that uses "nevermind" while texting. The English abbreviations we use the most are idk, idc, wtf, omg and tbh. Though I can't speak for everyone, this is just my personal experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 23:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nvm - short for "nevm" which means "I don't know" in Czech. Another one I can think of is z5 (5 is "pt" in Czech, so together it's "zpt" which means "back", as in " I am back") or "", short for "dky" which means "thanks". There's actually more of them but almost noone uses them tbh (at least as far as I know). A lot of people use the English abbreviations nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 22:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering I now live in the UK, I talk to the native speakers a lot, but if I stayed in my home country then I probably wouldn't. I was lucky though, we had lessons with native English speaker in both elementary school and high school (only once a week, but still). Not all schools can offer this to their students though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 22:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 15:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to think it's because I'm ugly, but then I was told it's because men find me intimidating, or, if they don't, I ignore them. When I look back, it kinda makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 15:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The weather is surprisingly nice for this time of the year which makes me happy and full of energy. On the other hand, I am tired and angry at my flatmates who came home drunk at 3AM and woke me up. So I would say I'm just alright.
What about you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 15:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a highly functioning sociopath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 13:28:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This reminded me of one movie where was a girl who desperately wanted a crossbow and when she finally got one for Christmas (from her uncle or grandma, not sure tbh), the rest of the family was just "who the hell gave that to her" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 13:23:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a shame I had to scroll for so long to find that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 01:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone once told me that ships are called "she" because sailors liked to compare their unpredictability to women's. It is also the reason why majority of ships have female names. 
But, as commenters before me already said, there are multiple theories why is that so and this is just one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 22:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg that is so messed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 22:48:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waaait, people turning mental disabilities into genders? Wtf? That's a real thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 13:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Czech person I have to say that I still refer to it as Czech Republic purely out of habit, but I don't mind people calling it Czechia. Tbh it makes sense to call it like that, we also say "Slovakia" and not "the Slovak Republic". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 13:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a book called "Projects in Linguistics and Language Studies" by Wray   Bloomer full of interesting and easily replicable studies for students (I used it several times in my first year). Maybe your library has some copies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 12:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who use their zodiac sign as an excuse for their bahaviour. "Well, I know this might be annoying for you, but I am xxx, so there's nothing I can do." This is a quote from my flatmate. No, you can do sth about it. Stop being a bit*h. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 04:28:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if it's on the list or not, but I would recommend "The Study of Language" by George Yule. It's written in pretty comprehensible language so to read it you don't need any linguistic background at all and it also covers all the major sub-fields of linguistics, so it gives kinda nice overwiev of what it is all about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 12:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It never came to my mind that the word could have such deep roots. I thought it would be just some weird coincidence. Wow, good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 22:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Czech the word /kakat/ means "to poop" (it's actually one of many words you can use to describe the act of pooping, this one is usually used with children). I really wonder how this happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are the views on tattoos in academia? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 11:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To give a little backstory, I am currently an undergrad Linguistics student whose big dream is to get a PhD and become a university lecturer. I am also in the process of getting a full-sleeve tattoo, which is quite visible thing. So my question is, would that be a problem in getting my dream job? Would I have to have it permanently covered with long sleeve, or do the universities just don't care? I haven't met many academics (at least in my field) with visible tattoos so that worries me a little. Or is this a country-specific thing? What is your experience? Thank you in advance for your answers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 17:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's actually more than one whistle language, but the most known ones are probably Yupik and Silbo Gomero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 16:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://lrc.la.utexas.edu/eieol I honestly don't know where I found this, but I used this page for improving my Latin and Old Norse, hope it will help you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 23:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Czech, "i" and "y" sound the same in the spoken language, but can make a huge difference in the written language - for example:
Bt = to be
Bt = to hit sth/someone
Then there are words where the misuse of i/y doesn't change the meaning but it still hurts my eyes a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We tried "hey Google" on Siri </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 13:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 13:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not alone, I'm also 20 and I love genealogy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 11:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just started the second year of my English   Linguistics degree so I'm not saying that my opinion on that is... valid? But from what I've learned and observed, I would say that English is getting more and more diverse (same thing that happened to Latin). For example, in countries which used to be a part of the British Empire the English was (and still is) influenced by the languages of the native people so it becames quite hard to tell if it is a creole, a new language, or just a very weird dialect. I would also say that a similat thing is going on in countries like the UK, the USA, Australia etc. where English is the oficcial language but as we all know there are some minor differences between the Englishes spoken in these countries, and in my opinion these differences will became more obvious in longer period of time (due to different factors, mostly cultural). So maybe in a few centuries, or maybe even decades, we might have a group of languages descended from present-day English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 20:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have tattoos, dye my hair red and black and you rarely see me in any other color than black. Though I don't do it every day, I wear my heavy boots and leather jacket/long trenchcoat with kinda dark make-up when I'm in the mood.
Idk what sorts of weird stuff people tend to associate with me (and I don't really care tbh), but a couple of things I've noticed:

you really don't smoke?
wow, I would never say you are such a fun person
wait, you go to normal parties?
Omg people, I'm not a satanist/emo/whatever TV stereotype you sorted me into, I love metal/hardrock music and style, but I am also a 20 years old student, I wanna have fun with other people

Speaking of which:

you study at uni and do science? wow I would never say you are so smart
Wtf is wrong with you, just because of my looks (and maybe the fact that I swear a lot) I must be dumb? I'm smarter than you and majority of people you know you douchebag

Also, I'm a bit chubby, so:

omg you really do sport/go to gym? 
Like, yeah, I'm in pretty good condition, I just eat a lot lol. But I run, lift weights, do TRX, occasionaly play volleybal and I love horseriding.

Please, don't judge people before you got to know them, for god's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 01:36:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries, thank you for your question! Languages are my passion and I also study linguistics so I find all the answers here really cool, and the fact that a lot of people are thinking in English even though it's not their native language is something that deffinitely might be worth a further study! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 00:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My native language is Czech and I speak 7 other languages, but I think mostly in English, idk why but I find it easier to let my thoughts just flow in my head. It almost looks like English is the default language of my thoughts, but I've learned it as a third language so it shouldn't be. But when I speak I prefer any other language because English often feels too slow to express myself in. 
Then there's this funny thing when I sometimes think in concepts, like no words, just the meanings, and when someone asks me what am I thinking, I look like a complete idiot because I can't find appropriate words  for the language I have to speak at that moment. That could be annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 03:08:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was 12 (or 13 maybe?), I was home alone, and I opened the door from my family's apartment just to find our schizophrenic neigbour standing in the hallway, pointing at me with a gun. He said nothing, he was just standing there. My first thought was "this isn't happening," but then I realized the shit is real, so I noped out, locked the door and called the police. Then the adrenalin kicked in and I started shaking. I wouldn't say that I was scared though, it was just all sooo weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>