<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4129</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 22:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont insert Q-tips directly into the ear canal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 02:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well 9 pints of beer just got spilled all over the bar top and the floor. Doesnt affect me much but its not the greatest situation to be in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 01:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, when I read through the ashcan rules, the shared powered character was probably my least favourite part of the system.

I generally dont see any reason at all why you couldnt just do away with that part if you want; the rest of the system should work to facilitate the type of story you want to tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 18:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On Instagram? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 02:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont understand what Im looking at here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 02:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a big theme of the campaign Im running; information is biased, everything has shades of grey, and the alignment system in-universe is just propaganda and couldnt possibly ever speak for an entire race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 02:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did think that was some black pudding at first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a friend who failed to grasp the concept of consistency, and thought that whenever I pointed it out to him, it was a personal attack. 

Hed home brew and house rule not because he thought it was interesting or enhanced the game in some way, but because he couldnt be bothered to learn the actual rules. Itd always be weighted against the players, usually because his story didnt stand up to the actions wed chosen to take.

A dragons ice breath, after having been used several times and dodged, suddenly started requiring a second DEX save to avoid sliding about on the icy floor. The DC must have been crazy high because none of us ever beat it. Also the size of the breath changed depending on if one of the other enemies was stood close by or not (barbarian was targeted with a precise blast while grappling an enemy, a blast which didnt hit the grappled enemy, and caused the grapple to instantly be broken). The human enemy controlling the dragon with a psychic connection also managed to run over an area that should have been slick from the dragons breath to make an escape from the temple, with no roll for a DEX save, when it wasnt their turn, only to have every one of us fall flat when we tried to give chase. Also standing up from prone on the ice takes your full movement instead of half is a rule that was introduced only at that point of the battle. 

You never knew what the rules of the universe actually were in any circumstance because hed change it on a whim to benefit the linear story hed come up with. He wondered why I never wanted to play with him after that session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A rouge, a munk, and a saucerer walk into a bar... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 14:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that has more to do with a lack of imagination on part of the players than anything else. The system is not limited to those two/three options. Anything is possible using the rules, but most player brains default to those outcomes.

Honestly Im not sure what else is wanted than those two methods; saying that everything boils down to aggressive or sneaky is pretty vague. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 13:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right... but that still doesnt qualify as killing kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 09:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Careful there chief, youre getting straw all over the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 02:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stroke her hair lovingly and spoon her for the appropriate amount of time.

And how long is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But will it be monetised? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 00:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there isnt a brain coming up with new scenarios for your actions

Thats why Ive started to love TTRPGs over video games! Endless possibility! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 23:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I am into fantasy and escapism. I play D D as a DM on a weekly basis. I obsess over fantasy fiction and tropes, as well as lore and mythology from real life, while writing my adventures and worldbuilding for my D D campaign.

And as I said in the post, I did enjoy them, dont get me wrong. I just feel that they said everything they needed to in that first viewing and they really have nothing to offer me by seeing them again.

Ive read The Hobbit three times, and Ive read all of the Lord of the Rings books once (as a child, before the films came out) including the appendices (told you Im a sucker for lore). So it just doesnt feel like the story is worth revisiting for me. Particularly not worth carving out over 11 hours in order to do so.

As I said in the post above, I love to see others enthusiasm for things they enjoy, I just dont get much from the idea of repeated viewings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 23:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To clarify, I never said I didnt like them. 

I said I saw them when they came out, and I enjoyed them. I just dont think that theyre worth rewatching (and I rewatch things all the time). 

I feel like I got absolutely everything out of them that I could the first time around and I really dont think its worth committing that huge amount of time to watching them again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine what a go-getter youd have to be to be crushing a cardio session while networking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:14:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to offer a differing opinion (and this is no reflection on anyone who enjoys them; I love the enthusiasm I see from people about the things they like) Ive actually never been able to rewatch them. 

I saw them all in the cinema when they came out, and I enjoyed them, but I honestly think that was more than enough. I have friends who have sat down to marathon them with glee and I just have less than no interest in committing for that long to seeing these films again. 

A girlfriend insisted we rewatch Fellowship, years ago, and despite feeling wide awake when the movie started, I was asleep shortly after they arrived at Bree, was woken up for snoring a little after, and went to bed feeling no great loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Ukraine is weak.

EDIT: get cultured, kids. https://youtu.be/fzLtF_PxbYw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 00:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 00:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, if the parents never explained or even said You get to keep this to the kid, then throwing it back seems like a very logical thing to do.

/r/ParentsAreFuckingStupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 00:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im also at this party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 23:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately I know who she is. Shes not shy about it and it makes things very awkward because Im not interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 23:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Claudio Sanchez is not a name I expected to see in this thread. 

But I approve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 23:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id like to enter my 87 minutes for consideration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 23:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. Like the entire point is that he keeps reassuring people they spared no expense but actually all the money went into the cloning and genetic research; the park itself had corners cut everywhere. 

Recreating the dinosaurs was actually pretty much the only thing they (arguably) got right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 23:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Out of Sight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 23:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sure a friend told me there are also scenes in that movie where the cave dwellers appear in the background and stuff like that, but theres no attention drawn to it by the film itself or its not the focus of the scene. Like, if you notice them, you notice them, but if you dont, you dont. Theyre still there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 23:22:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Live in Cardiff. Can confirm; every day is madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah thats the right one way Im going on to the gym now and I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is. 

And it still adds absolutely nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 17:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 12:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Player thinks theyre being hilarious by making a joke thats a long walk for a very short drink of water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 12:30:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem! I started out with 3rd edition when I was a kid in the 90s but Ive experienced the OG systems too. 5e is actually my favourite for how streamlined it is compared to all the others. Definitely a good one to start on :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 12:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good practice to be doing that anyway, to be fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 12:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, they still had AC. It was just that the method of calculating the probability of a hit was more complicated than it needed to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 12:24:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To Hit Armour Class 0

Its a long-winded way they used to calculate if an attack hit or not in the early editions.

Check out the table on this baby: https://dungeonsdragons.fandom.com/wiki/THAC0

Worth noting that in those early editions the *lower* the AC the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 15:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I conflated it with the Feynman Technique for learning which is;

1. Choose a concept to learn.
2. Teach it to a toddler
3. Identify gaps in your knowledge
4. Review and simplify

Its essentially the ELI5 concept, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 14:07:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. But if its simply rolled across its horizontal axis then itll never land on one of the ends anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 13:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aye. But the question was, What does a d3 look like.

https://www.scienceabc.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/3-sided.jpg

Triangular prisms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 13:44:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Triangular prism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 13:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people just seem to have no awareness when it comes to that sort of thing. I had a guy in my group who was the same. He'd comment, over me talking, about something I just said, then he'd relate it to something else, and before you know it he'd be talking across me to another player at the table, talking about a videogame or something, while I'm trying to get across pertinent information to the party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 12:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A couple of times, my players tried to coax me into doing this by forcing two NPCs to interact, I imagine because they thought it would be funny watching me try to keep track of the whole thing while having a conversation with myself.

They must have been so disappointed that I'll roleplay an initial greeting, segue into the conversation and then summarise the interaction for the party.

The Merchant and the Travelling Trader discuss business for about five minutes, and seem to come to an agreement to help each other, which they sign with a classic spit-shake.

Let's face it, it's going to be a matter of seconds before the party get bored with watching you talk to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 12:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was either Einstein or Richard Feynman who said something along the lines of, "If you can't explain it to a toddler, you don't understand it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 11:13:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the Daily Mail. Its a hate rag that is often deliberately inflammatory and sometimes only reports half of a story or omits facts in order to form a narrative. 

It may as well be considered satire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 13:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/uselessNobody </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 13:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neil was just leaving the lander ahead of me and stepping onto the moons surface. Seemed to be taking forever so I was just watching YouTube on my phone while waiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 13:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you lucked out

Conversely, maybe you just got unlucky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 12:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ANTI-social Network is the episode. The quote isnt about loaded dice, but a girl is complaining that someone uploaded naked photos of her to the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 12:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And in the CharDee MacDennis episode, he actually does cheat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 13:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These are my favourite ones. Where the nobody: precedes something literally happening only in response to something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 13:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found on a car sporting a pair of Truk Nutz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 03:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> StalacTites hang. Like Tits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 18:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It gets shaky at the perfect moment, at the moment of reaction. After all the action has happened. And you can still see everything going on. This is great. What are you on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 18:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That guy who rushes the camera though. Props for being so extra in his reaction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 01:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10 years old. Snooping for Christmas presents. Found what looked like a wash bag under my moms side of the bed. Opened it up. Weird purple cylindrical thing with a switch on it. Pressed the switch and the thing started to buzz and hum. Turned it off and put it back. 

Found my moms secret massager she must have used for stress relief. Feel so bad because I never really realised how much she was struggling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 09:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 09:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any time one of my players, in response to uncovering some lore or information, declares loudly to the others, "Obviously," followed by complete speculation, it's wrong. It's completely wrong, doesn't follow any form of logic apart from complete leaps and bounds, and it's always about the unimportant things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 18:53:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Used to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 02:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/lostredditors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 11:30:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Missed a username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 00:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. No. I do not like that at all. I dont know what it is. But I know I dont like it. Take it away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 00:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When the players themselves havent been a DM, they vastly underestimate exactly how much work the DM is putting in, both inside the sessions and outside, in preparation.

I write extensive notes to myself, world-building as I go. Adventures usually end up essentially being full module documents, with several backstories intertwined to create the circumstances of the adventure. I spoke to one of the players in my group the other day and mentioned that the current adventures Word document is currently 50,000 words and he was absolutely gobsmacked. Said it was seriously eye opening to him and hed never realised exactly how much work goes on behind the scenes. And that doesnt include the fact that I like to revise and reread the rules to keep myself sharp on the day.

Playing stops when you leave the table. DMing is a full-time thing.

That isnt often understood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 13:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indubitably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 12:33:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Through early morning fog I see  
Visions of the things to be  
The pains that are withheld for me  
I realize and I can see  


That suicide is painless  
It brings on many changes  
And I can take or leave it if I please  


That game of life is hard to play  
I'm gonna lose it anyway  
The losing card I'll someday lay  
So this is all I have to say  


Suicide is painless  
It brings on many changes  
And I can take or leave it if I please  


The sword of time will pierce our skin  
It doesn't hurt when it begins  
But as it works its way on in  
The pain grows stronger, watch it grin  


Suicide is painless  
It brings on many changes  
And I can take or leave it if I please  
   
A brave man once requested me  
To answer questions that are key  
"Is it to be or not to be?"  
And I replied, "Oh, why ask me?"  


Suicide is painless  
It brings on many changes  
And I can take or leave it if I...  


Suicide is painless  
It brings on many changes  
And I can take or leave it if I please  


Suicide is painless  
It brings on many changes  
And you can do the same thing if you please 

[https://genius.com/Suicide-is-painless-mash-theme-song-lyrics](https://genius.com/Suicide-is-painless-mash-theme-song-lyrics) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 00:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the prank? Whos being tricked and how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 21:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing wrong with it. But it sure as hell isnt cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 21:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All cookies are biscuits but not all biscuits are cookies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 21:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Almost entirely wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 17:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am literally laying on my bed in this exact pose, watching TV and browsing Reddit. 

Love a lazy Sunday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 17:03:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We take it in turns having a chronicler. Theyre responsible in that session for taking the notes on important revelations, story beats, anything that needs to be known, and then at the beginning of the next session, the chronicler gives the recap to get us up to speed.

Theres this one guy, his recaps only ever involve what his character is doing. His most recent recap was I rolled really high on a stealth check and managed to sneak into the castle undetected. Then I found some treasure. And while fighting the big bad, I got two crits. I ended up having to do a proper recap for everyone else, including very important story information which came as a complete surprise to the guy, despite the fact that he had been there and everyone had made a big deal out of it, but because it hadnt happened directly to him he hadnt even paid attention to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 16:20:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think they could do much to help. Theyre clearly having a seizure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 13:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10, 4

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 11:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made a tub labelled fucks to give which became ever-present in our kitchen. 

It was always empty, because we were out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 11:54:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 11:46:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody bothers to check what sub something is posted in. I imagine most people just scroll their front page and hit upvote on anything they find funny or approve of in some way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 11:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WNFPs?

Ninja edit: probably a typo for ENFP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 11:37:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Twelve was just so nothing. 

Crombie, slim jeans, black boots, white shirt. Later added a hoodie under the coat. Dude dressed like I used to when I was at college. There was no Doctor in the outfit it was just a standard get up.

I also stopped really paying attention during his tenure, which was unfortunate as I really wanted Peter Capaldi to kill it in the role. 

He did have one amazingly memorable episode that I thought was fantastic though; the entire episode was just him, start to finish, in a tower of some kind, running from something while trying to find his way out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 02:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never seen anyone wearing those first sandal/boot/whatever the fuck things in real life, but jeez are they hideous. Those gladiator sandals are also ugly as hell. But I actually kinda like those wedge heel trainers in the third link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 01:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our office has a very relaxed/no dress code. Any time the weather starts heating up, it's a constant parade of *f-tsch f-tsch f-tsch f-tsch* as people walk around. It drives me absolutely insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 01:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always refer to them as "snotcatchers". I can't stand them either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 00:52:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or girls who provide nothing but edited/filtered photos. They're a hard left swipe in no time at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 00:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See it's the complete opposite for me. When a woman puts on a pair of heels I instantly find her a couple points hotter.

I know it's weird, I have no idea why, that's just how it works for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 00:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> \*Looks down at own open shirt showing chest hair.\*

Yeah... Hehe... What if the necklace is *silver*, though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 00:03:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One and Two were very conservative.

Three had the ruffled shirts and the velvet suits but they were kind of "in vogue" at the time.

Four had the scarf and that kicked off something. Five had his cricket outfit and the celery brooch. Six was just... All over the shop. Seven had his question-mark sweater vests and his ever-present umbrella, but wasn't too radical.

Then in the new era, Nine had such a non-descript outfit (actually claimed to have been a purposeful design choice). Ten went into "geek chic" and basically wore a fashionable outfit. Then Eleven did the same thing with the hipster look. Twelve was... something. And Thirteen just looks like any girl you can pick out of a crowd in any town in the UK.

They've definitely moved away from "eccentric" and now just dress as normal people do. I was waiting for the reveal of Thirteen's outfit and really hoping it was going to be something super zany. I was very disappointed with what we got. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 23:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinking about this the other day; I used to be into Slipknot, Korn, Linkin Park, all the "alternative" bands. Wore somewhat baggy jeans (more "relaxed fit" as opposed anything we're talking about) and band shirts, hoodies, etc. Carried a skateboard literally everywhere even though I could pretty much only roll around on it.

I absolutely hated those super baggy JNCOs, and I'd rip on friends who bought into the trend. They looked goddamn ridiculous and I never had any desire to wear them myself, my jeans remained in the camp of "still looking like clothes a normal person would wear".

Came home from school one day and there was a pair laid out on my bed. My mum had been a huge supporter of me taking an interest in clothes and developing my "own style", so she'd bought me a pair of JNCOs so I could "fit in" or something. I absolutely refused to wear them and handed them back to her saying I actually hated those kinds of jeans. She asked me to just try them on, so I did, and I felt like an absolute tool so I handed them back again and said she should go get a refund. She did, and she seemed kinda upset about it. Later I overheard her talking to a friend with a disappointed tone saying, "I'm not sure why, but I bought him those jeans like all the kids are wearing and he didn't even want them".

Even typing this out now, I feel guilty about it all over again. But there was no way I was wearing those stupid-looking things. Not even to make my mum happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 23:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those flip flops that everyone seems to be wearing nowadays. Slides I think some people call them? Can't stand those goddamn things. My opinion of a person immediately drops significantly when I realise that someone is wearing them anywhere other than poolside or while relaxing at home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 22:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/suspiciouslySpecific

Used to be as it said. For posts that were just a *little too specific*. You might say, suspiciously so.

Now its pretty much just any time anyone has been specific. Doesnt need to be the slightest suspicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 02:10:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats *Jaleel* White, you plum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:29:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah absolutely agreed. 

I dont know how it plays as I havent seen Atomic Blonde, but just wanted to offer up an explanation in case you found it helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:24:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the point is that Atomic Blonde was specifically praised for realism. 

The Bond series typically isnt and hasnt been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They wont. Because they dont want a franchise with a female spy, they just want to exert their power over the existing Bond franchise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 15:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one literally begins with someone asking a question! 

How the Hell does "nobody:" make sense in that context?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Redditors who went to American high schools, how accurate is the whole "jocks, nerds, popular kids, bullies" dynamic that we often see in 80s/90s teen movies? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 16:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 12:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eh, you might just "run hot". I do too. My body temperature is always higher than my friends, to the point that they'll huddle close or cuddle up to me if we're somewhere cold because I'm giving off heat! I think it's due to my metabolism (find it quite difficult to gain and keep weight as well). I don't find myself getting sick any more frequently than anybody else does, even when I'm "underdressed" in winter.

I imagine (and I'm not scientist), if your core temperature is **actually higher**, then you wouldn't be at any more risk than anyone else of getting sick. But if it's a case of you only perceiving yourself to be warmer when actually your core temperature has dropped in line with the atmospheric temperature, the same as everybody else, then you need to be concerned because you open yourself up to illness without even realising it.

Grab a thermometer and next time this happens, compare temperatures with your friends around you. See if you're actually warmer, or if you're just "in denial". Adjust accordingly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 12:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only absolutely always </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 12:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> INTJ flair

Yeah. Checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 12:01:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where does everyone stand on the idea of verbal components to spells? (somatic also fall under the same discussion)

Ive always ruled that the content of the verbal component is irrelevant. The words or sounds are simply a conduit for the magic and it doesnt actually matter whats said unless specifically mentioned In the spell description (or in the case of somatic, what gestures are used). 

Case in point, was playing a game where I was a bard. My party were getting destroyed by the big boss at the end of the adventure and I arrived late to the scene. In a panicked moment, I cast Hideous Laughter. DM had made it clear early on that somatic and verbal components need to be roleplayed, which is fine, but due to the panic I couldnt think of anything funny to say, so I said Deus Ex Dickina!. The other players laughed, I felt embarrassed at my own stupidity. DM kept a stone face and said that the spell failed, didnt even roll for WIS. When asked why, he said, Well it wasnt a joke so the spell didnt work. He didnt find the comment funny. I shrugged it off and let the game continue, then pulled him aside after and asked where in the spell it said that a joke had to be made. His reasoning was Well why would someone laugh uncontrollably if it wasnt a joke? Like, dude, its fucking *magic*.

We had a similar tiff going over Vicious Mockery, where my comments werent vicious or insulting enough to cause psychic damage. Whereas I thought that hopping into a fray and distracting a water elemental from attacking my friend, with a cry of "Hey, Aqualung!" was bloody inspired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 20:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If Im measuring something to cut or drill. Ill use metric unless the measurement is in a exact number of inches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 20:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And yet I only ever dream of her... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 18:45:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo I know Im late but yall got any more of them 10mm sockets left? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 13:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard it. 

:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 13:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't work kitchens any more, but yeah, the waste used to bother me to no end. Head chef was a dumb fuck too. Conversation would have gone something like this;

"Chef, we've got all these bananas in the walk-in that need to be used immediately."

"Don't have time to make something with them now. They'll have to go in the food waste."

"In that case do you mind if I take some home?"

"Why do you think it's OK to steal from work? You didn't pay for them so you can't have them. Just throw them in the trash and get on with your prep."

This is the same moron who kept out of date stuff in the pantry (talking years) instead of writing it off and disposing of it, because he "Didn't want us to lose money". Also when a coworker went to him in confidence to tell him she was suffering depression and might need some time out, he decided to announce it to the entire kitchen while she was there, tried to ridicule her and concluded that "Maybe you should just kill yourself and do us all a favour instead of taking time off and leaving us short-handed". I was the only one who said anything. Made his shitlist for the rest of my time there.

Last I heard, he got sacked and ended up evicted and working as a garbageman so... guess he gets to deal with the food waste first hand these days.

Anyway... That was a tangent. Good on you, OP. Doing a great thing by ensuring these don't go to waste, and specifically go on to help others. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 02:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What am I supposed to use to plug all these manly bullet-holes I end up with on a daily basis now?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 02:24:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's practicing shuttle runs for his bleep test! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 22:31:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, thatll do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 21:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they were making a joke. 

So... /r/whooosh? Maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 21:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That theory sounds suspiciously specific... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 21:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spider-Man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 14:18:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nearly impossible in 5e. 

But bear in mind that they might be rolling an opposed check against an enemy who has a similar number of buffs. A 30 Stealth is still going to fail against a 42 Perception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 13:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 13:22:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its 12:23pm on a Sunday and this beer isnt going to drink itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 13:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you think you do have the willpower to wield a Green Lantern ring? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 10:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre looking at it the wrong way. You dont use your MBTI to figure out your signs, you use your natal chart to find your signs, then compare them to this to find out your MBTI.

I used this one: https://astro.cafeastrology.com/natal.php

This is only if you actually believe in this stuff. I have a very small belief in astrology, and according to the OP, Im an ENFJ, but I am absolutely for sure a P over J. So take it with a large pinch of salt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is awfully easy to be hard boiled about everything during the day time but at night it is another thing.

From Hemingways The Sun Also Rises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:07:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yeah, why would you take someones temperature if they werent sick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:27:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was waiting for a punchline or the bait and switch where it became obvious which show/movie you were making reference to but it just never came! Thats a wild story but it sounds amazing, and definitely something incredible to share with people about how you met. 

Im really happy for you, internet stranger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:22:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then a mariner took it out with a crossbow, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldnt it be easier to not wear flip flops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats where I keep my fanny pack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:13:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah absolutely. I get what you mean, and I definitely see your point. It does tend to lead to higher stats than other methods, but that tends to be what my players are hoping for. 

I usually play with groups made up of members of the same core group, and theyre all in it to play legendary stories about epic characters doing heroic deeds, so essentially gifting them some decent stats to springboard off of is my way of giving them exactly what they want right from the off.

Personally Im with you; Id like to play with a group who are happy with flaws and difficulties presented by lower stats, but only one guy I know is happy to go along with that. The rest of them want to be high flyers right off the bat, and in the early days theyd always get upset and frustrated early on when they ended up with super low modifiers and couldnt ever seem to be able to do anything as a result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 00:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, originally a Green Lantern villain. Then he started menacing other DC heroes, including both Superman and Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 00:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A smaller backpack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 00:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Family trees include links by marriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 00:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fluoride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 00:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, its a lollipop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 21:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wasnt at all worried at 18. Figured Id always land on my feet.

30 now and while I technically have always landed my feet, uh... I wish I had worried more when I was 18... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 16:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah thats exactly it! The type of person who answers the call to adventure and does so successfully should be an exceptional example of a human/elf/dwarf/etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 16:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah maybe. But I sometimes just like to have shows rolling in the background when I cant decide what else to watch. 

Im talking series where Ive already seen them through multiple times; Friends, How I Met Your Mother, The Office, Parks and Recreation. Itd be nice not to have to select an episode and just to have them fed to me in an order I cant predict.

EDIT: Adding Community to the list, as it's another sitcom I've seen start-to-finish a bunch of times, and makes a great pickup show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:46:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My ex had it happen to her once while she was standing up and leading a meeting at work. She told me shes never been so horrified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:44:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Highlighting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So Im 30 now. I havent seen my stepdad since my mum divorced him back in 2005. Before that I had 14 years of him being a complete asshole.

If I ever saw him again Id still lay into him without mercy for everything he ever did to us. 

So I guess 28 years and counting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive played with players who were forced to have shitty stats due to rolls. Invariably, they dont enjoy themselves, they dont engage as a result, and then they check out entirely.

The PCs are supposed to be remarkable people. And the players deserve to be playing as heroes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking for places to live recently over here in the UK, I was absolutely shocked by the number of listings that only include external images of the building. Like, that's not what I need to see.

Obviously they just want to get you in the room so the salesman can try and strongarm you into renting/buying a dive.

Went to see one place which was a complete pit. Kitchen walls were completely bare and covered in holes where the cabinets had obviously been taken out, "bathroom" was literally a cubby hole in the hallway with a shower head and a shower curtain across it, and the slightest movements made the floor creak from one end of the flat to the other like it was about to give way at any moment. Guy started laying out paperwork on the kitchen countertop while I was still looking around and then urging me to get a signature down so we could discuss things further.

Around the third time he dodged a question and tried to get me to sign, I literally just headed for the door and left without another word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was also the first thing I thought of. Can definitely picture Ricky in his houndstooth shirt, reeling off this as an excuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 13:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look at the other building to the left. Assume that the other side of this building, out of sight, runs parallel to it. The building kind of ends in a point at the corner closest to us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 11:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In retrospect, the above comment makes a good example of a regrettable drunk statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 11:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sent a flirtatious message to a girl who had been out with me and my friends that night. Basically told her I would have liked to end the night in bed with her.

Not a big deal in itself. Id been told this girl was really into me. 

Sent an almost identical message, moments later, to another girl who had been out with us as well. Also had it on good authority that she was into me.

These two girls were best friends. Who lived together. And I later found out, were sitting up at home together doing a debrief when they both received my messages.

Sometimes hedging your bets isnt the best move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 11:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id be down for that. Or selecting a category. I want to watch a comedy. Netflix, do your worst.

Also some kind of shuffle option would be nice. Certain shows dont need to be watched chronologically and itd be nice to just have random episodes play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 11:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4d6 drop lowest, 7 times, reroll 8, pick 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 11:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Curious. What made you go this route instead of using the standard array? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 10:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Signs off the majority of his Tweets with Hanx. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 04:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The gender neutral term for a gender neutral term is a completely different term </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 04:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? Fuck no thats not common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 04:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get the sentiment but if you dont want to be spoiled by set pics and seeing things beforehand, then just unsubscribe from the subreddit until the films out and youve seen it. 

Youre not exactly going to be missing much else at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 04:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems like a lot of people in this thread are ignoring all the headings. You dont just pick your Zodiac symbol in each of them. 

Your Rising, Moon, Mercury, Saturn, whatever else sign is likely different from your Sun sign.

Im a Gemini but my Rising sign is Aquarius. Moon is Sagittarius. Mercury is Gemini and Saturn is Capricorn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 03:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha thats fair enough. You knew what you wanted and you went after it! Respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 03:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like, you sent a message to the wrong person or...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 03:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What exactly did you Google for it to highlight those words? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 03:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think the logic tracks. 

Just think of the way Hollywood jumps on every trend when a film gets incredibly popular, and you end up with a ton of different versions of the same thing. This already happens with books as well. 

Maybe there was one diet book, and it worked, and it was huge. 

So suddenly everyone starts writing their own diet books to take advantage of this new trend, seeing all the zeroes appearing at the end of the bank balance of the person who wrote that first book, and all wanting a piece of it. Now were exactly where we are now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 19:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So massive international incident, killer clowns and attacking people were definitely pushing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 14:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its my homepage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 01:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally just a few days ago I was talking to a friend about a girl I knew in a town we went to university in.

"Oh, I didn't know her that well. But that night she saw me at the show and then came over in the lobby afterwards to say hi. Then when she found out my friends and I were going to a bar in town she told her friends to go on without her and spent the night hanging out with..."

"Dude."

"...fuck. She was totally into me, wasn't she?"

"You fucked up." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 01:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first monk I ever played was genuinely called Chaki Jan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 01:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Far less useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Source? This never happened. 

Which might have a lot to do with why future generations wouldnt believe it. Theyd be right not to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:35:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that makes sense. Thanks for the reply!

I thought you might mean the other sides were just randomly placed, was going to mention the opposing sides adding up to 7 thing lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our group plays with rotating DMs but the same characters going on different adventures. 

The other day I DMed a fight for them. They went in thinking they were unstoppable. What they dont realise is that every other DM so far has been super easy on them. Theyve never been into a fight without full HP and full spell slots. 

They narrowly made it through the last fight, and spent all of their resources. This wasnt even necessarily supposed to end as a combat encounter, but they got cocky with the wrong NPC and pushed for it. They dont realise that they have an actual fight coming up at the beginning of next session unless they do something to avoid it (which they never do). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:28:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean by the other sides are a random roll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is this in the PornHub colours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it too late to go to crab law school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 13:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell me more beautiful and inspiring things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 01:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is exactly the kind of framing I needed. Thanks OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 01:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Commenting for later as I get the same thing. 

Left eye also get a bit lazy when Im really tired/drunk. Never notice it personally when its happening but always see it in photos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 01:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats an instant pass on a health inspection with that level of commitment right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 01:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unlucky OP. 

Ask how shed feel about a sloppy three way with me and my cheap whore tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 01:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldnt. Theyre either an idiot, wilfully ignorant, or saying it exactly so you get wound up and flustered trying to explain it to them. 

Not worth the energy itd take to even acknowledge them. Move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 00:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...I cast Haste on /u/chesari </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 00:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive been hard at work

Ill bet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 12:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably a shortened form of alternative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 12:41:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well this comment was incredibly relevant. It appears we have a paradox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 12:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. This is why some people choose not to get involved.

Me? Im totally into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 12:40:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My players recently started bitching about it when I pointed out that theyd need to put some stuff down at some point or they wouldnt be able to pick some stuff up. Ive mentioned encumbrance every single time theyve collected something and now its actually going to be an issue theyre acting like Im springing a brand new rule on them.

They pick up everything not nailed down (the rogue is carrying three crossbows for some reason) and then when we get to a town none of them ever bother to sell or unload anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 14:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Goonies is exactly where I actually got the inspiration! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 13:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not at all. It's a reference to It's Always Sunny In Philadelphia, and if you don't watch the show you won't get it.

A couple of characters write a musical called The Nightman Cometh. Clip will explain better than I can; [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TzaVd6zl2bA](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TzaVd6zl2bA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 12:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'd have been absolutely on the money, my dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 12:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for this!

The fort above the cave containing the ship had also been taken over by a gang of angry labourers fighting against "the man", so this makes perfect sense why my player thought it had been lifted almost wholesale.

In truth, if he'd said, on seeing the pirate ship for the first time, "Is this by any chance ripped from The Goonies?" He'd have been right on the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 12:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ran a one-shot years ago that ended in a pirate ship in a hidden cave below a fort.

One of my players turned to me with a smirk when the pirate ship was revealed and said something like, "Is this by any chance ripped from a certain low-level raid in World of Warcraft?"

I'd literally never played World of Warcraft. Still haven't. I have no idea what comparison he was drawing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 12:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My party met a monk NPC on an adventure once. His name was Damon, the chosen of Amaunator, and was on a personal mission to find and slay a demonic horse who had been terrorising a local town, while on a larger quest, trying to spread unity and cooperation across the entire realm.

He was Damon, fighter of the Nightmare, champion of the Sun, he's a master of karate and friendship.

For everyone.

My players were so, so, so pissed off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 20:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We back on the Debbie Harry cycle? Usually followed up by Liv Tyler. Ill start collecting images now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 14:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very briefly saw Duchovny in there at first glance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 14:40:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It says If you roll a 1. Id rule it thusly;

When you roll at advantage or disadvantage, you only actually rolled the die that is the outcome after your adv/dis.

10 and a 1 at disadvantage? You rolled a 1. Apply Luck and roll that one die again. 

10 and a 1 at advantage? You rolled a 10. Luck doesnt apply here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 14:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To do something spiritedly means to do it with a lot of enthusiasm, energy, and determination. 

In this case it could be a euphemism for ragging the shit out of a car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 14:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why a d10? Why not, yknow, a d20, the standard tool of decision making that already exists at the table?

Im also not entirely sure why the DM is so adamantly and fiercely involved in something that should be an in-character choice resolved by role play and not mechanics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 13:21:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The liquor will work it out.](https://youtu.be/ol-kzzK6CGw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 12:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, the person in the meme is clearly building their own environment of suffering. Its pretty obvious that the comic isnt aimed at people with actual clinical depression, but those who claim depression when they feel miserable largely as a result of their own bad habits. A point which you actually touched on and then drove right past;

Sure, some people may only feel depressed as a result of their habits, rather than their habits being a result of their depression, but this comic is an appalling oversimplification of a brutal truth that many people face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 22:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am currently going through spaghettification and honestly Im still not sure how I feel about this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 19:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are you even thinking that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 19:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Roll a d10 and whoever is closest to 10?

What kind of fucky decision-making method is that?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 19:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guess you failed an Insight roll to spot irony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 18:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know the gazebo story but I wouldnt have picked up on that as a reference. Too non-specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 17:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Placebo button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 11:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you tried shooting at it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 03:05:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **Thats a lovely lovely goose** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 18:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or he knows how to pick his battles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 13:35:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think thatd make us both a lot happier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 11:42:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For you. Everyone else at the table got tired of it a long time ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 10:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cmon now, Julian. I just wanna make vodka and make some money. I dont want nothing to do with this whole saving the world responsibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 02:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flawed characters *are* fun.

Shitty effortless clich cardboard cutout characters who have no consistent personality or real depth are not fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 02:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha I probably would have been a bit unproductive as well but as I came in I saw a reflection of myself in my gym gear and felt ashamed enough to do stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 02:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be... quick, what are we thinking right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 22:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally just today, I got home from work, put on my workout clothes, jumped in the car and drove to the gym. Then I sat in my car in the car park for 5 minutes staring at the door to the gym, before starting the engine again and driving home. Just so was not feeling it today, so I came home and did some productive stuff here instead! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 21:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rowan Atkinson is ridiculously well-spoken. He speaks in a RP accent. Check out Blackadder or Johnny English; thats how he speaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 14:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, I think I came into the wrong lecture hall. Excuse me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 14:17:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a strange hill to die on, chief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 14:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not at all suspicious. Not even that specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 13:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More of this, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 13:54:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chappelle makes jokes about #meToo and LGBT (specifically Trans people) in amongst some other topics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 13:52:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A Russian bot. Sorry to break the news to you this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 13:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No idea what you're talking about. Link to a clip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 13:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this cat's name isn't Krang then I don't know what's what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 13:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This maf'k ight.

EDIT: Haa! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 12:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every single time this gets posted somewhere with the same bullshit story, it's pointed out that this doesn't look anything like a mugging, and the guy definitely isn't 75. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 12:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Milk in an omelette? For fuck sake, OP, sort your shit out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 13:16:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, but he was accused. And that's enough.

EDIT: come on, guys. Learn to read sarcasm ffs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 11:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries, bud. Have a good day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 11:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 11:15:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The point being made is that the guy from Catcher in the Rye doesn't take care of kitties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 21:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats awesome. Even 1s are non-existent at that modifier! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 21:32:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats the default flair, bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 21:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, thatd work on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 20:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but OP had to somehow include their own pointless comment in the screenshot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 18:50:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always found the gameplay lacklustre, but the story and the set-pieces were epic and awesome.

I dont quite understand why so many people seem to hold the opposite opinion. I had an ex whose family were playing through Halo 2 together all on one save. I was watching them play for the first time when they first reached Gravemind... and immediately skipped the cutscene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 01:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where I'd be if I hadn't got myself so deep into a credit card debt hole. If there's literally anything at all I could do to get 10k in one fell swoop and pay it off in one go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 00:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love clicking "Whatever" on the GDPR popups, only to immediately be fed a popup informing me about cookies. Wonder how many of these we can get going in a chain as the years go by and the legislation piles on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 13:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2023: ahh so it was Rami Maleks character all along! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 11:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow that looks really manoeuvrable... I may have to get a kilt for the gym. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 11:15:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chest pain is no joke. Hope youre doing OK, sis! Look after yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 00:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does the -T mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ouch! But, I mean... yeah </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 00:01:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:50:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not suspicious at all. She's clearly just telling a story about a thing she's seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 11:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not tall and I have yet to find a bath I can truly relax in due to the taps always being in the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 10:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Styrofoam display fruit?

...why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 10:32:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does a nat 1 have to do with anything? If your modifier is high enough then it doesnt really matter what you roll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 10:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfectly cut OOOoooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That hobgoblin himself, smushed by a bugbear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last time I played a bard, he had no interest in being that stereotype. He specifically had a tragic lost love in his backstory and remained faithful only to her despite her having died years ago.

The DM saw I was playing Bard and RPd every NPC I encountered as falling for my charm and being flustered by me talking to them, even outright throwing themselves at me in some cases. 

I still dont know whether it was a lazy lolhornybards thing, or if he was doing a genuine thing and testing my characters declared loyalty to a dead loved one. Frankly Ive always been scared to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the comment I was looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish he had. This player saw combat as a sign of progress and thought that the PCs would always be in the right. Further, he actually didnt think that the PCs could lose combat. 

He was given the chance to leave the tavern, and drew his sword instead.

The tavern owner beat him to within an inch of his life, while the other PCs actually didnt jump in to help for once, and the other patrons of the bar watched it happen. Then the tavern owner recommended that they all leave town while he was still showing some restraint.

The Ranger texted me after the game to accuse me of cheating because he wasnt able to kill the bartender, and demanding to know, How are we supposed to defeat him then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really cant relate. I meticulously plan *everything*. The adventure Im currently running started out as a few notes in a Word Doc. 

Its currently at 50,000 words and written such that someone else should be able to run it like a module.

One of my players accused me of changing things in the background based on their decisions after they did something they thought would be game breaking and the narrative got things back on track. I was just reading from a script which anticipated their fuckery months in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every tavern/inn owner my party have ever encountered has been a retired adventurer or other professional ass-kicker packing class levels. Well, to run a tavern in a fantasy realm, theyd *have to* be, wouldnt they?

I had a plucky little twat of a Ranger in one of my games who went around trying to intimidate every NPC into doing what they wanted by making threats. He actually made the comment to a tavern owner that he should be careful about refusing a guy with a bow and a long sword who just fought a band of goblins... at level 2. 

The tavern owner, a world-weary Goliath, retired from the Kings army with honours, a veteran of a continental war, who set up a tavern in the hopes of enjoying a quiet retirement but knew that he might still need to use his 15 levels of Fighter to defend his livelihood, gave a sigh and lifted up the maul he kept under the counter... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like 95% of the posts in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kit... *Fisto*? Yeesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 08:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering that was the question being responded to, Id say it matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 01:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure. But the question was

Do you really think a company could do something "out of the goodness of their heart"?

To which the answer is obviously, No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 01:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Os has already lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 01:04:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In which case it isnt out of the goodness of their heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 00:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Legitimate question for rural Australians... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 00:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which further illustrates exactly how lost, disaffected, and in need of guidance, they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 17:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Gang Gets TPKd was actually the episode name I gave to the email meeting invitation for my groups game, this week just gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 15:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have made this discovery very recently. All through my life I've had trouble concentrating, thinking straight, been exhausted all through the day, stomach complaints, headaches, muscle and joint pain, anxiety, not really being able to function socially, I've also always been underweight despite seemingly eating gargantuan dinners. A long old laundry list of chronic issues that I figured were just the way I had to live and that I must have something fundamentally wrong with me.

Turns out it's just that I never used to eat breakfast. Then I'd just scarf down a sandwich for lunch, and wouldn't eat a full meal until dinner in the evening, where I'd have seconds and sometimes third portions. Then I'd wonder why I was full of energy and wide awake at night when the day had been such a struggle. 

Since I started making sure I'm actually eating consistently through the day, most of my issues listed above have cleared up completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 13:04:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks more like a falchion than a scimitar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 08:56:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because what's the one major thing missing from all action movies these days, guys? Full penetration. Were gonna show full penetration, and were gonna show a lot of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 13:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our hubris as a species knows no bounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 09:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/FakeAlbumCovers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 21:36:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id say this is strangely wholesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 21:02:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And everyones like, Woah, they really are hot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 20:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great. Now thats going to show up on my Recently Viewed list...

At least Ill be able to find it again later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 15:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Can you taste it? Is it salty?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 14:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Favourite character in that movie. "Donk" guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 12:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Top marks for the dude who said, "I'll make sure it doesn't fall". Good job there, guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 10:26:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you propose could have been done to prevent the crash in this situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 02:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Attach the stone of shame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 02:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shut it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 02:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The party I'm DMing for pull this kind of shit all the time. They unironically burst into every town, announce themselves as "heroes", and try to tell whatever existing authority, that they "outrank" them. This is all while breaking and entering every property that gets described, stealing anything that isn't nailed down, and essentially treating every single NPC as a worthless cardboard cutout in a world built for their adventures.

They genuinely don't understand why most towns and NPCs in the world I've built, can't stand heroes and adventurers, and just want them to leave town as quickly as possible.

Though they still haven't caught on that the last Inn they stopped at charged them 200GP a head for a night, despite the fact that the written sign outside (which they did read) said 5SP a room (which have two beds in). Heh, "Adventurer Rates". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 02:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My last character was a Bard, he specifically had, despite a Noble background through adoptive upbringing, a great respect for the working man, particularly craftsmen. I went on a little solo shopping trip in a session where we had a stopover in a city. I paid the asking price for everything, while engaging in full conversation with the merchants and getting to know them all on a first-name basis.

One other member of the party in particular, every single time I just handed over however much was asked for, was so distraught, "Haggle with him, you idiot! Get a lower price! You're a Bard with high charisma for fuck sake! You can probably get all this stuff for free!"

This is the one time that this player disagreed with "It's what my character would do" (it may have been because it's literally the only time someone other than him has used it to justify actions.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 02:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Yeah. Yeah, that's good bro. You're gonna be solid when you get a girl. OK, now let me have a try."

"Oh yeah. Oh yeah, dude, that's some quality boning, right there. You got this, I got this. Let's go find some girls." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 01:45:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, not since I read *Horrorstr*... F that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 00:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never had a stronger urge to go and play Metroid in my entire life... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 22:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I put all my focus into a series of very intense and long term relationships, beginning at high school. Im very quick to fall in love and then to give my everything to that person. I havent been single for longer than a couple of months since I graduated high school in 2005. As a result of giving myself so fully to these relationships, I didnt study or work as hard as I should have in school. As a result, my most recent relationship (with the girl I was convinced was the love of my life, and wed talked about getting married), has just ended. Now Im sat here at 30 with 10k in credit card debt, nothing to show for it, a terrible, low paying job, no qualifications to pull myself out of this hole or get something better, and nowhere to turn. I do have some amazing memories of love and relationships, and some experiences within them, but I dont have much else, including money or meaningful work. 

The grass is always greener, my friend.

I can guarantee that, with the life and safety you have set up for yourself, you will be able to find someone. This missed chance is not the be all and end all, it certainly wont be the last chance, even if it feels like it now; a few years down the line, it wont. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 16:58:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Nah bruh...](https://youtu.be/9x-iZGnsLOU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 15:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trust me, Im more scared of it, than it is of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 13:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah... but thats less funny, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 02:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pray for a quick death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 23:35:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cant wait til we finally settle on Mars and can get to work on fucking up that planet too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 23:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god! What are you doing? Are you fucking me right now? I cant believe youre fucking me! This is so gross. Ugh, I should tell mom and dad. I cant believe my stepbrother is having sex with me! [No effort is made to change the situation in any way at all.]

And thats how Shakespeare came up with the expression, The lady doth protest too much, methinks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 23:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally never understood why people get so mad at video games. Ive had people go on full on rants at me on online games, trying to taunt me and stuff and Im sat there as chill as can be like, I just finished a twelve hour shift at work and Im fucking around to unwind. I honestly couldnt care less about this if I tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 23:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...  
...^^^^^^son ^^^^^^of ^^^^^^a ^^^bitch   
\*upvotes* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 22:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My players *wish* they had a Douglas Adams level of wit and humour to pull off Hitchhikers Guide as a comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 02:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mhm. Mhm. I see.

...now say that *someone* had already done it before seeing your advice not to, because she was walking around the house in those little booty shorts and a tight T-shirt that kept riding up and showing the butterfly tattoo on her left hip while she was reaching for the top shelf in the narrow kitchen, and *someone* stepped in to help her and realised a little too late that they were standing real close, and they end up looking each other in the eyes. In that moment they both realise that her sister is out and will be for a while and they both want it while they can have it before she catches her flight back to France on Saturday so they just give in...

Say something like that happened, for example. Then what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 02:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can tell that you have two feet... they are also flat. Roll initiative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 19:14:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The DJ button on the keyboards. Let her get a few words into what she was saying, then hit it DJ!

We kept it up even after the vein in her forehead started popping out. Then she slammed the glass jar containing the headphone splitters on the desk in an attempt to call for order. Shattered and split her hand open. She left the room shouting about how we were a bunch of little bustards. A stricter teacher came in and kept watch on us. She never came back to the school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 18:21:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> VATs maybe? I dont know, I never played it on PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 18:19:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right?

Most of the posts in this sub now are Just specific. Nothing suspicious about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 10:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First up, never dismiss your own victories as just being a small thing! A victory is a victory and you deserve to feel absolutely awesome as a result of it. When I was at my most socially anxious, if I managed to so much as say "Thank you, have a nice day" to a cashier in a store I'd be riding that wave for days, and I think that eventually helped me to climb out of the hole. So let yourself feel that and it'll help this become more of a lasting change!

I don't know what "turning up to" means in this context, as I at first thought you meant volume until you said the girl's friend did it to your music. But I guess it's like, dancing, or really getting into it or something?

Music has an incredible amount of power over our psychology when we let it get in. I've had similar experiences where it feels like I can embody the tone of the tracks I'm listening to and let it change my attitude. As soon as I can be bothered to get around to it, I'm going to be putting together some Spotify playlists for myself that help me get into certain zones depending on what I need to do. Grinding out a few more reps in the gym, going to a terrifying social event, job interviews, etc.

So glad that this worked out for you, man! Let this be a door opening into greater things! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 10:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Barefoot Assassin strikes again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 10:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean the one that says "Burberry"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 10:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I act like a different kind of dork depending on the groups and people I'm hanging out with. But somehow, whenever some of those groups have ended up in the same place, the persona I take on has been described as "Cool" and confident, and I apparently become a very desirable person to be around. I guess it's similar to how white is made up of all different colours in a light spectrum (or something, I may have come close to failing science in high school 15 years ago.)

Then the groups disperse and it all falls apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 13:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't relate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 11:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats real good going. Its been years but if I remember correctly, my first ship, Pioneer, was lost right near the beginning of Sector 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 11:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep on surviving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 16:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The swole brown fox jump squats over the lazy dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 16:02:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im the extrovert in a room full of introverts and Im the introvert in a room full of extroverts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 00:14:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you explain what you mean by a libertarian lean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 16:51:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thinking about how many people will love me once I start to get buff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 16:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Text-based conversations  In-person conversations  Telephone conversations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-11 21:43:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh crap. One for /r/LostRedditors here. I was reading /r/ShowerThoughts for ages and thought this was another Shower Thought! I do apologise! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-11 21:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The full expression is, "Great minds think alike, but fools seldom differ."

Which says exactly that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-10 10:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gone too soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-10 00:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can cover both of those a few times each before lunchtime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 10:51:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Driver picks the music, shotgun shuts his cakehole.

A quote from Supernatural, but its also been the de facto rule in every car Ive ever been in. Doubly so in my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 00:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How many licks does it take to get to the centre of a tootsie tent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 13:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Invent a job title. "Intermediary Planner". Plan events and things for people, but then leave the execution to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 11:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I told him, Learn how D D works and maybe I wouldnt have to. 

Then I left and never came back to his game. I spoke to some of the other players there that day, and apart from one of them (who didnt mind because he just wanted to play D D at any cost), none of them wanted to play with him as DM again. There was no Session 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 11:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your bone conducted voice is true to you, but the voice you hear on audio recordings is what everyone else hears as well, so thats your true voice. 

But which voice is true and which one isnt, probably doesnt really matter unless theyre both telling you different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 11:04:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [dan le sac vs Scroobius Pip - You Will See Me](https://youtu.be/j0gNWUMl8t0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 10:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only problem with these techniques and things given in videos like this is that Ill watch the video, Ill take it all in.

And then at the exact moment it becomes relevant, I wont remember a single thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 10:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 10:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but thats because the island ended up in 1976. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 10:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about the other way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 10:48:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Session 1 for what was planned to be a campaign, and our characters were starting separately, having a brief encounter alone and then meeting up together to start the adventure in earnest. I was up first. I was doing fine, and then I said that I wanted to do something. Dont remember what it was but it was pretty straightforward. 

DM: Hmm... roll a d6. 

Me: ...excuse me?

DM: Roll a d6 for me. 

Me: ...why?

DM: To see if you can [do the thing].

Me: ...so why not a d20 and [proficiency + relevant skill]?

He stared at me without saying anything for like five seconds and then said, Fine.

After the session, he confronted me after everyone else had left and said, Id appreciate it if you didnt undermine my authority as DM at the table in the future. If I ask you to roll for something just do it the way I tell you.

I get the feeling he was trying to be intimidating, but it literally took everything I had not to punch his lights out. Guess I rolled a natural 6 on that check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 04:26:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Back it up just a little bit... did he do it?

...please tell me he didnt do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 03:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a fan of this style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 03:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 03:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe so. But I was specifically responding to people who suggested she wore it under her uniform so she could go swimming straight after work without having to change. And I hope shed take a shower and change before getting into a swimming pool, due to the nature of her work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 03:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dexters Palabratoradin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 04:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now use it to stop a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 03:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I disagree with their logic. Just because nobody got up to go to the bathroom doesnt mean nobody needed to. 

I didnt get up to go to the bathroom when I saw it, but I 100% was bursting for the entirety of the third act and would have loved a bathroom break built into the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 23:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention; shes working in a hospital. All the disgusting bodily fluids and whatever that she could potentially get all over her during the shift... Id hope shes going to hit the shower the moment shes off shift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 22:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tell you, 3am feels like the moment my brain finally gets in gear, all that motivation materialises, my creativity spikes, everything. The rest of the day, nothing. 3am hits and I'm suddenly firing on all cylinders. Wish the rest of the world could be more amenable to my natural rhythm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 16:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He wouldnt care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 16:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work in an office with an extremely lax dress code, so people wear jeans and t-shirts all the time and my job is shite.

The decent jobs in the company are all the ones that still require people to wear suits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 16:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually had a first time DM do stuff like that once because he thought it was funny. DEX checks to turn door handles, STR checks to lift up beer in a tavern, it was like every single mundane action had to be punctuated with a check so hed have the chance to narrate some kind of ridiculous slapstick scene. 

He was the only one amused, everyone else just got very frustrated very quickly. I called him out on it, and he said, Rule Zero: The DM is always right. And then one player just got up and walked out.

We never let him DM again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 19:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lily is a treasure! This is so adorable in so many ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 15:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always reply almost instantly to direct messages. I get excited that somebody actually wants to talk and race to my phone/keyboard when I hear the notification. Especially if it happens to be a girl Im interested in romantically. I do often wonder if my keenness puts people off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 15:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unpopular opinion: even George R. R. Martin only *barely* pulls off GoT style stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 15:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Half-warforged

Um... *slowly raises hand* uhh... *slowly lowers hand again* no. I definitely dont want to know... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 11:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember seeing a video on YouTube a little while ago that proposed some ideas for revamping the series in some way. 

Among them was this idea of returning to the 50s/60s, using the knowledge of historical events and things to shape and inform the stories, but also, using knowledge of bleeding edge technology at the time, to make realistic gadgets for both Q branch and for the villains, which teeter on being sci-fi if the movies came out at the time, but we now know would have been in development during the timeframe the film is set in.

That always intrigued me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 11:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even better; I actually started out by scrolling really slowly, thinking it wouldnt be so long, then sped up, then did the thing where you just flick the screen out of the way really fast. 

That did the trick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 10:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was making a joke based on this exact conceit that if youre doing both anyway it doesnt really matter, but I always appreciate seeing the maths! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 10:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I can never remember whether this tip is to push or pull first so it takes about the same amount of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 10:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive seen them as a triangular prism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 10:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a player say this to me once as a reason for not role playing outside of combat or engaging with the world at all. 

He then later asked me, outside of a session, if we could change to a different system from D D, If theres something a bit more narrative-focussed and less rules-heavy.

He had no suggestions for such a system, he expected me to find one, learn it, and then tell the other four players that we were switching, mid-campaign, to a new system. So that the person who didnt role play at all could play a more role play-balanced game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 10:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. 

The kilt is the issue with the wardrobe in that film. 

Nothing else *ruffles* my feathers as much as the kilt does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 01:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The real bounty was the booty we got along the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 22:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's it. Didn't realise there was a name for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 21:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or just people who have been playing for longer feeling responsibility towards the people they got into the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 20:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody does; everybody starts with 0. 

But people who have already been playing for longer can give them some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 19:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I can guarantee that something like that would have happened if it hit a Nat 1 on the second roll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 18:15:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's possible, but knowing the guy, it's unlikely (Once tried to take a player's Natural 1 on a roll with advantage "because the 1 came up first"). I'm the usual DM for our campaign and he did this one-shot so I'd have a chance to play. He barely stuck to the rules as it was, and anything he houseruled or made up on the spot was specifically so he could fuck over the PCs (we had a fight on some stairs; he made the PCs roll DEX saves every turn to avoid falling down the stairs during the fight, "Because you're focussing on fighting and not on the stairs". We all fell down the stairs repeatedly. Took bludgeoning damage each time. He found it hilarious. Nobody else found it funny at all).

When the session ended he unironically said something along the lines of, "This DM stuff is hard. You've all been worthy opponents." Which, I think, says a lot about his mentality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 17:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I rolled for an attack with advantage once. First roll, I got a Natural 20. DM insisted I take the second roll, like, stubbornly refused to progress anything until I rolled the second die. Some kind of weird power trip on his part I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-23 14:47:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keyword: typical

Mine wasnt so much forged for war as for... reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-23 12:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That ones a classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-23 00:43:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insert that Tweet about D D being ultimate fantasy for adults; seeing the world, having close friends, sleeping for 8 hours a night, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 20:12:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah, I know, some of them dual-wield scimitars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 19:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Good point bro, door's open" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 19:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've lost count of the number of times I've explained to my players that Initiative order is essentially "how fast PCs, NPCs and monsters react to the development of a situation". 

You might be aiming your crossbow to fire and interrupt the big bad while he monologues at you, but he and his honour guard aren't stupid. They can literally see you lifting up the heavy crossbow and taking aim while standing 10 feet away from them. They've got a chance to react to that if they're fast enough, and that chance is represented by the initative roll. You don't get to leapfrog the system and suckerpunch everybody just because you shouted out while the DM was still describing the scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 19:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's kind of the point. 

I have a Ranger in my party who constantly interrupts my narration to "Fire an arrow" the moment there's any hint of a potentially hostile creature or anything like that (He thinks that if he does so he'll be able to skip initiative or automatically go first in combat, and even though our campaign has been going on for over a year, he'll still argue this point with me at least once a session, but that's a whole other story). 

Of course, loosing an arrow at the first sight of a troll shambling into the forest clearing might be in-character for the Ranger...

But let the damn DM speak and narrate the scene before declaring your actions, for crying out loud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 17:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im good to go now if you are? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 17:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds good to me. Let's do it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 16:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah sure! How would that work? Ive only ever done quizzes and things before; never actually had another persons input so it could be very enlightening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 16:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im actually doing some reading about it and I think I might be, you know. I took another MBTI test and got ENTP again for some reason but its definitely worth me looking into it some more. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 10:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think its something to dislike. Knowing how to pick your battles is a good thing. Nobody likes a belligerent ENTP whod argue the toss about absolutely anything just for the sake of it. 

If I feel like something just isnt worth the effort or particularly important, Im more than willing to just let it go. 

But Ill argue down to my last if I think something is worth making a point about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 10:31:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not even used in a way that makes sense most of the time. 

Wouldnt too angry to die necessarily need to be *in response* to something trying to kill the barbarian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 10:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone else find it really weird that they skipped the one with the prominent cross on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 10:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had a friend who was about 58/59. His D D character was a barbarian who was 65. Hed often give his height as a counter argument when a DM wouldnt let him do things. 

He wanted to lift up my dwarf and throw him over a 30ft chasm to attack the group of goblins on the other side who had just cut the rope bridge. DM said he wouldnt be able to lift and throw a dwarf so far and he just said in this dejected way, But Im 65...

As if height was the only thing preventing that feat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 22:10:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is that suspicious? They're describing a thing they've obviously seen... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 19:20:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seen this so many times that its only going to be unexpected when it doesnt end with the punchline about the dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 15:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive actually put games down and not come back to them just because there are so many indicators and marks on the map that I end up feeling all at once overwhelmed, and as if Im never going to possibly deal with all of them, and frankly cant be bothered to.

Present me with a storyline and a map and let me explore the world myself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 02:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well for iPhones its a pain in the ass to put custom tones on the phone. So most people use the ones already on the phone, or leave the defaults as they are.

I say this as someone who uses one and put a custom tone on my phone just the other day. Its ridiculously convoluted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 02:06:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Put up your swords!

*Pulls out Beretta with Sword 9mm engraved on the barrel.*

I totally, unironically, love that adaptation with all my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 20:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats what bugs me about these images; the quotes posted over a random picture of a celebrity that has nothing to do with the quote in question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 20:10:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like something from a game boy Pokemon game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 20:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To add on to this, the DM is still a part of that team. Theyve either put in a lot of hard work designing everything for you to play in, or theyre making the effort to DM everything for you, keeping all those plates spinning trying to help you have a good time.

Purposely trying to break every environment or interaction or test the DM by doing annoying things is just as bad as pissing off the rest of the players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 20:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But be sure to include some kind of vetting process.

I was using an app for random quotes recently to gain inspiration for writing a short story each day. There was a function to add your own. On the third day I got DEEZ NUTZ LOL.

The resulting novel has just hit the point where it needs to be split into a five-book series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 19:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant believe this still needs to be explained to people. Whenever anything like this comes up its like people think hes got it all stuffed under his mattress in cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 17:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww, you were doing so well at the start of your comment and then it all fell apart... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 17:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Used to work in a restaurant in an entertainment complex. The whole place opened at 0800 but the restaurant didnt open until 1200. The entrance to the restaurant was a staircase in the main entry corridor that had a velvet rope across it until the maitre d opened it.

I was running around doing prep one morning and had to duck downstairs to get some supplies. On the way back there was a family waiting in the corridor next to the stairs, checking their watches and grumbling to themselves. I ducked under the rope as always when the father figure reached over and grabbed my shoulder. 

Excuse me, is the restaurant open?

Yeah, we open at 12.

But its 10 to.

I just kind stared at him for a moment, dumbstruck. What do I say to that? Im glad weve reached this understanding? Gathered my thoughts and kinda stammered out my response. 

Yeah, well be open at 12.

And then he says something thatll continue to confuse me until my dying day, for the sheer balls on the guy. The absolute sense of entitlement. The assumption that the world operates on his whims...

**Can you take our order now so itll be ready when we get up there?**

I couldnt believe this guy. Im standing there in chef whites and chalk stripe trousers, does he really think Im gonna take his order and have the kitchen make it so he can be served as soon as hes seated? I waited for a moment for him to laugh, smile, anything to show me its a joke. But nope. Nothing. Guy is dead serious. With no idea what to do at this point I literally gave the loudest, fakest laugh Ive ever given in my life and continued up to the kitchen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 17:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not just old people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 17:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lidl have pressure washers at the moment?!

Off I go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 17:04:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, see, OPs is worth more because its more scarce. He only has one of them.

Youve got five, so the market is saturated. Yours arent even worth the 50p pieces that theyre printed on.

Trust me, Im a money guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 17:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some bullshit about bossing around Siri when its a woman but not doing the same when its a man. 

Its absolute crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 16:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody alive does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 16:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could eat... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 19:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/ThanksIm~~Cured~~Tall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 12:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Starbz? Seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 02:11:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah absolutely. When we had session zero for Hyperlanes and pitched our characters to the DM, this player kept trying to insert his character into our backstories. He was determined that he was going to have a pre-existing rivalry with someone for some interesting conflict in the party. Funnily enough nobody went for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 01:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah its happened twice now. We were playing Hyperlanes (a full-conversion Of 5e to sci-fi), and we had a captain meeting up with different neerdowells to put together a group of smugglers for a job opportunity. This guy was playing an engineer and got all difficult when approached. The Captain player stared him down for like three seconds and then just said, Suit yourself. Youre not as special as you think you are. We can find another engineer.

He was the second of five characters the Captain approached. So the DM had the Captain recruit an NPC engineer, and then played out the other PC meetings, letting That Guy sit in a panic like he wasnt going to get to play. Then turned to him once the rest of the crew had been assembled and said, Do you want to try that again, or should they leave without you? It worked pretty well to get him on board. (Though he did whine to me after the session that he wanted to make things interesting and everybody ruined it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 01:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its certainly true in England and our mens team is pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 15:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> \players actually reading the PHB

Yeah right. Now Ive seen everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 13:40:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heres a tip; if your response and subsequent attempt to prove someone wrong begins with, So youre saying, then that probably isnt what theyre saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 12:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive always run into the opposite problem; the party are willing and accepting to bring the new PC along. Either through meta reasons or genuine in-character acceptance of any and all. 

But we have this one guy... his characters always arrive with the attitude of Why the hell should I go with you? You have to convince me. No matter how many times Ive told him to knock that shit out. Its gotten to the point where one of the party will now literally say, Fine. Dont. Well find someone else.

And when hes one of the surviving party, hell antagonise every new player character relentlessly. It could be fine, it could be interesting, but he does nothing interesting with it. Its the same every time; remain obstinately stubborn about not accepting them, make some incredibly easy and unfunny pun on their character name, end up making the player not have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 12:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If theyre all having fun, then who cares. 

Clearly the DM, who is just as entitled to have fun as everyone else around the table, but isnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 12:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And then they get back into the heat of battle only to realise that Bard was just a run-of-the-mill minstrel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 11:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This could be a screenshot from a couple years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 12:58:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. So Daily Beast couldnt even read the press release properly either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Yet*... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is this suspiciously specific? Its a headline describing what the story is about... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sticks and stones may break my bones...

^^^^^but ^^^^^words ^^^^^will ^^^^^hurt ^^^^^forever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:30:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please tell me the name of that company so I can boycott them. Theyve clearly gone too far by giving away that title to someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A guy I used to be friends with cooked us salmon fillet once when we went over to his place. When he served it up, someone asked him where the skin was.

Dont worry, its in the bin.

Everyone went nuts. He didnt see what the issue was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well considering in the original novel of Moonraker, Ian Fleming himself wrote that 0011 went missing on assignment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 00:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What happens when they do the fusion dance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 23:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no. Im not going to that sub ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 23:02:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothings so black and white as that. Its just insecure people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 22:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why Skynet will never get off the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 21:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So many people getting up in arms about things who clearly cant read... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 20:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real? I had no idea. Thanks for the correction. This does just make it seem so much worse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 20:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youve somehow managed to talk yourself in circles on that first point and honestly thats admirable in a way. 

I'm not gonna post a lot on this sub because I don't care much about action movies.

Really says everything that needs to be said about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 20:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When not a single film in the series has included "James Bond" anywhere in the title at all, why would they start now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 19:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **TL;DR: I go into way too much detail about a load of stuff that doesn't really matter. Whole game can be summed up by your thoughts about Franklin; so much potential, that they never really did anything with.**

They never really did anything with any of the characters. I finished the game and found it incredibly hollow; because it was all basically there to set up GTA Online. Lamar deconstructs the nature of GTA games early on when he says to Franklin, to paraphrase, something like, "We work for someone for a while til we kill them and then go work for someone bigger". And then that doesn't really tend to happen in Five, because all those NPCs are used in GTA Online so they needed to be left alive, and as a result you just kind of bounce along the storyline with no real feeling of achievement. **[EDIT: This has been corrected down below and it turns out that theres no real reason for these characters being left alive and a lack of sense of progress.]**

Personally, I found Michael's story of being trapped in a life he found nothing in, with a family who hated him, relateable and interesting the whole way through, and when he started getting involved in movies I thought it might be beginning to get *really* interesting. And then the game just ends.

Franklin, as you said, had a ton of potential, but then just nothing happens. He gets a huge house in the hills fairly early, moves to it and then kind of sits along for the ride.

I don't even remember what happened to Trevor, but I also couldn't care less. I know plenty of people liked him as a character and I've got nothing against that, I just hated him from the moment we were introduced to him in-game. Also didn't help that he beat Johnny Klebitz to death for no reason, who I actually particularly liked. Interestingly my opinion towards Trevor changed when I went to a tattoo place while free roaming, and saw for the first time that the tattoo of the cross on his arm is a memorial for Michael. If we'd explored him more as a character dealing with intense grief over the loss of a friend he saw as a brother, or seen him slowly unravel to the monster he is when we meet him, I'd have found him so much more interesting as a character.

I think I would have preferred the game if the three storylines had been either entirely separate game modes, or if you select a character and then play through only their story, which sometimes crosses paths with the others, instead of being forced into segments where you play as one of them individually. To give more time for character development and growth.

Kind of like how GTA4 did with the two DLC stories. You had Niko's main story, then The Lost   The Damned and The Ballad of Gay Tony, which each told an individual story, but they cross paths at times in the narrative until they all clash in a certain mission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 19:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went on a date with a girl once who said that her perfect guy would be someone like Dean Winchester. I assume she didn't think any farther than the looks department, but it was a red flag.

Having said that, I do probably drink too much, have a short temper and chronic depression. So maybe I'd have been perfect for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 18:46:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly still crease up at the Curse sketch every single time I think of it...

[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZNno63ZO2Lw](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZNno63ZO2Lw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 18:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe he also starts with the most cash on hand out of all 3 of them if I remember correctly. A couple hundred thousand dollars. I remember seeing the figure and being taken aback like, "What?! How did this trailer trash have so much more money than the other guys?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 18:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My girlfriend bought the game and played it for hours, loving every moment of it.

When she got up to the first time you play as Trevor, when you're forced to do his missions for a little while, she did a few, then turned the game off. That was 2017, and she still hasn't picked the game up again. When I asked her about it, she said that she has no interest in Trevor as a character and doesn't want to be forced to play as him, as a result she doesn't really care how the rest of the game turns out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 13:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Specific, but not at all suspicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 05:23:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its funny you should post this; last night I had a ton of things I should have been doing, and scanned through all the films available to me, hoping to find something new to watch, before ultimately settling down to watch Goldeneye... again. 

And I dont regret it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 02:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone let me know when the genderflipped version of this question gets put up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 02:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This comment is gas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 02:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im gonna be honest, Im imagining him rapping with his usual speech cadence and Im already on the verge of losing my shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 01:59:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wheres John Titor when you need him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 00:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ^ This is what a WIS score of 20 looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 22:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just need you to tell me Im a good person... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 21:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some of these features allow you to increase your ability scores, either increasing two scores by 1 each or increasing one score by 2. You cant increase an ability score above 20. 

Basic Rules (p.12)

And yeah the belt would be a magic item, which I made concession to.

Out of curiosity I looked it up and the World Record for long jump is 29 feet 4.25 inches, so I guess it makes sense that someone with an inhumanly high strength would be able to achieve such a feat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 20:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Polymorph replaces your ability scores, but youre still aware of who you are and what you were planning to do. You might just be required to make saves in order to stay focussed.

Although Ive since changed my answer anyway; the bardiest of Bards wouldnt even have any Bard class levels. Having realised that they can play with tits on a whim by transforming into an animal, would have immediately taken 2 levels in Druid and never even bothered with Bard training at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 20:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt there a cap at 20 for PC ability scores? A PC can only get a strength over that with the use of magic items.

Still. That seems pretty broken if thats the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 19:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, dont do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 19:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A hundred feet? You can jump 33 feet from standing *before the spell*?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 19:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just so you know, you can swear here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 18:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre good at cooking that one thing. Youve specialised, but unless you can do more than one thing youre not good at cooking in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 18:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive seen it even farther back than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 18:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tried a straightforward calendar app? Most of them allow you to automatically repeat events on a certain day and have note room for your exercises, sets and reps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 18:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do that when he can learn Polymorph? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 18:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I like this. The separated grid section and the DM corner. Plenty of table space for the players without needing to put the battle map in the middle. Every table Ive ever played at has been cluttered and could have done without. 

Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 18:06:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt even see fookin, I saw a litany of swears and I automatically read it in a Scottish brogue. Keep your tam o shanter on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 17:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why I always let my players reroll 1s when theyre rolling for stats these days. 

After a few instances of players getting stung right off the bat like this, and realising that they subsequently have less fun as a result, its pretty shitty to force people to go on with stats they dont like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 17:26:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a meme, bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 17:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is neither suspicious nor specific... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 17:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats suspicious about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 17:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really dislike the gun from the film. If I remember correctly from reading the book (its been 10 years), Scaramanga just had a golden revolver, which, when imagining it, I always found far more aesthetically pleasing and interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 17:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use [f.lux](https://justgetflux.com/) for this purpose. Its adjustable, and you can set it in a timer to gradually darken and lighten through the day.

Only problem is if your work at a computer involves colours at all; obviously a red-tint filter over everything affects how colours look on screen. 

It does include a button to switch this off temporarily for short periods if necessary, but for long-term, other solutions might need to be found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 16:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah my first thought went straight to Scotland for that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 12:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yours sounds more ambitious than most others, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 23:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to admit to not knowing what that is.

Am I really so out of touch already at 30? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 17:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres nothing suspiciously specific about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 17:00:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you like to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 16:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That Chris Brown thing still ticks me off to this day.

Men are accused of doing something and lose jobs, respect, get raked through the coals without any evidence being needed. 

Chris Brown actually physically beat up Rihanna and was allowed to continue his career, barely missing a step. Its disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 01:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gonna need some names... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-10 20:28:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The other side better just say lol jk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-10 18:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yoooo what the fuck!

...how have I never watched Yee-haw Game Ranch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-10 18:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ehhh... not claiming a cure. 

They specifically said themselves that theyve never experience depression so theyre just saying how they think theyd deal with it, coming from a place of clearly not understanding what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-10 10:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The bard knew ***exactly***. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 21:08:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bard knew *exactly* what he was getting into...

^^^or ^^^what ^^^would ^^^be ^^^getting ^^^into ^^^him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 12:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love playing cleric and then deciding who lives and dies. 

Literally every single time Ive played cleric and introduced my character, someone has made a sarcastic comment about me being an altar boy, or harmless churchgoer, or made fun of my god, or stereotypical Catholic-priest-based joke, both in-character and out.

And then they turn to me when their blood has spilled, and demand to be healed. And I smile a wry smile to myself and continue to swing my warhammer as if I havent heard a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 12:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I reckon you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 12:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah Ive seen this come up a few times and the distinction really needs to be made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 12:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy breakfasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-08 08:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 20:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember having to try and explain the concept to my players several times over before they got it. 

Battle Time is simulated. 

Each round is six seconds. Each player and creatures turn in that round is showing you what happens in those same six seconds, from that PC/creatures perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 19:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive always said the same thing; if I had dietary concerns that might actually kill me or cause me to be very seriously ill, I would never trust anyone but myself to prepare food for me. Dining out would most definitely be completely out of the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 19:42:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And what were all the other players doing while this went on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 19:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, dude, you dont have to answer the questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 14:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knew someone pulled it open again, had to rewatch to see who. 

Looks like there is some weird portal-based fuckery going on at that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 12:32:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it really suspicious if its laid out in full detail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 11:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guy in yellow is the reason the guy after him was not so lucky. Pulling the door shut screwed his aim up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 00:09:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/ThatHappened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 20:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt that the entire point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 20:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Final Fantasy VII boss theme. Again and again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 14:16:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id probably already be all mind blown out by the fact that I was on an alien planet to begin with. Anything I see beyond that is just not going to surprise me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 14:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, this could be said about literally anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 11:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, this one seems to capture something that the others dont. Must be the level of detail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 11:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty much all of the posts here are. I dont remember the last time I saw one that was actually suspicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 16:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My players did the same thing. Ignored clues, didnt dig deep enough to find any lore or background info and essentially brute-forced their way to finding out the solution and then killed the bad guy before asking questions or letting him talk. When I announced that the adventure was over and congratulated them, all of a sudden they had a ton of questions.

But who was the minstrel? Where did he get that magic book from? Why was the ambassadors door wide open? Where did the gnome guards disappear to? Why was he doing all of this? Where did he get the artefact from to begin with?

Sorry, boys and girls. Guess youll never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 11:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats suspicious about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 10:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right? I can do a dull job for a lot of money, or an interesting job for not a lot of money, but if my job is dull and I'm not being paid well for it then every single second of it is agonising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 10:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be remembering this when I'm struggling to do 1 pull up at the gym later on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 23:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I keep to myself and I just gently poke my keys through the gaps in my fingers. So that if I do have to hit one of them, *Ill fucking kill him.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 21:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah... once... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 14:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> openness to experience **92 out of 100**

agreeableness **50 out of 100**

conscientiousness **46 out of 100**

negative emotionality **46 out of 100**

extraversion **58 out of 100**

 #x200B;

Edit: Worth noting that I consistently test as ENTP these days on various different tests, but whenever I read traits I find myself disagreeing that that is what I am... Unless that's an ENTP thing in itself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 14:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [projects.fivethirtyeight.com/personality-quiz](https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/personality-quiz)

Link for the lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Helpful, Wholesome Adv- Oh </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 14:03:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 12:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If one guy calls you a horse, you punch him in the mouth. A second guy calls you a horse, you call him a jerk. But if a third guy calls you a horse, you need to think about getting a saddle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 12:37:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A couple months ago a friend of mine asked what music I'd been listening to recently.

"I was listening to Maroon 5 on the drive over, actually. Never really listened to them before but I quite like them."

"Oh. You mean the band that had one good album, and everything since Songs About Jane has been a few singles with nothing but shitty filler? The band that has the fake funk sound in some songs that's conspicuously absent in others and they go over the top with guest rappers? Nah, they're shit."

Everyone is more than entitled to hold whatever opinion they like about those things. But if someone hasn't asked, then keep them to yourself. And particularly if someone has just told you that they like and find joy in something, don't use that as an excuse to shit on them.

I like Maroon 5. I don't really care if you do or don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 12:24:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not one-upping unless you're trying to make your trip to X seem more important/better/cooler/more rewarding than their vacation that they're talking about. It's fine to talk about a vacation of your own, but don't shut them down talking about the one they just had that they're excited to talk about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 12:23:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like she was trying to invalidate /u/CelticRosa's pain by showing that she had it worse, ultimately showing that she was the one who was insecure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 12:21:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're relating, you're not one-upping. There's a subtle difference.

Relating: "I'm tired. Didn't get much sleep last night.""Yeah, I struggled to get to sleep last night too. Must be the humidity."

One-upping: "I'm tired. Didn't get much sleep last night.""Yeah? Well I haven't slept well for the past two nights because of reason XYZ."

If you relate, you're meeting them on common ground. If you're trying to one-up them, you're trying to show that your situation is much better/worse than theirs is and essentially trying to say that they have no right to complain/be proud of themselves and essentially invalidating whatever they just said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 12:15:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is absolutely true.

Doesn't make it any less toxic or irritating though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 10:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the actual reason, right here. I'm not even sure what Phineas and ferb is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 10:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And thats how we end up with Draconic sorcerers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 10:20:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well they seem to be happy and enjoying themselves playing it, while youre sat here grumbling. Whos the real loser? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 10:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/imafaketotalpieceofshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 09:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm. The website was full of all sorts of interesting background stuff before the movie came out, including a bio for Craig's Bond.

One disappointment I have so far with Craig's Bond is that his bio specifically mentioned scuba diving exercises/missions he'd successfully completed. And we have yet to see Craig dive (or even spend any extended time around water, really). I'd like to see that, along with some colder locales, in his final film. Enough with the blazing sun and temperate climates, already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 09:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like the problem there is that they're absolutely prepared to throw these characters into a thresher. They're not building "characters" that they actually care about, they're just building "a rogue", "a fighter", etc. This is a much harder problem to address, and one I'm still struggling with myself and one of my players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 23:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dismantle the infantiarchy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 23:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, definitely not anything to do with social media. Ive had this imaginary audience since I was a kid in the 90s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 21:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wu Tang Killa Beas! We are the swarm! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 16:40:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not a rule for the subreddit; I, personally, am asking you for context.

Because I'm interested to know how you came up with this ranking, in order to start a conversation. What is this list based on? Attractiveness? Character usefulness? Acting performance? Story arc?

I'm interested to know what made you select the order you have, rather than simply taking a list at face value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 16:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are you reading hostility when I asked a simple series of questions? Is it really so much to expect some context along with a post on a discussion board? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 16:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You given us a list, but you haven't given any criteria for the list. Why is Camille above Vesper in your opinion? What traits are they being judged on?

Is this a matter of opinion, or something objective? Do you consider this to be a definitive ranking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 16:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Based on...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 16:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fairly solid advice, to be fair. Whenever another DM talks to me about their players thinking they're invincible, rushing into combat constantly, not paying attention or not taking things seriously, my advice is always the same: kill one of their characters. Properly dead. 

Not through railroading or forced events, but just stop pulling your punches. Because you do. And they know you do. But as soon as someone actually dies, they'll sit up and take notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 15:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went to see The Force Awakens by myself a few days after it came out. Hands down, single best cinema experience Ive ever had where the goal was to actually watch the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-01 11:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ever thought that you and most of the other people on this subreddit are just creating your own misery by refusing to see the good in anything at all?

No, things like this won't cure your depression or your mental illness (not to mention, this one isn't even claiming to), but you self-perpetuate by purposely blocking out anything at all wholesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 19:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha no worries. I have a group of players who try to out-lawyer me when it comes to the rules every single week, especially when it comes to gaining advantage. Gotta stay on my toes!

EDIT: Just seen your edit- Yeah, that would work. I had forgotten that part of Sneak Attack! ...dont ever tell my players this happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 19:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. The disadvantage granted by the dodge action negates any and all sources of advantage.

If circumstances cause a roll to have both advantage and disadvantage, you are considered to have neither of them, and you roll one d20. This is true even if multiple circumstances impose disadvantage and only one grants advantage or vice versa. In such a situation, you have neither advantage or disadvantage (PHB 173). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 19:15:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ~~Advantage granted from Inspiration wouldnt cancel Disadvantage.~~

But that would just mean a roll without Advantage or Disadvantage. Which would be a flat roll and therefore not eligible for sneak attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 18:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not suspiciously specific when it was framed as a question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 18:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And what if I am seeing results but I havent stopped drinking heavily or eating entire pizzas every weekend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 17:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention the fact that theyre all relatively successful. If they were all struggling along on welfare and part-time jobs then maybe theyd have that kind of time, but were talking a head chef, an academic/professor and a couple of executives. Phoebe and Joey are the only ones who would really have any time to hang out. And even Joey would struggle once he gets his regular spot on Days Of Our Lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 16:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats a weak-ass BBEG to be killed off by a single sneak attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 13:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does No one really add anything to this meme at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 13:24:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretending to be surprised? My party are genuinely shocked when something happens that was explicitly mentioned in the previous session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 13:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plot twist: Ravisher125 *is* Spencer Perry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 12:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wha... why would your mind even go there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 10:51:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why? Is she claiming to cure depression or other mental illness? 

Without any context its really hard to judge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 02:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who is Dave Rubin? And what tour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 00:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could I get some context? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 00:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My first reaction to Pattinson was a "Fuck no", because I've only seen him in a couple of things (Twilight predominantly), but he just seems to be a mopey, wooden, uninteresting actor to watch. But I'm willing to give him the benefit of the doubt and not go into this expecting to hate it. I may well have, in my younger days, objected to the casting of Heath Ledger as The Joker, so...

With regards to the rest; fuck yes, I really hope we get a Detective Batman story for once. The Long Halloween remains my favourite ever Batman comic book, and I am always more gripped by the tales in which he's doing detective work than the ones where he's punching supervillains and demigods. Plus the Arkham games are incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 23:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually crave it when Im hungover. That point when Im past the worst of it and can start thinking about solid food again. 

Something about the juicy pineapple with the cheese and tomato just feels like exactly what my body needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 20:48:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will never not reblog this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 15:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :O

Everything that follows that declaration is a whirlwind of emotions. Cant help but tear up over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 13:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I taught myself how to do it because of the movie as well. People are always pretty impressed when they notice me doing it. 

Can confirm; getting it smoothly onto the pinky is hard work. 

Occasionally Ill get the smooth transition without thinking about it and Ill be so taken aback that Ill mess up the return or drop the ring altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 12:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nat 20? Good for you. Whats your modifier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 19:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He absolutely would have!

...this thought actually made me tear up slightly. Whats with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 10:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention that at this point, fantasy is pretty much built entirely on clich.

It's what you do with the clichs that makes all the difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 10:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I think that's why most threads get 0-2 comment, even though there's 60k subscribers. It's too hard to help most people here.

Bear in mind that many will subscribe hoping to find advice, but not being in any position to give it. It's kind of in the sub's nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 23:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What language is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 22:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Do you? Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 21:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about this is suspiciously specific? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 20:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think I just got caught in a siren song for a moment there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 20:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right? He said how to *avoid* student debt, not how to get out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 20:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You gotta really lean into it and make it super obvious.

*rowg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 09:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I overheard some people at the office talking the other day about TV shows and one woman mentioned disappointing endings, citing Lost as an example. The four others in the conversation hadnt seen it and asked how it ended. So she said Oh it just turned out they were dead the whole time. I was seething. 

Fuck you, Jenny. Learn to pay attention, you bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 07:15:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The dialogue isnt from Doctor Who? ...this goes deeper than I ever imagined </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 00:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive seen this meme with the number as 3, 4, 5, and now 6. What is the actual number in the original dialogue and am I being wooooshed somehow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 15:22:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you even read to the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 15:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All the Roger Moore ones. I just cant enjoy them for some reason. 

I await my crucifixion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 15:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think OP is more talking about memes that say things like, 

The rest of the party when Finbar the wizard asks the DM what colour robes the NPCs are wearing:

[Ah shit here we go again.] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 15:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you dont want your party to abandon the main quest line to follow up a side quest, dont offer them side quests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 14:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clearly a library book. 

And who said OP didnt just see the photo of the book online? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 14:43:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 22:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this a British-specific thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 19:39:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, when I make spaghetti bolognese I put dark chocolate and milk into the sauce so... yeah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 14:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dungeons   Dragons, man. I could filibuster an entire conversation for hours if I can turn the subject to D D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 13:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you stop trying to work out margins of error and just stick within the limit, youll be even more golden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 12:57:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best thing to do when you notice someone else trying to manoeuvre is to maintain speed and position. Theyre taking action based on your current circumstances. Hold off on the accelerating or moving until theyre clear of you. Then adjust for yourself once youre no longer in an interaction with another driver.

Youre good. The whole thing is a learning process, even after you get your licence. Youll get there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 03:24:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Voodoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 23:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its BMWs that dont. 

To be fair, most of the time if you see someone driving one of the German Big 3 (BMW, Audi, Mercedes), its a fairly safe bet that theyre going to do something twattish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 18:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is literally the plot of a Rick   Morty episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 11:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buy me a pint! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 11:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bitch. -James Bond, Skyfall 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 11:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Casino Royale, by an exceptionally large margin. I saw it three times in the cinema and then watched it almost every day for about a month (I know, Im weird) when I got it on DVD. In one of those days I actually watched it twice (first thing in the morning and then in the evening when Id had a drink or two)

Probably Quantum of Solace next because since I got it on DVD I usually double-feature them both. But its not a close race.

Then GoldenEye. It was, I believe, the first Bond film I ever saw. I played the heck out of the N64 game and then my stepdad realised I had never seen the film so we watched it. 

I ran through Brosnans films last year and I have to say I really miss the self-contained nature of each entry in the series. Im hoping we can get back to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 00:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah man.  Clifford

...may have to knock that wall through though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 15:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually ran a skill challenge in my 5e game very recently when the party were crossing a thick forest to escape some pursuers. Threw in a couple of random encounters and the threat of being vastly outnumbered in combat and potential capture if the challenge was failed.

My players all remarked afterwards at how it was a fresh change of pace (it felt like a kind of minigame) and kept them all engaged and feeling useful. They all hoped to see more skill challenges in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 15:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking forward to the Most Haunted Live overnight special about this place (do they even still make those?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 14:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was in university, I was on the committee of an academic society. We arranged a nice formal event (going out for dinner, champagne, a boat ride, and drinks after), and hired a photographer to come to the event so we had some photos to go on our page besides the usual drunken debauchery.

This guy showed up to this event wearing shorts and a dirty hoody. He was 22 years old and his excuse was, I dont own any smart clothes. I still dont understand how that happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 14:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big Bloody End Game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 10:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is where so many DMs go wrong. They have a plan. Their adventure is The party do this. And then they go here. And they do this. Their stories rely on specific interactions and decisions in order to play out. And the players will rarely do those things unless theyve been somewhat railroaded.

A good DM writes locations, people, and situations that could well play out or exist without the partys input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 00:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did I write this tweet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 00:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a DM, I abso-fucking-lutely despise that RR class feature!

The principle was bad enough but my Ranger seems to think it equals absolute clairvoyance and omnipotence. What exactly are they? What are they doing? Are they in a house or a camp or what? What are they thinking? And every single time I have to explain that he doesnt get any of this information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 00:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt it the case that the XGtE Ranger subclasses were based around the PHB Ranger only and were never intended to be used with the Revised Ranger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 23:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I learnt about this thanks to Matt Colvilles Running The Game series! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 20:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mate Star Trek has universal translators itd say it once in a fully understandable language smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 20:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But sometimes they dont respond well to the subtle support. 

So thats when you crank it up. Give it an extended Woo! At the top of your voice. Pump your fists in the air. Get a clap going. Draw everyone around you into the event to cheer on just how much this person is mastering the cash machine! Like the fucking absolute don they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 14:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 14:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Extravagant, flamboyant bard or nothing tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 18:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3-4 is the sweet spot. 

I know one guy who is always trying to set up games and he insists on having at least six players every time. He once started a WhatsApp group chat with 12 people in it, trying to get everyone to sign on for a long-term campaign he wanted to run. Funnily enough, that never took off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 18:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually get breathing anxiety and feel like I cant get any air into my lungs if I think about my breathing too much (its happening now just from watching the video) so I dont think this would work for me, despite being pretty good advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 18:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-17 19:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you have to be depressed about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 03:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice, a drawer that'll never be anything but a junk drawer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 02:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats my characters fetish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 00:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw the picture, I read Acrobatics check in the first line. I anticipated the ending. 

Needless to say, this meme did not go the way I expected it to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 00:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once accidentally TPKd a party in a one shot at the first fight. A brawl erupted in the tavern and I was rolling openly. Theyd made me promise beforehand not to go easy on them and not to fudge anything. None of them could seem to meet ACs (openly declared), and the other combatants just kept getting high rolls.

Somehow they all still thought I ran a fun session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 18:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/AwardSpeechEdits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 13:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or the fact that theyll no doubt decide to take up more TV time by also showing the Love Island US series over here as well as the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 13:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah it doesnt work like that. Its more like herpes; weve given it to someone else but we still have it. Forever. 

Also a much more relevant metaphor for Love Island. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 10:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still dont understand why theres a Tarantino Star Trek movie in the works. It just makes absolutely zero sense to me.

While Id be curious to see what Tarantino would do with a Bond film, I also know it probably wouldnt feel like a Bond film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 09:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Use another wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 03:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my case he always bases his character off a Marvel movie character rather than anime but yeah... same deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 03:11:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fantastic stories! And what a guy, to give your grandmother what she wanted despite it not being something he knew how to do! 

The world could use more people like your grandfather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 01:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wait until she starts getting frisky, tries to bite my lip and then I throw her to the ground and point a gun at her, saying No, no, no. No more foreplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 01:24:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We dont really go in for that sort of thing any more. 

Unless its the film that immediately proceeds the one where I said this, when well give you an exploding watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 00:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When Casino Royale came out, I and many others said that we loved a Bond that got beat up, cuts on his face, showing signs of the scrapes hes been through.

Crutches may be a bit too far though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 00:39:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why dont you go and find something to spray aerosol cheese onto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 00:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing. But try feeding that to most kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 00:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it when I come so hard my brain explodes into baked beans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 20:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always do. Exactly because I want my DMs to take them and run with them. Incorporate them into the world! Make me feel a part of it!

Only one who has ever even acknowledged that I had living parents in my backstory, had them murdered off-screen while I was out of town, and told me out of session that he just did it for character development.

The killer, by the way? Caught by the authorities and executed before I arrived back in town. He was just some guy who decided to break into their house and kill them. There was no thread to follow beyond that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 10:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP.  
OPs coworkers whose skid marks remain on the bowl.  
Me.  
My coworkers who dont flush.  
/u/MakinCakes.  
/u/MakinCakes coworkers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 10:42:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 22:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And here comes the Bard now to sell you a d4-based fruit salad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 22:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 30 years old and I still smash anything I do when Im wearing one of my Batman t-shirts. Even if its under a sweater or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 22:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a tattoo place. Edgy signs are commonplace.

When I got mine done I was told to lay down on my back. On the ceiling directly above the headrest was a printout that said Im not a fucking hairdresser. Keep your mouth shut and dont talk to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 22:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I deleted most of my older relatives from Facebook for this reason. I like to post status updates with a humorous self-deprecating tone about stupid or embarrassing things Ive done, and Id always get my great uncle (who I havent seen since I was probably 4 years old) commenting on it as if I was specifically talking to him. 

Lighten up and take it one day at a time, lad.

What is this, a confessional?

Cant help you with this one.

Ive just had an omelette for dinner and Im sitting down to watch some telly before bed.

Its weirdly wholesome in a way I guess, but I honestly just found it annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 20:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, well he didnt even want to have a Session Zero to start with. I and another one of the players finally got him to agree that it might be an idea if we had a proper introduction, considering he was going to be using a completely homebrewed setting. On the lead up to S0 he started saying things like So well talk for about half hour and then get started on the campaign? And I kept saying that a Session Zero shouldnt have any gameplay at all, we need to go away and think about all the information well be given. He was just too overeager to get started and it ended up killing the thing before it began.

Im now Forever DM for a group at my office. We play a couple times a week during lunch at the office, and then on the last weekend of every month well either grab a boardroom in the evening, or go to someones place and have a full-length session. Its been working out incredibly and Im so happy with how its all unfolding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 19:47:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This just reminded me of this fucking guy who DMed for us once. We met up on a weekday evening after work. Fought rush hour traffic at his insistence to get to a place to have a fully comprehensive Session Zero. Went into in-depth discussion on every aspect of the upcoming campaign. Made characters, created hooks into each others backstories. Ended up finishing the talk at like 2330. Exhausted but happy with the productive session. 

At this point the DM insists on role playing a little bit to get us to a starting point for the adventure. We figure its going to be like five minutes a piece maybe, so we agree. 

0100 in the fucking morning and he has us, having finally all met for the first time in an alley, jumped by a group of muggers and roll initiative. I stood up, said fuck this, Im out, which seemed to be the catalyst others were waiting for and we all ended up leaving despite the DMs insistence that If we just do this quick combat we can stop.

We never actually met up again for a Session One, and nobody apart from the DM made any attempts to have the campaign actually happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 03:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sugar cube is in the backrooms now. 

God speed, little sugar cube. God speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 03:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just imagining that he was sent down here to live amongst humanity in secret, but his supervisor keeps having to call him back upstairs to try and tell him to Just be a bit more like a human being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 03:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I too browse Reddit while Im on the toilet in order to improve the quality of my BMs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 02:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All those chain mails in my hotmail that I just deleted... it explains everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-12 21:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im so awkward I end up staring at the TV even if its off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-12 20:21:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PCs: \*finish one single easy combat encounter*

PCs: better take a short rest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-12 12:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not that I know of, but I hate the natural 20 = auto success house rule so I was rebelling against that.

I like the meme itself; I was trying to be funny but apparently, after lots of beers is not the best time to try that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-12 00:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nat 20 memes

*REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-12 00:46:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, without knowing what he actually says... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 09:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jumper cables...

Stay away from my nipples! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 01:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YOURE ALL BREATHTAKING! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 22:14:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my experience, Irish people from Ireland have some very choice words for anyone who ever uses the expression "part Irish". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 21:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Whether the yearly dues are too expensive etc"

Excuse me? You have to *pay for the privilege* of putting up with these assholes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 19:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldnt call them a comedy duo, no; they are characters in a comedy play, they arent a double act who perform different shows or as comedians.

Penn and Teller are magicians first and foremost and so I wouldnt consider them a comedy duo either. If I was in the mood for comedy I wouldnt ever think to myself Ill watch some Penn   Teller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 17:34:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> None of those are comedy duos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 16:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im usually in the same boat, dont worry.

I imagine you must be able to set a password instead of a thumb print but something tells me that if this dad is using a thumb print to unlock his phone, hed be using it for the parental locks as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 14:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mitchell and Webb!

...fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 12:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a person watching those movies, I saw the protagonists as obnoxious assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 12:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makes you wonder why they didnt call themselves Peele and Key </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 12:21:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How many times are we going to see this same GIF posted on this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 12:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When my Ranger found out that Arcane Archers exist, he didnt think it was fair that a Fighter is better with a bow than a Ranger and tried to argue with me that he should get all the things that Arcane Archers get as well as all his Ranger stuff. He essentially wanted two classes simultaneously without having to miss out on anything. I told him no, that he could multiclass if he liked but it would screw his progression as a Ranger. He said Fine, forget it then and stormed off in a huff.

In the next session during combat he made a hit and confidently announced I use my Arcane Shot to... I stopped him and asked him to explain what he meant. Then I asked to see his character sheet.

He had added all of the Arcane Archer class features and things alongside his Beastmaster Ranger stuff. He thought he could slip it by me unnoticed.

But this is the same guy who argued with me via text for three days straight because Rangers should always automatically go first in initiative order, because thats the point of a Ranger, that his attack bonus with a bow should be a lot higher as its unlikely Id miss, and also told me to tell other players what they should be doing because they werent accepting him as the self-appointed party leader. So Im not really surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 12:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, wouldnt the parental lock just be the thumb print anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 10:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A month or so ago, four days in a row, I received a call originating from Germany. All at different times, and yet every single one arrived as I was taking a morning dump at the office and was therefore unable to answer. Its like they knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 10:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello, FBI? I think I may have some information about one of your most wanted... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 01:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh dear. Thats not good.

I think I was expecting something darker. Thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 00:58:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally every homebrew from danddwiki </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 00:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let me try again; Im half a bottle of wine down, so I apologise if Im not being coherent.

I mean, the effective range **begins** 5 feet *away* from you. 

So the net does not have disadvantage when being thrown at a target two squares from you. Farther and its outside the 5 ft range, closer and its subject to the ranged attacks up close rule. So its still a stupid rule clash, but there is a range at which it can be used effectively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 00:46:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does range (5/15) not mean that you can throw the net up to two squares away? 

Like when a weapon has reach or a monster statblocks say an attack has reach 5ft it actually means they can attack two squares from them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 00:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Way too much lore built around Boblin these days. What about the nondescript townspeople going about their business in the marketplace? Id like to talk to every single one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 00:24:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pastiche. Or homage. 

As long as the rest of your story isnt also about a party of adventurers trying to take said object to a place to destroy it before a dark lord can reclaim it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 00:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What did the post say? Its been deleted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 23:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats probably like 90% of this sub these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 00:54:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bucky OHare!

Lets croak some Toads! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 23:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hah! Levels. 

Its all one level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 23:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If What your character would do fucks things up or ruins the game for the other players, *have them do something else*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 18:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its literally the only thing on the menu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 09:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just know Walkers would do that if they bottled water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 03:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are the hands of a game assassin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 02:59:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I turned 30 two weeks ago and I have less than no interest in having children. People have started on asking about it (which is a pain in the ass enough as I broke up with a girlfriend of 4 years back in October and havent had anyone since), and when I say Im not interested they give a little chuckle like I dont know what Im saying.

Coworkers too, telling stories about their kids or trying to show photos of things and I couldnt possibly care less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 02:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whomstd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 02:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That makes sense. I had an ex girlfriend years ago who never drank (nor anyone in her family) and she thought that it only took one drink to get you blind drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 02:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Teetotal or lightweight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 02:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Less likely to dial it by mistake. Or its to do with the sound the numbers make. If a number starts with a 9 its a clear signal to the operator. Like a command key, or pressing Ctrl before something.

I dont know, Ive had four beers and nothing to eat since lunch, I could be full of crap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 01:49:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats what bugs me about this whole Nobody: thing. So many of them follow up with X happening because of Y: which means that somebody or something said something to get a response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 01:29:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are some long legs for a mountain dwarf. Is this a result of the mobility feat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 01:21:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah... and Coruscant and Tatooine were probably a clue that this wasnt D D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 23:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fjester confirmed canon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 14:09:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone laughed when I announced that my character was going to be a bard. Jokes were made. Shade was thrown. Oh how useless hes going to be!

Not laughing now Ive been carrying this damn party for the best part of a year, are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 00:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This Nobody: shit has to stop. It doesnt even make sense most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 23:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. This description could just as equally apply to an undead creature. Nothing specifies otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 09:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its worse than that. Someone has lifted [this Tweet](https://twitter.com/mynameisntdave/status/610495898712416256?s=21), rewritten it very slightly, made it into a stand-alone image and then disseminated it without credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 01:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is good advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 01:05:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lack of options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 00:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Black-ass mama! White-ass daddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 00:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Went round to a new girlfriends house once. Sat watching telly with her and all her family when I leant forward and grabbed my coffee off the coffee table. Girlfriends mum said, Pass us the box while youre there. I stared at the table, with its two TV magazines, TV remote, other peoples coffee cups, stared at her, back at the table, back at her. What box?

They all started laughing and acting like I was the idiot, new girlfriend included. And they never dropped it for the entirety of the relationship, which Id like to say was later that evening when I went home... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-03 00:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I physically cant eat for a few hours after I wake up. Its always a pain if I have like a long trip ahead or something where I wont have a chance to eat until much later in the day. But Ive tried eating breakfast and Ill literally sit chewing a single bite of toast for like half an hour and struggle to swallow it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-03 00:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was literally looking at three of them in a zoo earlier today. They were very much not-extinct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-02 23:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well done you. Doesnt mean everybody else would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-02 01:05:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesnt sound anything like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-01 13:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dubs on the right, yeah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-01 03:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That wouldnt be called a hashtag anyway as it doesnt have a word or phrase after it. Its just a hash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-01 03:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember when I was working in TKMaxx about 12 years ago and they started charging for carrier bags. I remember every single customer kicking off when being told about it, as if I personally, the 18 year old cashier in a red polo shirt, had decided to institute this rule. Even going so far as to tell me in some cases that what I was doing was illegal! Among other ridiculous things; Those bags better be blank because Im not paying to advertise for you, Ive spent over a hundred pounds in here and now you expect me to give you 5p for a carrier bag?!, Well you better give me a carrier bag for free; how am I going to carry that out of here? On my head?

But my absolute favourite was the woman who slammed her hands on my counter, leant forward with a squint and told me I was trying to extort her. And not only that, the next time I come and shop here, Im going to bring my **own** bags! From home! Thatll show you! 

I shrugged and said, Well, yeah. And she snatched up her purchases and stormed off out. Clearly having entirely missed, but also somehow understood the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-01 02:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Reddit app recommended this sub to me the other day and I honestly dont know either why it thought Id want to subscribe, or why it exists.

But I am very uncomfortable with all of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-01 02:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Used to work in kitchens as a chef, man. 

Every goddamn pastry chef is a stoner.

Every other chef too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-01 01:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like I can tell which one is as extrovert and which one is an introvert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-01 00:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excessive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-30 11:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sandi Toksviig, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-30 11:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why was your mother filing her divorce papers in your class? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 22:44:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The section on resting says Adventurers can take short rest**s** in the midst of an adventuring day and **a** long rest to end the day.

Grammatically, this suggests that you can take multiple short rests during a day, but only one long rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 15:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5 Worst PC Classes

5. They  
4. All  
3. Have  
2. Merit  
1. Ranger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-24 11:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Five attacks, but dont they need to be against different targets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 17:38:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And even if it did, both of them would be redlined anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 17:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And keep it on your bedside table so you dont have to get up to turn your alarm off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 11:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asking Source doesnt automatically mean someone thinks something is porn. It just means they want to know what the thing originally came from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 11:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because you dont get caught doesnt mean its not illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 11:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But then youd literally be doing nothing, standing there with a prepared action just waiting for someone to cast a spell at you.

Plus if your action was prepared for When someone casts a spell, the effects of the spell will be resolved before your prepared action happens. So youd transform after the spell had already hit you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 11:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But in terms of the actual lore, Bards do get access to magic because of natural talent.

Not anyone can just pick up a guitar and start using it to cast spells by strumming a few barre chords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-21 00:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didnt even realise! Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 18:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a shitty showerthought. You can say that about literally anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-18 03:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So from what I can gather, theres a ton of shit stuck to the walls due to static electricity. Guess this is just a thing kids do now. There are pens, what looks like a calculator, other things.

What I *cant* work out, is exactly what about this is supposed to illustrate and therefore make it an appropriate post for /r/KidsAreFuckingStupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-18 02:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can of Diet Coke, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-18 02:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Standard array, fuckers. Fight me IRL RN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-18 02:05:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I get extra attack and I teabag him again. Then I spend a Ki point to use Flurry of Blows, and I teabag him twice more. Thats 1d10+5 bludgeoning damage from a magical attack each time my nutsack plops onto his face. Four times in a round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 10:08:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This entire comment thread is democracy manifest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 10:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a few different group chats on the go in different apps. Some of them I know why Im there, others I dont have a clue. One constant is true between all of them; they are all muted indefinitely. Occasionally Ill check in if only to get rid of the notification balloons, but I dont tend to leave them in case something useful comes up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 17:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Swear this has been posted at least once a day for the last ~~4~~ 69 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 17:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glad she circled it. Wouldn't have seen the thing she mentioned in the tweet otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 17:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally, on that scale, my line is drawn after fan art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 17:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to write fanfiction. I still do, but I used to, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 11:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They look like they might be valuable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 11:57:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MOAR LUNCHBOXES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 01:57:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is this a nice girl? This is just a crazy bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 01:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When Ive prepared scenarios and scenes and locations for my players as DM, and then they purposely start trying to break things or wander off for their own amusement, then no, I am not having fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 23:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 09:29:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We did actually go through a phase of both, at different times.

Ill let you decide which one applies to the story above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 00:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was playing a support role and kind of supervising a guy who was DMing (hes done so before but wasnt too confident so I was kinda spotting him while playing and hed occasionally turn to me for advice or something). There was a part where one of the party stormed off from the others down a forest path and one of the others said I shout after him, Hey, dont wander off alone!. 

DM turned to me and said What do they need to roll for that? I asked what he was making anyone roll for, and he said If he can shout loud enough to be heard. 

I did have to laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 00:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That d4 has no right being that sharp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 00:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was in school my friends and I went through this phase of doing this friendly clap on the cheek thing. It was a greeting, a congratulations, a condolence, any purpose, quick gentle double clap on the cheek.

My dumb ass thought itd be a good idea to do it to a teacher one day...

I was physically removed from the room, and my friends and I swiftly abandoned the cheek slap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 23:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You do you, man. 

Im saying that for me, that moment of unity in stillness that fell on the audience, for that one brief moment, we were all frozen by what we saw, amazed by the thing wed just seen, and then realising that I had actually forgotten to breathe for a moment. 

For me, that will always, always beat a clichd expulsion of feeling that you can see any time and any where for any number of reasons. I still tangibly feel that stillness now. If wed all cheered as an audience, I wouldnt have given it a second thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 23:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my viewing there was an audible gasp in unison when Mjolnir returned to Caps hand, and the quiet awe was way more appropriate and satisfying than anyone shouting Yeah! Woo! would ever have been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 22:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 22:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never said Sell your soul for instant reality-bending power, its a contract for continued fealty in exchange for slowly progressing power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 22:38:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus Christ, it was a fucking joke. Stop posting this shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 21:56:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Ive seen it so many times where its $100 and receiving/paying out or something similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 15:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 15:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All the more reason, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 15:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bad idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 20:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not clever at all. It's a complete non-sequitur unless "lasagna" means something else in itself, giving it a double meaning. Lasagna doesn't "move in silence".

Switch it out with any other word with a silent G and it doesn't lose its meaning. 

Real G's move in silence like gnomes (which arguably actually makes more sense)

Real G's move in silence like bologna

Real G's move in silence like design

Dude literally just thought of the first word he could where the G is silent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 19:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If thats fun to you, more power to you. Its not fun for me. 

If Im watching a movie for the first time, particularly something Ive been eagerly waiting for, I want to be able to watch it and immerse myself in it. I dont want to be in a cinema with a bunch of people hooting at a screen, I want to be transported away by the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 19:07:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So glad somebodys saying this. Ive seen tons of posts where people are saying and the crowd just went wild! People were yelling, standing up and saluting, whooping and Im just thinking that sounds like a fucking terrible experience and the exact way that a movie would be ruined for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 18:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> roll seduction

\*twitch* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 17:32:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better yet, find a middle ground. Just because youre not constantly cracking wise doesnt mean you have to be crying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 15:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id agree with her. Literally every guy Ive ever known who has been told by a girl that theyre funny has subsequently taken it to a complete extreme, to the point that you cant have a normal fucking conversation with them because everything has to be a goddamn punchline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 04:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not literal paperwork. Just more to keep track of.

I dont understand why people head into an epic fantasy RPG and their first thought is Hmm, I really need a pet when there are so many fantastic choices available in all the other classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 04:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do so many people get hung up on the animal companion thing? Ive never once gone into an RPG and wanted the extra paperwork that comes with have a pet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 01:21:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...motherfucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-10 17:46:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah I get you! Sorry, I misunderstood :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-10 17:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never used the word cure, nor claimed that it would cure.

It was more about the idea that people will piss on the possibility of something helping at all without even trying it for themselves first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-10 17:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right? Its like this is exactly the reason people are so often told not to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-10 17:30:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right? Sometimes its not even hard to take advice. People will get pissy if you suggest that they do something as simple as go outside for 10 minutes for some natural light and fresh air or a change of scenery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-10 13:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Coming soon? How long did it take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-10 11:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/AwardSpeechEdits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-10 04:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never saw you roll those stats. Reroll in front of everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 20:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did she underline hoe that doesnt care what you do and then caption it with 100% me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 13:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dandd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 12:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My god, I hate that rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 12:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah thats right. As DM you roll for them behind the screen and make a note. They shouldnt be aware of how good their insight reading was or how well theyve hidden themselves. Unless its a catastrophic failure, the characters should be convinced that theyve done the best they can in a situation.

Ive found the pages in the two guides I have;

Bottom left of page 15 in the 4e DMG. 

Top right of page 235 in the 5e DMG.

In both cases theyre on the pages about table rules. Definitely a handy read and certainly my preferred way of playing now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 01:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Key. Lighter. Penknife. Change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 01:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a save against the casters Seduction skill to take half damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 01:11:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You heard him, he said Hi there, thats tantamount to a threat in my book. He initiated combat first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 01:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I play the rule where things like this are rolled by the DM. Stealth checks, Insight, checking for traps, anything where the player knowing they got a low result will change the way they act is done by the DM behind the screen.

I know it was suggested in the PHB or DMG for 4e but I dont know if 5e suggests the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 00:53:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A rock is an improvised weapon. So 1d4. How would that kill Orcus even at a crit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-08 23:04:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does the weapon really need to be labelled with Attack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-08 15:42:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yeah, the kids will always beat her. 

That makes them winners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 21:12:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that sounds like something an ugly virgin would say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 21:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've yet to find a bot that responds to any level of "Go fuck yourself" by saying anything like "Ugly virgin hahahaha" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 16:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure. Im from the UK, and I know plenty of homeowners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 12:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was literally coming in here just to say is this loss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 12:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah!

I mean, like, unless they actually own it. Which is a thing that can happen. In which case, yeah it is their house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 13:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because this kind of thing doesnt happen often enough to warrant a subreddit dedicated to it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 12:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mastresses really says more about this whole thing than I ever could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 01:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *gril </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 01:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tried it. Chicken clawed my eye out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 01:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My players always jump to conclusions, and I kinda know how they think now so I engineer situations where I know what theyll assume and I can pull the rug out and subvert expectations.

Ranger on a solo mini adventure met some kids sleeping rough in the woods (they were between the ages of 4 and 7). They were near a campfire with a sleeping carriage and horses nearby. The kids told the ranger theyd run away from home and they had to sleep outside because Bud was bigger so he got the sleeping carriage and they only got a tent. Ranger immediately said, out of character, Im killing this pedo, proceeded to enter the sleeping carriage and planned to stab the adult through the sheets while he slept. 

At the last second, while raising his sword, he pulled back the cover. Turns out it was a 10 year old boy who had encouraged the younger kids to run away from home. I almost think he was disappointed that it turned into a social encounter and escorting the kids back to their village, but the other players contacted me after the session to say how much they loved that twist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 01:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My players actually did this when happily greeted to a tavern by a barman they deemed too friendly. 

He literally only smiled at them as they approached the bar and said, Welcome to the Silver Stag! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 23:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would definitely not have stuck my face against it if a kid was slapping the pins back down on the other side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 21:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well thats one side of the story, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 14:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well thats enough to keep you up at night... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 13:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/ThatHappened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 13:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maple keeps better time than I can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 11:35:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of Level 9 Rogue doesnt have a super high Stealth modifier that would render a natural 1 meaningless? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 11:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You dont need to type Umm.... Thats a verbal placeholder, and the only reason to include it in a written comment that you have time to think about, is if you want people to know youre being an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 11:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is such a nice change from the usual, Rolls a Natural 1. Trips over and breaks his nose on the ground </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tell me its not just my players... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 02:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 23:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont vax me bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 20:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a Warlock with the personality of Malcolm Tucker.

It is so so *so* much worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 19:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally called out, "No! Moonmoon!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 18:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/ForbiddenSnacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 18:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id rather you didnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 14:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then I pray you have a bard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 15:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems more like reassurance than a cure. Still a platitude, but its not claiming to cure depression via anagrams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 13:42:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How hard were you clenching? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 13:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, editing history. Joseph Stalin would be proud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 12:34:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has everyone in this sub lost the capacity to recognise a joke recently or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 01:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, fuck you, OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 01:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Getting a reflex save against a critical hit attack roll is some DM fiat bullshit of the highest order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 01:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention, you eat a donut by biting into it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 16:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> English as a Second Language (I think) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 15:10:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose the closest thing would be to default to whichever brewery owns the place ("Two beers." "Carlsberg alright?" "Sure." "Pints?") but I think in most places if you asked for "beer", you'd get a tired and sarcastic response of something along the lines of, "Got plenty of those, you'll have to be more specific." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 12:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 12:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now theres a reference I havent heard in a long, long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 11:59:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same, man. Im at work taking a quick five minute break while I wait for a project turnaround. I cant get...

...[Aluminium Christmas Trees](https://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/AluminumChristmasTrees)  are real? Huh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 11:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im just imagining trying that in a pub here in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 11:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a friend at college who would hang up without saying bye. Id always immediately call him back just to say Bye, Joe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 21:31:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was literally just thinking how I didnt seem to see posts from there any more. The fuck happened?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 21:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What an absolute boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 16:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a shitshow this sub is becoming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 04:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cue James Browns Living In America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 03:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Many years ago one of my friends in college here in the UK had a few of us round his house while we were ditching classes. He mentioned that he had an old pistol of his granddads upstairs and went off to get it. He brought it down and one of our friends asked if he could see it. 

Said friend immediately took the pistol, aimed it directly at the owners face from like a foot away and squeezed the trigger. Clicked empty. 

The owner slapped the shit out of him and snatched the gun away. Apparently the thing had been loaded, and literally one second before walking back into the living room, he had decided to unload it. He still had the bullets in his hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 03:41:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum used to do this back in the 90s. Soap in the mouth, either a bar or a few pumps of the hand wash. Taught me not to swear for about a half hour until the soap aftertaste disappeared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 03:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More planning time...  
  
  
  
  
...To make that player pay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 03:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of thread do you think youre commenting on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 03:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt that from Civil War? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 03:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do you guys live that this yoga pants are by and large a good thing? The kind of people I see wearing yoga pants around here are all the ones that I really wish wouldnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 02:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds awful. I cant stand people talking in the cinema. Ive come to see a film, usually one Ive been looking forward to for a while, not to listen to other people converse over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 02:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Arent there a few times where people come into the kitchen mid-service and then they just stand there shooting the shit in a relaxed way. Nobodys rushing around or shouting or anything but supposedly the restaurant is full of customers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 02:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh. Oh thats a shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 14:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may be thinking of Ellen, not Jo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 01:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chandler would be irritating as hell to know in real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-25 22:41:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do kids have to do with anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-25 13:21:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once had someone try to help me get over my social anxiety at potentially saying something stupid by saying something along the lines of, "In 10 years, nobody's going to remember. Do you remember things you said 10 years ago? Of course you don't."

Like, I'm gonna stop you there. Remembering stupid shit I said 10 years ago and feeling embarrassed about it is pretty much an hourly activity for me.

Actually made me feel a ton worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 10:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, this is literally how I always play it.

You got a Nat 1? I dont care; this is a skill check. What do you get when you add your modifier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 00:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A guy I know tried to convert 5e into Star Wars to run a one shot as his first ever attempt at DMing for some friends of his. I pointed out that this wasnt a smart idea, and that several Star Wars systems already exist. He didnt want to hear it. Went ahead poorly converting 5e into vaguely Star Wars related stuff.

I spoke to some of the people who played the adventure and its widely agreed that the whole thing was an absolute shambles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 16:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Baby owls? Unsettling? They couldn't possibly be! How could a few cute little  AGGHH!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 16:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alex Trebek?!

Whos gonna believe you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 16:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless its Cops and the X-Files. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 01:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the old Movie Maker program! My brother and I used to make so many crappy movies in this thing and then showcase them to one another </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 00:58:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who in their right mind dumps charisma? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 23:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rest in peace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 19:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm pretty sure this is what's usually called a "joke", specifically one of a self-deprecating persuasion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 02:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which crime? My answer will vary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 17:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Turning 30 in May. I still feel 18. 

Please make it stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 17:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which half? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 17:26:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. Sounds right to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 16:59:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I overheard a guy in my gym the other day saying to his friend that his eyesight has gotten real bad and hes been given a glasses prescription, but he hasnt filled it because hes starting on keto so his eyes will get better.

The fuck is wrong with these people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 12:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thatd be great, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 11:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Roc Hudson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 11:53:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit rolls downhill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 11:51:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats how one of my players suddenly decided his character came from a wealthy city we arrived in. And that his estate was still standing. And that his father had recently passed and left him a large inheritance in a safe which he was going to go back for. An inheritance that included much gold and a magic item or two. 

He dropped this revelation at the table mid-game as a This is what Im going to do right now, and I was too thrown off by his brazenness to improv a way to screw with him so I just said Nah, fuck that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 02:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have a page number? Ive never seen that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 00:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would That Guy invent a new race when he could just play as a Drow but argue that he shouldnt have sunlight sensitivity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 10:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cant handle the truth, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 10:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No no no. 

Leave the crocs *on*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 09:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This explains why every time I mention the hobby to someone who doesnt know what D D is they ask Oh so you like dress up as an elf and stuff? With a sneer.

No... its just a game that I play with friends. Theres no dressing up involved at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 09:38:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will not do a continuous thing for a one-off payment. If I received 20 million every year or every month or something then yeah sure. 

On the other hand you just said I had to agree to it, not actually do it. So sure, Id agree to do it and then probably not actually bother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 00:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cosplay stuff for D D? Do people actually do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-19 00:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My Fiestas dash looks like Yoshi: https://i.wheelsage.org/image/format/picture/picture-preview-large/f/ford/fiesta_zetec_s_red/ford_fiesta_zetec_s_red_8.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 15:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gods get a Critical Hit on anything higher than a 10.

Immunity to every damage type.

Frightful Presence with a DC 30 Wisdom save. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 14:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seen this so many times that I'll be genuinely surprised if anyone ever says anything about breastfeeding being natural, and it isn't in the form of this joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 14:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, Intelligence would be a better fit for that purpose... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 14:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure did!

Fuck you if you think that a God's statblock is going to be comparable to, or even follow the same rules as anything else, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 13:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was so very pleasantly surprised by that film. I wasn't expecting it to be anything other than tolerable when I put it on out of curiosity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 13:46:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which is exactly why he shouldn't be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 22:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Frank Catsle: The Pawnisher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 15:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What Ive found is that the technical stuff is the easiest. There are rules in place for everything. Learn them, learn why they work the way they do, and dont homebrew anything mechanical. The synergy is not going to have gone through the hundreds of thousands of hours of play testing that the existing system has, so dont mess with it. 

Role playing on the fly with a group of people staring at you, and trying to keep plots straight in your head, and on track at the table, while fielding questions from the players, trying to remember who knows what already and whats new, is what I find the hardest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 13:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right?

"No you didn't. You aimed for centre-mass, because you're not an idiot." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 11:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do I do it?

Every single day is a How do I do it day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 11:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I said I aimed for its head.

Fucking Ranger. Every single turn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 01:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well this is a new low </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 20:42:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He hasnt. He has two shoes and two slippers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 20:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play it again for me like 17 times Sam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 15:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This meme brought to you by Sexy Bard Gang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 22:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clearly a troll question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 14:50:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So many people in this thread saying things about killing the clone yet OP never once mentioned killing anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 14:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish my players in one of my games would do that. If Im not narrating an obvious thing for them to interact with at that moment, they tend to sit there dumbstruck and waiting for me to place the next thing to solve in front of them. 

Their characters have literally never spoken to each other in six months of play time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 14:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spoiler tag and then includes the phrase swan song in the title. Bold move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 14:34:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine drinking hot chocolate through a really long donut like a straw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 14:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats up YouTube? Its ya boi here today to talk to you about how many holes in a straw, but first, to make sure you stay up to date with all of our delicious content make sure you like and subscribe down below so you dont miss out. You can also follow me on every social media in existence, which Ill list and spell out individually, so you can be sure youre always in the loop about my upcoming videos. Before we begin today Id like to thank our sponsors that have nothing to do with our content, probably something to do with food and probably something to do with books, with an individual two minute read each. OK, so now onto the content, to understand how many holes in a straw, first I have to tell you a personal story about when I was a little kid and we went on a family vacation where a thing happened that takes forever to explain but for some reason, I think is tangentially linked to straws, so it justifies me putting it here. If I drag this story out just long enough then Ill reach the minimum required length where YouTube will let me monetise the video, so Im just going to keep going until we get there. So now thats that, we can actually talk about straws. They have a hole on one end and a hole on the other but as theyre connected its actually whats called a through hole. So its one. OK thanks YouTube and once again dont forget to like and subscribe. Leave your messages down below in the comment section if you have any questions at all about straws or holes in things. Let me know what subject youd like to see me tackle in a video next so I can ignore it but the comment numbers inflate on the video and increases the exposure and engagement levels on YouTube analytics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 14:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is a bard *not*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 14:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 32 months in prison and a $1.4 million fine?

After further costing the taxpayer with his prison stay, doesnt he just about break even at that rate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 12:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why I unsubscribed from subreddits about social anxiety and depression. You'd get me\_irl type memes with hundreds of upvotes and a stream of comments to the effect of "This is me".

If anyone even suggested that there are ways to mitigate and overcome issues, they'd be downvoted to the ground and swarmed upon by people giving them shit. 

I joined because I thought that with a community of likeminded people, we might be able to work together to come to some solutions, and there'd be some decent advice.

But nobody wanted to get better. They wanted to just wallow and pat each other on the back about how hard they had it. Sometimes this subreddit seems to be leaning in a similar direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 22:24:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 22:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, if youd said any of this in a way that implied it was concern or similar, Id probably be more responsive. 

As it is, its phrased like youre being judgemental and condescending. So feel free to take your own undamaged liver elsewhere and have a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 22:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does one enjoy a vital organ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 22:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By working jobs we hate that take up all of our time so we really need a drink when were done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 21:38:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But at least you found a way to feel a smug sense of superiority despite being so busy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 21:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, we make the most of it. Because that one week a year is as good as it gets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 16:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I met an American student before for a date. I drank a little too much but remained pretty coherent while she nursed her way through only a couple of drinks. She described us as an entire nation of high-functioning alcoholics. 

I wear that badge with pride, while I drink my requisite 3 double whiskies every night after work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 16:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you need someone to bounce some stuff off, feel free to PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 16:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a South Park character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 16:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you OK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 22:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you mean dissatisfied? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 10:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found quite early on that one of my players, as a hobby, pretty much just reads D D sourcebooks. Even when he's not playing. So he's read Curse of Strahd, Storm King's Thunder, etc. and knows every twist and turn even though he's never played either of those two modules.

And he may have a slightly eidetic memory, as every time a monster was introduced early on he'd say things to the other players like "They're Kobolds, they've only got 2d6-2 HP and a 12 AC so they shouldn't be too much of a problem" so I had to be sure he wouldn't know everything about *my* monsters.

I've found the best way to do it is to add in a little something when a monster gets low, kind of harking back to the "Bloodied" state from 4e: so when the party have a troll surrounded and whittle it down, to suddenly find themselves standing in a poison cloud. Or when my subsequent Kobolds gained a multiattack out of desperation if their HP got threateningly low or they dropped to 0 (also gave them that Relentless Endurance trait, reflavoured as a scrappy desperation/survival instinct).

I'll let PCs make Arcana/Nature rolls, etc, and I'll give them clues to things if they ask, but for the most part they usually end up surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 02:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive made some good friends recently and Ill be turning 30 soon. Theyre determined to give me a good birthday, as I said Ive literally never had a decent one. But when my friend who is organising asks what Id like to do I have no idea what people even do on their birthdays because its always pretty much just been another day to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> People who enjoy your birthdays, what do you even do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 02:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 02:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alexa, play Despacito </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 02:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pull the trigger and the nightmare stops!   
Pull the trigger and the nightmare stops!   
Pull the trigger and the nightmare stops!   
Forever you will, forever you will learn!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 02:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buttered like half a loaf of bread. Sat on my armchair with a stack of buttered bread to me left and a bottle of malt vinegar to my right. Dashed each slice with vinegar for flavour and ate the whole thing. 

This was around 0500 and I had just come home from a 12-hour drinking session to find the cupboards almost bare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 01:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Weekenders had various outfits. Theyd wear the same outfits in different episodes but they wouldnt always be wearing exactly the same clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 01:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a troll. Sounds like a troll. Smells like a troll. 

But in my game they have a climb speed, and release a poison fog cloud when their HP gets low. They also require cold damage to stop their regeneration, rather than the standard acid or fire.

Pretty basic changes like that. To keep people on their toes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 01:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ruoge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 01:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dibs on the next one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 00:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lair action. Bam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 00:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont reskin. I do the opposite. They see a troll, but screw my metagameyist player if he thinks he knows what a troll is in my game world... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 20:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hence the Tinder buttons down the bottom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-08 15:59:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But isnt that because a tailor is a maker of mens suits and the female equivalent would be a seamstress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-08 15:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing wrong with being a bard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-07 15:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I imagine it would have been played differently. More stoic than devastated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 19:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shadow Boxing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 21:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You misspelled ranger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 09:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was DMing the other day and had to cobble together an impromptu NPC when the players went to speak to someone I hadnt planned for. I decided to give him an Irish accent. Only it kept slipping into something unreal, but I went with it because it was comfortable. 

One of the players asked why his accent kept falling out of being Irish. I pointed out that theres no Ireland in this fantasy realm, so any similarities are purely coincidental, and any differences are characteristics of this accent in this world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 01:16:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My Gnomes are Australian/Kiwi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 00:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was one. 17 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 00:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does he call someone something if he can only communicate by controlling dice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 00:35:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody has done it because an attack cant deal negative damage. It bottoms out at 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 00:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive always found food to be a distraction at the D D table. I always groan when one of my players shows up carrying food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 20:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, if you insist. Youll be hearing from my attorney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 19:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The title of the original post is Only in New Zealand. 

The person commenting in the video has a New Zealand accent. 

What makes you think its a British person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 20:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A real human bean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 14:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should have cut the crust off one single edge as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 10:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 02:06:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> College of Gains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 01:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember this game coming out and finding it so random that there was just this one individual Bond game coming out based on just one of the old films. I was trying to figure out what it meant and (obviously) getting nowhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 01:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just like in Bobs Burgers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 00:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But can they talk to girls IRL? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 18:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine defaults to 01 01 1900. No scrolling involved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 17:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But then it wouldnt be inordinate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 15:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Somebody told me once that theyd read something to the effect that an inordinately large number of Steam users were over 100 years old going by the birthdates given on their client. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 15:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most people on Steam were born on 1st of January 1900. Myself included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 13:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I think Fighters and Barbarians offer the greatest versatility and possibility for creating the most interesting *characters*. If you're mechanically basic, you have enough room to be flavourfully exceptional.

...unfortunately every barbarian is a low INT, alcoholic, pseudoviking with anger issues, and every fighter is a "guy who hits things with a stick". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 13:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ranger: "i swear I'm a unique class"

This every fucking time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 13:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With a modifier of 0? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 13:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because the web series that the still for the meme comes from is a BBC3 production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 13:24:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I meant roll a Nat 20 on a D6." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 13:17:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ichabod Crane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 23:37:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its like its written for someone that wants to play a monk but always wants to take some great parts of other classes instead of multiclassing. 

There are so many official archetypes/subclasses that could fit this description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 14:46:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I genuinely can't have an actual conversation with someone until after my first meal of the day. Its like my brain just wont get into gear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 10:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adds value to picking money of corpses I guess, otherwise why pick money off corpses ./

Oh yeah, absolutely. My D D players are like magpies, they'll go out of their way to grab a single gold piece even if it means they're waylaid in the long run. They go on about treasure and loot all the time, so I was completely shocked that when I essentially said "This city is literally here to serve whatever purpose you want, so if you tell me what you want to buy, that shop will exist here", and I was met with silence. Couldn't think of any suggestions to make either, so they just set off again.

Not entirely sure why they're stockpiling gold if they don't have anything they actually want to buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 10:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 007 in New York </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 10:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Property of a Lady is my favourite of these. 

The Hildebrand Rarity sounds a bit too Sherlock Holmes. 

Risico just doesnt strike me as a Bond movie title. (I also dont think that Spectre was a good title.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 10:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do people shop for? I had my players in a city the other day and told them if they wanted to buy anything now was the time, none of them could think of anything to buy except for restocking basics and we were done in five minutes tops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 10:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 18:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. You are correct that they are different things. 

However, if youd like to re-read my post theres a part where I say in the UK we call ketchup tomato sauce. Ask a Brit for some tomato sauce and we will hand you a bottle of ketchup.

So yes, that is exactly what it means on this menu from a likely UK-based restaurant. Your pedantry doesnt change that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 18:05:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It shall be done! :) thanks for the great ideas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 17:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im running a sci-fi TRPG campaign right now, and theres a prison space station coming up in the crews very near future. The cells are going to be like this now. How would you like to be credited? I could name an NPC after/for you if you like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 16:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have wedges too. Because historically we like to be difficult. Chips are somewhere in between the two  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 15:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah essentially thats it. Fries tend to be thin (and often crispier) than chips, which tend to be thicker cut, sometimes stumpy in comparison, and fluffier on the inside. Thats how Id characterise the difference anyway. But when looking at a menu there is a difference if something is served with chips as opposed to with fries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 15:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, kind of... we still have fries. Which are different to chips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 14:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure how it is in your office, but where I work, people dont carry their phones around with them all day while at work. YMMV, obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 13:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats the beauty, and the real life hack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 11:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The implication by going to bed early is exactly that you wont be sleeping in. 

Had a guy in our dorm at uni who would go to bed early, and sleep in late. He was definitely called lazy every time he said he was going to bed early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 11:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right. But in this context, it does mean ketchup. Because here in the UK we call ketchup tomato sauce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 11:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did people actually enjoy Carte Blanche? I genuinely thought it was absolutely dreadful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 11:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, it kind of makes sense but doesnt really stand up to scrutiny. 

Youre talking with someone about something you need to make a note of, dont have anything to write on, so you make a note on your hand. Then you photocopy it (one button press, probably several photocopiers throughout the office) instead of writing it out again, so you can wash your hand and dont walk around all day with ink on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 10:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you people do this?

Arent there specific places you can go to discuss this instead of hamfistedly trying to cram references into every single other thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 10:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I swear that every time I see this meme the paddle gets a little bigger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 10:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That very last one is a real stretch, but the rest of this is pretty spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 10:28:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Easier mnemonic; Saruman looks like a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 03:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First and surname both begin with A. I usually went first for pretty much everything.

I have social anxiety. Being first is not always a benefit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 03:31:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But every time they say bee, Microsoft Sam recites every known digit of pi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 03:26:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the book, Hammond had a miniature elephant (I believe) in a cage that he would take to investor meetings as a proof of what they could do with genetic engineering. That whole possibility was already right there in the source material and they did nothing. Nothing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 00:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well now I can't stop imagining it and I'm sad it won't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 11:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll stop complaining when the idea that they're auto-successes stops becoming so widespread that it pervades any group I play in, to the extent that players will full-on argue with a DM who rules a 20 as anything other than a complete reality-bending success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 11:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And if someone just wants to take Magic Initiate and have a 1d10 cantrip without having to sell their soul *or* study for years to get it, then that's their choice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 08:45:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Claim its some kind of flash mob/prank and theyre looking to get everybody in on it kind of thing?

I find it hard to believe that not one single person in a park full of 200 people is just some guy on his lunch break enjoying being away from the office.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 08:38:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just dont mention it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 08:37:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hold my hymen, Im going in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 01:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive been looking for an alternative to cockney for a half-orc character Im about to start playing... think I might have just found some potential. Hes gonna end up sounding like Will Hunting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 01:06:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guilty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 00:18:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too far off. I get Eldritch Blast *now*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 19:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 19:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a good week or so it was Debbie Harry. Thisll pass and then itll be someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-19 21:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, youre a chef? You must like cooking!

Well, I *did*... once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 22:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats an apron, you plum. You cant see what hes wearing in his lower half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 02:07:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Critical failures arent a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 02:03:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best execution of this meme that Ive seen. You can have inspiration for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 01:50:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally, someone speaking sense! It bugs me that the second Lovecraft is mentioned on this site, you know for a fact someone is going to smash in through the window just to shout, He was racist ya know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 01:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that always got me kicked out of speed dating but if a *cat* does it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 23:09:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Customer perspective:

When the restaurant says it opens at 12:00 but its 11:50 and the doors are still closed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 23:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or youre so hungover you cant drink water without feeling like youre going to hurl, but youre still standing over a hot range so youre convinced youre going to die on that shift...

...that may just be me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 19:18:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Humans get a +1 to everything (or an extra two points and a feat) because PC humans, the ones that become adventurers, are already supposed to be a bit more special than average.

But ultimately I dont think they ever intended us to look at the system in this much detail! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 18:09:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As opposed to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 18:06:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its just average of all races. 

Thats why races get stat increases. To align with the average stats of those races. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 18:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All work will stop, and the ground will relieve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 14:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair, he *did* stop his heartbeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 05:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah! Im an ancient African woman. What about *me*?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 04:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well.

At least I already know what my nightmares are going to be about tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 04:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least youre not suffering any more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 03:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As you enter the city gates you... you see the Crownsguard... the- the- guys, the Crownsguard... no? OK. Thats fine. We can have a conversation about Marvel movies if you like. Thats not a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 03:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I use a quivering palm on myself it just creates awkward situations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 05:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I gotta do it, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 04:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was convinced this was a meme for like five minutes and I was staring at it trying to get the satirical point being made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 04:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is some kind of double layered meta that I dont even wanna fuck with... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 13:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One push-up. 

One. 

Its not healthy to do one single push-up every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 02:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But how would they know the plot isn't interesting if they don't follow it?

The issue is that the *hooks* aren't interesting enough to draw them in.

Just for the sake of argument: I actually have the opposite problem. My players are pretty much laser-guided onto the main plotline of the campaign. They pass up any opportunity for side-quests presented to them, heading straight for the end goal. It's really weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 21:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've got it, dude. As long as you don't go and make wild, baseless assumptions like this one, based on very little, with no logic behind them at all, guarantee you're golden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 19:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ours did it in a *very specifically* thatched roof, wooden tavern. Then, when the whole place caught fire and went to shit, he whined at the DM saying that it shouldnt have happened and it wasnt his fault the DM decided to do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 18:35:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was one of my favourite really subtle moments from Taliesins understated comedic talent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 15:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the only word they'd ever have to learn is "Smite"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 15:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm making my own Iron Throne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 13:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know that was the case in Pathfinder. I know he owns the starter set, but he said that whenever he played it with anyone they'd "Just make up their own rules". So it's still hit or miss whether he actually knew of the Pathfinder rule.

I just think he's conflating a Critical Hit/Success on a Death Save, with any other roll that requires a D20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 13:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a one shot I was once playing as a character with 9 INT. had the other players and even the DM at different times point out that You wouldnt be smart enough to think of that, your character is basically retarded.

One point below average is retarded?

Funnily enough, the 8 STR wizard didnt like when I pointed out that his character probably wouldnt even be able to open a door by that logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 13:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously though. I hate those fuckers who take like four sets of dumbbells, grab a bench and just seem to build up a hoard of equipment nobody else can use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 12:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Because it's a title code name. NOT an actual singular person. 

But it's not. And it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 12:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A Gordon Ramsay show that's *actually about the food* would be fucking fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 10:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a shitty subreddit.

"Someone named a brand instead of using a verbose generic descriptor, must be a shill!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 23:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dunno, I think its just that implying a certain day is a day for something works (especially if a discount is included). 

A bar in my University town used to do Vodka Tuesdays and would always be packed out on Tuesday nights. Another did Gin Thursdays, and it was the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 23:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 23:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe the Uber driver used to work for Lyft but switched over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 23:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, a lot of people house rule it that way, which is fine. But its not the way the rules lay it out, and its not the way I play. I dont agree with the concept. Never have. 

This campaign has been going on for well over a year and the guy still does it (as recently as yesterday). Even before this, wed played together many times before so he knows how I feel about it. Weve even had discussions about it away from the table. 

Its not the thinking you can crit skill checks that bugs me, its the smug expression, the nonchalant recline and declaring it like he thinks, this time, *this time*, Im going to say it, and its going to override the DMs decision.

Hes the same kind of player who will declare Im rolling Persuasion instead of saying what his character does or says, roll without being asked, and interrupt narrative to call out the result of his dice rolls for things I didnt even know he wanted to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 20:34:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure there was a joke in an early episode of Archer where someone admonishes him about constantly introducing himself as Sterling Archer, the worlds greatest spy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 20:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have this player who, when rolling a Natural 20 on a skill check, will declare Nat 20 and then sit back in his seat with his arms folded and this smug fucking look on his face. Every time, Im like Good for you. Plus what? To which he looks incredulous and repeats that its a Natural 20. 

Every. Single. Time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 20:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally the only reason I ever went to that dumpster fire of a website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 20:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How dare they bring me a check, demanding payment for my succulent meal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 18:33:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its high noon... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 16:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the warning. Im always right on top of the new episodes as soon as they release, but its good to let others know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 13:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fastest subscribe ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 21:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seducing people as a 12CHA fighter.

You heard me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 20:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If someone gets out of the car and runs inside then therell be no weight on the seat for the car to register as a passenger without a seatbelt on. 

I have a 2015 Ford Fiesta that makes a noise when someone isnt wearing their seatbelt. But it only does it for seats with someone sitting in them, and only when youre moving at over like 10mph or something.

Its a non-issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 18:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe wear your seatbelt? Then it becomes a non-issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 18:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You got a raw deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 13:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cant wait til he gets to Hogwarts and meets potions master Professor Slughead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 10:59:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This seems to presuppose that DMs have memorised every player's modifiers for every skill in order to be able to respond in that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 10:21:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I played a character like that, years ago. Tried to talk my way out of every combat and often succeeded. 

Unfortunately between the DM who ruled if you didnt fight then you dont get XP and the player who was literally only interested in combat, and would interrupt me trying to talk the situation down if he thought we could win the fight, it ended up not really being a good fit for that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 01:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But put it in a bowl of rice first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 23:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Micro cupcakes. Theyre like a mini version of a mini cupcake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 23:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have one player whose every character so far has spoken with a terrible fake Cockney accent with a gruff delivery. Like a bad impression of Phil Mitchell. Then he tries to throw his weight around and intimidate NPCs and other PCs alike... even when hes not playing a particularly intimidating character.

It gets really tiresome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 23:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any news at all... please, for the love of God... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 21:31:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Genuine quote from a player in one of my games once:

"Do there *have to be* consequences for every single thing we do? That's not really the kind of game I want to play."

EDIT: Im starting to get some replies, and while I can understand the points being made, allow me to add some context.

This character was a Dragonborn (so rare in the custom setting that in a year of play, hes still the only one we have ever seen), who kicked open the door to a store (because its funny), demanded to know what kind of discount he was going to get, when denied a discount on the basis of nothing, tried (failed the roll miserably) to intimidate the shopkeeper, then, in plain view, started helping himself to items (whats he going to do to stop me?). All this in broad daylight, in the Empires capital city, where Crownsguard patrols had already been established as so commonplace so as to seem oppressive. This Dragonborn, pockets full, then casually strolled out of the shop, and wandered across the road into a tavern where he began to behave in a similarly conspicuous way. A short time later, a group of Crownsguard, having spoken with the shopkeeper, found him being an asshole in the tavern. He then, out of character, wanted to know why he was being picked on.

I wish this were hyperbole, I really do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 20:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mildly? No no no... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 12:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Going by what little we can see of the floor... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 11:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> +/u/User\_Simulator u/subject4129 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 13:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OK, good to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 13:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im sure that using any martial art against a police officer is going to go well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 12:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or somebody mixed up Trojans and Spartans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 11:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once had a session where practically every roll was a 9 or below. 

The few that werent, were natural 20s. 

It was an odd session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 04:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but then they roll a 20 and expect to be able to achieve it. Never let them roll if theres no chance at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 03:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come on maaaaaan, dont just say vicious mockery, I need to *feel* it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 11:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He still looks pretty sad. 

Thats not my ball. I want *my* ball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 11:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats a 20... plus six.

*...fuck* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 11:31:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its... ^its ^just ^a ^chair. ^^Its ^^a ^^^chair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 11:30:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats a pretty awesome bit of organic world building. I quite like it as a quirk for a race. May have to steal that one. 

Now have to think of an ass-pull reason, for when my players inevitably ask me (table talk, not in-character), Y tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 11:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bendy Scrooge Crumpet Thatch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 11:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A big *chair*?

**The** chair?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 03:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP if this is your house what time can I come over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 03:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We split a six pack when we wanna get really crunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 02:49:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The blurring around the edges really makes this a surrealistic nightmare of a photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 02:48:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that really what happens in that scene? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 02:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont tell me what not to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 01:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How old is he? Maybe its time to start weaning him off the dice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 18:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 16:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You motherfucker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else feel this way? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 21:47:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Taliesins immortality confirmed by autocorrect Twitter game </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 20:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First time DMs be like </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 11:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Call it morbid curiosity </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 12:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EDIT: I think I did it wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A girl put her number in my phone and I don't really know what to do about it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-03 12:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else hear music on the edge of sleep? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-26 08:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TL;DR I hear music when Im drifting off, Id like to capture it somehow, not sure how I can do that. 

I wasnt really sure where else to post this. But I think it could make a good conversation. 

Does anyone else hear music in the hypnagogic state? Ive started noticing it more, recently. And it always seems to be original music as well (grain of salt, thinking about how the subconscious mind works). 

Thing is, I know that a lot of greats swore by inducing the hypnagogic state in order to fuel creativity (I think Dali and Einstein are said to have done it). Id like to start capturing these songs but Im not sure how. There are a few problems. 

While I play guitar (and piano/drums to a far lesser extent) and learned how to read and write musical notation in secondary school, I dont know, remember enough to write these things down in any useful way (plus I cant recognise notes just by hearing them). 

Secondly, these hallucinations are pretty fleeting. As soon as I move they seem to disappear fairly quickly and its a struggle to hold onto them. You know what its like trying to remember a dream as it fades away from memory?

Id voice record myself humming/singing the melodies but there are a couple of problems with that; I dont think Im a competent enough singer to get the right notes and cadence. And secondly, if I start making noise Im pretty sure it will wake up my girlfriend. 

All of this of course assumes that I am actually hearing a tune of some kind rather than my brain just saying You are now hearing a pulsing club beat with just a hint of melancholy. Either way I think it would be interesting to explore. 

Thanks for sticking with me so far. Im interested to hear any thoughts/experiences with similar, or suggestions. Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [UK] Im about to move into a new building with concierge service. What does that mean, and what would I use it for? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-15 14:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>