<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8857</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 19:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Il tait une fois la Vie" (which is on Netflix now).

I used to watch it instead of studying for bio class when I was still in school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 18:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *A wild belgian appears* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 18:05:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for being genuinely nice and joyful people. We make fun of you but we secretly like you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 14:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have french friends who say it. Depends on the region maybe but you would normally say it because it precedes a starting vowel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 23:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But the hijab doesn't even cover the face. I think it's more about France wanting to remain a "lac" state where there must not be any visible religious signs (although they haven't talked about banning headscarfs for nuns) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 23:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Parliament is the almighty one in your country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 23:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll admit that your bread is the best one, though I hate to compliment the french </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 23:03:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard that our daily TV news programmes are way longer than what's normal elsewhere, they last for more than an hour typically. Don't know how true that is though.

The news in belgium typically lasts 30-40 minutes. I guess you really like to be thorough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 23:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wtf ? Those are real cities ? And I thought americans didn't like recycling... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 20:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say Middle Ages and before is pretty old. Usually the old city walls get a "can't believe this shit is still here" from me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 15:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it was actually about std/i's.

And it was belgian mussels, how dare you ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 12:50:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmmm... I don't think french is that tricky, except maybe for pronunciation, but there's worse.

I think the trickiest thing could be "les liaisons". It's only used when speaking but basically in some cases, the last letter of a word is pronounced in a sentence when it wouldn't be if you just said the word on its own. Ex: j'ai beaucoup aim (say the p) vs. il a beaucoup d'amis (don't say the p).

It's usually the last letter of a word if it comes right before a word that starts with a vowel. It's not that complicated but quite hard to do naturally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 09:48:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's some pricey potato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 02:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm usually very blunt about it and just ask them to try and make less noise while eating. From experience, they'll either get mad or just shrug and keep doing what they were doing, the noisy little bastards.

You either have to live with it, or invest in noise-cancelling headphones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 01:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same for me. I don't usually tell people about it because I feel like an asshole but I have definitely stopped hanging out with people around eating times because it drives me insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 01:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she complimented my netherlands

Genuinely thought you talked dirty in Dutch and she liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 01:01:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never tried it. To be fair I haven't even tried most sauces, I just tend to pick the ones I like already. I don't like to live life dangerously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 00:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You monsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 22:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I was going to say that is a very dramatic way to say bye to the bus driver hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 18:44:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blind dude loves dressing up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 18:37:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it was the balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 18:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the glaswegian accent. The less I understand, the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 17:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And therefore all other mayonnaise-based sauces. Belgium is the empire of all sauces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 17:43:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had that sauce and it is good. I'm not scottish therefore my opinion is unbiased. Edinburgh, I'm here to save your tarnished reputation !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 17:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For Charleroi the bad rep comes from being poor, dirty and ugly. I know that in the last years they've really made an effort to try and turn their reputation around by making the city nicer. And it's worked, I think a lot more people are willing to give it a chance nowadays. In that case at least, the bad really did come from reputation alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 22:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. Never used octante. Only ever quatre-vingt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 18:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries. Can be confusing. Hope you found what you were looking for and that you make it there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 14:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That Adam Smith invisible hand is good for more than just one thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 14:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep they actually put out a suicide hotline for Take That fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 11:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean fries aren't the healthiest in the first place, so why not go all out ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 11:38:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hungarians like paprika ?! What a shocker !
There's this restaurant/snack place that makes fries with paprika (still dip them in mayo too) and it was the first time I tried it. Actually really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 11:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey there. How come you didn't find any information regarding visas? Here's what I found.

[https://www.talentscotland.com/work/working/visa-and-immigration/how-do-i-work-in-scotland-non-eea](https://www.talentscotland.com/work/working/visa-and-immigration/how-do-i-work-in-scotland-non-eea)

Since you're a US national, the only possible visa you can apply for is a student visa. The other visas are not applicable to you. I suppose you don't have a grandparent of British citizenship since you didn't mention it.

[https://www.scotland.org/study](https://www.scotland.org/study)

Here is some info regarding studying at a Scottish university. The rest is up to you. I hope you find what you're looking for. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 00:50:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For example, for some reason, instead of jogging we say "footing".

We say that too in French ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 12:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "This mess we're in"- PJ Harvey and Thom Yorke. Also been re-visiting Radiohead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 12:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes !! Love "You're a germ" and "turn to dust" from the same album too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 12:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a mini heart attack and then realised Luxembourg isn't even in the list... Wonder why that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 02:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really ? I know everyone hated him in that book and it never really bothered me. I read it again recently and, you know what, I see where he's coming from. As a hormonal teenager I probably would have reacted the same way. The only one I wanted to smack was Dumbledore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 05:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. Seems a bit like cult-ish behaviour. Especially coming from a country that is not patriotic at all. The only time I take out the flag is during the world cup. I understand being proud of where you're from but in the US it's engrained in your brains from the day you're born. You're told over and over that it's the best country on earth. And the pledge of allegiance... that's just bizarre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 04:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The good thing about Scotland is that you have all four seasons in one day, so who can complain ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 03:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn... What was Fred like for you then ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 22:08:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep same. As soon as I moved out of Belgium I made a lot of flemish friends. I do think it's a shame that we can't speak flemish as well as you guys speak french and I hope that'll change in the future.
I don't think there's hate between us irl. The only hateful people I see are on the internet, extremists, and politians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 14:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a good way to start, but don't talk about uni only, try to steer the subject away from classes (I know I don't wanna talk about classes all the time). Idk how international your uni is but try to ask them where they're from and connect that way, try to find similarities between the both of you. If you feel like the conversation is heading in that direction, try to tease a bit (in a friendly way, the goal is to make friends first).
I'm really trying to help you here, I find it bizarre that none of your friends have female friends. Maybe the problem is just where you live because where I'm from, everyone I know has both male and female friends. Or there's just something that all of us are missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 03:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude that's irish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 03:44:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Easy to pronounce but leaves an awful taste in the mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude travelled a whole lot just to give you a phone call. Must have been urgent, can't believe you ignored him like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:55:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course don't move on from it, it's totally normal for it to be on the back of your mind. But just let it be on the back of your mind, not at the forefront. Just don't let it consume you. 
And don't wait until you're back at uni to try again, don't wait a whole year to spark up convo.
Don't mind me asking but could you perhaps give an example of how you try to approach girls ? Seems really weird that everyone you've talked to brushed you off. Or you've only met assholes.
And talk to your friends, ask them for advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey you mentioned you're a law student. Why don't you try striking up a conversation with girls at the start of lectures or during contact hours. Just start with the thing you have in common (law studies) and go with the flow. Don't try to seem desperate or too pushy and don't talk to them with the only goal of sleeping with them. First and foremost, try to make friends with them.

And please don't say you've tried and they've answered with one words. That just shows you haven't tried hard enough. Also talk to your friends, ask them for honest opinions, what they think of you and what you could do better.

Also pleeeease stop obsessing over this. Believe me it's not the most important thing in the world. Also don't believe those dating gurus on youtube because they don't have the best advice.

You'll eventually get a date, don't despair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 03:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can only provide limited information because I don't actually work there but my parents do so it's mostly from their experience.

Cost of life is generally the same in regards to food, clothes. The only drastic increase will be for alcohol and accommodation. 
The average price per m2 is around 1500 and the space is limited. I don't know your finances but expect to be living in an apartment. Having a car is also quite expensive. 

I checked on the foreign ministry website and you and your wife will not need a visa (don't think the skin colour will have any effect if you were worried). The procedure of becoming a resident is quite lengthy and you'll need a lot of paperwork.

For pets, I think most condos accept cats and dogs in apartment, I've seen plenty when I was there but that would depend on the landlord also. 

Regarding salaries, didn't your colleague give you an approximate of what you could expect ? I'd generally expect an increase in salary because the rent can be quite high. The tax rate is lower but there's no such thing as a retirement plan so you'll need to put that aside I think. And normally your future employer should provide healthcare to you and your wife (or hers if she'll also be working).

For more detailed information I suggest you ask your colleague or possible employer as I don't really know what your salary could be. It depends on the employer. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 02:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean we have to see the holes in the road somehow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 22:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You uncultured swine. You will not disrespect my culture like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 20:20:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Ils croivent" instead of "ils croient" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 20:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's illegal but it's not really well enforced. There is this guy that decorated his house with all sorts of Nazi symbols and they asked him to take them down but they never really did anything. I think he only took them down himself recently but it still took five years or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 17:03:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From the start it was so clear they would be extending the deadline. Two years is a ridiculously short amount of time for leaving an institution which they have been a part of for more than 40 years.

Also taking into account the indecisiveness of their Parliament and the reluctance of the EU to grant a deal without making sure the Good Friday agreement is upheld, it was almost certain that they would extend the time.

As for if the UK is going to leave, I think they still are but they won't totally be independent as they wanted to before. I think maybe they'll end up with a Norway-type deal or something. At this point nobody knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 16:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waffles. Waffles, waffles, waffles. Everytime I meet someone they wanna eat waffles. But they always talk about the kind that has no real taste if you don't put tons of chocolate and fruit on them. Those ARE NOT the good waffles people. Get the Luik/Lige waffles for the love of god. They are sooo much better, easier to eat, the best kind of waffles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 16:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do hate to hit my quintus on furniture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 16:24:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either fries or kebabs but mostly it's whatever's open and whichever you stumbled upon first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 16:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also your second grade teacher sounds like an amazing teacher.

Yes, that's such a thoughtful thing to do. And a clever way to get more kids into reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of my teachers had sex with his son's girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:06:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looking back now, I should have known better.

HE should have known better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On our last year school trip to Northern Africa a guy got arrested for trying to buy drugs in front of the police station. He ended up spending that night and the next day in jail with one of our teachers. He was released and could finish the trip but was expelled right after coming back home. Pretty fun trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 22:40:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, we're definitely not friends with each other, that's for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 02:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> France for me or Luxembourg with how many belgians there are you don't tend to stick out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 02:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think they were on the fence about wanting to quit for a while but I guess this was just their last straw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 15:46:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haven't they watched Derry Girls ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 00:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard the critiques thought it was garbage but the audience loved it. And I mean if the people like it that's what matters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 21:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also try to be mindful of your diet. And avoid loud noises especially in the morning, big changes in temperature and being exposed to cigarette smoke. Try to wake up as gently as possible because I've found out that a brutal waking can give you a headache for the rest of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 21:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a mocha pot the water boils and then becomes steam. The pressure from the steam makes the water go up the tube, through the coffee and into the top part of the pot. If you do that with milk you'll just get burnt milk. Don't do it. Also don't try to heat up milk in a kettle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 20:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It seems like you put more effort into your friendship than them. Maybe it was a lack of communication but try to reach out to them and tell them that you felt excluded. If they're good friends, they'll make more of an effort, if not, I suggest you find people who are more aligned with your views on friendship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imma have to say the most multilingual country is Luxembourg mainly for the consistency at which people speak a minimum of three. And that's a minimum because most people also speak english and portuguese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 00:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ketchup song or whatever this thing was

https://youtu.be/AMT698ArSfQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 23:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude what is swedish ? It's like the opposite of polish (who could use some more vowels) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 01:33:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure dirty is juste written "sale" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes. I just seem to always see it in movies and such </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd advise KUL. The university of Luxembourg is quite young and good but KUL has a better rep. Also, Luxembourg is very expensive for renting and I generally think you'll have a better student life in Leuven.

However, I haven't been to either uni, I'm only basing my advice on the echoes I have from students and from living in both of those countries. If you're more set on one programme than the other CHOOSE THAT ONE. Only take my advice if you're torn 50-50. Good luck

Edit: also depends if you wish to stay in the country you've studied in after your degree to find a job. Based on that my answer may change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are the first in the world after all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd vote for making EU even more integrated, maybe even a one big country.

Yep that's actually the idea. More and more integration striving towards a "united states of europe" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:22:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marc Dutroux but yikes I hate saying his name. He's the most vile and I would suggest learning about him only so that when he dies we'll all know whose grave to go spit on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No definitely not. For the Benelux I'd suggest English and French because:
- those in Belgium that don't speak french generally speak english, but those who don't speak english usually only speak french
- in the NL you can get away with speaking english
- in LU just whip out english or french. If they don't speak one, they'll speak the other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 20:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BE: 1-XXX-000 red on white 
Every car is different but most start with a 1. I think those starting with a 0 are those very poluting cars. The King has his own separate license plate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 17:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hence why I said I agree with his view on marriage and finance, not the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 17:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. Most people I know who work in a farm only chose to do so because it was the family business but it's very difficult for them to get by. I'd advise to choose your region carefully as some tend to be more farmer-friendly then others (ex: in my former town all the farms of the region joined together to form a sort of coop supermarket so the residents shop directly from the farmers without third-party intervention). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 17:27:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We learned about it in my Ancient Greek and Latin classes. But we also talked about it in French class funnily enough. So yeah everyone in my school at least was tought some basis of it but we'd go into more detail in the "specialized" classes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 17:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree with your Ramsey comment. I didn't know about him and watched a couple of his videos. Some things I don't agree with but his view on finance within a marriage are spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 16:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about Place Vendme ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 16:43:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We like to call it the most beautiful square in the world.

Our pride and joy 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 14:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who's Joe ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 11:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Je pense donc je suis"- Descartes - I think therefore I am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obviously Portugal doesn't count </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:53:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cats are very famous in most of Europe for choosing soulmates. It is a commonly accepted law that if someone's cat likes you you have to marry and mate for life. DO NOT EVER GO AGAINST A CAT'S WISHES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey maybe he likes it. Don't kink shame him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well at least the return rate seems pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that Italy is a must. The city depends on you and your preferences but please do not go to Europe without at least visiting one italian city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:28:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. It's a bit rude of people to question your intelligence or how you got into the uni you did. If you feel bad for answering them however then change your answer to be as polite as possible but if people ask you up front I don't see why you should lie to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think there's any typical weirdness that comes with being adopted, not any more than the usual adult/child relationship. The only weirdness I've experienced comes mostly from strangers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't have to go to catholic school every week like all my friends. Felt like the luckiest child in the world. I did have some resentment when they all came back from their confirmation with tons of money and gifts though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems to me like she's not that interested. She doesn't answer quickly to your texts and when you clearly suggested you wanted to be with her she said she had to think about it. Since you're not afraid of being rejected I'd suggest just asking her plain and simple (don't be too agressive). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean "stop"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 21:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do understand why you'd be pressed and think you make more of an effort towards his gifts than he does towards yours. Maybe in the future don't ask him what he wants and just come up with a reasonable option or talk about it with him and put a price limit on gifts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 21:55:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Respect by Aretha Franklin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 21:54:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you guys should have a serious discussion about money before you get married. If you are engaged and he is not willing to divide the finances so as not to put you in financial burden come the end of the month then that seems like a huge problem to me that'll only get worst once you get married. I think one of the most common causes for divorce is money disagreements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 21:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait you're married ? Genuine question but why don't you guys combine your money into a joint account ? Then you can still pay for a meal or treat each other without putting yourself in a financial burden. Is it not normal for a married couple to (forgive clichs) become "one"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 21:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. You asked him what he wanted and he said airpods but only if you can afford them. I understand why he's angry as a cheap pair would break soon after use. The best thing to do was to have asked for another cheaper alternative after your sister said she couldn't afford it. Also your reasoning is basically he doesn't get me anything nice so I won't get him anything nice either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 13:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. In my school we learned about the kings and the revolution in primary school. In secondary school we talked about general european stuff (from pre-history until Middle Ages) and from about the start of the 18th we focused exclusively on France until about Napoleon. Then it was back to general european stuff when we covered WW1, WW2, Cold War and the financial crisis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 22:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll need a whole course on Irish pronunciation after that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 19:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> French:

Ponytail = queue de cheval (horse tail)

Pigtails = couettes (doesn't have any translation as far as I know) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 19:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do it too but I was told it was because holding them upwards puts pressure on the stem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 19:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's Remus and Romulus. I learned about them in my Latin class but as far as I understood it's just mythology. It was never mentioned that this was the true history of the creation of Rome and wasn't based on any existing person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 22:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't dismiss Belgium quite so soon. Don't forget about the football world cup, because we haven't... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 22:56:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair I think we'd just kill ourselves, no need for outside interference we hate each other enough as it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 17:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very true. As soon as I go to Flanders I notice the differences. Different houses, different infrastructure, different people. Also, so many bikes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 02:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doing things. Moving from a quite populous country (BE) to Luxembourg, if you don't live in a "big" city, there's nothing around. I've started communicating with the cows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>