<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4690</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-09 15:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its deliberate as Bagas are weird too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 23:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ru and Michelle not knowing the connection between chippy, vinegar and battered sausage in Bagas video was triggering to me as a proud brit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 03:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like british isles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 10:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a massive fan of internal trade routes purely for extra production </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 06:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worcestershire, Evesham in particular, has a larger claim to being the Shire over the other counties because:

a) the axis you described (from the Black Country to Malverns and Wye Valley) lies almost entirely in Worcestershire.

b) Pipe-weed from the Shire in the books corresponds to tobacco cultivation in Evesham (Worcs)

c) Tolkeins maternal family were based in Evesham..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 17:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> France is wrong on this map </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 05:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 05:05:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This film was such a mindfuck which is why im struggling to remember key details. I think its fairly recent (within last 2-3 years) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [TOMT][MOVIE] Weird movie about a surreal cult-like warehouse retreat with different rooms. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 05:04:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cannot remember the key details which is why Im on here.
It starts with a guy getting convinced by a friend to go to some retreat. This ends up being a warehouse where the first room he enters is a guys rally.
Another room he goes into is a dark aquatic-ish room with the sound of the sea and a set of chairs. Two other people in the room start getting it on.
One room is like a weird sit down therapy session off this weird wooden corridor.
He kinda goes mad and ends up back in the first room but shouting at everyone.
The film ends with him back home with all this merchandise from the company that owns this weird retreat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 09:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This actually happens in the UK on bonfire night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 17:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, Tolkein based the shire on Worcestershire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 19:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reality TV production does involve making a lot of open ended decisions as you cannot predict what will happen. Richard is effectively a pawn for production because hes not able to win. I imagine if everyone arguing too much they would have tasked him to do something more stabilising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 14:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neither of those pairings compares to any from last season imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 14:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know Richard was planned from the start. im talking about the recent plot to make him an adverse player. hes the only one making the show entertaining imo and its like production are trying to compensate for the lack of drama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 14:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obviously richard was planned to go in from the start. but im talking about the recent plot to make him an adverse player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else finding this season boring? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 08:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that production had to get Judy (Richard) to stir the pot in order to get blocked indicates that even they know that these contestants are getting on too well....

Edit: by saying to get Richard to stir the pot, I dont mean by his inclusion in the circle (which was obviously planned from the start). I mean the recent narrative to make Judy an adverse/hostile contestant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 07:43:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are the colour meanings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 01:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still scatters your army. Furthermore, u cant be suzerein of another civ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Open borders after Liberating </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 19:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw a post about this a few weeks ago and Im really disappointed that they havent fixed this in the recent update! Its such a deterrent to liberating cities if your units are then scattered after doing it. Why is it so hard for them to do auto-open borders after liberating?!

Edit: does anyone know a mod that corrects this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 07:54:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having a shower before sleep does it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Leave Means Leave </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 23:00:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 03:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean 1750s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 12:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA because its a shitty situation to be in.
But if this childs life gets permanently worse because of this, can you live with the fact that you could have prevented it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 14:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  r/woooosh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 12:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its dubbed.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 17:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres actually a series like this called Queen of the South but its for drug cartels.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 01:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is fun and all but honestly, Prue eats like fucking animal and it wouldnt hurt to learn some table manners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 21:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sims 4 can go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 20:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watch Sirens. His character is a gay bottom slut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 22:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These meandering lines are not created by ocean currents but rather deposit flows between the continental shelf and the abyssal plain which can form underwater canyons overtime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 22:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not if youre into it.
I dunno about women but in the gayworld a lot of guys are into sugar daddies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 10:53:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would swap the nutella and the marshmallow around.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-06 04:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Build units and conquer.  Its way better than bothering with Settlers or wonders in early game when other players dont have walls or are focusing on other things. Dont target those that are also focusing on military at the start as youll have costly wars. Enough conquering and youll quickly get too large to fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 06:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/Brexit should be r/RemoanerCirclejerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 21:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LPT: If you find porn on the internet that you may need again in the future, download and save it. There is no guarantee that the porn will be available again in the future, and now you will have a digital copy.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sister Morpheus Trashbags </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 04:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 16:17:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not disputing that what you say are valid pro-remain arguments. Im saying you are actively ignoring what people would consider pro-brexit arguments.

They are out there if you vary your news sources a bit though I get the feeling that you wouldnt want to hear them anyway. Even what you said about Boris, some would consider him being PM a great thing (albeit not who I would want).

Its fine that youre being stubborn but dont pretend that youre not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 15:46:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the stubborness that you accuse brexiteers of is exactly what you are displaying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 15:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i do believe politics matters. But people who voted for brexit believe it was the right thing... similar to how those who voted remain believe it is the right thing. There is evidence (and speculation) to support both remain and leave. Yes, idealised views and zealous ideology do muddy the waters, however, you add to that mud in the water yourself with your anger and your absolute belief that youre right and everyone who disagrees is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 13:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems youre the one who wants an echo chamber. Most people are fine knowing someone has voted differently to them however, it seems you feel that aggressive confrontation is necessary when seeing someone who has a different opinion to you. Perhaps you should seek some therapy or anger management if someone disagreeing with you politically is such an enraging trigger... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 12:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes really! They have not said anything hurtful or insulting. All they have done is voiced an opinion in an objective inoffensive way. And the fact that you see that as a cue to call someone a cunt (along with those upvotes) sums up what this sub is all about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 12:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> now now, I think dumb cunt is a little uncalled for.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 06:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, this is the wrong subreddit. I know its called r/Brexit but it is in fact r/RemoanerCircleJerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 03:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ALL THE COMMENTS HERE ARE DESCRIBING REAL LIFE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 03:24:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is job shaming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-28 17:08:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally.... This has been what Ive been trying to say all along: People have different opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-28 16:13:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Regions being left behind is irrelevant to the question of the EU. Unfortunately, it has more to do with economics rather than politics and revitalising regions is very costly if there is economic pressure against it. Furthermore, youre assumption that I vote based on balancing UK regions is completely misguided. I dont believe governments are capable of balancing regions, especially with so much economic forces against it.

I dont know where you get this idea that I believe in an empire.... If anything, voting to leave the EU surely is a vote against what seems to be a proto-EU Empire.

I know exactly what my government has done and Id vote for them again (if they Brexit properly). The tax breaks have been great and a look forward to more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-28 15:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not hypocrisy. I prefer the UK system because I believe it to be more democratic than the EU system. Furthermore, it is more local than the EU therefore it considers UK interests more so than the EU.

If I could have a referendum on the House of Lords, or further devolution, then that would be great. However, the referendum was about the EU.

You should read up about the commission before attacking me considering that it is a fundamental part of my argument.

Better yet, you dont have to attack me at all. Just accept that I dont want to be in the EU.... the same way that I accept that remainers want to be in the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 18:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> isnt everyone getting 2 points the same as everyone getting 0 points??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 18:47:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What has the House of Lords got to do with the EU commission being undemocratic? What-about-ery doesnt go against my argument about the EU commission.

Yes the House of Lords is an undemocratic institution based largely on appointed members. However, it does not preside over the commons. Whereas the appointed institution of the EU commission presides over the EU parliament...

Furthermore, youre taking the argument to an EU administration versus UK administration where Id always prefer the UK because it prioritises the interests of the UK, irregardless of how the system works (even though I do believe it to be more democratic than the EU system). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 14:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I disagree, at least the cabinet and executive in the UK are part of the parliament.... unlike the EU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 13:54:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> actually, by youre own definition im correct. If democracy is citizens voting, then the EU commission is undemocratic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 13:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> clearly everyone has their own definition of what is and isnt democratic. They have elections in North Korea but I dont see anyone calling them democratic.

Also, it sounds to me that youre the one that wants to start an argument. All I did was reply to OP and people had a problem with some of the words I used. I dont believe anything I said was inaccurate and arguing over wording does not make my views or opinion any less valid.

The worst part of this is that I have not tried to de-validate any remain views however, it seems some remainers on here are just so bewildered that someone would not want to be in the EU that theyre willing to start arguments over wording.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 10:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess its a matter of opinion. The way I analyse it, is based on the purpose of the commission. The EU parliament acts as an elective buffer between the public and the commission which for me reduces the grade of democracy or grade of mandate or w/e. Without the commission I believe the EU would be more democratic. Which is why I call the commission undemocratic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 15:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its undemocratic because theres no public mandate on which the commission is appointed despite its considerably higher level of power in comparison to the parliament. In the UK, the executive and cabinet are part of the parliament rather than a separate body, this makes them more accountable to the public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 09:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If only! I wouldnt be opposed to the EU if it were just a multilateral trade deal (which it used to be). The ever increasing breadth of EU powers over national governments is something Id rather not be in. However, I do understand why others would want that.... I just wish some remainers would accept that not everyone wants an ever closer union. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 09:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Commission. And although the parliament is elected, they have limited powers... some of which youd expect a parliament to have. The structure is designed to allow for legislation to actually happen as I would imagine that without a commission and with increased powers to the parliament (which is far too Huge to function solely) then nothing would be achieved. I accept that for it to work then it comes at a cost to how democratic it is... which is why I fear its potential for tyranny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 09:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  vastly different comparisons. US food standards are not as prohibitive as common agri/fisheries policies and are nothing to be scared of. Nonetheless this is a matter of opinion, which is why Im struggling to understand why youre so insistent to tell me Im wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 08:55:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> common agri policy and common fisheries policy is an example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 08:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im not confused about sovereignty. Youre just making an argument about it because youre assuming my initial argument was about being sovereign in the most extreme sense. I know what I meant by when I said sovereign - to clarify - is that legislative powers moved back to the UK parliament. At no point did I say this to be economic isolation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 23:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its unnecessary to start namecalling when ive explained to you what I meant. Again, youre twisting words. I have no obligation to put things using the terms of your choosing. In fact, ive used the terms Merkel and Macron used. Whether you believe it to be loaded or not is youre own issue.

And no, Im happy with the UK in NATO. Its further EU integration Im against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 22:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre putting words in my mouth. I said EU army as a quick way of describing further defence integration (which i imagine will result in some joint forces in the distant future). I brought it up because Nick Clegg and some other remainers during the campaign were adamant that this would not happen... when it it really will. My argument had nothing to do with what the EU army looks like.

Again, people in this thread seem to misunderstand the fundamental difference between leave and remain. Its whether you want further integration or not. And personally I dont want further integration of defence, even if you believe it makes sense or not.

Twisting my words or putting words into my mouth means youre not addressing my point, but rather turning my point into something that it isnt and then arguing against it.

My point was never about what the EU army would look like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 22:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its impossible to say if it would be similar to NATO or if it would be more centralised. Its still a discussion at the EU council. Merkel has expressed something more centralised than NATO which makes me uncomfortable. However, my overall point when mentioning this was not about what I would look like, but more about the fact that Nick Clegg some other remain campaigners were adamant that further defence integration would not exist when it looks like it will... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 22:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just google it. this was late 2018 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 21:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its been widely reported that Merkel and Macron have called for it. I accept that this doesnt make it a certainty but it does make it an agenda. Personally, makes me very uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 20:47:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im not arguing for economic independence as I have never seen that as a reality. Again youre making the argument about the definition of sovereignty and I told you that economic independence was not part of my argument or why I wanted to leave the EU. Youre conflating ones desire to be out of the EU with the desire to be completely economically independent. Those are two different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 20:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had to way it up. I was originally a remainer but after seeing how the EU operates I could not with any sincerity support it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 20:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my post, sovereignty does not mean economic independence. You cant label your own definition of sovereignty as fact when fundamentally its legislative independence.

As for the power plants I am actually for them. I have nothing against trade arrangements and cooperation.  I am uncomfortable with some of EUs undemocratic institutions and its aim for further integration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 19:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I support Brexit and I guess its because of something weird. 
I fear tyranny and the way the EU institutions are structured allow for a less democratic and more authoritarian ways of legislating. Further integration of EU member states will, overtime, result in more and more transfer of power from National Level to EU level.

The pro-remain arguments to counter this point have been denial about further power transfer (e.g. Nick Clegg denying there will be an EU Army), however, it seems that an EU army is on the agenda and that EU bureaucrats want to speed up the transfer of powers so it becomes easier to fight growing euro-scepticism across Europe.

My vote was purely based on sovereignty over anything else. I just wish the remainers would at least respect that not everyone votes for economic reasons... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 18:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you seem pretty hostile. i didnt say anything about not wanting you to reply. However, you wrongly assumed that I was demanding a reply. Whether you replied or not wasnt something I had an opinion on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 17:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no. i didnt. no-one did.
chill. theres no need for hostility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 17:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no-ones asking you to say anything. Chill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 17:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ya but the unpopular opinion does include a caveat  regarding original material so not quite off topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 14:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mary Queen of Scots film should be considered fiction seeing as the storyline is so far removed from reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 01:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all research is not conclusive on what exactly causes homosexuality.

I need to point out that genetics arent always as simple as just inheriting what your parents are.... well it is that essentially but within the set of genes you inherit (your genotype)  theres combinations and hierarchies involved to determine what and who you are to the world (phenotype). However, you can still pass on whatever genes are in your genotype... So even if there was a gay gene, then there is a chance it would skip generations (like ginger hair).

Furthermore, being gay does not stop you from reproducing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-10 12:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TBH the difference between very cute and very creepy is if youre into him or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 08:07:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes, because it was hilarious how a non-EU member state hosted it this year.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sankey diagrams of your personal income are old, tired, and now is just a way of boasting about your personal income and how little money you waste. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 07:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seeing one was fine. It was interesting. And seeing an unusual one can be somewhat interesting - For example someone who earns income entirely from their (re)investments or perhaps someone who lives in Middle Earth or Wakanda.

Most of us dont and seeing one personal income/expenditure Sankey is enough.

However, this has not stopped the fortnightly post of some persons income and expenditure organised in a rainbow appearing at the top of data focused subreddits (e.g. r/dataisbeautiful).

Now, dont get me wrong, do enjoy a Sankey diagram however, there are millions of more interesting topics than publishing your own personal finances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 01:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> theres no difference between a northern irish teacher and a drill instructor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 17:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That I have to have the same political views. For example, in the US theres this expectation that you have to support the Democrats if youre gay and that supporting Republican is some sort of heresy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 08:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes and no. depends on the person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 14:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finasteride can slow it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 14:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> finasteride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 00:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the tory Brexit squad are scared because they will lose votes to the Brexit party and UKIP (like they did in the last european elections). Theyre not concerned about these elections somehow getting in the way of Brexit.

I dont know how remain is going to benefit from these elections. whilst the pro-Brexit parties are trying to tear each other apart youre forgetting that theres proportional representation and were (albeit by a slim majority) a pro-Leave country. If anything this means that pro-leave supporters will have more options of who to vote for without worrying about splitting the vote (unlike in FPTP).

Furthermore, euro-scepticism has been on the rise in other EU countries so I expect these elections will be very messy and in no way support pro-EU causes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 21:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/unintentionalASMR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 02:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its around the same size as 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 01:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what the fuck, im jamaican-italian, born and raised in britain and never met anyone like me until i randomly read this on reddit.... hi cousin...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 23:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that looks like a mouth ulcer. No you cant pop it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-02 17:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> barracks and conquer. Conquered cities will have the other districts (and some wonders).  Youll grow powerful extremely quickly and it will give you the choice of what victory you can aim for (except religious due to prophet limit) The majority of games I play nowadays dont involve me making settlers at all. Any settled cities are usually from captured settlers.

Edit: also barracks is the only district with production benefits in early game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-23 02:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im suleiman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 23:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Legendary Starting Position for Montezuma </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 23:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 19:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this was my coming out story.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 15:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that is in most cases however, XM state that they waive the swap fee without increasing the spread or commission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 04:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not hating. I think shariah-compliant accounts should be open to everyone regardless of religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 04:44:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its better because XMs islamic accounts literally have lower costs. Unlike other brokers, they havent re-engineered the swap fees into another form of cost. All they have done is removed swap fees while keeping spreads and commission the same.

Edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 04:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> actually youve missed my point on this. Im not disputing the existence of shariah-compliant accounts. Im disputing that they should be Muslim-only accounts. What would be legal is if non-muslims were allowed to have shariah-compliant accounts. For example, islamic banks allow non-muslim clients.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Islamic trading accounts for Muslims only. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 18:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive seen that a few brokers (e.g. XM) offer shariah-compliant accounts that are more advantageous than the standard accounts (they waive swap fees without increasing spreads or commission).  However, they require you to prove you are muslim...

I dont know about laws in other countries but XMs UK based operations are regulated by the FCA meaning that it needs to comply with the law. Most notably the Equality Act 2010 which states its illegal to discriminate against clients based on their religious beliefs.

Ive reported this to the FCA as one should be allowed to open shariah-compliant accounts regardless of religious beliefs. However, I noticed that other brokers who are under FCA regulations who also illegally discriminate based on religious beliefs.

Im curious to here if this has been an issue for anyone else or if this has been raised in the past?


Edit: please do not misinterpret what I am saying.
I am not disputing the existence of shariah-compliant accounts. I am saying that shariah-compliant accounts should be open to non-muslims. For example shariah-compliant bank accounts are open to non-muslims and legally brokers should follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-04 18:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> couldnt get past the 2nd question because im mixed-race lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-14 18:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I pretend to pray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 02:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SOMEBODY MAKE A PORN PLATFORM ASAP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-02 05:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did u forget AS3 snatch game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-01 02:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes! the analogy of forced perspective was so ironic in this video!

Also the use of identity politics to support remain arguments made this video unwatchable. In fact, the majority of this video was dont support brexit because THESE people support it and that makes you just a bad as them. Its like calling someone who likes bread a Nazi because Hitler liked bread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-12 09:39:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> theres so much going on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-12 09:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like wtf the girl with a FUCKING STAFF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 18:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to be fair, the amber light did turn on which in a lot of cases people drive through. This problem probably would have not happened if it was just a red and green light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-02 14:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its a screenshot on google street-view so imo it counts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> meanwhile in the UK </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-02 09:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-22 06:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> actually its This isnt RuPauls best friends race.... not aint.
2/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-12 02:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have my food delivered so I have one less reason to go outside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-11 16:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no. it has to actually look edible not just resemble the shape. this looks like mdf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-08 14:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes you a right. i misphrased what I meant. Modern building techniques allowed for stations to be more basement-like as opposed to tunnels. 

An architect is best for figuring out what to do with all that extra space. (architects cant do much with the narrow tunnels seen in stations like oxford circus or covent garden). Thus why these stations have distinct interiors.

Its relevant because Waterloo and LBridge are the only ones in the extension that dont do this (Southwark is basement-like for the majority of the station). Perhaps theres a mixture of reasons for this?

(i know the picture is of a tunnel-like part, but the aesthetic was determined by an architect because of the extra space because of improved construction tech) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-08 13:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a lot of them were built around the same time during the Jubilee Line extension from Westminster to Stratford.

different architect firms were selected to do each station (not just engineers) and hence why the stations have better designs and larger interiors as opposed to the tunnel-like design found in most stations (though with every new redesign these are gradually being phased out like with the current Tottenham Court Road redesign).

The extension had one lead architect (Roland Paoletti) to impose some consistency of the design thus why precast concrete and polished metal panels make up baseline aesthetic of each station. 

Precast concrete and metal was a popular choice of aesthetic during the late 90s (when the extension was done) for high-order architecture. This is why it still looks futuristic as it takes a while for the latest styles to filter down to large scale low-order commercial/residential architecture (cheap architecture). For example, full height single pane windows are still popular today (particularly in large-scale apartment developments) however, this was first done in 1929!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-04 01:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its principle. You can clearly see the lady coming off had to adjust her path as he didnt allow her off first.... i hope he received a mild tutting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-04 01:06:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> buses have separate exits to entrances.... on the tube letting people off first is a must! if you do not do it youll receive mild tutting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-04 01:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG LET PEOPLE OFF FIRST BEFORE EMBARKING!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 00:55:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it looks like testicles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 21:44:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alaska eats like a horse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 19:43:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, really resorting to namecalling? Overreact much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 19:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Firstly, understand what literally means. Theres very rare instances where you can use literally and suggest over the same thing.

Having integrity IS easier after winning $100k.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 19:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and what has this got to do with ANYTHING i said??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 19:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> READ my comment. what part of it says dont pay for stuff? Overreact much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 17:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Easy to say when you won $100k

Edit: Wow. Drag race fans really do have no chill.
Oh this person said something. I bet that something actually means somethingelse. Oooohhh I HATE somethingelse. I must overeact by aggressively commenting about how I hate somethingelse even though the person said something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 01:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this reminds me of the dress... I see brown though im sure the sign is red. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 05:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no. nonono. vampires have shadows. Its reflections vampires dont have. Furthermore, if she were a vampire she wouldnt be outside on a clear day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 02:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its all green screen so it can be edited easily. notice how she has no shadow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 23:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vixen shoulda done Whitney Houston for snatch game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 21:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah the poster on the window confirms it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-16 08:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nono, this post is inherently white. Not all white people (but only white people) have this level of a skewed risk-reward ratio to pull this shit. Its like how only white people go into haunted houses.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-10 23:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 24, had misophonia since 8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-10 18:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Petra porn, you can at least improve tiles with petra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-09 03:40:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i wish there was a way of improving rainforest without getting rid of it. At least in Civ5 trading posts could be built. Civ 6 gives no reasonable option for keeping them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 23:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She looks like sherloid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 16:36:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to real life. Sounds like you feel exactly how you should at this stage in life and youll probably feel like this through to your mid-20s. Stay productive and active and keep pushing forward and youll start to see yourself progress into someone more accomplished and the self-loathing will lessen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 16:22:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if youre a skilled trader then you can make it all again. This time take chunks of money out on occasion and save it or put it in low risk investments (like bonds). I trade myself and Ive lost it all several times but ive always had contingency cash stashed in order to live off and to restart.

Edit: You may find that in the long term that the wealth you build will be from the cash you stash away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 00:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stop taking recreational drugs (including weed and alcohol), just stick with the drugs that are prescribed to you. Set yourself targets that arent social or recreational goals but productive ones (e.g. this can range from career advancement, getting fitter, building a shelf, or learning a language). Be sure to make sure theyre achievable and within a timescale that you can work with. And commit to them. This may come at a cost to your social life but it seems thats the problem at the moment. Changing this (whether temporary or permanent) may help.

I used to be emotionally dependent on my social life and took recreational drugs (because im more fun and popular when taking them) but overall I was sad inside. Someone gave me similar advice and although Im not as sociable or popular or outgoing anymore, Im definitely happier. Im more accomplished, im more comfortable with myself, and its made me closer to my family and people I trust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-27 14:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my games ive found myself razing about 60% of cities. at the start Ill mostly keep cities but after you have around 7 cities you should only keep cities if they have amenity advantages. Keeping used to help with taking more but Ive found that the new loyalty mechanism has somewhat made it harder since the cities captured rebel while youre still trying to capture opponents cities. Razing stops this from happening and it makes keeping the odd city easier due to the reduction of opponent loyalty.

Also keeping every city will mess with amenities enough so to hinder production and potentially cause rebellion in your more established cities... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-25 23:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can always raze cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-25 21:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its supposed to cover the joint between the wall and the floor.

Why? Because this joint can be uneven and unsightly depending on materials used for floor or wall. Furthermore, the joint can be subject to wear and tear overtime of which the skirting board protects against. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-23 22:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DelaWhere?.... sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-23 22:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, Winston, like Rockstar, was easy to wind up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 18:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> one of the main ones is road damage, for example on the east-west streets the shadow from buildings may result in half the road getting maximum exposure and the other half getting none. This can cause road deformities. Its only when buildings are tall enough to limit overall exposure when this becomes less of a problem.

Another one is ice - the diagonal grid allows for a more even exposure to the sun which can prevent ice patches remaining the streets during the day.

south facing houses on the north side of an east-west road are unfortunately positioned. Their front rooms may get too much sun resulting in issues with glare and overheating. And the house casts a shadow on their back yard where youd ideally want a lot of sun. Buildings that are built at a diagonal orientation get a more even distribution of sunlight amongst spaces and less areas of extremes however, this can only be realistically done with a diagonal grid.

Its all about evening out exposure and reducing the areas of minimum/maximum exposure. In the north-south east west grid these are located down the lengths of streets. In a diagonal grid, these are limited to being at junctions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 17:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no. diagonal results in more even sunlight distribution.

north-south east-west, although easier to read on a map results in extreme differences in sunlight distribution which causes long-term problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 17:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the difference is sunlight. its more evenly distributed when grids are orientated diagonally.
when its orientated north-south east-west it results in extreme differences in sunlight distribution which can cause a multitude of complications. 

Edit: Grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 15:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the evil one is the one who decided to do north-south east-west grids. Diagonal is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 08:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kraken Simulator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-06 03:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what flower is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-04 19:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i dont think the waterfords would have cared either knowing the skeletons in their closet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-02 03:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no need for settlers, quickly build army and conquer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-30 15:28:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah maybe they need to allow military engineers to do have that ability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-29 18:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the flower, not the description  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-24 16:12:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was called the Big C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-14 15:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate Nazi jokes Anne Frankly I find them distasteful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 23:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> also the average rents have not been standardised to a per sq ft or a specific control for type of property. if this was done then im sure the prices would look more otherworldly exorbitant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 03:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RIP the kid - hell be lucky to survive the whooping he is in for lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think its due to dogs walking to the side of their owner. this creates a desire path parallel to the original. Then if humans start  using these new desire paths, dogs walking to the side may then create a new one... and repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 04:11:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, I found the way she ate more disgusting.... barnyard animal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-21 14:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mean girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-18 05:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> stop trying to make neva lavd yah happen.
its not going to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-25 17:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Solved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-18 15:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a TV Show first and a competition second. So appeal really does excuse making Trixie a winner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-13 05:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was posted elsewhere and someone said that it was to do with the thin layer of water magnifying the suns rays which can potentially overheat the tortoise. The covering with dirt is a defence mechanism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-31 21:12:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like anyone else they dont realise until its pointed out. Im sure if its pointed out to him hell stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-31 21:10:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive tried becoming noisier but it doesnt help as my misophonia is the worst when Im trying to focus so adding to it doesnt help. I have more tolerance when im not doing anything. However, like anyone else Ive been unaware of sounds I make that are triggers to other people but I stop forever making the sounds pointed out to me as triggers as I understand what it feels like.

Just point it out to him that it triggers you and hell stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 20:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 15% is not a majority..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 20:23:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I imagine it is a fantasy for some people but that would make it consensual and then technically not rape but rape-fantasy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 20:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on how its done, theres different ways of getting raped and people feel differently to being sexually assaulted in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 03:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 03:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you stop a baby from crawling in circles?

Nail its other hand to the floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 03:25:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take pictures of it before you move all your stuff in! You may need it those pictures as reference of the condition it was in when you moved in.
This helps for when your tenancy ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 03:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> theres a place for everyone in pornography.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-06 05:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EU4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-03 23:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean... theres loads of mammals that eat other mammals... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-07 01:09:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that really the entire list of first world countries...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-18 18:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excuse me?! (Sips tea) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 16:21:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goodbye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:19:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> N </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goodbye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-12 15:09:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-09 18:58:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wash your hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-02 16:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 22:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 22:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-18 00:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blind people get given them and they use them when they're a passenger... but i'm not ruling out that they've been driving without a license </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 21:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They've always given placards to the blind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-01 17:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I watched youtube tutorials to learn all the overwhelming number of mechanics in the game
[These ones](http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLs3acGYgI1-uWvHEhlIvx-vzsX0vhMOZj) I found most helpful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-21 01:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Botox wearing off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-17 11:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smosh - Pokmon Theme Song  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-15 23:13:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've specified Scotland and England, but not Wales or Northern Island. You're better off just putting the United Kingdom.

Edit: Furthermore, Faroe Islands should also have (Denmark) like Greenland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-11 15:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's doesn't speak on behalf of London or British queens! It annoyed me that she tried to justify her crap lipsync by claiming britishness. She's not really British tbh and I hate how she hijacks the British brand when really she's just an anglophile stuck in her own idealised views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-06 16:00:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can gingers even survive in aus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-04 22:51:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-02 19:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't joke about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-30 01:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do the same at fast food restaurants but with sauces and paper towels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-30 00:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what I was looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-30 00:46:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For many people i'm sure that is a great buy one get one free...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-22 14:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HUNGER GAMES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:00:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mrs D, Mrs I, Mrs F F I, Mrs C, Mrs U, Mrs L T Y... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-17 08:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No need to be so aggy... dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does if it's supposedly a low calorie alternative to sugar when in fact the calorie difference is more negligible than the "negligible amount of calories".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, like my point, it isn't 0 calories and the FDA consideration is simply a marketing loophole. And plenty of brands do it.

Obviously the video only investigates one brand, i'm not going to post a whole reference list of everything I can find online.

There's no need for such hostile sarcasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-14 13:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not 0 calorie. It's bagged at 4 calories (same as sugar) but you can sell something claiming it is 0 calories if it is less than 5 calories.

[look here](https://youtu.be/EN6COaYLS_A) 

Edit: by "same as sugar" i mean same calories as sugar and not that it is bagged the same as sugar.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 0 calorie sweetener </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Russian leaders tend to be on the shorter end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your own conception </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you eat clean ass then it gonna taste like ass mucus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can use a plastic bottle if you're cheap and just press it against the anus and push water in.

You can use a plain douche you can get special ass douches with different heads.

if you're fancy you can use a shower head piece

Just anything to squirt water in.

(Warm water works better at emptying the entire bowels) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With a douche bag.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a homosexual I know exactly what mucus you're talking about. I clean my ass out before sex and after my boyfriend has finished up there I've sucked his dick ("ass-to-mouth") and tasted the mucus (which I found tasted more sweet than the stuff up your nose). I don't go out of my way to find it and eat it like you do but I guess I get why you do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:03:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10 year old La Roux! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would still like to see them fuck though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-30 13:20:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They missed Horn Hill and the Twins from the intro sequence :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>