<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8910</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 14:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude if you're still in class, you're young enough that this isn't something to be suicidal over. You have so much time to make friends and meet people and in that time you'll form so many different relationships. Don't sweat it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 23:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey dude. Message me if you want to talk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 00:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here man. This place is wonderful  #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 02:25:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like sending this image to my friends when I want their attention is gonna be a real fun experience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 22:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like your tat dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 17:44:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>if it's any consolation, any victory; even small ones, are worth celebrating. You made it days without cutting and even though you say it's 'nice redditors' it's because you're strong. You should be proud of yourself, I'm proud of ya  #127800;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 18:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries dude. Writing down stuff definitely helps add some structure into life. I try and complete at least 5 daily tasks, like working out or practicing guitar for a few hours. It's nice to look back on what you've achieved too. Peace and love my friend  #128155;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 22:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome pic dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 00:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome dude!  #128077; #127998;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 15:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I roll my weed with rolling tobacco; always have really, I kinda feel like burning pure weed is kinda wasteful. It burns all weird and I never get as high. On the subject of using chip, I'd hate to use a straight cigarette as chip, the way it burns is just too damn quick. I always use American Spirit rolling baccie in my js, tastes so damn good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 15:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>American Spirit master race unite!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 17:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I met him in London after a show with Mobo last year. He signed my shirt, really cool dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 23:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Free Throw are wrestling fans? Awesome,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 02:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Random wrestling fanpage on instagram said they didn't like an Ospreay match, Ospreay found the comment and liked it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 02:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It just made me laugh. Big wrestling superstar, gonna be a name for years to come, searching the internet for negative comments about himself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 21:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very inspiring! So proud, you rock!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>