<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9119</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-24 20:53:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think you #8217;d look great with ashy blonde hair :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-11 14:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>if you were friends with that stacy then why did you start talking to the guy you knew she liked? thats not what good friends do, im not surprised she was pissed about it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-22 15:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes there are definitely guys that I regret rejecting when I was younger and thought I was too good for them. I feel sad when I think that I could have had a meaningful relationship by now if I #8217;d been more open to certain people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-24 14:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah there's a big difference between being 'girl pretty' and 'guy pretty'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-31 10:43:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely get what you mean and although its hard, I #8217;d recommend taking more pictures of yourself so you become more used to how you look in them. A lot of the time its a persons awkwardness that ruins the picture, the more comfortable you get in front of the camera the better the pictures will be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>19F Verification</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-01 00:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-03 10:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you #8217;re beautiful and your smile is lovely x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-08 16:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't worry about this too much, its not really common to be hit/asked out by random guys even for really attractive women.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-09 12:00:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>another one is strawberry legs - I didn #8217;t realise that there was anything wrong with my legs until I saw hundreds of articles of how to get rid of them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-09 12:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I #8217;ve never really let it bother me but hearing that people are so insecure about it that it stops them wearing dresses/skirts makes me feel like I should be insecure about it - ridiculous I know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-12 22:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>your dimples make you look so pretty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-22 17:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand how photofeeler calculates the final score, 21 people finding you somewhat attractive doesn't sound like you'd be a 3 out of 10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-23 14:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>9/10, you are so stunning and I love your style x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-23 15:35:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely get your point, but I #8217;ve definitely experienced a guy being embarrassed to have hooked up with me. Men have impossibly high standards for women.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-23 19:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its okay don #8217;t worry about it! I think its because I #8217;m in college where guys only see girls and pieces of meat and its the norm to rate girls they #8217;ve hooked up with. Also college guys view big boobs and a big butt over pretty much everything, neither of which I have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone else watch Abi Gibson on youtube?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-27 00:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>She hasn #8217;t been active in a while but I love her her videos, especially her rants about men. She #8217;s so relatable but at the same time I find her boldness and confidence really inspiring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>accurate</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 18:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>