<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5284</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-01 07:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s neutered now, and they spend very limited time together (and ONLY when supervised) for everyone #8217;s safety. They #8217;re actually both rescues, prev owner (coworker) was simply irresponsible and never vetted them. I was the one who was like, yo, your cats pregnant, and ended up taking them in. The litter has spay/neuter appointments for late Oct, and I #8217;ll schedule mom #8217;s once they #8217;re all weaned. 3/5 kittens already have good homes lined up. I hope someone else benefits from your comment, but I #8217;m not the one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-05 06:09:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look at those friggin toe beans  #128571;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-12 00:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>*their parents</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-12 23:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOVED this! Great story, and very well written!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-13 05:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>enters dissociative state The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-14 08:25:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Identify  #8220;hot spots #8221; and make them almost inaccessible. I crammed my fixtures together and added unnecessary display tables and that corner of my store is an inconvenient maze now. I remerchandise my store almost weekly, moving my targeted items to the opposite corner of the store and throwing off the shoplifters. File police reports for EVERYTHING. Call the police as often as you can, and be an absolute delight when they arrive. More calls equals more police presence, which effectively deters theft. Track what days and times thefts occur. If it #8217;s always Thursdays 30 minutes before close, maybe you should lock your doors 30 minutes early. My last hour is usually a shit show of grab-and-runs, and I have been unapologetically locking my doors and watching cameras in the back. When someone pulls on the door I run out and unlock it and claim using the restroom as my excuse. Shoppers don #8217;t care, and shoplifters have already given up. Don #8217;t give them the opportunity. Make shoplifting as inconvenient as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-16 02:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My kittens are 3 weeks old and nowhere near that big! Must be good eaters, ha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-16 04:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s so great! Congrats. You #8217;ve got this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-18 07:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the last couple days, I've been mixing kitten milk replacer with wet food. I also put out one small bowl of KMR and Mama was curious but it ultimately went untouched. Every morning I put down one can of wet food (adult formula, various flavs), and I make sure Mama's gravity feeder is filled at least half way with a dry kitten formula (its never empty at the end of the day). She gets another can of wet food at night (kitten formula). She never eats the whole serving of wet food. I'll try warming it up a little. While it's a great suggestion, I'm not going to try and bottle feed or use a glove- I work too much for them to become reliant on that. Honestly, either the kittens need to acclimate or Mama needs to get over herself until they're ready. Someone's instincts need to kick in. If warming the food doesn't help, what can I do about Mama's teats? She's very clearly uncomfortable. :( edit: a word</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-18 08:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like this question. I'm in my twenties, and have been struggling with a misdiagnosed/undiagnosed mental illness for over 10 years. I self harmed on my stomach and legs. My parents found out, and it lead to hospitalization, my expulsion from school, and years of humiliation and fear. I was shamed into hiding my cuts and scars, and eventually replaced that coping mechanism with something else (spoiler alert, it was drugs). I was in recovery from SH for about 5 years. I don't ever wear clothing that reveals my scars, so no one besides intimate partners knows about my scars. I relapsed about 6 months ago, and these cuts are much deeper than anything middle-school-me thought I was capable of. I have moments of clarity where I recognize that I need help. I sought out counseling services, but I'm not making progress. I'm still on my parents' health insurance, and I think using that resource would be extremely beneficial, but that would require opening up a dialogue about my mental health and coping mechanisms. I don't know what kind of help I need. I don't know if I need medicine, therapy, in-patient treatment... etc. I could make a pros and cons list for every option available to me. I feel extremely isolated. I want to get better, but I don't have the right support system yet. I want someone to see my cuts because I fucking need help. I just don't know who that "someone" is. I don't want anyone to see my cuts because the shame I faced years ago still haunts me. So let me validate your feelings, yeah, I want people to see my cuts but I also don't. I feel u.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>