<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2745</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-01 01:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It damn well better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-04 21:50:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most online stores have a lifetime subscription that is not proportional to the person's life. This is due to the rapidly evolving nature of things online, such as 2b.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-04 21:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good on him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-05 03:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loathe my parents for doing that... didn't help, and it just made it worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-05 05:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am all of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-07 00:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can quite easily walk 125k nether without losing hunger. Frankly, I doubt that would happen..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-07 05:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure hause changed it so that it shows the amount of people on the queue proxy server thing. Meaning that the people shown online is the amount of people in the queue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-08 03:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Generally, naturally spawning mob grinders do nor work on 2b, there are so many people online at once  amp; there is a plugin that limits the spawnrates as well. Tbh, youd be better off with hunting in the ocean, duping it or setting up an afk fish farm for them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-12 03:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing the 2b is the oldest server or even oldest minexraft server is crap. CFUK is many days older and is a anarchy server. Villagecraft (kind of dead, but still online)  amp; minecraft online are also older than 2b.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-15 07:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to mention that this was really badly written.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-15 07:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thou ar'st a hume of the godly tier for the conception of said sentence!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-18 01:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could have a chat game. Like riddles, find out what letters are missing in a word, type a word quickly, etc... perhaps reward the winners by moving them up in queue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Weird habit that I've developed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-19 06:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Over the past few months I've had like 15 outbursts of extreme paranoia, I would sit in my room with a knife thinking someone was coming to slay me, not talk to anyone out of fear of what they were saying about me, or even go to school. Before the school year, one of my best friends completely betrayed me and posted screenshots of our text messages to a school forums board, in them were some of my darkest secrets. Unfortunately, they spread almost instantaneously and everyone in the school starting gossiping of me. By now, most people have forgotten about them, but they still refuse to talk to me, including the other friends that I once shared with this person. After each of these outbursts, I get really paranoid that someone's going to hack me and expose some of the writings that I've made (they're quite dark). Before all this I had a different 8 digit alphanumeric password for each of my accounts, over the past few months however, I have slowly been expanding them to the point where they are now each 60 digits long and I have to spend like an hour to memorize each of them. I have also taken additional precautions and have made each of my documents (stories) password protected with another of these really long passwords. Does anyone else fo something to this extent, or am I going really overboard?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-19 06:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am really sorry for you. If you are close with the family of your friend, you should really comfort them - it'll take your mind off of cutting and it will help them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>