<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject347</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-16 00:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129315; #128128;BRUUUH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 16:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really sure I got it at my smoke shop it #8217;s super heavy good quality!! I got it half off it was $100 and the only one like it there !! Caught my eye  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 16:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It really is!! Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>always keep a clean piece ! An essential</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 16:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 16:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg  #128569;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 16:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!!  #129402; #10084; #65039; #128553;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 18:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use rock salt you put into an ice cream machine and 91 percent rubbing alcohol and you #8217;re good to go !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 18:16:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a fact</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 18:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmaooo  #129315; #129315; #129315;dude posted on reddit instead of calling the police  #128553; #128569;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More lovely pics of this gorgeous ass piece!  #128553;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-22 02:48:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-22 02:50:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-24 02:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s seriously A BIG FACTT  #8252; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128524; #8252; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-24 02:36:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The people on here hate on me for no reason  #129315; ... At least my bong is clean  #128556;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-24 05:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-24 20:22:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I didn #8217;t make the tweet  #128569; so sorry you #8217;re grammatically offended</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-29 20:38:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>God damn it looks like a fucking hurricane hit that place #129315;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-30 21:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>God damn! Nice ass piece !!!  #129316; #129316;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-30 21:48:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a legit company! I used to buy all my carts from there. Some are better than others in my opinion! But most of them were good ! Very reliable but shipping takes awhile usually. I would never get a shipping confirmation either which was a hassle but I always got things figured out! Would recommend if you don #8217;t have a reliable plug.. the shatter was nice asf but one of the pens was a little off. The danks were the best! Next to the TKOS. No complaints other than the one strain I got that definitely did not get me high. It was the fruity pebbles cart. Didn #8217;t sit well with me.. not sure what it was. But I definitely didn #8217;t get high off of that cart! Other than that it #8217;s a legit business but I would recommend ordering when you see what you want and you better get it fast! They sell out quickly but the shipping is a hella long. They say 2-3 business days and I wouldn #8217;t get my carts for weeks lol. Not even that bad as long as I #8217;m getting high!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>lol so true #129315;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #129335; #127997; #8205; #9792; #65039; #129335; #127997; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 18:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>isn #8217;t that a true statement hahaha</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 18:43:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 19:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn straight ! Good for you !!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 19:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Listen, nobody #8217;s a beaten down loser unless you #8217;re my abusive father.. don #8217;t let yourself down. Stay true to yourself. Man, I #8217;ve been there. Psych Ward and all. You don #8217;t want it to be you! Trust me your life is more valuable than words could ever meet! Don #8217;t dwell on the past, instead think about how you can better yourself. Nobody deserves to be alone and doubtful of themselves.. that #8217;s fucking living hell. Just get through the bad times cause I know there will be a hell of a lot of good times if you just push through it. I #8217;ve been through thick n thin with my family and life. Doubted. Not worthy. But that #8217;s exactly not true at all! Nobody is a loser! You need to find yourself in there. Deep down. You #8217;re a good person. Don #8217;t beat yourself up, rise up instead. Become the someone you #8217;ve always wanted to be and never turn back! Don #8217;t let society beat you to the core.. Life is full of ups and downs but that never justifies taking your own life. Sit back, Relax and never dwell on bad times. Strive and be you! Don #8217;t let a few bad things take your life. Stay true to yourself and always say the words  #8220; I am trying my best  #8220; cause the only way you #8217;re a loser is if you let yourself get the best of you. Surround yourself with love and positivity and good vibes. Block out the negative energy and release your happiness. I promise you as long as you have faith and hope, it can get you anywhere. You can succeed and you will!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>