<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5914</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dwarf Chilean flame questions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 05:21:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! I'm getting my first tarantula, and have my eyes on the Euathlus sp red. I watched a video that gave me some info, but I want to double check some things and ask some questions. 1. What tank size should I get? I was thinking 10 gallon (my betta is in a 10 gal, I like to give my pets a lot of space) but what would be the minimum tank size for a full grown while still being roomy? 2. What substrate should I use? I heard they like it dry, and not to use bark chips. The lady in the video used some kind of moss. 3. How often should they eat? The lady said hers eats twice a year, and that the abdomen should be a certain shape to indicate health. How will I be able to tell my T is hungry without starving her? 4. How often do they molt? I'm a little creeped out by the leftover molt, the tarantula my family had years ago molted a few times before we gave it away and I hated seeing the molt. I want to get over my disgust of it but I'd like some more info. Here's the video: https://youtu.be/-eynusLViSw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good place online to get a greenbottle blue?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 20:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well title says pretty much all. I wanted a dwarf Chilean flame but they proved too rare to find online, except at one breeder who was terrible. So where would be a good place online to buy one, preferably female?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Contrast between where the sun has hit and where it hasnt.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 16:48:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tfw</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 15:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>People are talking about what age they lost their virginity and you had yours taken at 8 years old :))))</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Well</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 03:04:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think my new years gift to the world should be for me to kill myself :))))</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you find your dream gun</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 17:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The perfect model plane</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 04:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A knife addition to a subway order</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 11:35:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When the mods don't appreciate your awesome shitposts</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 22:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now I can let everyone know I'm addicted to cutting (minus the cocaine) plus always have a razor on hand</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 02:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this a transformer?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 00:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dammit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 06:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was planning on cutting all up and down my arms tonight, hoping to get at least to fat layer, mostly because the voices tell me I need to so I can be at peace again but my fianc #233; always makes me promise that I'll be good every single night and I looked into his eyes and I just can't do it. I can't break that promise. But the addiction is wearing away at my soul, I need to cut so bad and it's all I can think about... But he hates it when I cut and I love him but I can't get over this addiction, it's consumed my mind and my vision I just want all this to end, but I'm too much of a coward to kill myself...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>