<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6784</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[16F]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 02:35:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>^true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh, I have noticed that people are this frank and kind only anonymously online. I don #8217;t understand why people bully others, it just destroys the other person. I have been bullied since 9 years and though people like me now but Idk . I hate myself for simply existing and that #8217;s mostly because those  #8220;bullies #8221; were  #8220;joking #8221; around. After years of being bullied I found out that the person who started bullying me was jealous of me and still is (cause I just act as if I am happy and good and all that bs).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well frankly speaking, I hate myself and I don #8217;t date anyone cause I don #8217;t want to cause anymore problems for anyone. No matter how much someone would love me or even I love someone (yes I haven #8217;t love anyone long story,but I have liked someone more than anything and it kills to see them everyday and knowing that you #8217;ll never date them or even go beyond  #8220;friendship #8221; ). It #8217;s like drilled inside my head that I am not a good person, a burden so I just don #8217;t date and yes even I sometimes whine that I don #8217;t have bf/gf but that #8217;s cause I can #8217;t openly say that I hate myself and I don #8217;t wanna give trouble to anyone. Though I agree anyone in my school would die to date me, idk what do they even see in me? I am just not good at anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have asked for help from my mom (long story, short version- she made me hate myself even more cause  #8220;kids #8221; like me can #8217;t be  #8220;depressed #8221;). I don #8217;t want to ask for help in school (I hate it as it is) and I can #8217;t ask anyone else in my family. I don #8217;t really trust any adult either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyday</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 05:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol that #8217;s why I don #8217;t date, I don #8217;t really need to burden someone else when I know I am not in the right mind to date someone or even keep myself alive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 05:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol no, I am just waiting for that  #8220;tiny hope #8221; to leave me so I can peacefully die and not quit an attempt every other day cause my brain feels like messing me up even more. See another reason not to date, I #8217;ll probably wreck that persons life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 05:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel you. My parents used to taunt me cause I wasn #8217;t as good as other kids in school during 1st grade and the kids used to bully me in school, the teachers joined in and when even my parents did I just accepted the fact. I #8217;ll never be okay even if I get help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 05:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well if I was, I wouldn #8217;t really hate myself to this extent. But I am not 18 nor am I going to try and convince my family again that I need help. My mother #8217;s reaction was good enough for me to understand that they wouldn #8217;t help me cause  #8220;kids #8221; like  #8220;me #8221; can #8217;t be  #8220;depressed #8221; and what used to hurt me even more was that she has told me that she has been through depression and how meditation helped her all that bs and when I used to hear that it used make me feel even worse especially when she forced me to join some meditation group she goes to and all the time I hated myself even more (and she told and took me there before I told her I was depressed cause I needed to  #8220;focus #8221; on studies and they had heard that a topper used to meditated everyday and what not). She used taunt me and tell me that I am  #8220;using depression #8221; as an excuse to cover up my  #8220;bad grades #8221;. After that I stopped arguing with her and let her treat me the way she wanted to, it was better than her voice ringing inside my head always telling me that I am never gonna be enough or a kind/ good person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 06:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;ll have to contact my parents and no matter what someone would say they wouldn #8217;t change their pov</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 06:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm I keep relapsing in anorexia and self harm (cutting), never had the energy to stop my depression and anxiety. And lately I have been letting my anger take control of me again (and my anger is not good at all, I don #8217;t even realize what I am doing until I finish and I don #8217;t even feel sorry after taking my anger out most of the times).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 09:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol don #8217;t be sorry, it #8217;s not your duty to give me an advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 03:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Few friends know about it but they ignore the topic and we #8217;ll others just know me as the cheerful and funny person of the group. But I feel lonely around everybody be it friends and we #8217;ll especially family.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 14:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well the doctor didn #8217;t even made me roll up my sleeves, I feel silly for avoiding going to the doctor since almost 2 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 14:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it #8217;s like you will stop being a burden on people in time and how good it would feel to not feel what you are feeling. Then the worst feeling after that acceptance is when you try to attempt, you can #8217;t do it. Your brain starts giving those small, tiny thread of hope and it stops you. Yet in an hour or two, you find yourself crying for not attempting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 14:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you kidding me? Who told you that you are ugly?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 14:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been feeling like that since a year. Don #8217;t let it stay for long please. There are times when I feel some emotions but that #8217;s it, I don #8217;t care about myself, my life or anything other than the people around me. That #8217;s it. It #8217;s pathetic for me to not give a damn about myself but only stay alive because  #8220;it might affect somewhere #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>