<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject350</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-15 16:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Start with the [videos on Hacker101](https://www.hacker101.com/videos) and work through their CTFs. Most, if not all, can be done with the community version of Burp, which is free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bloodstained physical is here</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 03:59:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 04:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Performance is fantastic. First time playing a -vania style Metroidvania, and it's utterly amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 04:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does run at 30fps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 04:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Na, local game store</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 04:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seeing the smooth 60fps on other plastforms has me a little jealous, but it's great being able to play portably.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 05:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are slight dips here and there, mostly when loading a new area. Nothing during critical moments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 19:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stuck at 720p docked, i assume the same in handheld</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 19:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>No patch for the switch version yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-19 21:55:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some displays can output the resolution; the FPS difference is obvious once you've seen both</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Baldur's Gate is here! Overwhelmingly large and well-written</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 19:31:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 20:36:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Font size is adjustable. This and the zoomability in the enhanced edition makes it totally playable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 20:40:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It runs great, but feels like an old-school CRPG. UI can feel a little clunky at times, and the paused-base combat takes some getting used to, but it's really fun once you get into it. It's also a direct translation of D amp;D rules, so combat/weapon/armor stats are all based on dice rolls rather than arbitrary numbers/number ranges. It's a fairly complex system, but it's refreshing to see exactly what is going into damage calculations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>