<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9896</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Body Dysphoria</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 02:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG my lower body dysphoria is off the records tonight! How do you guys get through it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>body dysphoria</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 02:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>how do you guys handle your bottom dysphoria? mine is really bad tonight and i can't seem to get around it. any tips?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>welp that was interesting TW</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 14:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just insulted by my mom. She thought it was funny. She called me a "shim" I almost cried. Like seriously? I don't get that from other people enough everyday? What would you do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>transgender</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 15:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>does starbucks still cover transgender affirming surgeries?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 15:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was so caught up in the moment I couldn't even respond. I think she just thought it was funny and was being thoughtless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 17:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was really hurt and really shocked. I didn't know what to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 17:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome! Good for him and good luck to you all keep us posted!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 17:34:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn't make you an asshole. You're just not attracted and that's cool. It's not like you're insulting people. You're cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 17:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're so brave is one on soundcloud/youtube by chas ross</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 17:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried being a girl for a day and thought I was going to die. I lasted 15 minutes. I was pretty certain then I was transgender. I'm more confident in myself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 18:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HRT and voice training</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 18:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am in a bit of a rut. I cannot go on testosterone due to some health issues so I'm wondering what I can do to make my voice sound more masculine? I've looked on youtube but am having a hard time finding voice training for guys. Any suggestions?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 23:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know right! It blows</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 23:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats great to hear though! I'm glad you found someone you like!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>screwed up....again...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 05:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>another clean streak down the drain. I feel like I'm never going to kick this no matter how hard I try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>