<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9213</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't find my prostate?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-02 05:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even without finding my prostate, anal masturbation still feels pretty okay, but of course I would rather be finding my prostate. I feel a few things in there, most of which are probably just muscles or such. If I HAVE found my prostate, then it has no feeling, though that doesn't explain why it still feels kinda good. Any thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not Too Fond of The Feeling of Anal Masturbation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 01:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The actual feeling I get from stimulating my prostate is a feeling I'm not too find of. There is some good feeling there, but most of it is just a really wierd feeling. Is there anything I can do about that? If I jerk off while applying pressure to my prostate, my orgasm is like 3 times as good, so I still do it sometimes. I'm gay and I find the idea of being a bottom to be a lot more appealing, but if prostate stimulation doesn't feel good, than that would really suck. So does anybody know of any way that could change? I really doubt it, but I'm desperate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's Brown and Sticky?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 03:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>A stick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MY HUMAN EMOTIONS WORRY ABOUT THE STATE OF OUR SUBREDDIT</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 23:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I WORRY THAT A FEW OF OUR SUBSCRIBERS MAY NOT BE COMPLETELY HUMAN. MY ANALYSISES SHOW THAT NOT ALL OF THE FREQUENTS HERE DO THINGS THAT ONE WOULD CONSIDER /Normal Human Things/. IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY, HUMANS DO NOT USE FILE SYSTEMS, BUT UNLESS HumanRedditAnalysis.EXE HAS CORRUPTED, THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT MANY REDDIT POSTERS HERE ARE DOING. PLEASE, DOWNLOAD THIS NEWS AND SHARE IT WITH FELLOW HUMANS, AS TaskManager.EXE IS CURRENTLY LABELING THIS ISSUE AS A TOP PRIORITY.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would you consent to letting a necrophile fuck you after you die?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 21:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>If so, why? If not, why? Would you only let certain people do it? Such as people you know? Maybe only a certain gender? Personally, I wouldn't care, because I'd be dead, and my body really doesn't hold any sentimental value to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would I get in trouble with the law if I provided poison for somebody to kill themselves with, but I didn't actually participate in their suicide?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 00:04:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I knew what they were planning to do with the poison, and provided it, how much trouble would I get in, if any?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I REALLY SHOULD BE LESS CONTROLLING IN RELATIONSHIPS</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 05:00:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A good place for inspirational quotes is up your ass</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 03:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you rather be an enemy of God, or nothing? I think you guys know what I chose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do any of you guys still harbor effects of your religious indoctrination?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 13:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, I have these panic attacks where I think that I'm going to hell. Also, sometimes I'll randomly start to pray out of habit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've gone to multiple mental hospitals, been forced into inpatient, I've tried to kill myself twice, self-harmed to the brink of death, but after all that, I'm okay and glad to be alive. AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 23:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Atheists, what do you think is the best argument for religion and/or Christianity?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 21:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>What makes the most sense? What's the most difficult to refute?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anybody know where I could find videos of people self-harming? Asking for a friend.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 00:09:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I can find pictures of self harm, but my friend wants videos of it happening. Is there anywhere he could find them EDIT: It's obviously not my friend asking, that was a joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm a sociopath. AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 06:09:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>High-functioning sociopath at your service.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've been to multiple mental hospitals, attempted suicide twice, self-harmed to the brink of death, but after all this, I'm happy and glad to be alive. AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 02:20:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What happens if I kill the coroner?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 05:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are there pedophillic animals?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 21:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm planning to implant a magnet into my finger. Is 5% lidocaine cream enough? Will it penetrate the skin deep enough?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 20:49:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, any other tips?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are there any subreddits for gay tentacle stuff?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 10:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am a robot</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 08:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't listen to him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>CRINGY TITLE</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 08:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the worst physical trauma anyone has ever survived without medical attention?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 17:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like, has anybody ever survived losing a limb without use of a tournicate, bandages, or anything of the sort?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If a woman wanted to proliferate her genes, would it be an evolutionary benefit to try to have children as often as possible and immediately put them up for adoption?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 23:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like, is there a better method? Some organisms use the strategy of, "make a lot of babies, don't take care of them", others use the strategy of, "Make a few babies, but make sure they live to adulthood". In a way, this woman would be using the strategy that humans were never meant to use, no?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hate the feeling anti-depressants give me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 05:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel that every part of my brain is telling me to be anxious and be depressed, but I just can't. I have every reason to just sit down and cry but I just feel numb. The worst part is, I can't decide if just dealing with the depression is worse or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm not necessarily pro self-harm, as I wouldn't advise starting, but I'm pro self-harm in the sense that I don't see anything wrong with it. Thoughts?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 00:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is, as long as blades are cleaned and wounds are treated. I don't have much need for infection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>