<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9232</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-10-10 22:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heyo, I'm a sound engineer/foley artist and musician, if you could use my talents at all, even maybe further down the line, I'd be happy to help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dropped this back in August, I'd love some thoughts and feedback!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-10-10 23:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-10-11 02:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recording sound effects ranging anywhere from footsteps to monster noises to rain, using real life objects to emulate sounds in games and TV, if you google it you #8217;ll see some pretty astonishing work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-10-11 05:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure thing!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-30 22:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so cool, I think you hit the nail on the head. I #8217;ve never really listened to a ton of experimental stuff, but if I #8217;d have any feedback to give, there #8217;s some frequency on the high-end that #8217;s biting my ears the wrong way with some of the whooshing build sounds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-30 22:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://soundcloud.com/marentinf/up-up-up/s-PVEad My personal favourite song from my EP, wondering what I could improve? It #8217;s a dream-y indie pop tune, with mostly just tracked instruments with the exception being the mallet/bell sound and the drums.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-13 01:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only 1 slot left: 4792-2294-5999</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-13 02:11:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>We #8217;re full now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Walmart Canada is back with a new  #8220;Placeholder #8221; date.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-15 01:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need some advice on my live set.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-21 02:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently decided to switch over to sample based performance instead of relying on my loop pedal and guitar for everything. My plan is to take my laptop, running ableton live, running into a Scarlett 18i20, and sending 6 to 8 tracks to FOH (Drums mono, Bass mono, Guitar with fx stereo, And some other stuff possibly.) I feel like this is the best way for sound guy to get a good mix and saves me from having to guess that everything sounds good. I #8217;ll be triggering samples and playing midi during the live show through various controllers. If anyone has any idea if this will work or can give me ideas on how to make it even better, that would be great. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-21 03:40:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is great! A lot of very relevant info, thanks! I forgot to put this into my original post, but I #8217;m also debating whether to run my live vocals through ableton for FX purposes or just run it straight to FOH?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-21 03:44:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! Thanks, I #8217;ll keep that in mind!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-21 03:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the past year I #8217;ve been using a Boss RC-300 Loopstation and there #8217;s 3 loop channels on it, but only a stereo output. Makes things sound quite muddy when you #8217;ve got drums/bass/guitar all coming through it full force (also a pain in the ass for my engineers). I feel like this is a turn in the right direction. Thanks for the advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do I have here? Harmony Archtop, would like some more info and possibly value.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-30 21:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can finally rest easy knowing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 19:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>