<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6699</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-18 15:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Knights of Badassdom!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-12 06:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like a changeling film, not uncommon in old Irish folklore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In honor of Romero, the first piece to my horror sleeve. Pittsburgh, PA/Justin at Pittsburgh Tattoo Company</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-17 09:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-21 20:41:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I already have visible tats on my arms and a larger one one my back  amp; work in the restaurant  amp; craft beer industry, been working for breweries over the last few years in sales and marketing/bartending and it's honestly the norm  #129335; #127997; #8205; #9792; #65039; I decided to go for the hand because I've got a few I can see unless looking in the mirror or taking a pic  amp; I loved this design so much I wanted to see it every day + I typically love to wear a ton of rings on my hands and I love the combination of the 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-21 20:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not too bad, obviously wasn't the best feeling but it only really hurt like a bitch around my knuckles, that was less fun..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-04 04:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Xz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Next Up: Creepshow! Apparently couldn't resist another Romero one but tossed in a little Stephen King this time  #129321; Pittsburgh, PA - done by Justin Sims @ Pittsburgh Tattoo Company</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-24 16:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Next up: Creepshow! Apparently couldn't resist another Romero piece but we invited Mr. King to the party this time - Pittsburgh, PA / Done again by the awesome Justin Sims at Pittsburgh Tattoo Company</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-24 16:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-24 17:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard great things about Susie as well, though I've never gotten anything from her, and seen her work - she's also fabulous! Love Justin's work, we're planning a whole sleeve together and stylistically we just work together so wonderfully, not to mention he's cool as hell and is also a big horror film fan :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Far side of our Pittsburgh, PA living room looking onto studio space  amp; iron staircase leading up to roof  #128525;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 19:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>