<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1806</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I messed up last night</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-23 15:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last night I almost went through with my plan to kill my self the only reason I didn #8217;t is I didn #8217;t want to hurt my best friend who #8217;s always been there for me but I #8217;m scared that soon I might actually kill my self.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-23 17:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man I #8217;ll take that into account</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-23 23:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same for me man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don #8217;t want to live anymore</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-23 23:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve hated life for a while now I haven #8217;t felt good in a long time every day I I #8217;ll wake up and lay in bed for up to 2 hours then I #8217;ll get up and wear a fake smile and put on a show for people around me and When I can finally stop the show I #8217;ll lay awake for hours wondering who would miss me if I was gone and I #8217;ve been wanting to end it for a long time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-24 00:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey man thanks for the advice I told my friend and she understands and wants to help me I really wouldn #8217;t have told her if it wasn #8217;t for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-24 00:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man have a good day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-24 07:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey man happy birthday</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-24 16:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>More of the same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can #8217;t do anything but fuck up</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-25 04:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend has been trying to help me and she told me not to do anything that would be considered self harm but I #8217;ve started cutting myself everyday I cut deeper and deeper they started as little more than scratches but now I need to soak the blood up and put pressure on it. I am a complete fuck up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I failed yesterday</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-26 21:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yesterday I was going to try and make it through the day without cutting and I was doing pretty well but then I had a bit of an episode because I had to much time to think but I ended up cutting twice and I was wondering if anyone knows a way to help with that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>