<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject544</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>M/20/5'11" [220lbs to 180lbs] (6 months)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-18 11:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do you want to know about the Xperia 5</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-03 13:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been tasked with reviewing this phone, and I know that the Xperia community would appreciate this more than the wider smartphone market So I wanted to know what you guys want to know about the phone. Any requests? Continuation of another post ( https://www.reddit.com/r/SonyXperia/comments/dcdeoh/what_do_you_want_to_know_about_the_xperia_5/?utm_medium=android_app amp;utm_source=share ) which I accidentally deleted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-04 13:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Review has been submitted, just waiting for approval from editors. I took on 90% of requests. Will post link in new post soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-06 22:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because theres no changes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 01:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is really weird. It's like he's turning in different directions so I wouldn't use it as an example Prayer is supposed to be fixated in one direction, towards the Kaaba.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 02:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>AJK is Azad Jammu Kashmir. It is the part of Kashmir on the Pakistan side. It is self governed and separated by the LOC from Indian Occupied Kashmir. They are marching towards IOK (Indian Occupied Kashmir) as a symbol of unity, to show that they too will keep fighting for their freedom across the border. They won't actually cross the border into IOK (I hope), but it shows that the people aren't going to sit at home and do nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 16:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>stop crying man, just get better. The ground is fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IsItBullshit: Being dark skinned puts you at less risk of sun damage and cancer?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 16:44:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does being brown or black put you at less risk of getting cancer or other diseases associated with sun damage? I'm brown and I've never been sun burnt in my entire life, I don't even know what that feels like. I've also never worn sun cream, so I don't understand when white people place a lot of importance on applying sun protection before going out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 16:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's say you could do a skin graft and give a white guy, black skin, or a black person, white skin. Would the white person who now has black skin, be protected from the sun? And would the black dude with white skin be more vulnerable to it? I guess what I'm really asking is if the protection lies solely at the skin level, and not in other deeper areas of the body</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes sense. So we developed darker skin to protect ourselves from the sun, which is why people tend to be darker nearer hot climates. Well, I should I say we developed lighter skin in cold climates (if we all came from Africa originally). Why is lighter skin more beneficial in colder climates, wouldn't they want to absorb more heat rather than reflect it in a cold country?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:40:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, so could a light person get too much Vitamin D if they lived in a hot country, as a dark person can get too little in a colder contry? I know too much Vitamin D can lead to a higher concentration of calcium in the blood, which can be super bad apparently? And as Vitamin K2 helps absorb the calcium into bones rather than floating around the blood, could white people supplement Vitamin K to prevent this if they live in a hot country?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Without sounding like a racial supremacist, does this mean the ideal and most adaptable skin colour would be in the middle of black and white? Like mixed race people or South/East Asians (Afghans, Mongols and Chinese), basically people who are neither dark or light.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 18:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, so whilst a mixed tone would work averagely in all places, they wouldn't be able to work great in any one place? It's a fair trade off I guess, you give and you get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>