<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4819</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-11 11:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!! I took my dog to the big dog park one day. This man had his two small kids with him. This little girl started running and my dog jumped up on her and knocked her over. She was stunned at first and then started laughing. After apologizing I still got the nastiest look and no response. My dog does have experience with kids. He's good with them but when they run around him and yell he thinks it's time to play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-25 07:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>strawberry pie!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-28 05:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>We love Kobe! He's a good boy for being there for his mommy. I hope you find peace  amp; happiness and that your douchebag ex gets his karma. You deserve better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-04 17:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>do you agree with that diagnoses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-07 16:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>they say that crystals can find their way to you. the universe is sending a message. cleanse them, read about the properties of the stone and see if it resonates with current events in your life or what you're dealing with. work with the crystal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-07 17:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>of course :) that is fine. there are many different methods for cleansing the stones. i'm almost certain what you have here is rose quartz. check out https://www.energymuse.com/blog/beginners-guide-to-healing-crystals/ and http://www.crystaldictionary.com/crystals-by-color.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-08 06:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>nta but you shouldn't stay with him either way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-14 13:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>YTA. You handled that situation very poorly. It's not all about you and you need to take into consideration that people grieve differently. If you are so uncomfortable with her being there maybe you should find a new place to live instead of kicking that woman out of the house she GAVE you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-15 13:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>When did you realize you had an eating disorder?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-17 07:39:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Melothria scabra</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 03:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>NTA I really don't think a baby cares what their room looks like. As long as your child isn't forced to conform to a certain gender and such while growing up, I don't find it an issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 03:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>YTA. He will not learn from his mistakes if his own mother is enabling him. I don't care if he's going through a rough time. There are other ways to be there for him. Maybe try giving him a ride to an AA meeting rather than to go out and get a drink..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 14:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>So cute! Is your brown pit a brindle?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 14:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's adorable. :) Looks very similar to my pup too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-02 07:48:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would sit down and have a talk with them. Say you feel like you should see a professional that you can speak to just so they can help you sort out your thoughts and such.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>