<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6322</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 22:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m seeing a psychiatrist and have talked to my gynecologist about this. I #8217;m currently trying to find the right antidepressant bc the ones I #8217;ve been on in the past and currently haven #8217;t helped. I might consider changing my bc to something different to see if that changes anything. Thank you for sharing this with me, I can already tell this site is going to be very comforting for me. Good luck to you as well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 03:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been on BC for so many years, the same kind though so I do eventually want to talk to my dr about changing them up. Thank you for letting me know your experience! Take care</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 23:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much for all of this. I need to start motivating myself to work out because I know that would change a lot. I get in these moods where I just like to bathe in self pity because it #8217;s what I #8217;m used to and anything else is uncomfortable for me, if that makes any sense. I also go through phases where I #8217;ll be super into taking vitamins but then I just stop. You mentioning this has actually motivated me to continue with start taking them again so thank you! I actually talked to my psychiatrist about CBD oil and he was really for it and has seen it being a lot of success with people. I bought my first bottle from some random head shop so now I know I need to go somewhere else. Thank you for mentioning the CBD subreddit, I #8217;m for sure going to check it out. Your kindness means a lot :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 23:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I need to stop drinking, it #8217;s recently become a nasty habit that I turn to late at night when I mentally don #8217;t feel well. I need a lifestyle change, and the things you have suggested are very helpful so thank you for that. I need to stop making excuses for myself and actually go through with things I say I #8217;m going to do because I #8217;ve been this way for far too long and I need a change. I appreciate all your kind words and advice, take care!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 20:35:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve tried a fidget cube as well! I #8217;d didn #8217;t do much for me though. Even when I put my hair up I have the impulse to take it down and just start picking. It #8217;s like my hands always need to be doing something, whether it #8217;s with my hair or ripping apart my cuticles. I think I need to start meditating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 23:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re right about this, I had my hair shorter for a bit and it made it much harder to pick at. I think this week I #8217;m going to go for a shoulder length cut. Thanks for this and good luck to you too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 23:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do plan on getting my haircut somewhat soon, I think it will help. Thank you for your input!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 21:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s very sweet of you, I appreciate that. I just hate the looks I get in class from professors or classmates, they don #8217;t get it, I #8217;m trying all sorts of things to get my mind at ease and to relax my hands. Best wishes and take care!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 03:48:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sounds corny as hell but my boyfriend has helped me through all my demons, he writes me things that make me feel okay about myself and situation. I #8217;m just the kind of girl who likes to reread texts from him when I #8217;m down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 03:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bf literally commented last week on how proud of me he was that I haven #8217;t don #8217;t anything physically destructive to myself. I cut my leg open pretty severely last night. I feel like a fraud in a way. Just know you #8217;re not alone, hang in there okay?  #10083; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>