<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3762</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need help with extreme age SBR ( also new to reddit)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-04 02:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-13 21:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oops sorry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2070 or 2080 (Super?)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-02 13:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m currently trying to pick which gpu I should start saving money for, but I don #8217;t want to over spend for the 120hz on the index. Which should I get, a rtx 2070, rtx 2080, or rtx 280 super (no 2080ti cause holy shit that expense) Edit: I thank you all for the help, I decided on the rtx 2070 super. I start saving once I #8217;m done saving for an index</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-02 14:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>700 bucks is a lot of money though, I don #8217;t know if I should save that up, or just get the cheaper rtx 2070 super</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-02 16:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aren #8217;t used GPUs know to be unreliable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-02 20:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great to hear that, I #8217;ll think I made my mind up. I #8217;m getting the rtx 2070. The 2080 super is just way to much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-02 21:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both are very expensive, plus I already made up my mind. Rtx 2070 super is fine enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-02 21:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What vr games do you have, I am curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help me make a team for fighter legend goku</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-03 11:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-03 11:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those characters I clicked on are not for the team, I just have big thumbs lol  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Steam wallet support removed????</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 12:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I have been saving up money for a valve index for about 3 months. I been using steam wallet code because I don #8217;t have any credit cards. However, when I tried to check the price of everything (tax), there is a pop up that says that steam wallet is not a valid payment method. You can check yourself too, just try to buy a valve index, and the same thing happens. Now I #8217;m sitting with 578 dollars in my steam wallet that I can #8217;t use towards a valve index, and now I #8217;m very very pissed off. Edit: Also, I #8217;m pretty sure this is against the steam subscriber agree that they made, cause in section 3, it #8217;s states that steam wallet can be used on hardware Possible theories: 1) it could be an error when I don #8217;t have enough steam wallet funds, but that would t make sense cause it would probably get me to pay the rest off with a credit card 2) funds from the market place Edit 2: currently still waiting on a response from steam support. Here #8217;s how you can help, send steam support a ticket, but also mention their steam subscriber agreement, and how that steam wallet can be used on hardware. If we make enough tickets, we will more than likely gain a response faster. Edit3: Finally got a reply, and it is indeed no longer possible to buy a valve index with steam wallet credit. That mean they are not following their own steam subscriber agreement. This is complete bullshit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 14:23:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lucky  #128557; #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 14:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know if it #8217;s possible to combine multiple prepaid credit cards on pay pal, cause if I need to start over (hope to god I don #8217;t) that #8217;s the payment method I would go for</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would explain, but it #8217;s a little embarrassing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in New Jersey, so I have no idea why it won #8217;t work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:42:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think a prepaid visa gift card could work???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 18:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I don #8217;t, do you think a prepaid visa would work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 18:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, when I first used steam (around 2012) before they had their own gift cards, I used a visa gift card to buy portal 2, so I think it will work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 18:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, when I first used steam (around 2012) before they had their own gift cards, I used a visa gift card to buy portal 2, so I think it will work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 20:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m having the exact same issue, looks like they removed support</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 20:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It didn #8217;t work for me and another person who tried using 100 dollars of it, and his PayPal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 23:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which is even worse since it goes against their OWN steam subscriber agreement (check section 3 to see what I mean) Btw, what the heck is webpay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 23:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doing the same as well, will update the post or make a new one when I get a response</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 23:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it #8217;s similar to the vive wands, it #8217;s pressing the menu button and the trigger at the same time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-08 01:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t own one, but I guess so idk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Psa: you can no longer buy a valve index with steam wallet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-08 14:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-08 14:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So yeah, this is just complete bullshit, they are not following their own god damn subscriber agreement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-08 14:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128587; #8205; #9794; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-08 14:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only thing we can really do to fix this is quote the steam subscriber agreement, which clearly states that steam wallet credit can be used on hardware</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-08 14:41:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>What sucks the most is that I had 578 dollars saved up for it, and now I can #8217;t use it for the valve index</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-08 14:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thank you for finding the quote, now just send tickets and spam this idk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>