<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1858</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-04-29 10:11:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm. Well the laws of the universe have broken down so my main is kinda genderless/no real defining features, midlength curly black hair, black eyes and very pale skin, slightly blue-ish from the visible veins beneath. They're an archeologist, very curious with an incessant need to make sense of things and a little impatient. It's really at the end of times ft. The end of the universe and a snake god.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-04-29 10:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sometimes imagine what an ideal review of my story would be. What elements I want to have pointed out and praised the most. What effect I want my story to have, what emotions I want to evoque, etc. etc. It helps me focus my energy on certain aspects and think about how I can attain my goals. For example, I'd like people to feel very bittersweet at the end of this short story, but satisfied with the character growth. So I'm going to focus on it a bit more. Might not work for everyone but when I've finished an outline or a rough draft, I stop and really think about what I want to achieve with it. It changes with each one and sometimes it's just "I want to have fun!" So the imagined reaction to it could be "I can tell she put a lot of joy and love into this one." It's not about caring about what others think or writing for others. It just helps me keep my majn goals in sight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-09 09:54:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, you got double Dreaf? I'm so jealous.... Share a bit of luck with the rest of us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-09 10:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably why! I'm a lazy player so I don't do stages for big chunks of time and the xp just rolls in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-21 11:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kpop albums. It's like buying a pack of Pok #233;mon cards, but way more expensive and with real humans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-04 20:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First watercolour landscape (got lazy with the trees), super new to art (since june)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 00:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 13:08:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 13:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much for your encouragements and taking the time to comment! I actually stopped touching anything related to art a long time ago because I wasn't good at it at all, so having "natural talent" associated to me isn't something I expected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 13:13:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a closer look at some ukyio-e works and I can see what you mean! I might try using them as reference since it's a style I really like. Might have done it subconsciously too since my grandma recently got me a book with japanese prints in it. Thanks a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 13:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! As I said earlier, I stopped touching art when I was pretty young because I thought I was rubbish so it really touched me to hear you positive comment. I'll be sure to post my next attempts! I want to try my hand at flowers (maybe lavender?).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 13:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've done watercolour a grand total of twice and really enjoyed the feel of it. Especially mixing the colours and adding water to lighten them. It's so fun to experiment so I'd really recommend it because the process is incredibly enjoyable and that's why I started to art. Hope that you post what you do!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 15:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 15:33:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was exactly my mind set. I decided I wanted a hobby and that I didn't have to be good at it. I just wanted to enjoy the process of it and decided to try art again. It was kind of a impulsive decision and I'm really happy I went for it so congratulations to you too! I know we easily get obsessed with getting good and comparing ourselves so it's so great that you did it despite that. Can't wait to see what you have to share.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 15:40:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kokobop. Warmed up to it now but I fucking hated it at first. Literally any of "The War"'s tracks would have been a better title track. Wasn't a massive fan of Overdose either but I still like it a lot. Oh and Lotto too. Again, I've warmed up to it now but the autotune is horrendous, its only saving grace is the iconic lines.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 16:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally have never sketched... But I'm far from being an expert. Just don't limit yourself if you wanna try it out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 16:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much, I really appreciate it. Since it's my first time, I might explore other styles but I really like this one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 20:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stan loona</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-01 18:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda remind me of my mom and my mom is a very pretty lady  #128149;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-02 15:34:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't get the point, rats are amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-02 15:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>SM really... Is a mess. I'm interested in seeing it but I do feel like this is a weird decision. The choreo is gonna slap tho.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I like my scars and bruises</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-03 16:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to hate them. It would literally trigger me to look at my right arm but now I've grown fond of them. I don't know if it's a coping mechanism or something changed or I'm just sick but I genuinely like them. I often trace them, draw on them, etc. Same with bruises. I self harm by hitting myself with a hammer and try to build up a good bruise before I stop. Before, just hitting was enough but then I started needing the bruises. I found them pretty. I like having them. I often take paracetamol before so that I bruise better too. I don't really know why. I used to be incapable of looking at myself but now I like those features.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>