<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3994</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-21 23:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, I have been looking through this subreddit on and off and decided I would try dropping all my games. I wouldn't say I have terrible addiction problems, just that I have wasted so much time playing games and I have no real hobbies or interests. Wish me luck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about youtube</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-22 02:25:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you guys do about watching youtube, I am not watching gaming videos and the videos I am watching are more educational ones I suppose but sitting here watching youtube doesn't seem that much better than gaming. cheers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-04-14 04:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow you summed up how I feel pretty well...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-18 06:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep it #8217;s about all I do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-18 06:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also find myself just listening to videos while I #8217;m trying to sleep or do anything really. Idk I think it #8217;s comforting to just listen to someone talking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-21 09:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I agree with a lot of what you said and the comments as well. I think it #8217;s still important to acknowledge that some people might still be depressed just not as severely. This doesn #8217;t make it any less of an issue, they just might not understand how much worse it could be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-21 14:34:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I agree with that, there are definitely people who are not depressed and just get sad about something and say that they are  #8216;depressed #8217;. But that doesn #8217;t mean that those with less severe legitimate depression don #8217;t deserve help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Feeling like depression is my fault</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-22 07:19:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do some of you feel like its your fault your depressed or that you should just be stronger and get over it. Cause I feel like I fake my depression to make an excuse for laziness. So how can you actual tell the difference?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-22 07:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry to head about that, I would definitely talk to your therapist about it. Even if you think you deserve to feel bad, we all make mistakes and maybe you should be a bit nicer to yourself. I've had similar things happen where I disappear for a while because of depression and ignore everything from everyone feeling they would be better off without me, then one person got really mad about me ignoring her so idk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-22 07:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah for sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-23 01:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happy birthday! Keep fighting hard bro :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-25 07:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I 100% relate to this, I #8217;m glad to see there are others experiencing this. I guess it #8217;s just part of the whole guilt that depressed people often feel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-08 19:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exact same thing happened to me, shit hurts :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When do mood swings occur for people?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-17 02:27:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do your mood swings between hypomania and depression happen gradually over a couple days or is it like an overnight transition?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do people do with their time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-18 07:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What does everyone do when they are depressed and really have no interest in anything, i just end up watching random YouTube videos all day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-21 04:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, I feel like my few friends hate me and just pretend to like me cause they don #8217;t wanna be nasty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My depression seems silly</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-21 07:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone else feel really silly about their depression? Like when I try to explain how I feel to my parents for example, I immediately feel really silly for feeling how I do and that I #8217;m just lazy and useless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-21 12:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I get that, I think at this point my parents are just sick off me doing nothing, would be better if I wasn't around</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-22 03:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah they know but I don #8217;t think they understand it properly, they just tell me to force myself to do stuff. Which if it was that simple no one would have issues with depression</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 05:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it #8217;s all I do, sad existence</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-30 09:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel this. Some people will wanna give you support and all but at the end of the day depressed people are no fun to be around and I understand that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How often does hypomania occur for people</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-06 10:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, I #8217;m possibly facing a diagnosis of bipolar type 2 and I #8217;m trying to better understand it. For most people how frequently do you have hypomania episodes and how often do you cycle between it and depression. Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-15 08:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow this is so true for me it hurts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-18 07:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah for me I just have no motivation whatsoever to do anything. Only thing I still somewhat enjoy is playing games</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-28 00:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes this exact thing happened to me and I felt so good after</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>