<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9604</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-14 01:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Etsy. I have bought 3 from the seller Jacqpot. Make sure to get the 2 #8221; width.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inherited an oil painting. Attempting to research the artist. The signature looks like the artist name is Nina Head. My grandmother was from Scotland but many of her antiques are French. If anyone is familiar with the artist, we would appreciate any details you could share.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-17 22:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-17 22:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>[upclose signature ](https://imgur.com/gallery/OxHG03M)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-20 02:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Be patient, it takes time to acclimate. 2. Be prepared to be a celebrity in your neighborhood  #8220;oh, you are the one who has a greyhound #8221; 3. Interact with other greyhound owners. It #8217;s so much fun to watch greys with other greys. 4. If you live in the southeast US (Florida particularly) be prepared to fight hookworm for a while (not a big deal, not expensive, just annoying) 5. Enjoy a very good decision you are about to make. How I don #8217;t have 3-4 retired racers by now amazes me. I just want to pet, walk, and hang out with her all day. My kids too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-20 18:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Separation anxiety tips. Feel free to add more. 1. Frozen Kong Toy filled with peanut butter or cream cheese. Takes her a while to eat it all and by then she has forgotten you left. 2. NPR on the radio 3. Don #8217;t make a big deal when leaving or coming home. Be very nonchalant when letting her out of the kennnel. 4. CBD oil can be helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beatrice rocking her 1st day of fall attire</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-24 01:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Instant Karma</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever thought to yourself "where is a cop when you need one"? Thank you TPD, HCSO, or FHP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Justice Served. Thank you TPD, HCSO, FHP!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 19:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>