<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject267</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-30 04:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a severe flare up when I was diagnosed so for me it was pretty obvious that I was in remission when I wasn #8217;t going to the bathroom 15+ times a day. However, I will say that lately I #8217;ve been trying to stave off a mild flare up, but I still think I #8217;m in remission because I have like you said, no blood or mucus. I just don #8217;t always have solid BM #8217;s.. which usually can be contributed to what I ate the night before if it #8217;s less solid than usual.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-10-03 20:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>who opens for them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-29 05:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! I applied and was accepted this past semester with a 3.9 but had friends who were invited to take the admission essay with a 3.2. It #8217;s a really exciting program and I had a great admission experience. Take your two pre-req classes: Intro to ADV and Intro to PR... pay attention and learn the major concepts because you need that info to write the admission essay. You #8217;re invited to take the essay based off your GPA (they choose a small number of the highest out of the applicants) and then you take a proctored essay in which they choose half to be admitted into the program. Let me know if you have any questions! I #8217;d be happy to help a fellow AD/PR enthusiast!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-29 23:29:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Summer is the least competitive semester to apply, and you have a great GPA so you should definitely get through to the first round! As for the essay, like I said, study your notes and have a good understanding of those concepts. Relax, do your best, and you #8217;ll do great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-30 04:23:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is this your only chance? I knew someone who got in with a 3.0 and that was in the Fall! Anyway, if it doesn #8217;t work out, there are plenty of related classes you can take as a Communications major, and you can join the Ad Club or Quotes as well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-30 12:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, gotcha! I #8217;m sure everything will work out fine, let us know!! Good luck and let me know if you have more questions at any point!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-01 00:08:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe you will too! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-01 01:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey! what #8217;s your top 3 favorite songs rn?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-01 01:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I listen to SWS!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-01 02:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like kick me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-01 18:45:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re the band that got me into that kind of music a long time ago! I like Mayday and PTV!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-02 00:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah absolutely, DM me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-02 00:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never heard of them, I #8217;ll do that, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-12-04 01:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d say it #8217;s a habit at this point. Unfortunately it #8217;s a hard one to break. I #8217;m in the same boat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>