<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7365</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-29 16:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>For fumbles/sacks; I play legend solos on Easy and line up on defense in the special teams play  #8220;Straight Rush #8221; . I user my starting FS on the left side of the line and just bull rush the QB every time. My FS is dawkins with 92 Hit Power so he almost always makes it a sack fumble but i #8217;m sure anyone can do the same by hitsticking. Sometimes the RB will block your side of the line but you #8217;ll just get a sack from the other side in that situation. I get about 25-30 sacks per game and about 20 fumbles but I score instead of punting it back since I need other stuff as well. Only downside is the fact that the games will take 30 mins at least</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-03 03:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guaranteed tackle when hitsticking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-03 23:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely going to be Peters. It #8217;s so sad what they did to Jordan Howard #8217;s TOTW after a 3 TD game, but gotta start somewhere I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-05 05:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>new urlacher hype for u</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-05 22:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>u get scum kicked at all? unless u suggest fair catching a kickoff at the 11 idk about that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>4 rushes 2 laterals 2 or less incompletions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>anytime, sorry for mobile formatting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>2 laterals, 4 rushes, 2 or less incompletions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 first downs, 3 stiff arms (just spam it), win game, safety yourself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shady Signals Challenges explained</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Page 2: Perform 2 laterals, rush 4 times, 2 or fewer incompletions Page 3: Pass 5 times, perform 3 ball carrier moves, score a passing touchdown Page 4: 3 first downs, 3 stiff arms (just spam it), win the game, safety yourself. *I was winning this one and ran it out the back of my own end zone and won the challenge 5 stars. Page 5: 5 rushes, score 14 points, turn the ball over, force a turnover</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/MaddenUltimateTeam/comments/del6vd/shady_signals_challenges_explained/?utm_source=share amp;utm_medium=ios_app amp;utm_name=iossmf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes sir</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 17:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I scored a touchdown before getting a safety on myself so take the lead may be correct as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 18:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was lining up with 2 receivers on one side of the line and doing an out route and having the other one in a screen. i would throw to the out route and pitch it back to the screen. worked both times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>