<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1819</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-31 10:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Accio. Just calling things to you. No more losing my headphones. No more scrambling around looking for car keys in the morning. No more digging between couch cushions for the remote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s the craziest video you #8217;ve ever seen?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-31 10:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-03 08:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably because individual humans have individual preferences.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What would a world populated by clones of you be like?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-03 08:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-04 17:48:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was engaged. Planned to move to another city for new jobs. I was going to go first, and he was going to go as soon as he could find a position in that city. Got to new city, already knew something was weird. Over skype he told me he wasn't coming. Haven't seen him since. Took me 2.5 years to even attempt to date again. Still hurt by it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s the weirdest thing that has happened to you while working at your job?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-04 17:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-06 16:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Making positive connections with others and enjoying those around you. It is a lot easier to sit on the couch and watch a feel-good show then it is to go have dinner with your in-laws when you are tired - but what is the point in sitting there watching TV? We all waste way too much time doing crap like that. Better to build meaningful connections while you can. There are millions of super isolated people in the world as well who would kill to have someone to have dinner with. Squeezing every bit of enjoyment out of life. I need to walk home - I can either take the subway for 5 minutes underground or I can walk 30 minutes through a park and tree-lined streets and truly enjoy it.. maybe get an ice cream on the way. I'd pick the fast way every time before, now I'm constantly looking for the most enjoyable route instead. I work in healthcare as well and am super grateful for that right now - there is such potential to do good and make an impact no matter which field you choose. Sorry if I am rambling or this is overly-simplistic. It feels good to type this all out and makes me happy that people are thinking of these questions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What actors or actresses play the same character in almost every movie or show they do?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-06 16:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-11 20:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me get back to you on that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-13 19:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talk to them. I don't know if its just a MN thing, but everytime I am anywhere old people start talking to me about random shit. I dont just quickly move on. You wanna talk about the weather old lady in Wal-Mart? Fuck yeah I'll talk about the weather with you. Old man in the post office today talking about his wife? Lay it all on me man. I'm married too, lets chat. I got nowhere to be and nothing to do!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When did something start out badly for you but in the end, it was great?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-13 19:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-14 17:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Text and walk. It never works. They always fall directly on their face</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Which protagonist from a book or movie would make the worst roommate?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-14 17:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-17 15:35:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Learn piano, drums, woodworking, welding, plumbing, leatherwork, and as many languages as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If magic was real, what spell would you try to learn first?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-17 15:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-17 16:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>they're between amber and light brown, i'm assuming based on lighting. you're both kinda right. but it's lighter than regular ol brown eyes so he's not just making it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was the best thing that happened to you today?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-17 16:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 10:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You joke, but if I walked into someone #8217;s house and there was a wall lined with skeletons I #8217;d turn on my heel and run the hell away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s the most embarrassing story from your childhood?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-21 10:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Golden Retriever Dog.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-22 14:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-22 14:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>dammit looking so cute!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hong Kong protester shot by police charged with rioting and assault</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-03 15:39:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-03 15:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't unsee this now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-04 13:50:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Yorkshire Terrier was first seen in England in the 19th Century and the Teacup Yorkie was first seen in the 20th Century</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best costume ever.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 19:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best Costume Ever.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 19:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>