<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1018</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-08 18:03:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only my husband would let me, I have myoclonus and was trying to train my own dog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chat room</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-06 02:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are there any chat rooms out there for people in the US who are having suicidal thoughts or self harm thoughts, to talk to others in the same head space? Not a help line chat or anything like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-06 15:40:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just wondering the same thing. Why are we always staying alive for other people? Afraid to take the leap for fear of what will happen to others</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>15 years of friendship, 15 years of fighting to stay alive, 1 divorce, 1 ending</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-06 15:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>My meds have been making me suicidal again, although it #8217;s not really again if it never went away. Being left alone after being so close to someone and even married to them is my breaking point. When the cutting doesn #8217;t help anymore, it #8217;s time to find the right pill combination.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-06 23:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking the same thing as my husband said he wanted a divorce. There #8217;s a girl who calls me mom and every day I get a text saying  #8220;mommy please don #8217;t leave me, you promised #8221;. It kills me and breaks my heart. How will your daughter go on without you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-06 23:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What have you done to keep going?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-06 23:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are so young with so much life left to live. There has to be someone who will miss you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-06 23:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you in danger?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-21 02:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the people I cared about was taken away from me today. The last two weeks have been hell and just getting worse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What to do when there is nothing left?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-21 02:47:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the past two weeks I have lost my husband who wants divorce, best friend of 14 years (husband), my job and today a 15 yr old that I was I guess  #8220;mentoring #8221;. She called me mom and pushed me to fight the same as I pushed her to fight. She got baker acted last night and as of what her dad said today I will never see or hear from her again. My doctors see my medication and want to change it, but the last attempt at that left me in an even worse place. I #8217;m massively depressed and my anxiety is through the roof. I have family who are trying to be supportive and friends trying to be supportive. But when I face the facts that I will likely have to sell my horse (my best form of therapy), I can #8217;t really care for my dogs. I don #8217;t want to care for myself. I feel like a waste of human resources and a drain on the economy. There is nothing left to really live for, so why bother. I just can #8217;t seem to find the right mixture even though I try almost nightly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-24 03:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get how you feel. I #8217;m a burden on my friends, family and soon to be ex husband. I lost my job and can #8217;t afford to take of my animals let alone get through a divorce and I #8217;m too depressed to do anything about it. People always say  #8220;you #8217;re not a burden #8221; but it doesn #8217;t change the feeling. Maybe talk to your grandma and tell her how you are feeling now. I #8217;m pretty sure she wouldn #8217;t want you to kill yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-25 01:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because we actually care about the people we leave behind. And the body doesn #8217;t actually want to die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-25 01:23:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You and me both, sadly I don #8217;t even think we can any disability. Depression and ocd are hard. But it seems like ending it all is even harder.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-25 01:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly there will be guilt no matter what you do. Guilt for breaking up, or guilt left after you #8217;re gone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it life or the severe depression</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-25 02:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been suicidal for years now, I #8217;ve also been cutting for years to stop from crying or to calm myself down. Lately with my life falling apart I #8217;m back to being extremely suicidal again. I say I #8217;m staying for my mom or my friends. But now I wonder am I just too scared to do it? Am I to scared it won #8217;t work and I #8217;ll get baker acted? I #8217;m I too scared it will work and worrying about the people and animals left behind. Is this just another phase of the depression being unbearable? The anxiety doesn #8217;t help at all either, and to top it off psychiatrist are wanting to change my meds at the worst possible time. I don #8217;t care the Benzodiazepines cause Alzheimer #8217;s, it #8217;s only a problem if I live long enough to experience it. My friend and I talk and joke about it bc what else can you really do. So every day I fight not to take the pills at night or during the day. Not to drive my car somewhere and take the forever nap. I keep questioning myself so maybe I #8217;m not  #8220;suicidal #8221; but I definitely don #8217;t want to be here and my first thought every morning is  #8220;shit I #8217;m still alive #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-25 02:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re far from alone. It has a weird calming affect that #8217;s hard to explain to those who don #8217;t get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>