<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3081</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-22 05:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My arms and a razor blade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't know what to title this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-11-26 05:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-03-31 18:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im gonna try</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-07 00:52:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel bad for asking this but, whats the anime called?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-08 04:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not so sure I want to watch it anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've fallen in love with the voice in my head.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-11 09:24:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>About 2 to 3 years ago, I fell in love with the voice in my head. She is very kind and loving, she is always willing to talk, and she seems to know what is wrong and what I should do, even if I don't. Just to clarify, She is not a physical voice. It's more like a thought I didn't have. It feels like another person is inside of me head. I'm just curious if anyone else is like me/what is going on. I've already asked around and didn't really get an answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-28 06:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The dumbass didn't even cut the right shape</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Spent too long in a dream. I don't want to forget it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-06 09:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>About 3 years ago I had a dream that lasted too long. By too long I mean years long. I fell in love and lived the life I wanted. I won't go into to much detail because it would be to long. Then I woke up. Over the past few years I've devoted all of my time holding on to it. I've already lost some of it and I don't want to lose anymore. If anyone has any help to hold on to the dream please let me know. I really don't want to forget.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-06 09:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-06-06 09:34:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hardly remember the beginning of it except an intense feeling of calm. It jumps to about mid 20's. I remember the dating and marrying the love of my life Jaclyn and everything in between. It jumps again to around early 40's. I'm dancing with her in a feild. I very clearly remember her saying "time to wake up" and I just dismissed it. It then jumps to what I think is the late 90's, this part is very fuzzy. I remember a sunset and her saying " you've been here long enough." Everything goes black and then I woke up. That's a pretty shortened down version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s it like buying razor blades?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-24 15:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m only 14 and need new razor blades. I just broke after one clean month. I was going to go to fleet farm to buy new blades but got worried they might ask questions. Do they or do they just not care?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>