<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7841</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 10:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always had a rain after school every day~ This is honestly the drink I miss the most.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 11:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The crabs are a fond memory for me, my friends and I always just screamed CRAB BATTLE and got them to all mimic that for the round.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help! My AC died and need cooling tips!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 01:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry if this isn #8217;t a proper reddit for this, but I figured I #8217;d give it a whirl. We have a ball python and normally we regulate everything just fine, but our outside ac unit just died and now needs to be replaced. I already had to have her deal for the last 12 hours or so but it makes me feel terrible, she just keeps looking upset (as she should be- it is 90 room temp in our house now almost all day). I might be able to move her to a friends house temporarily but I #8217;m not getting swift replies so I don #8217;t know, I know I can move her probably Saturday somewhere else. What I need to know is if there are any tips or tricks I could possibly do to help cool her down that wouldn #8217;t be too harsh on her skin nor break her cage? I don #8217;t want our baby to die just because of this terrible timing for our unit to break...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-10 10:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not sure about online groups, but there are support groups hosted by NAMI in a lot of cities- it sounds odd but it really helped me with my anxiety. Usually online I just search out any anon site or forum (r/anxiety, chats, etc) You can search for NAMI groups here: https://www.nami.org/Find-Support Some states/counties have options for counseling or other services that accommodate to your money too, if you end up wanting something further or one on one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-12 17:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that you, depression dog?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-12 17:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do, it just might be hard to notice. If your eyes are burning it is probably sweat dripping near your eyes. But yeah if it is hot enough you do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-22 01:21:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not the right time frame, but the closest I can think of is maybe katethegreat19/erutan? At first I was thinking maybe Jillian Aversa but I don #8217;t think she #8217;s folky enough for what you #8217;re searching for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-30 03:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone was watching Gumball and decided they could try to do it too I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-26 08:49:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>IGN: subject7841 Nice meeting you guys :3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-26 08:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added! IGN subject7841</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-26 08:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!~ IGN subject7841</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-26 08:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added! IGN subject7841</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-26 15:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added~! My IGN is subject7841</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-26 15:17:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added you~ my IGN is subject7841</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-05-26 15:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added! IGN subject7841</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-25 16:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know but... If yes, does that mean that if you accidentally leave your keys, phone, etc that you #8217;ve corrupted your save file?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-25 21:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds like Tetris Worlds but I think that was only on PS2. There were several modes and the  #8216;campaign #8217; story was you were rebuilding the tetriminoes worlds (they were like customizable aliens shaped like a square block)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-02 03:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. I needed this so much today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>