<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7434</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this just coloring, or something to be concerned about?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-16 23:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-16 23:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve only had my snake for a little over a month, and he #8217;s just a baby, so it took him a while to get used to me handling him, so I never really got to get a good look at his belly to know if he #8217;s always had this or if it is new. I #8217;ve never seen him soaking in his water dish and he doesn #8217;t have any mites near his eyes or under his chin. These dots are only on his bottom half of his belly, the rest of his stomach is completely white. Are these mites, or something else, or is he just freckly? thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are these just spots, or mites? Is the dark streak in the middle of his belly a cause for concern? help!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-16 23:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-17 06:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aspen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-17 06:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>will do, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anybody able to translate this? Is there a website or an app that could help me translate?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-07 01:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-07 18:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The front is a picture of a library, and it says it #8217;s from Massachusetts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-07 20:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great, thank you! I #8217;ve never heard of shorthand before i found this postcard #8212; are you saying that the code changes each month? There were no characters for the names of the months that matched the ones on my postcard (i could only find a Youtube video for those) nor did any images or PDFs of the alphabet. Im not really sure about how this code works or what to look for, but i #8217;ll do more research to figure it out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-07 21:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is interesting! Thank you very much!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My little boy hanging out in my sleeve:)!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-08 02:25:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-08 06:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>[enclosure!](https://imgur.com/gallery/ZK8iOcF)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-08 07:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>hAH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-08 23:38:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>corn snake!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-09 20:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s from Parlin Public Library, Everett, Massachusetts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Going to a concert soon, wondering what drug would be best to heighten the experience</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-14 06:06:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>my friend and I are going to a Tyler the Creator concert. What #8217;s a drug that #8217;s under $20 and recommended for concerts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-14 06:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>what #8217;s ur experience with mdma? does it make you feel depressed the next day or is that not super common</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-14 06:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>we were thinking of microdosing some acid bc were kinda.................. pussy do u think that would still b cool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-14 23:35:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>wow! thank you so much for the help!! i was really struggling to find out what system of shorthand this was, so thank you!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-23 20:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>such a sweet baby!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>i started cutting but i don #8217;t want it to become a habit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-06 04:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>i #8217;ve had self-harming tendencies since i was a child, but a few days ago was the first day i actually started cutting deep into my skin. i was surprised at how easy it was to do and how much relief it brought me. i was so angry with myself and so sad that i thought i was going to explode but after i cut myself it all just evaporated. i can #8217;t stop thinking about it. im sure im going to end up doing it again but i #8217;ve seen how much people become ashamed of their cuts or regret them, as well as how much it takes over people #8217;s life and becomes an addiction. i don #8217;t want it to become a big part of my life. any advice on how to resist the urges before they get too hard to push away?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>