<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6870</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(Unix Shell) Question about the script command</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 15:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone ! Could someone explain to me how the -r option of the script command works ? I read on man pages (like this one : https://www.freebsd.org/cgi/man.cgi?script) that the -r option records input, output and timestamping, but I can't seem to find any more detailed informations. Does anyone knows how this option works preciseley ? How and where does it save input, output and timestamping informations so it can be played back by the -p otion ? Thanks a lot, and I wish a very good day to every one ! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 14:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really too much adorable  #10084;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 01:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi ! I did something that actually helped me a lot about my relationship with my boyfriend. I started a diary in which I committed myself to write everyday, the more sincerely possible, about every fear or emotions I felt in the day. By sincerely I mean that when my fears where unfounded, I had to write that too. It helped me to be more rational. After the day's summary, I write how I could have handle my emotions better or how I could have act differently to make things better. After that, I write a list of every positive thing that happened to me in the day, even those that can seem insignificant, because they are not, they count as much as every other good thing that I can take. And I finish everyday with a very encouraging conclusion, where I force myself to compliment and encourage me. In a few days I could already control my emotions better and rationalize more ! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 21:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's Ricardio from Adventure Time !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 23:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Scooby-Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed]( https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0ajwqddbQAQ)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 11:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your eyes are really beutiful !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 00:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>So cuuuute  #10084;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi reddit ! Meet Souris, my aunt's cat !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 12:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:47:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, and her first cat was called Poisson, like "fish" !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:49:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would have suit her because she can be a lot of trouble when she wants to!  #128523;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 01:41:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing, that is true art</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi guys ! First time posting my work here. I've been drawing for a few months, and i really enjoy coloring with a graphic tablet. I truly want to improve, so any advice ? Thanks a lot !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 13:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 17:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your advice! What do you mean by 'changing the thickness'? Do you think I should variate the thickness of my lines or you think I should change it all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 18:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much! It's very nice to ear that! :) I will try to post more stuff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 18:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha thx! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 18:51:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>OK, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 13:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's very encouraging! Thank you again :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 13:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for all your advices, I will try to think about all that from now on ! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5 : How does the MixColumns step of the AES algorithm works ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi everyone ! I want to improve, do you have any advices ? :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-10-08 03:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-26 08:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to do that but I can't seem to find the right moment. I was with him all yesterday, I slept at his place and I'm still with him right now and I did not manage to tell him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>1. The magician</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-07-31 00:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2. The High Priestess</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-01 03:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I drew that while smoking today  #128522;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-04 16:29:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Day 01 : Ring</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-04 14:17:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wanted to share this amazing selfie of myself that I can't post on insta because all my family is following me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-10-07 14:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>