<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8737</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Friends concern</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 06:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my friends has expressed a concern in my drinking but I truly don #8217;t think it #8217;s an issue. He said he #8217;s worried about it becoming an issue in my future more so than a problem in the present. What are some signs of alcoholism developing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bb</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 06:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Unsatisfying therapy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 06:40:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went to therapy a few months back. It was so disappointing. After years fighting myself to go, I felt like this is just who I am. I #8217;m meant to be depressed and anxious. With tips to just talk positive to myself or do yoga, I felt so hopeless. Am I just meant to be this way? Is therapy just one long tumblr post on how to feel better?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Movies to Cry to</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 06:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m feeling so numb and I #8217;ve been dying to find a good movie to cry to to feel something. Suggestions?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 07:02:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any specific songs or playlists you #8217;d recommend? I mainly use Spotify idk if that helps or hurts suggestions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 07:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much  #9786; #65039; I #8217;ll check it out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 07:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my all time faves. So sad. So good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 07:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both? I did one one-on-one session and like 5 group sessions. The one -on-one was after like 3 sessions so she kinda got my vibe. And then she kept repeating how I  #8220;didn #8217;t feel good enough. #8220; Which is true but her repeating it over and over I #8217;m the one on one didn #8217;t feel like helping just felt like a reminder</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 07:42:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly only talk about it with my BEST friend. Hence his concern on the matter. He knows the most about how often it drink which is why o think hes concerned. I almost always get drunk alone and at my house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-10 07:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s so dumb. I feel so guilty when I do it that I almost feel like I HAVE to tell someone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-11 05:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its almost always alone which is why I think it caused the rift of worry in the first place. I #8217;m very introverted and so that #8217;s when I feel like I can take it easy. But I do get your point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-11 05:40:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same with how to deal with it. I sometimes have to audibly say  #8220;no thank you #8221; to shut it down  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-11 05:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg Ducky was one of my favorites! I love that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-11 06:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was once a month lately once a week or so. Only to the point of getting buzzed like 2 drinks. I really don #8217;t think it #8217;s that bad but I #8217;m paranoid it might become that bad someday</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Flu and Anxiety/Depression</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-12 03:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got the flu for the first time in my life this week and my anxiety and depression have been super strong. Does this happen to anyone else or is this just a coincidence in timing with my flu and flared mental junk?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-12 06:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had never heard of this! Thanks for the tip! I also have some OCD tendencies so this would add up. So interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do you do when depression makes you numb?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-01-15 01:42:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m in a big pit of numbness and I just wanna know if anyone has tips for riding it out? It #8217;s been a few weeks now and it just sucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hopping from Coping Mechanisms</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-02-10 06:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been reading A Bright Red Scream which is really enlightening about self harm. Anywho, I had an epiphany that I kinda just switch from coping mechanism to a new one weather it be self harm or alcohol or skin picking or nail biting etc. I was just wondering if anyone else does this or has a hard time turning on to  #8220;positive #8221; coping mechanism. Or maybe has advice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>