<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1750</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-14 18:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want 12</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-26 02:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have cerebral palsy too I #8217;m not in a wheelchair or too much into little space as you (I #8217;m guessing) but I wanted to say hi:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-26 03:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im honestly kinda worried about losing strength in my legs but thats not important right now. i am a little i think its that i dont have a daddy and i dont really like playtime play. so theres not much to do myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-26 04:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>i have my stuffies and disney movies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-26 18:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes a lot  #129392;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-26 21:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Katara found a new form of bending ; cumbending</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-28 04:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>That just made me crave Cheetos lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-31 05:38:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t wait to see a 1__ instead of 2__</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-12 19:40:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The hate for myself drives me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-12 19:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Parkour!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-14 01:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s just a 4 in the background</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you have accepted your disability that #8217;s great I will never accept it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-15 15:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>(25F)I hate myself and my disability so much, I can #8217;t and won #8217;t talk to a therapist cuz all they want me to do is to take pills so my  #8220;perspective #8221; will change but after I accept my disability I #8217;m still disabled and I #8217;m still useless. I #8217;m not looking for sympathy. I #8217;m just so angry I have to live with this half and half lifestyle (the right side of my body is affected the left half is normal -and my brain doesn #8217;t seem as affected as some-) I wanted to be everything that I physically couldn #8217;t do I wanted to be in the army CANT wanted to learn drums CANT wanted to be a women #8217;s fighter CANT . And everyone says I want these things because I #8217;m disabled no I liked it but I will never get to do what I want because of this. I #8217;m always going to be second best and not even that . I #8217;ve always wanted to kill my disability but everyone always took it as I want to kill myself (sometimes I do but it was a way to deal with this curse normal people call a blessing) so they #8217;d be like no look how great you are. Yeah look how nice and sweet I am to people... but do I have any real friends...no not one ..everyone is always  #8220;so busy #8221;... so what #8217;s the point to this rant. I want people to stop telling me I should be happy even though I hate myself to the core and cerebral palsy is not a blessing it #8217;s a curse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-15 16:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow at least they handed me one but when I asked about people with disabilities the looked so sympathetic when they said no. Followed by my teacher asking after class if I asked on purpose to get a reaction because I was kinda a class clown but I asked because I wanted to bein the army it was a dream to follow my grandfathers army days ever since I was 10 till 14 when that happened</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-15 18:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>No #128521;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-15 18:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for reminding me:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-17 12:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one loves onions that much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-22 20:58:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought I was the only one I cut my legs I can #8217;t cut my arms because of work but I just really want to one day cut up my whole arm and pretend like they don #8217;t exist just to see who would care and it makes me feel bad but feeling like no one cares feels much worse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>