<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2599</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hey, ever wonder why we're here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 11:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fuck everyone that has called me fat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 00:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck them, Im gonna try and push myself to not eat for a week and see how skinny I become</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have no idea what's going on</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 04:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>First my heart started to beat rapidly then it started to hurt then everywhere around started to hurt then my throat felt like someone stabbed it then when I tried to stand up I got cramps in my legs its still happening I don't know whether to go to the hospital or not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Guy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 06:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Foxtrot looks around at the canyon walls wondering "Why are we fighting for this?" He see's no one around so finds some shade sits down and starts working on his book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How come no one says bisexual?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 13:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like if I ask someone "Whats my sexuality?" they'll say either "Straight? or "Gay?" like there is no in between and when I tell people I'm Bi they get disgusted I'm just shattered on how people treat other people opinions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's been since October on my last account since I've been here.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 13:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been so long. How's everyone doing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm getting scared for my best friend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 03:00:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>She told me not to show anybody this but I need help so we've been writing notes and the latest one caught my eye I'll put it here "Hey, It's me again...Are you gonna be there then when I'm crying? Are you gonna be there when everyone is gone? PLEASE,PLEASE,PLEASE Don't leave me alone in the darkness when no one else will show me the light. I want to stay friends with you, I REALLY do. But I know you'll be gone soon, everyone always leaves me when they realise how much of a bad human being I am, I actually am. I want to make this last because when I remember I know that these memories will what brings me back from anxiety attacks, my suicide attempts, and when I'm broken and crying. I love being bestfriends with you, and I love spending time with you. You are one of the few reasons I'm still alive. Thank you for being there for me when no else cares. I'm there for you, no matter what happens." Man this got me chocking up so much. I'm so worried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did Brian D. appear in "No country for old men"?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 01:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear I saw him he gave his shirt to Anton right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I told my Best Friend about being suicidal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 02:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I told my Best Friend how she's always there for me when I need it. So I haven't been on Reddit much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to get fingerprints off of a blade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 05:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need help on how to get my fingerprints off of my razor. I liked it looking prestine but ive ruined the look with my fingerprints ive tried soap and water ive tried just water ive tried scratching it off ive tried all the things I've thought of</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>