<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject197</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I feel paranoid and also feel like someone or something is watching me at all times</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-03 04:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>To start off, I have bad anxiety. I get panic attacks about 1-2 times a day(on average) and they #8217;re usually pretty intense. But recently in the past couple of months, it feels like I #8217;m being watched by someone or something even when no one is around. I also sometimes hear things that aren #8217;t there, or a very quiet noise that no one else heard. I also sometimes see people out of the corner of my eye that aren #8217;t there. Anyone else have this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I feel like I have the need to self harm myself when I get panic attacks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-18 05:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I get panic attacks, I get this sensation of bugs crawling all over me and that my skin is crawling and the need to scratch(I have scars on my arm from it). My anxiety keeps getting worse, and with that the panic attacks increase. I now get about five per day. The bug crawling sensation is also getting worse where the scratching only scratches the surface(bad pun). I feel like I need something sharer in order to get the sensation to stop. I #8217;m afraid of what I have to use in order to stop it. If just scratching my arm can leave scars, I #8217;m afraid what sharper objects will do. And if I don #8217;t scratch or do anything to the urge, it physically hurts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I feel like I have the need to self harm myself when I get panic attacks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-18 05:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I get panic attacks, I get this sensation of bugs crawling all over me and that my skin is crawling and the need to scratch(I have scars on my arm from it). My anxiety keeps getting worse, and with that the panic attacks increase. I now get about five per day. The bug crawling sensation is also getting worse where the scratching only scratches the surface(bad pun). I feel like I need something sharer in order to get the sensation to stop. I #8217;m afraid of what I have to use in order to stop it. If just scratching my arm can leave scars, I #8217;m afraid what sharper objects will do. And if I don #8217;t scratch or do anything to the urge, it physically hurts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-18 05:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a teenager so I still live with my parents. My parents said they won #8217;t put me on medication because they don #8217;t think that it #8217;s serious enough. It took me months to convince them that I needed to see a psychologist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-18 05:59:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have very sensitive skin so hot/cold showers won #8217;t do any good. I #8217;m not at cutting, yet. I scratch my arm till it breaks skin and bleeds but it #8217;s now not working like it used too. Im afraid what it #8217;ll lead me to use</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-18 06:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve already tried to tell them that it #8217;s serious. They #8217;ve seen me in public when I started to get a panic attack and start scratching. The most recent one was in Walmart a few weeks ago and my mom told me to stop because people were looking at me weird. She also said that I was talking like a crazy person when I told her about the scratching. She threatened several times to lock me up in a psych ward because of it also.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-18 06:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My moms parents died when I was really young. On my dads side, his mother just died and we #8217;re moving my grandfather out to Texas so there is a lot on his mind and my dads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-18 16:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much all of my family lives in the Texas and Midwest area. The only cousin of mine that I trust is also in Texas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-21 03:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not angry at myself. My emotions for the past couple months have been flat. I haven #8217;t really felt any genuine thing expect panic and paranoia. I really have to try to be happy and sometimes I can only muster a smile for a few minutes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-21 04:16:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea it #8217;s weird for me too. It #8217;s like my brain telling me that I almost need to do it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-23 22:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love spicy food, wouldn #8217;t work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-08-25 07:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that if I do it it will only transfer the pain to others and I love my family and friends to much to do that. It #8217;s what keeping me alive. I always try to keep a little hope left. And I #8217;m hanging on a thread of the rope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I consistently feel paranoid and hear things that aren #8217;t there. And sometimes I see things that aren #8217;t there</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-01 20:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>All this topped with constant panic attacks and anxiety. I always feel paranoid, like someone or something is watching my every move. I never feel alone. I have to check everywhere every time I enter a room just to be sure that nothing is there, but it never goes away. I also constantly hear footsteps around my house. I #8217;m a teen and live with my parents and brother. I hear them when they #8217;re home, but also when they #8217;re not. I also hear stuff in my attic moving around and I #8217;m convinced that a person lives up there. After multiple checks, no one is living in my attic, but I still think that someone is. I have conflicting feelings also, like happy and sad at the same time, love life and hate life, extreme and intense mood swings, and feeling hot and cold. I also have terrible anxiety. I don #8217;t think there was a day where I didn #8217;t have a panic attack in August. It #8217;s mentally exhausting. I also think I see a man outside of my room. For context, there #8217;s a little space like a loft outside my room. We keep nothing there, so it #8217;s empty and I think that I see someone every time I go up there. Anyone else have these problems? Any advice would be appreciated, because I have a therapy appointment at 5:00 pm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I lied to my therapist today</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-02 05:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>He asked me if I ever attempted or thought of self harm. I said no. But we both know that #8217;s a lie. People can see your arms and the therapist can too. Please be honest with yourself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I cut for the first time yesterday</TITLE>
    <DATE>2019-09-22 18:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>