<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4847</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-01 17:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're called "Spiro-Papas" in Mexico</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-03 18:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drum Corps International</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-03 18:13:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drum Corps International</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 03:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. I just thought he'd change or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 03:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm trying to give him a chance to be normal! :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 17:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, gotta admit that was kinda harsh of me to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-06 23:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tried to tell him soooo many times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-06 23:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had already explained to him that I'm not interested AND why so many times. He just thought that I'd change my mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-07 03:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup! Finally decided to block him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's a blog. Full of grilled cheeses.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-02 21:32:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First time builder, $500-$600 budget.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-12 17:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;**What will you be doing with this PC? Be as specific as possible, and include specific games or programs you will be using.** * This PC will be used for gaming, mostly The Sims 4, GTA V, Minecraft, and Battlefield 4.  gt;**What is your maximum budget before rebates/shipping/taxes?** * $500-$600.  gt;**When do you plan on building/buying the PC? Note: beyond a week or two from today means any build you receive will be out of date when you want to buy.** * ASAP  gt;**What, exactly, do you need included in the budget? (Tower/OS/monitor/keyboard/mouse/etc)** * Everything except a monitor. I will be using a tv instead.  gt;**Which country (and state/province) will you be purchasing the parts in? If you're in US, do you have access to a Microcenter location?** * US, Texas. No Microcenter location nearby.  gt;**If reusing any parts (including monitor(s)/keyboard/mouse/etc), what parts will you be reusing? Brands and models are appreciated.** * Everything will be new.  gt;**Will you be overclocking? If yes, are you interested in overclocking right away, or down the line? CPU and/or GPU?** * Not interested in overclocking.  gt;**Are there any specific features or items you want/need in the build? (ex: SSD, large amount of storage or a RAID setup, CUDA or OpenCL support, etc)** * Nope.  gt;**Do you have any specific case preferences (Size like ITX/microATX/mid-tower/full-tower, styles, colors, window or not, LED lighting, etc), or a particular color theme preference for the components?** * A window would be nice if it fits into the budget.  gt;**Do you need a copy of Windows included in the budget? If you do need one included, do you have a preference?** * Windows 8.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-12 22:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Than you all so much for the suggestions! I really appreciate it! (:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>just [f]or you  #127872;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-29 08:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-29 08:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol just a mild teaser ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 01:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just gathered enough nickels to buy $3.00 worth of gas so that I could drive 5 cities away to sell my bodily fluids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This hamsters name</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 17:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 17:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some light stalking and location tracking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 18:05:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard that LSD and weed don't mix well and will make you feel extra melty, if that makes sense...also have had some rough trips with dxm. Actually, every one of my dxm trips was a bad one. Wouldn't recommend but if that's the kinda trip you're looking for, go for it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 03:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every time I wash clothes my undies disappear one by one...I'm down to 5.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 21:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live on the Texas/Mexico border if you're interested in something spicy. ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 05:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sandy Fish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 19:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drown by Front Porch Step "I'm so tired of the rain falling softly on the ground, just enough to get my feet wet but not enough to let me drown." (Nevermind...)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 20:38:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn you're right, fuck that guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 21:50:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking the same thing! I've never seen this white queso stuff and I live like 10 minutes from the border.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 01:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also punch myself and hit my head against things after promising not to cut. I hate finding new ways to hurt myself when I'm upset.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>