<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject549</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Academic] 3-5 min survey about the use of VR and AR tecnoloy (18+, students or professionals) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 18:14:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 06:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 05:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's probably warmer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 18:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usualy think in spanish but if I'm really sad I think in german. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 00:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why the long memory part? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the first thing that comes to your mind when you think of Mxico and its culture? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 00:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Indoor navigation wthout arcore </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 00:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm trying yo develop a ar app to find the Office youre looking for. I'm trying yo us mapbox but don't quite understabd how ir works. Can someone help me with some advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PIC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 21:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PIC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 06:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 08:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you live a peasefull live with someone you love so you dont have to be alone any more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 08:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems like everyone hast theyr future figured out and I the only one who doesnt know what is happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 08:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the militarization of Mexico and the way the government is canceling anything culture and science related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-28 10:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blue - Marina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 23:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you, I will look into it during the summer vacation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 08:18:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> where did you learn to use zbrush. Ive tied using it but I find it kind of confussing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 00:57:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finish my proyect for the semester </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 08:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People shoud be able to make theyr own decisions. The same way they shoud be hold responsible of the conceuences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 08:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it woud be evidence like the searchhistory or the places they visited or the people you talked whit before the misscarige, because I think it cant be proven any other way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 07:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I been in dark places in the last 4 years Ive been  with my BF. Hes been rally pacient with me. He tries to come see me offent and let me know hes there for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 07:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Espero que pueda aceptarte y respetarte por quien eres. Sin embargo lo del racismo y clasicismo es algo muy comn en Mxico y no entiendo por que no tiene sentido. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> suggest me a book about programing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 07:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a animation student. Sometimes we learn a bit of programing but I want to learn more by my self. I woud like to learn specificaly about C# </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 07:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My gay friend has said to me he finds vaginas disgusting and kind of strange. So mayby thats it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 07:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. Jobs shoudnt be influenced by this tipe of thing. They asking fot this requierments only make this kinde of inequality problem worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 06:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But they are not showing anything explicit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 07:18:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had kind of a similar situation about a week ago. The upstairs department is a rental so I dont know the people living there now I spoken to the owner a few times. 

So they used to have arguments every now and then but they werent my buissnes so I just ignored them, but one night I started hearing screeming and people runing. At first I tought it was the kids playing but suddenly the doors began slamming and things were beeing trown across the room. Then a woman began screming leave my kid alone ore something like that and a child started crying. I called the cops but at first they didnt answer so I called again and I left the report but they never arrived. After around 40 minutes they didnt stopped screaming so I put music. It was near 3 am so it drew attention and they stopped. Later I told the owner and she said she had already had some problems with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 07:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really liked the begining but the ending does sound kind of yandere. Maybe the voices made him kill himself and Emily was the one controling them or something like that. I don\`t know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 05:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My parents had this "rule" when i was little, around 7 or 9 that if i coudn\`t reach for the spider it was alowed to live there so I wached every spider in the house to se if they trespassed the imaginary line they told me. I was really afraid of them and the house was full of them so may parends kind of got tired of me teling them to kill a spider so offten.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 20:35:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, nice to meet you. The only way you\`re going to get even better at english is to practice and we are here to help. People shoudn\`t make fun of how  foreigners write because they have learnd something new and you shoudn\`t be ashamed of that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 20:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also want to have as many animals as posible but it shoud be obvious taht you have to have some kind of financial stability to be abel to take care of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 09:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. My bpyfriend dosnt liked trimming either so I used to help him with it (eventough it was scary)  so he gradualy got used to it.  Some coud think it was gross but I didnt think so at the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 09:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH I he has been treathing you like this your whole life someone shoud have noticed. You shoud speek to your parents to try and solve this situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 09:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  NTA I think that if you have a genuin interess in learnimg it shoudnt be considerd something bad. Maybe dont talk about it too openly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 07:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. If he wanted to have your childrens aproval and consider you rules he woud have proposed diferently and then you both coud have gone speek to your children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 05:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I'm not used to writing english. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 05:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But they coud not have like theyr lives after they had theyr child. Im not soure what happend. Maybe they considerd it buy then didnt want to go trough with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 04:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who knows. She made a video saying she was confussed when she posted that she wasnt going to vaccinate her child.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 04:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I belive in my country there are. They make campaigns and give out free vaccines for pets so you dont have a excuse not to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 04:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard that to, that vaccines coud make your pets have some kind of bad reaction but I hadnt heard of a case. Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 04:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its because of the routine. And fear of what youre gonna do one youre no longer with that person. But as time passes youre gonna realize it was the best. If not for bout at least for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 04:11:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think is because were seaking atenttion from wherever we can get it. 

Many of muy schoolmates have trobles at home or the parents blow out theyr frustations at theyr childern so the children have to carry along the responsability. i dont realy know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 04:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If hes saying thinks like that is trying to make yo feel bad. He soud understand that you meed time to yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do anti-vaxxers vax their pets? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 03:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do anti-vaxxers vax their pets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> tragus piercing? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 06:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do tragus piercing get in the way of using headphones?

I\`ve thought of getting one but y don\`t know how much it will hurt or if it\`s going to affect my life much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 05:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She  should tell you what she likes. Kind of explore together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>