<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4999</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-09 01:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Animals as Leaders, Periphery, Monuments, TesseracT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 13:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pincushion Protea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 22:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom is a nurse at a large hospital and her deductible is $3k. Which is ridiculous to me. 

Edit: forbidden word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 12:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "But why? This is the part that makes me question it.
If someone is truly poly, why will there be negative emotions?
If it causes this much anguish and unhappiness, then why is it a good thing?"

I've just tried to explain that the negative emotions are temporary when you're first opening up. Mostly because they're a byproduct of social conditioning and you're not used to facing them. That fades with time and experience. I'm not sure what else you wanted to hear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 17:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then what is it about? You mentioned being newly open. Typically, working through jealousy instead of drowning in it is a new skill that needs to be learned. 

I found that the process of opening up was much like going through therapy. Identifying what was hurting me, reframing it, and learning how to handle it better in the future. It's a process and doesn't happen over night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 14:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recommend lovehoney for toys. They have an awesome refund policy so if your toy breaks in the first year you can easily get a refund and get a new one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 06:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You won't be able to change him if he doesn't want to change himself. You're not wrong for wanting your partner to be interested in pleasing you. I do think you should reconsider your relationship with him over this. I say this as someone who was in your situation and stayed for 6 years- he never made an effort and I felt like I just wasn't communicating the right way.

If he isn't listening to your needs regarding sex, is he listening to you and taking care of your needs in other ways? Probably not. Really take some time to think about whether this is part of a pattern of him not listening to you or providing you what you need out. I know the thought of starting over is scary, but being with someone who is excited to engage in sex with you and makes you feel wanted is so worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 05:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually just once, maybe a second time after a recovery period. But during sex I usually cum several times with no recovery period needed, which is sooooooo preferred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 22:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.morethantwo.com/jealousy-insecurity.html

Unfamiliar things are uncomfortable, but that doesn't mean they're bad. Becoming secure is something that takes some folks more work than others, unfortunately. But there are resources available to help you during the transition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 06:06:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because monogamy is all most people have ever known. We're told our whole lives that it's wrong for our partner to want anyone else while they're with us. We're convinced that others can take our partner away from us. It's normal to feel incredibly jealous when those are our baseline assumptions.

It's possible to recognize logically that these things aren't true, but to still experience the emotions that they cause. But managing them is something that can be learned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 22:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's not stupid. She knows what's going on in the other room. You're still allowing this abusive, violent behavior to occur in your daughter's home. She is being exposed whether you try to run damage control or not. You have a responsibility to protect her from this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 05:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still have this album on repeat. So good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 00:57:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nipple play does nothing for me either. Silver lining, I can get them pierced and I won't risk losing anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 00:25:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you make this in an oasis bouquet holder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 21:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Red3E! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 18:12:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's true. If that's the case, that's a conversation that needs to be had </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 02:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should make sure you make it a broader conversation. "I understand that you're really tired right now, and that's okay, but this is a pattern and I'm feeling incredibly (insert your feelings) about it. We need to figure out why this is happening and work together to fix it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But 1. Is she actually asexual, or is she just not sexually attracted to him? And 2. If she changes the boundaries of their relationship and takes sex off the table, that affects him as a sexual person. Will he have the ability to seek sexual fulfillment outside the relationship? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Polyamory* only works when both parties consent and agree to the rules and boundaries involved. This is just cheating. Don't let her terminology confuse you. Proceed as if you discovered her infidelity in any other case because that's all this is. If it's a deal breaker for you, that's okay. I would be much less inclined to forgive her cheating and move forward with her given her reaction, though. She's trying to pin the blame on you instead of owning up to her actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 20:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mix my cactus soil 50/50 with perlite for more drainage. Even the cactus soil retains too much moisture sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 16:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not wrong, I agree. That's what I do with my partners.  But OP's partner wasn't communicating at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 14:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How was she supposed to communicate that to him if he didn't tell her what his problem was for 2-3 months before blowing up about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 14:27:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA, your boyfriend is insecure and a poor communicator. He didn't tell you what the deal was for months and then blew up at you over something that's incredibly normal. He gave you the silent treatment instead of having an actual conversation, and isn't listening to you now. You're not being insensitive, he's being ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 07:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you're not disgusted by the dishonesty, underhandedness, or flat out hate by Trump and his allies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 07:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard to say that when we don't know what "fucked up shit" this guy is facing 8 years for. Would you really want a rapist as your family? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 06:51:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Different people handle trauma in different ways. And different kinds of traumas elicit different responses. You have no way of knowing how you would've handled this if you were OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 00:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course it will be easier if she gets to benefit from the arrangement before facing the hard parts of overcoming jealousy. You both will have to face a lot of negative inner emotions throughout this transition. It hurts, but it's a necessary part of the process and is easier for some than others. If she really wants to explore being open, she shouldn't shut down your opportunity because she's feeling bad. She should work with you to identify those feelings and learn how to overcome them. Dealing with them will be largely her own task, but you two can work together to figure out how you can best reassure her throughout the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 20:44:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would fucking celebrate. I would celebrate the day of his death every year for the rest of my life. That man deserves nothing good in this world. Fuck him and fuck his entire family. My only wish is that I could make a scene at his funeral and tell everyone who he really is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 04:16:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a partner like this. He wasn't great to me, but this was what made me feel the worst for a long time. He would outright reject my cuddles and move away from me to the other side of the couch or bed. It made me feel so unloved. 

I explained to him that physical touch is my strongest love language. It's how I most like to receive affection. And one of the ways I show affection the most. He would cuddle with me when he felt like it, and that was nice, but when I really needed to feel secure and cared for he would push me away.

This is a basic incompatibility. I'm sure you guys could work around it, but unless you're head over heels for her and things are phenomenal in other ways, I don't think it would be worth it. You can find a partner who is not only willing to give you the cuddles and affirmation you need, but loves to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 02:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA, this is a responsible conversation to have before becoming sexually involved with someone. You should add questions about their recent sexual history and testing status. But your mistake is that this conversation should be had before sexy things are actually happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 17:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same same same! My only problem is that I rarely, if ever, reach a point where I'm fully satisfied. It's a blessing and a curse. I have some wonderful partners who are into it and really know what they're doing but even they can't keep up, unfortunately. It's a little ridiculous tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 05:07:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that trying to convince your friends that your partner was worthwhile was normal. My friends and family always saw that I put so much more effort into my relationships than my partners did. At best, they were indifferent about me and about everything. At worst, they said they cared about me but treated me poorly and talked shit about me when I wasn't there. I always defended them because I thought they had enough redeeming qualities that fighting for the relationship was worth my time. Protip: it wasn't. 

My partner now is super fucking amazing and I haven't had to convince anyone. They meet him and they know. And I never have to question it because he's amazing to me 100% of the time. It's the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 20:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually propagate or rescue to get new plants. I haven't purchased one in about a year. This broke my streak  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 19:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could be wrong, but I think it's a variegated aloe walmsley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 19:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cutting off the leaves with browing tips is a good idea! My window space gets loooots of direct sun, so I think this guy will do okay even with such little chlorophyll. Especially since the pups are much greener. Even my aloe vera can't handle the level of sun my space gets, but my cacti and succulents love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 19:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know how I can prevent more browning on the tips? I'm relatively sure this is an aloe variety and I have others, I just want to make sure this babe stays happy and healthy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found this variegated beauty for $5! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 19:28:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 19:50:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because my stepdad had gone to jail for molesting me and my family convinced me to withdraw my statement so the charges would be dropped. One teacher in particular was very upset because she thought I had ruined a poor man's reputation so she would pull me into the hallway to yell at me for no real reason, call me a liar in front of the classroom, and "lose" my homework </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone who knows this and insists that she's invited anyway should be disinvited themselves. This is simply unforgivable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 22:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the one I've always gone to! So beautiful, more chill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 16:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ginnie is a private spring that allows alcohol and can be really crowded and rowdy. There are state parks with spring asccess nearby that are a little cleaner with less drunk college kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 06:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aunty Anti is the cutest thing I've ever heard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 06:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On income over 10m. (In this hypothetical) They're already making 10 fucking million dollars a year. They aren't exactly struggling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 04:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To quote another comment here, your gf was described as "a multi-orgasmic, submissive sexual pleaser that likes rough, hard sex" and that describes me as well.

I love to satisfy my partners, and sometimes my partners are the dominant type that are incredibly pleased with having their way with me.  That typically means I don't have to do much in terms of planning the session, but that's because we both like the dynamic to work that way. They call the shots and I'm along for the ride.

It doesn't seem like you're happy taking on the dominant role full time. That's absolutely okay! But if she's used to always being in the submissive role, she's going to need more guidance to break out of it. You'll need to more clearly communicate what you'd like from her.

You can have that conversation outside of the bedroom and let her know that you'd like her to take charge and focus her active attention on you more frequently. Then, in the moment, you can ask her to change positions, or back off of her and pull her on top of you. Tell her you want your cock in her mouth and then lay back and let her take care of the rest.

Edit: p.s. blowjobs to completion are HARD. I have a light gag reflex and I still struggle. Is there anything you can do to make a bj to completion more achievable? Get close to a certain point with sex and then finish with a bj? Or alternating oral with hand strokes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 00:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why can't you push her back to her side? That's what my partner does when I start to take up his space. I scoot back to my side and fall back asleep. That's the reasonable approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 05:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm an alcoholic in recovery. Just over 450 days now. Unfortunately, I lost quite a few friendships when I dedicated myself to sobriety. There were just some people who couldn't handle my refusal to drink and tried to sabotage me at every turn. The small "Are you sure? It's so (fruity/unique/local/insert buzzword), you should just have a sip to taste it!" comments were the hardest to turn down without seeming unreasonable. I only hang out with people who don't use alcohol as a coping mechanism now and it's allowed me to develop much healthier relationships. Highly recommend that you avoid all scenarios that might include alcohol with these people, if not cutting them out entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 01:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Netflix cancelling Sense8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 23:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scissoring is one tribbing position, but tribbing includes stimulating the vulva on any other body part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 22:22:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tribadism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 19:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oral, manual stimulation, grinding, tribbing, using toys, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 22:13:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooooooof I had a guy call me by my full name when I cut him off. He had pushed my boundaries and made me uncomfortable. He initially apologized, but when I told him I didn't want to see him again, he kept contacting me frantically trying to change my mind. But mixed between messages where he was trying to justify his actions were things like "oh wow. Just wow. You won't even talk to me? Come on, (my real name). Give me a chance."

I don't use my full name on any dating platforms, Facebook, or any other social media. I suspect he checked my mail the one time I had him over. Honestly, that was the nail in the coffin. He's contacted me several times since then trying to apologize and make amends, but I haven't responded since I initially told him I was no longer interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 22:06:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went out for drinks with a guy from Bumble ages ago. He was 32 but his profile said 29 because "younger girls always put their upper limit at 30 " He bragged that he'd had so much wine before the date, and talked a lot about his investment properties and how much money he had. 

Unfortunately, against my better judgement, I let him join me back at my place. I tried to keep the mood light and keep talking and I sat on the floor to pet my cat, but shortly after we sat down he said "are you going to come here or not?" In a way that made me really nervous. I joined him on the couch and he got really physical with me really quickly, pulling at my clothes and grabbing me hard. We ended up in my room where he told me he wanted to fuck. I asked him if he had a condom and he said "I don't use those". I told him it wasn't negotiable, so he said "fine, whatever, we can just do other stuff then" laid me on my stomach, fingered me, and then climbed on me and tried to put his dick in me anyway.

I'm lucky that he actually got off of me when I pushed him back and told him to leave. He tried to lighten the mood by saying "poly girls are always the ones who insist on using condoms hahaha" So he obviously does this a lot... 

I haven't used Bumble since :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 18:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course! Yeah compromise is definitely easier when you have similar desires and preferences to start. I have "compromised" too much in the past, which was really just accepting whatever my partner wanted with no concern for my own needs. Unlearning that has been hard and is an ongoing process. I'm also not monogamous which is super helpful because I don't need any one of my partners to keep up with me lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 17:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't had that experience yet, but I was in long term relationships for years and wasn't able to orgasm with those partners at all. Since I learned to orgasm, the partners that I've had ongoing relationships with are happy to work with me one way or another.

My long term romantic partner has a lower libido, so I'll cum multiple times with him but sometimes he'll hold me and kiss me while I use toys to get off some more. My newer more casual partner is really into getting me off so I don't anticipate him getting tired of it lol. 

I prioritize open communication with my partners. I'm super happy to work with them and their preferences, and I expect the same courtesy in return. I don't want them to do things they won't enjoy (neither of my partners particularly enjoy giving oral, for example) but it's important that we can compromise and find activities that are satisfying for both of us.

Edited to add: I think that frustration comes from thinking that they have to be the one always making you orgasm, and that can be a difficult task. I communicate changes in positions with my partners and do my own manual stimulation to get myself off so that they can focus on enjoying themselves. And if I am left wanting more, I carry my toy with me and can use it for a quick fix lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 16:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My newest partner calls me his "sex soulmate" and this sounds like us lol. I'm also multiorgasmic and he's got a high libido like me. We have similar kinks and sexual interests. I haven't found my exhaustion point yet though 

Congratulations on finding such a great match!! It's so much fun and I find myself kinda zoning out and getting lost in it in the best way. I'm always so happy to hear that others experience the same thing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 22:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I clicked this expecting a fan make and I'm so pleasantly surprised!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 05:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awww that actually hurts my feelings a little lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 16:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like you care a lot about their body and choices they make lol. You seem to care a lot about other people's penises. Otherwise you wouldn't mind making a minor change to your language to show respect. The truth is it's not your business and you're being intentionally disrespectful. So yeah, people are going to give you shit. Unless you change your approach, don't expect that to change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 04:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Start informing them of your rate when they start unloading stuff on you unprompted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 03:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gender dysphoria is scientifically classified as a mental illness and the treatment is TO TRANSITION lmao. You can make comparisons to inanimate objects all you want but it just shows that you lack even the most basic understanding of gender identity.

Honestly who gives a fuck about someone's biological sex? Do you inspect people's genitals when you meet them to make sure you're not accidentally calling someone the "wrong" pronouns? Do you check people's birth certificates to make sue you're using their birth name? I bet you fucking don't. Because it's none of your business. You don't get to decide how people identify and what's "correct" for that person.

It comes down to basic human respect. If your full first name is Alexander and you prefer to go by "Alex", I'm going to use that name because it's your preference and I respect that. Or if you prefer to use another name entirely, I'll call you that instead! I'm not going to call you by your full name and say "but that's who you really are!!1!" because that's NOT MY CHOICE TO MAKE!" 

If being disrespectful to people is a part of your religion then yeah, your religion is going to get a lot of shit. There are a lot of religious communities that agree with respecting the agency of individuals and their identities. Even some Christian communities. They show respect and care even if they don't fully understand what transitioning means. They make attempts to use proper pronouns and vocabulary even if they don't always get it right. They deserve a mutual respect and myself and other members of the LGBT community are happy to show it. We might not all agree on everything, but you can totally have an amenable relationship with someone when you're not shitting all over their entire existence :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 02:56:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What? Calling a trans woman anything other than "her" because you refuse acknowledge her identity is absolutely disrespectful. It sounds like you don't understand transitioning. This teacher singled her out and addressed her in a way that other students in the classroom caught on to the discrepancy. He can keep his garbage beliefs, but if he can't treat students that are different from him with respect then he shouldn't be a teacher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:38:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dated a guy like this for 2 years! He wouldn't want to cuddle on the couch, he'd recoil away from me when I would touch him, he didn't offer me verbal support and was very critical of me. I felt like I was crazy, like I was always doing something wrong or like I was unattractive. It really hurt my self esteem for the duration of our relationship and for a while after. 

My partner now is the total opposite. He hugs and kisses me all the time! He's always telling me how much he loves and appreciates me and how grateful he is for me. He congratulates me on my accomplishments and helps me when I'm struggling.

I wouldn't even worry about why he acts this way. He may or may not be a good person, I don't know, but he's certainly not a good partner. He's especially not a good partner for you, given that you're feeling starved of affection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 22:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a dahlia, unsure what kind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 16:50:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely add compliments! And add lots of forehead kisses and hair stroking when you're cuddling. They're such small gestures but so intimate and loving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 02:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She needs to break up with him no matter what. She needs to talk to an adult about this as well, this guy is dangerous and needs to face consequences for this before he pulls the same stunt on someone else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 02:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loveeeee doting on my partners. So many little displays of affection. I'll kiss their heads, lay their heads on my chest and play with their hair, kiss their face, hug them from behind, buy them flowers. It's all I ever wanna do cause it takes so little effort but builds such intimacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 16:50:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your support of Trump shows your daughter that these behaviors are acceptable to you. Of course she's confused. The things she said in that note have the same tone as things that he has said about his opponents, reporters, journalists, etc. Why does that behavior disgust you when your daughter partakes but not when the President does it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 23:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because marriage is important to her and he doesn't seem interested, which is a basic issue of compatibility. Plus he threw something she's self conscious about in her face, which isn't something a good partner would do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 22:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this with my bf all the time!!! It's so sweet and intimate. It's an awesome compromise since my libido is freaking ridiculous and he's a fantastic cuddler :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 20:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He doesn't get to leave OP out of the conversation though. They share bills and have a child, he needs to be transparent about his finances with here because it's THEIR home and they're partners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 20:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. You say they bully your older son to tears and don't know why they chopse to argue?? Your younger children are bullying your older son and you're piling onto him as well. It sounds like he's trying to deescalate the situation by asking them to leave him alone, walking away, and trying to get your support to back him up. He's being the bigger person and you're not backing him up. His siblings won't change their behavior unless there are repercussions.  You need to start listening to what he's telling you and punish your younger children for their taunting and immature behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 16:37:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To add to the great advice you've already gotten here, I suggest using OKC as your platform. There's lots of room in your profile to outline what you're looking for and you can include that you're looking for nonmonogamous dating only. As a poly woman, I seek that out when I'm matching with people.  You'll have an easier time finding women who are already open to a nontraditional relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 17:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second putting on music and singing along. I had a period of time where I mostly stayed home and that really helped me when i was feeling lonely and isolated. Bonus points if you have a google home or something like it that you can tell to play music for you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 05:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's generally a wholesome human being. He's over a foot taller than me so there's lots of head kisses. We're both super affectionate so we touch each other a lot- always hugging or butt grabbing. He's the cutest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 18:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you get unloving from this? That's obviously incorrect based on OPs post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 18:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yikes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 21:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leaning back and rocking your hips like some other posters mentioned works for me.

My fav though is reverse cowgirl for this reason. Especially when he spreads his legs and I put mine under. I can lean forward and support myself easily and can alternate between rocking my hips and bouncing up and down depending on how much stamina I have. My fav about this though is that it's really easy to hold a vibrator in this position  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 21:41:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His staff can take the fuckin metro like the rest of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 06:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She mentioned a pattern of him getting bitchy with her when she asked him to cut down on his free time specifically because his contributions aren't equal. She provided two incidents to back up that claim. He might think that things are being divided equally, but that's because he isn't listening to her when she communicates to him that it isn't. Her husband should spend time on his health, but not at his wife's detriment. She deserves free time just as much as he does.

Plus she wasn't even asking him to skip the gym so she could have some personal time. She needed to sleep! She needs sleep to function. That's so obviously a priority compared to working out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 04:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But they're not getting equal free time. His free time is coming at her expense. She's the one getting up with the baby at night and he's not, so he needs to make up for that extra time that she's putting in first and foremost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 03:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Girl. Respect is the most basic thing that you should expect and demand from literally every person in your life. Much less the person you're dating. This is a jumbo sized red flag and worthy of an immediate breakup and block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 05:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you do tolerate the rudeness. You're correcting him, but he hasn't stopped doing it because he doesn't care. You said elsewhere that you want him to put in effort. I'm so, so sorry, but he just won't. He never will. He's entirely capable, as you can see in the way he treats the people around you. But for some reason he just won't. I've been in your shoes and you can beg and you can plead but nothing you do will make him respect you. That's a reflection of his character, not a reflection of you. He sees you as his property and doesn't think your needs are valid, but they are. Start separating yourself from him and stop keeping his life in order for him. You deserve so much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 20:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Honesty and open communication 2. Get new testing results between partners. That's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 20:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my experience, not really. But grinding is. Lining things up perfectly so that you can grind on each others thighs just the right way while making out and touching each other everywhere... yum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 00:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be sure that he keeps it on. Honestly, I wouldn't trust this guy to keep the condom on the whole time. If he slips it off you most likely won't be able to tell unless you're really paying close attention. And if that's something you have to worry about, you shouldn't be having sex with him in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 06:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a bad experience with Bumble and haven't used it in well over a year, so I really can't say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 05:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DC. Also a lot of professionals here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 06:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For reference, the next person I went on a date with was almost the same stature as the guy who lied. I would've swiped right either way. If you're lying about what you have to offer, you're missing out on quality matches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 06:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He straight up told me that he knew he gained a lot of weight since the photos on his profile. It was very thought out and planned, the newer photos were at sharp angles and harder to make out while the older ones were full body photos. It was set up to deceive in this instance at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 06:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My only Hinge success thus far! And if things continue to go well, the only one I'll need! I'm reaching my cap on partners  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 05:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 5'2", mid length brown hair, green eyes, 125lbs, big hips/thighs/ass and C cups. Not sure how tall he is, maybe 5'8"? Short brown hair and short beard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 05:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the time since this occurred he did lose his job :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anal on the second date~ (f) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 04:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 02:08:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 02:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right?? So looking forward to our fourth date  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anal on the second date~ (f) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 01:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've (25F) been pretty sexually frustrated lately. My libido is ridiculously high and I just haven't had a consistent outlet for it. I love my vibrator, but sometimes that just isn't enough... After a disappointing hookup last week, I went back to Hinge to try to set up another date.

I matched with someone who really caught my attention, and planned a date right away. Our first date was a nice brunch. Casual and relaxed. We walked around for a while after and just talked, getting to know each other a bit better. When we parted ways, we didn't even kiss. Just exchanged a quick hug and a "talk to you soon!"

For our second date, we hung out at his place. Netflix and chill. But when Netflix wasn't working, we made our way to his bedroom. Holy shit I wasn't expecting the sex to be so fucking good. It can take a little bit of time for me to get used to a new partner before I can cum, but not this time. He fingered me and made me cum before we even fucked, which is super fucking impressive for me. Luckily for me, once I get comfortable and cum once, I can keep going and going.

He fucked me missionary first and I wrapped my arms and legs around him and came over and over again. Next he bent me over and fucked me from behind. He laid me down and fucked me prone, reaching between my legs to take over rubbing my clit for me. I've never had someone else rub my clit for me during sex and managed to cum, I've always had to do it myself. To have that happen the first fuck is something else entirely. Holy shit.

After a water break and searching for some lube, I climbed on top and started working his cock into my ass. He's thicker than I'm used to, so it took a little more time to loosen up than usual. I rode him for a while before he flipped me over on my back, his cock still in my ass, and fucked me until he came.

Fuck. It was amazing. I've seen him again since then. I came over a dozen times again, just like the first time. No anal the second time, but hopefully third time's a charm ;) I need to make sure to use my plug first though.. Hands down, best first fuck of my life. I'm hoping it'll get better and better the more we see each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 15:09:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on the extent to which they're lying, I suppose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 04:26:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same happened to me recently. His photos were really, really old and he'd put on a significant amount of weight. He was also much shorter than his profile listed. I didn't really care about either of those things, but the deception rubbed me the wrong way. On top of the fact that he lived 30 minutes farther away than his profile listed, too. Big nope from me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 04:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lying about anything (age, height, appearance) before meeting up is a huge red flag and automatic no-go for me. Good for you for sticking to your guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 23:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're saying it's okay for the church to treat your sister as less than equal... because she's already seen as less than equal in the rest of society? Wow. What a shitty justification. You don't deserve your sister's time or attention. You clearly think poorly of her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 05:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What conditions do you keep yours in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 18:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His rollercoaster tshirt and the broken branch!!!!! Love the continuity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 01:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I keep my hair trimmed but never shaved completely. I haven't had razor burn in ages and I skip the worst of the hair growing back in. I use conditioner to provide a bit of glide on my skin and only shave with the grain. The shave is close and not perfect, but so much more comfortable. I use a salicylic acid pad after shaving and moisturize after a half hour or so. I've never had any complaints :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 23:09:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cut flowers from this tree are called Genestra filler. Might be helpful info in your search! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 16:28:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because a relationship is the best you've had doesn't mean it's good. She's manipulative and a poor communicator. The best thing you can do for yourself is block her and work on moving on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 07:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To make a long, long story short, a girl I worked with decided she felt like fucking with my life. This is the shortest possible version of all the shit she pulled:

She got flirty with me over time, and decided she wanted to fuck my boyfriend when I showed her his picture. This was discovered later. In the meantime...

She and I had a fling for about 4 months(which our partners knew about, open relationships). She promised me that she deeply cared about me and encouraged me to tell her about my issues with my boyfriend. She promised me a place to stay if my relationship ended. She asked to have a double date and hit on my boyfriend so hard at dinner that her husband had to tell her to cool it and that my boyfriend was off limits based on the terms of their open relationship. She started sleeping with my boyfriend that same weekend when I went out of town. She convinced my boyfriend to break up with me (wasn't hard, he was being shitty in other ways too).

She told me I couldn't stay with her after the breakup like she promised because she had family in town. She stayed at my apartment fucking him and told her husband that she was staying with me to support me through the breakup. She lied to me about sleeping with him and accused me of being crazy. She texted him asking him what excuses to make while I was asking her what she had done. She told several people at work that I sexually assaulted her after I showed her husband proof of the affair. Finally, she started wearing my ex's clothes to work all the time in some weird power play. She was 10 years older than my ex and I. 

I cut all everyone involved out of my life and I don't feel crazy anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 00:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Geez. Be careful that this controlling attitude doesn't start to work it's way into other parts of your relationship and life in general. This is a major red flag.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 05:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What stitch did you use for the stems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 04:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure this is the Arboretum in Northeast DC? It's a 202 phone number and everything . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 04:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of moss topping is that? It's so lush! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 03:56:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's Up by Four Non-Blondes, Sense8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 01:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 25 and I also went through a ridiculously abusive and harmful upbringing. I was able to stop my spiral but it took a total mental breakdown (like the 3rd I've had) for me to make changes. Things still aren't perfect but I'm on a slow upward trend in terms of getting my life together.

I started dating my partner over a year ago. I was in the depths of my alcoholism, my credit card was maxed out, and I was smoking a pack a day. I was getting blackout drunk at his place and crying a few times a week within our first 2 months together. He would hold me a hear me out. Some-fucking-how he saw through my poor coping skills and liked me a lot for who I was.

I would have ended up here without his support, but it may have taken a little longer, and it would have been harder. Today I'm over 400 days sober, paid off my credit cards (and then had a major car repair... so I'm starting over), and I quit smoking 8 months ago. I have a better job in a management position with more room for growth financially and professionally. I'm also 25lbs smaller because I quit drinking.

He always liked me for who I was. But now that I'm utilizing healthier coping skills (or at the very least, avoiding the really bad ones) I can be a better partner to him. His neverending support of me gives me an extra incentive to push through on days that are extra difficult. I know I have the skills to do these things on my own, but it's so validating to have someone around who has seen the changes firsthand and who has loved me through all of them. 

Being vulnerable is so scary, but I'm so glad I found someone who got to know me in that state. I feel like he has a more solid understanding of who I am and how my experiences have shaped me than he would if we'd met 3 months later.

This is all just my experience, but I hope it offers you some perspective, even if you come to a different conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 01:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is actually my partner's problem. Even I ignored his message at first because he was too hot. I get lots of messages so I must be right in the sweet spot lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 22:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in shitty relationships for a long time. Now I've been in a serious romantic relationship for a little over a year with a man who treats me sooooo well. I'm head over heels in love with him and we haven't had any relationship problems because we communicate so well. We're both depressed and it's hard, but we're both good at listening to each other and providing security and endless cuddles and forehead kisses.

In terms of my other relationships, though, it's been hard to find anything that sticks. I go on dates and things go...okay. But I don't have time for okay relationships. I just had a great first date with a girl that I feel really good about. We're looking for the same things and she's fantastic company and so freaking cute. So hopefully that'll be a lasting connection 

Depression is super tough and it makes maintaining my relationships really difficult. But I gain so much from them that it's the first thing I devote my limited energy to. I get love and affection and cuddles and my laundry doesn't get done for weeks at a time and that's ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 19:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check my sneaky edit, too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 19:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I enjoyed The Ethical Slut and the Multiamory podcast. More Than Two also has some helpful articles on their website

Edit: here's a multiamory episode on opening relationships
https://www.multiamory.com/podcast/118-helping-your-partner-open-up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 19:14:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's absolutely your business who she fucks and vice versa from a sexual health perspective. You two need to have an understanding in place regarding safer sex with partners outside your relationship. You need to be able to discuss exposure risks, testing statuses and results, slip-ups, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 05:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely salal, lemon leaf. I wonder if they chewed on the eucalyptus as well- I can see that causing really bad stomach problems because of the strong waxy coating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 18:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My personal experience,

I have oral HSV1 like most of the population. I get cold sores when I'm extremely stressed or really sick (usually once a year, but this year I've had 3 outbreaks) I avoid any oral contact with any of my partners from the first sign of an outbreak until a few days after it's gone away completely. Everyone else in our network is aware and totally okay with that.

As for genital HSV2, someone in our network has it and I'm totally okay with my partner playing with her because she's on antivirals and they would use protection 100%. Everyone isn't on board with that, though, so they don't engage in any play where exposure is a risk. No oral for her and no penetration. I think it's incredibly unfortunate as she's taking precautions and being proactive in communicating her status and reducing the risks. But I also understand the other side. HSV2 has so much more stigma and not everyone wants to open themselves to that risk at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 04:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They look a lot like mine!!  I'm 25F/5'2"/127 as well. They're sisters not twins! I do love how they look from the side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 02:43:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the bottom one?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 06:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The truth bomb is my go-to strategy. I start with "I don't drink" and if someone asks why, they learn right away that I respond to those kinds of personal questions extremely honestly. It always goes one of two ways: the person realizes that they asked something very sensitive and dial back, or they respect the honesty and are also open to having those kinds of honest conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 01:31:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me fucking too. I was involved in local politics for a while but it's so exhausting. I moved away and I live in a liberal metro area now. My day to day life is so much more peaceful. I love my home town and wish it wasn't a racist cesspool, but that's the reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Client's employee kissed me on the neck.. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 05:27:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For some context, I work for a woman who owns several different businesses. I run one of the retail stores day to day, but occasionally I run marketing events for one of the other businesses. Tonight I put on a marketing event and it was going really well. I was getting along with the building staff and the residents and they were responding really well to my pitches. 

One of the building staff members asked me about one of my tattoos when I went to refill the food, and we talked about the video game reference for a minute. He was talking to me quite a lot, even following me back to my table and sitting behind it with me. He kept making the conversation really personal (example: he offered me wine, I said that I don't drink and he asked if I'm an alcoholic, which I am) and I kept interrupting him to talk to customers.

As the event was ending and I was packing up, he was socializing with his coworkers and residents. I was packing up my supplies and kept passing by the group. He asked me to hug him several times, and kept touching my back and my shoulders. He even said, "don't stop hugging me or I'll be really uncomfortable" which I responded to by pulling away and coming up with an excuse to walk away. 

I tried to sneak away when I was leaving but he insisted on helping me to the car. I insisted that he not but he followed me anyway. Hew asked for my contact info and I told him I wasn't interested. He claimed that I misunderstood his intentions and he just thought I was cool and wanted to get to know me, he doesn't date people unless he knows them first. He kept insisting and I relented and said it was ok for him to give me his work number, since he claimed he was only interested in a professional relationship. After he gave me his number, I said goodbye (again) and he hugged me and kissed my neck before walking away. 

My boss is livid. I've been a victim of sexual assault many times in my life, of many different kinds. I'm struggling here (as I always have) to figure out if what happened to me is "a big deal" or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 04:42:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had purse whiskey! Seriously. I thought people wouldn't smell whiskey?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 21:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Focusing on literally anything for longer than 10 minutes. Unless it's a really compelling movie or album that I'm really digging, something related to one of my hobbies (even then not always), or something with a tight deadline, I just can't get through things. I have to set timers so that I'll work for a set amount of time before sitting down and resting. It's so frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 20:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lots of painkillers, living on a heating pad, lots of napping, all the snacks. But typically only on the first and maybe the second day in extreme cases. My period hits me like a freight train for one day and is extremely manageable afterwards. I went to the gym on my second day this time around and didn't experience any discomfort at all, so I know I'm lucky compared to others :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 19:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I could have written this about my partner, who is coincidentally also ridiculously tall (6'5" to my 5'2")

 Always happy to hear that other people have equally amazing relationships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 19:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's my tactic, too! "Are you seeing your boyfriend after work today?" "No, it's his other girlfriend's turn to spend the night!" It's a totally normal part of my life so I speak about it as such, and have gotten mostly positive receptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 18:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, I love all forms of physical affection. Hugs, kisses, cuddles. Physical touch is my top love language.

But my absolute favorite thing is my partner running their fingertips up and down my back. Soft, long strokes. It's very nostalgic for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-06 20:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, it's usually pretty easy for me to cum with my partner. But if I'm ever struggling, I can tell him I'm close and all he has to do is call me a good girl or tell me to cum and that's all I need to hear to push me over the edge lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 01:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a leatherleaf fern to me. Rumohra adiantiformis. One of the few I'm familiar with as a florist, though I could be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 00:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was dating my boyfriend at the time for 2 years. We became poly and he started dating a new girl. The new girl had a boyfriend of a year. The four of us got together and her boyfriend and I hit it off immediately. 

I stopped seeing my long term boyfriend shortly after, and he stopped seeing his long term girlfriend. It was really dramatic, actually. There was only about a 2 week window where things were stable enough that we could meet. But here we are over a year later, so grateful that we met. Our relationships with the people we were dating when we met were not great for different reasons, but we're so compatible and are crazy about each other. So it was all worth it in the end 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 00:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ask for them to show you their results. If they aren't mature enough to handle a conversation about testing, they aren't worth your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 21:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need to focus on keeping your back straight when you reach for your toes. Advice I've seen here that's been helpful is to imagine that you're trying to touch your stomach to your thighs. She's rounding her back a little bit but generally has better form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 23:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't even need to delete WhatsApp. Just block her on it. And on every other social media account you use that you know she also uses. Focus on keeping the blocks in place and continuing to use your social media accounts the way you enjoy, without worrying about seeing her activity. It's easier to let the anxiety pass when you won't come across this person's content on accident and there's an active step (unblocking) between you and them. Whatever you do, don't unblock her. Time will help you heal. Spend time with friends or time alone taking care of yourself. 

The anxiety that came from this person's erratic behaviors have likely been weighing on you for a while. At least it did in my anecdotal experience. It's so heavy at first, but as time passes without that anxiety being triggered, you'll have a clearer picture of how this person mistreated you. You'll feel better about moving forward and leaving this person in your past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 20:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lisianthus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 19:12:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you make the succulents in molds first and then place them on top of a loaf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 04:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, you would. I come from a broken home. My mom being away from her abusive husband would have been a dream come true, even if it meant we struggled even more than we already did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 16:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm telling you, it won't work. He doesn't clean because he doesn't care and it doesn't bother him. It'll bother you to your core and you'll just resent him in a dirty house instead of a clean one. 

I went through this same thing. It all came to a head when I cooked Fourth of July dinner for his entire family. I even did most of the dishes. Left one sink full for him to wash while I went out of town to see my family. 3 days and 20 hours of driving later, I come home to more dishes in the sink than when I left. The same grime on the counter tops. Flies buzzing around in this $3000/month apartment that he wanted but wouldn't care for. 

I broke. But I should've left long before. I'd been cleaning up after him for a year and no amount of begging or pleading or chore charting ever helped.

My partner now isn't great at cleaning. He keeps his place presentable but has a hard time keeping up. I end up doing a good amount of his dishes and sometimes do his laundry because I know it's overwhelming for him. But he is so grateful and expresses that to me, and tells me often that my cleaning is appreciated but not required.

The attitude change is so refreshing. On top of the fact that it's so much easier to keep my apartment clean since I'm only cleaning up after myself. I'm not doing 3x the laundry just for someone else to throw stuff all over the floor. 

Strongly consider if continuing to date someone who is content living in filth is something you're willing to put up with for the rest of your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 05:15:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would reconsider this. I'm poly and I've also been in an open relationship, and this would be a solid no-go for me. Asking to meet someone after a few dates, or before things progress physically I could understand. But having your first date chaperoned? Not cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 18:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "knowing about it" is kinda the whole point of polyamory. This is just cheating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 06:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On top of all the soaking suggestions that'll definitely fix the wilting, I'd suggest putting it back inside or at least making sure it's not getting too much direct sun. Keep in mind that the more light exposure, the more water it'll need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 18:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So glad you can relate!! I hope more people get to experience these feelies :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 16:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner is a lawyer, too! He has 3 degrees and no student loan debt, and his first job allows him to afford a place to himself in our HCOL area. He doesn't love his job but he's self sufficient, has a pretty great work life balance, and maintains a lot of meaningful relationships.

I've been working since I turned 15, grew up in an incredibly abusive household, couldn't get through college due to mental health issues, and because getting FAFSA documents from my mom was like pulling teeth. Historically, I've always been a bit of a mess. I was really confused (but excited) when he expressed interest in me, especially when he started referring to me as "his partner" after just one or two dates. My ex made 4x what I did and was always embarrassed of me, always talking down to me for not "trying harder" to succeed when he had a LOT of luck on his side. It was a sudden change of pace.

We struggled at first due to the actions of other people in our lives that we couldn't control. But once that passed, it still took me some time to trust that he really, truly wanted to be with me. He's incredibly attractive, educated, personable, thoughtful, I could go on and on. He's so supportive in a way I'd never experienced before. My mom is unreliable, my friends are messed up too, my ex was abusive. I always wanted to do more but never had the sense of stability that I do now.

Since my partner and I started seeing each other, I've gotten sober, I stopped smoking cigarettes, I paid off my credit card and tuition debt, and I got a better job with more growth opportunities and a lot of responsibility. I'm planning on going back to school in the spring because I found a program I really want to do, and my job will work with the schedule. 

He really likes me for me, for all of me. I post about him on Reddit all the damn time because I've never had a healthy romantic relationship before now and it's revolutionary for me. I've had very few healthy platonic relationships as well. Bring treated the way he treats me has changed the game in terms of my self confidence and self worth. 

Because of the structure of our relationship, I'm more independent as well. I know that I could have done those things on my own. But he provided me with a secure environment that made it so much easier. I'm so grateful for him :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 14:00:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like some other posters said, you don't "allow" them to do anything. If she's going to date someone else, they get a say in the relationship as well.

If you're really into the "letting him spoil her" part and really want to maintain strict rules, she should look for a sugar daddy instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 23:42:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ty for the source! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 23:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you elaborate on this? I don't pay any attention to Ben Shapiro but I have the same name and don't label myself as Jewish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 23:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But they LOVE Israel. Wouldn't want people to think they're anti-Semitic. Apparently that's what they don't like about the four congresswomen... Apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 23:22:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also a Feinberg. Weird read for me, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 22:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saying you'd prefer for her to be straight is homophobic!!! Jesus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 22:25:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything your daughter was partaking in was consensual. She wasn't breaking any rules in your household because she's allowed to be sexually active there. You give no reason why what she did was wrong other than "I think it's icky". You're an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 01:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have a friend schedule for them to be out of the house while you do that. Don't see them. It won't be good for your mental health, and they're just going to try to manipulate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 18:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm fully Poly but was open for an extended period. If she's the one pushing for this and it goes against the original framework that your relationship is based on, then starting out with rules doesn't go against the whole idea. The rules exist to provide you with structure and solid expectations during the transition from exclusive to open. Once you guys have been open for a while, and you find yourself more comfortable with the dynamic, then you can reassess later on and change the rules to match that.

She's allowed to have ideas about what she wants the dynamic to look like. But don't blindly agree to those if you're uncomfortable. You two need to find compromise and middle ground or things won't work out long term. She needs to be willing to take things extremely slow to accommodate you. She needs to be willing to provide you with extra care and affection, or whatever your love language is, to reaffirm her commitment to your relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 02:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An open relationship should only be considered a next step in an otherwise stable, healthy relationship. Not a means to fix a broken one. Not that it couldn't work for you guys, but you need to get to a point where you are happy with your sex life before it can even be considered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 02:18:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really is  he pets me and kisses my head and calls me a good girl when I cum. I always thank him after. He's the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 00:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner and I have sex every week or so. Sometimes more, sometimes less. I have a really high sex drive and his tends to be pretty low, or at least takes some convincing. We compromise by having regular sessions where I use a toy and he holds me. He doesn't have to do much, but I can direct my feelings towards him and his touch and his presence makes the whole experience really enjoyable. 

He's so accommodating. He's so humble about it, too. At this point, I'm so into him that I pretty much start cumming as soon as he penetrates me and don't stop until he cums, too. It's pretty amazing.

I also had a partner whose sex drive matched mine and we would meet up weekly for a few hours. That definitely helped me keep my libido in check. But he ghosted me and I'm too tired to put effort into finding another partner whose sex drive matches mine. So the toy cuddle sessions will continue lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 00:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 25F with lots and lots of FFM experience. With myself as part of the couple and as the third. Read most of the comments and haven't seen this mentioned yet. Your partner may have some performance anxiety and it can be frustrating but totally normal. Talk about what things you want to try if penetration isn't possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 05:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5'2, my boyfriend is 6'5. We've figured out how to make it work. I'm really good at balancing on my toes now. He kisses my head and pets me a lot. I hug him tight and kiss his chest all the time. I extend my arms aaaaall three way up and play with his hair when we hug. I always stand one step higher on escalators and it's the only time we're face to face, so we always kiss and hold each other on the ride up. I'm sure people on metro think we're gross. Friends always comment on how cute we are lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 05:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My experience with the court process is from when I was 10 years old. My mom's husband had been abusing me for 2 years. The first time they questioned me, I spoke to an officer alone. But my mom was present for the first physical exam they did, where they projected my genitals on a screen while they inspected me for tears. She was present for most of my testimonies moving forward, and I was rarely able to speak freely.

After 2 years, my mom convinced me to lie to the courts. Tell them I made it all up. It was easier for her to handle than following through with the rest of the process. She said he would live with his parents and financially support us, but I wouldn't ever have to see him again. In reality, he moved back in with us and I lived with him until I was 18. 

I requested the court records a few years later. I blocked out so many memories from that time. He wrote a confession. He was facing life. I could've put him away. I was so close. For 6 more years he abused me, just in new ways. Here I am now, still dealing with where that left me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 03:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Walk around our middle class neighborhood unsupervised. I didn't have friends :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 21:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought my partner was out of my league when we met. We had even matched on OkCupid four months prior and I never responded because I thought he was too hot and maybe a catfish. When we started seeing each other, he started calling me his partner in conversation after like two dates and it started to stick that he really actually liked me. 

Since then he's been a constant source of support for me. My response has been to recognize that and take the opportunity to improve myself. I've gotten sober, quit smoking, got a better job, have plans to go back to school. I treat him well in return and always communicate how grateful I am that he's in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 16:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could also see if there are SMART recovery meetings in your area. They're secular and the exercises that they provide on their website were helpful reading material for me when I was struggling a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 04:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in DC and walk/metro to and from work every day. I wear sunscreen every day except around my eyes (I use spray and it hurts when I sweat lol). I apply in the morning and before I leave work to go home. I also wear a sun hat every day! I have breakouts on my face that I'm working on but the rest of my skin is really nice and healthy and I don't really have tan lines despite being in the sun for extended periods of time every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 18:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boss owns a 130k Tesla and I get to drive it around for work errands. So fancy. So nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 18:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just realized I was doing the same thing!! When I was in high school my mom always bought me size 8 shoes because she was a size 8. For years I always bought myself size 7.5 shoes because I recognized that the ones I'd been wearing were a little too big.

But recently I tried on a pair of 6.5 because they were on clearance and OMG. No more flopping off the back of my foot! No more shifting! Turns out my toes are calloused from flexing my them to keep my shoes on my feet. But now they're perfectly snug in my shoes and it feels amaaaaazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-28 23:05:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in a financially abusive situation with a partner who made roughly 9k per month while I made a little less than you make. We lived to his standard of living and it bled me dry. I was never in credit card debt before we moved in together, but I was for a while after we broke up.

Honestly, what I learned from that was that my partner thought his time was more valuable than mine. I mean, he makes more money so that makes sense right? But it's not right. Anyone who gives a damn about you won't let you struggle to make ends meet while they have thousands of dollars left over to play with every month. Your bills should be split so that you work an equal amount of hours to pay them, meaning he should pay 3.5x what you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-28 04:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a florist. Aside from the issues that everyone else has brought up regarding you putting your mother's desires above your fiancee's, unless your wedding is in a week or less, you can change your flower order. Just because your mom placed the order doesn't mean that it's set in stone. People change their wedding flower order all the time and as long as you do it as soon as possible, the shop should be accommodating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 18:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This concept is a big part of the reason why I prefer to date poly people in my solo dating. Not that monogamous people or those in open relationships are incapable of that level of empathy. But I need the freedom to be able to build a connection knowing that it won't be affected negatively by another relationship out of my control. This isn't always realistic, but so long as there's an attempt to establish independent connections, I'm happy to work out the details individually.

In my experience from the couple side of things, we've tried really hard to accommodate potential partners. Matches often ask us what we're looking for, and that's so hard to answer. We're just looking for genuine people and taking things from there. We encourage the people we match with to figure out what their boundaries and comfort level in a group dynamic would be and we start from there. In some cases, they've asked to connect with one of us first and to meet the other after some time has passed. In some cases, we both go on independent dates with someone before we all get together. If we weren't attempting to provide what works for them, knowing we have the inherent privilege of an established relationship, we wouldn't be benefiting them at all. And benefiting everyone should be the whole damn point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 17:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree! I make it a point, to some potential partners discomfort, to talk openly about my history of abuse and addiction on the first or second date. I'm sober with some experience with healthy relationships now, but the things I've been through provide important context for who I am and what I need from a partner. I could easily wait until later on to share those things, but they've been such a big part of my life that inform the way I think and the behaviors I'm willing to accept.

 It makes the most sense to tell someone those things up front. I can tell a lot about someone by the way they respond to that conversation. Relationships are built on trust and honesty and I find that I'm comfortable giving that from the first moment. Even if I don't continue seeing that person, we always end up having genuine conversation and I'm grateful for the brief connection even if we aren't compatible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 02:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I relate to this so much from both sides. My partner and I are poly and almost completely date separately. We made a couple's profile on Tinder that he manages with the mindset that it would be really cool to meet someone that's into both of us, but we don't want to push someone that isn't into one of us. Our profile makes it clear that we aren't a package deal and sometimes people will ask to chat with one of us, which is totally okay. We've gone on quite a few group dates and had one go really well where all of us were into each other, and other scenarios where one of us continued to connect with that person. We're flexible because that's the only way to make sure you're not taking advantage of people or making them uncomfortable.

I have one couple that I still travel to see (when I can, rarely) that I hit it off with back when my ex and I were swinging. Part of why I like them so much is that our relationships were separate. They each went on dates with me independently and together, and we played independently and together. I never felt like I was forced to see both of them to keep things going, I could have chosen to only see one of them at any time. That's not something I've found with a local couple since I moved, though admittedly I haven't tried very hard because I have little patience for the kind of BS you've been dealing with.

Relationship dynamics are complicated. Adding a third person just exacerbates that. I've always gone into group scenarios (and all relationships, I suppose) with the idea that I want to figure out what dynamic works best for those involved, rather than finding a person to shove into an idea I've created. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 03:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play stupid games win stupid prizes. Alex made a choice that caused a lot of pain for Kate and your friend group. I'm probably biased because I was in a similar position as Kate, but the best thing you could do for her is to uninvite Alex completely. He made a choice that has consequences and Kate shouldn't have to suffer to be part of your wedding because of it. Even if the affair partner isn't there, Kate will not be comfortable being around Alex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 04:13:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My best friend and I first became friends when I told her that her boyfriend was cheating on her. I knew because the other girl had been my friend and talked openly to me about it. We were in high school and did extracurriculars together so it was rough for a while and I personally got a lot of backlash, but it was well worth it. I couldn't sit back and allow someone to be misled like that. Kudos to the neighbor and fuck cheaters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 23:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've done this both ways.

With my ex, we were platonic friends for a year before we started dating. I believe that's the reason why I let him get away with treating me so horribly when we did start dating. I'd known him for long enough that I thought he was a really fantastic person who was making poor decisions, but he was really just an awful partner. We should have stayed friends but once I crossed that bridge I became attached and made excuses for him because I had thought so highly of him when we were friends.

But with my current partner, we meet through friends and went on our first date and hooked up the first day we met. I maybe shouldn't have trusted my gut because I've made so many poor choices of partners, but I just had a really good feeling about him. He's amazing and I'm so glad that I jumped in feet first. I fully trusted him from the beginning and it paid off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 05:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just tried it tonight!!! The outter roll is a soft mild cake and the inner filling is thicker than I thought it'd be, similar to mousse in thickness. It tasted a bit like sweet potato, all in all it wasn't particularly sweet. I had no real expectations going in but it was still less sweet than I anticipated. Texture and flavor were on point though. Would try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 03:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was a teenager, didn't shoplift. Just took extra food from the lunch line cause I was poor (and on free lunch in the first place). But I always felt horrible about it and never stole anything else. Lots of people at my first job at a grocery store thought that stealing from their employer was a totally normal, okay thing to do. They usually didn't keep their jobs for very long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-17 04:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dated someone for 6 years and we were not compatible and both had so many issues. I tried as hard as I could to fix things, but I couldn't fix both of us and our relationship on our own. I was far from perfect and often treated him poorly, but spent a long time in therapy trying to deal with my trauma and be a better person and partner. My attempts to convince him to seek help weren't great for either of us and eventually I left him.


My next relationship was 2 years long and he was terrible to me. Cheated on me, didn't want to commit, spoke down to and about me. But he was also charming and passionate so much of the time that he kept me roped in even when he treated me poorly, and when things fell apart because he didn't want me anymore, I blamed myself and tried to do anything I could to fix it. We were always sexually experimental or open but became poly towards the end and I spent so much time learning how to communicate effectively, how to navigate jealousy, how to be a better partner. But nothing I did mattered because he didn't reciprocate those things.


I met my current partner and started seeing him about 2 months before my ex broke up with me and kicked me out. In those 2 months, I felt what it was like to be treated well by a partner. To be treated kindly and with respect. To be listened to and cared for. To be supported. Ultimately, feeling those things without strings attached for the first time helped me cope and recognize that I had been beaten down emotionally for a long time.


He let me stay with him while I found a place to live two months in to our relationship. It was a risk, and I was a mess. I'd go to his place drunk and breaking down and he would hold me and listen to me rant. I never felt judged even when I was struggling the most. I put myself back together more quickly with his care and support than I would have otherwise. 

I was severely abused when I was younger and all I ever dreamed of as a little girl was someone loving me and giving me affection without hurting me. This is the first relationship I've had where I can say I have that. He cares for me in that way I always dreamed of and I'm so happy to give him all of my love and care in return. He's an exceptional human being and I'm the partner I want to be when I'm with him. I'm not seeing anyone else right now, though I've been actively going on dates, because knowing what a relationship can be like has raised my standards. I'm not settling for "okay" relationships anymore. Not even "good" ones, really. Because I know what a great one is like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 18:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slightly different circumstances, I did qualify for aid but getting the tax paperwork from my mom was like pulling teeth. I was only able to attend school some years because I wasn't always able to acquire her W2s and such on my own. So I'm done with 2 years of school with no debt but am only now able to go back and finish my degree because I'm past the age 24 cutoff for parental support on your FAFSA. 

I've heard a lot of stories like yours, however. I've worked full time and gone to school full time before. I'm about to do it again for two straight years while taking out loans if needed so I can just finish my degree because I've gotten so tired of waiting. But most of my friends have already graduated because their parents were so supportive, if not financially, then at least emotionally and logistically. It sucks how far behind the lack of support can put you, but you're not alone. I wish you the best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 23:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cervix is also tilted. I haven't had any issues with leaking but I found the diva cup was too uncomfortable to put in. I did research and used it exclusively for months before giving up on it. In your experience, is the blossom easier to insert? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 22:59:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't been able to use my cup consistently because it's so uncomfortable to put in. I would love to take advantage of the environmental and health benefits but I just can't get over that initial discomfort- even after exclusively using the cup for months. I don't feel it when it's in and I haven't had any leakage problems. Do you have any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-12 05:03:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, it can be applied to literally anything. But people aren't perfect and that doesn't mean that people will always reach the right conclusions, even with the best of intentions. Or that there's ever really a consensus on what the "right" belief ultimately is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-12 04:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men are largely the ones who benefit from those beliefs, though. That's the key difference here. Women are expected to be modest, maternal, and mild mannered. They're expected to cater to the needs of the men in their lives. Many women reject those beliefs entirely and blame all men for the difficulties and pressure that result from a larger societal structure that not all men contribute to. That's a real problem. But it's a reaction. 

It's hard for a woman to work to change their relationship with men in a positive way when they're interacting with men who literally do not believe that women are equal to them.

I'm of the belief that everyone needs to be better. But the bulk of the work needs to come from men, at least at first, because of the nature of the power dynamics involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 23:39:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right that most men don't choose to be brought up holding these beliefs. But men are capable of using reflection and introspection to rewrite their beliefs regarding women. Many never do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 06:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish it hadn't been necessary, like I wish it wasn't necessary for you. We didn't choose this. But we have to do what's best for ourselves because we deserve better. You're brave, too. Taking about this is so difficult. You posted here for support and that's not easy! I'm so proud of you, truly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 04:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Give it more water. Water it thoroughly until it drains from the bottom and let it drain completely. Once it perks back up, give it 2 to 3 cups of water every other day or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 04:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I told someone. Things got a little tougher for a while when I did, but ultimately, I'm so glad I did. I wish you so much luck. I lived with my abuser for years even after I said something and it hurt me for a long time. But just know that a time will come when you can choose to never see this person again and it will help your healing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-11 02:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stay at my partner's place frequently and we don't do the sheets changing thing, primarily because nothing dirty happens in bed. But we always have a clean spare blanket to throw on the couch lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-10 21:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm about where you were in January, this is so motivational! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 21:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm definitely an odd one out, here. The only rules my partner and I have are 1. Discuss new sexual partners before risky sexual contact (unprotected oral, protected sex) 2. Exchange test results with the new partner before sexual contact and 3. Make sure new partner is willing to adhere to those rules moving forward. 

We're flexible about compromising with new partners as long as safety is still being prioritized and communication is good.

Between ourselves, we don't have any rules, really. But we always speak kindly to one another and always communicate when any kind of difficulty comes up (jealousy, anxiety, etc.) Even if that just means saying "I'm anxious right now but don't know why and don't know what to do about it".

I go grocery shopping and cook for both of us, he pays for most of the groceries. I fold the laundry and do the dishes pretty often just because I know he doesn't like to. He covers me when we eat out pretty often because he knows I'm trying to save money. We take turns making coffee in the morning based on our schedules and we take turns making breakfast on the weekends. We just always try to be good to one another and I think we do a great job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 17:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have on succulents because that's where I've experienced the most trouble, but be warned that if your succulent has a coating the spray will take it off and it will be left looking splotchy! But that's better than bugs :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 16:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had luck getting rid of pests by spraying 1/2 water 1/2 rubbing alcohol on the leaves after manually cleaning them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 02:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are lots of guys that like to Dom bratty subs. And as a brat myself, I'm super respectful of my partners and prioritize their pleasure and satisfaction. I think you may be confused, here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 02:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also a brat and thankful for this. Very helpful for when I try to explain it to my next partner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 15:53:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner and I had our first threesome together! I'm rather experienced with group sex but he's only had one threesome before this and it wasn't a good experience for him, so I'm so happy that this one was an overwhelming success. We're definitely going to be seeing her again when she's back in town. 

I didn't cum when the three of us were together (I was distracted lol) so after she left, my partner helped me get off by using a dildo on me while I used a vibrator. It was so intimate and sweet, he held me and looked me in the eyes and I came so hard that I started bawling. We cuddled so closely for like an hour after and it was just such a great time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 04:18:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awe I got so excited about this possibility before your comment! There's a 15inch height difference between me and my guy but I'm willing to try it anyway lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-02 04:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably the opposite of what you're looking for, but I'm in a long term committed poly relationship with someone I have a strong emotional connection with and who I hope to be a life partner. We have no intention of making our relationship exclusive at any point in the future and our conversations about life plans and goals have included the planned uncertainty that other future partners would bring to the table. 

There's always the possibility that we might change our minds, but I really don't think that's realistic in our case. We're crazy about each other but really value our Independence and our ability to have other relationships. The most important thing is that we always make time for each other. We consult each other about big decisions because we value each other, but not because we require permission. I feel more stable and secure in this poly dynamic than I ever did in a monogamous relationship, but that's 100% a reflection of my partner and not a result of the style of our relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-02 04:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To challenge your analogy,

She isn't asking him to eat pizza more than he would like to. She's asking him to spend time at the dinner table with her while she eats her pizza. This is a totally reasonable compromise when one partner wants way more pizza than the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-02 04:06:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner and I do this all the time. I generally have a very high libido and never say no when he's in the mood, while his libido is much lower and tends to be reactive. I haven't quite gotten over my dear of rejection enough to initiate more frequently, but I'm comfortable asking him if he's okay with me using the vibrator before bed and he never says no. But he knows that it helps me get by and that all I need is some cuddles and kisses. He's sometimes willing to be just a little  friskier for my sake and will smack my ass or choke me lightly but that's entirely up to him and it's just a bonus lol.

Have you made it absolutely clear to your husband that you don't expect these sessions to lead to sex? That they aren't meant to pressure him? He might feel content knowing that all you really want is his company. This is worth a sit-down conversation where you let him know that you're absolutely happy with the current frequency and quality of sex and that you don't expect him to keep up with your libido. But that there's some room to meet in the middle.

I personally make it a point to keep my sessions short and thank my partner after I finish. I always tell him I appreciate him and his involvement, even if it feels minor and insignificant to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-30 19:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Consider getting a quality vibrator and practice kegels. Find some porn or erotica that you really enjoy to get yourself in the right mindset. I couldn't cum for many years and, after months of practice, learned to with the vibrator. I worked my way up to being able to cum by doing kegels on a dildo and rubbing my clit. Penetration used to do nothing for me on it's own, but now that I've spent a lot of time practicing I have more control over the tightness and have figured out a rhythm that works for me with and without a partner. Using the vibrator is easier but I don't use it every time, and I still cum pretty much every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 19:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I considered breaking up with my partner. We're poly and met because my long term boyfriend started dating his long term girlfriend. When things with my boyfriend at the time imploded, having a connection back to him and his new girlfriend (who effectively replaced me) was incredibly painful. So it was never about anything my partner did, just how he was connected to the situation.

He had been so kind and considerate to me and I was really struggling with my decision. He reached out to my best friend, who he had never met, just to make sure I was safe and doing okay. But he never pressured me to talk to him when I needed space and he offered whatever support I needed at the time. He had seen me at the worst of my alcoholism and never judged me, he had supported me in getting sober, he was always so thoughtful in a way that I had never experienced before. Ultimately, I decided that having him in my life was worth the discomfort of being connected to my ex. 

Luckily for me, he broke up with his girlfriend shortly after anyway. It's been almost a year since then and he's absolutely amazing in every way. I'm crazy about him and I'm thankful for him every day. We just celebrated our year anniversary and I'm so looking forward to the future with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 22:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner and I do this a lot, too! Sometimes his libido is really low so we masturbate next to each other to get things started, sometimes it leads to sex and sometimes it doesn't. Either way, I think he's so hot and I'm into just watching if that's all we end up doing. Even when we're having sex more frequently, it's sometimes not enough for me. So, pretty often, I'll take the vibrator to bed and use it while he holds me and kisses me. I'll thank him after and he always says he didn't do anything, but being able to masturbate while having contact with him is such a different experience than doing it alone. We also treat it like a process that serves a purpose, I just have a higher sex drive and we compromise to make it work. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 04:57:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriend also doesn't give oral, and he's very accommodating to make up for it. I use a vibrator to warm up and we're handsy in other ways, he's happy to finger me and we have other dildos and plugs we use on occasion, too. 


Our situation is unique because we aren't monogamous, so I do still receive oral from other partners. But not very often at this point in time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 19:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been in this situation. Unfortunately, your partner seems to asking you to change your behavior with your other partners and prioritize them. That isn't something I was willing to do, I'll gladly provide reassurance and do what I can within reason to meet their needs, but I refuse to have someone dictate or criticize how I spend time with my other partners.

In my case, this person wanted to be a primary and wanted to feel superior to my other partners in order to feel secure, and I couldn't provide that. They kept score of everything and refused to work on their insecurity. Ultimately we were incompatible because I wasn't willing to make them my #1, which was what they were really asking. 

It sounds like this is what your partner is asking, too. They're okay with poly as long as they feel they're a priority and don't feel threatened by your other relationships. In my experience, no amount of reassurance was enough as long as I was spending a similar amount of time with another partner. Maybe this isn't the case for you, but your post reads much like what I might have written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 01:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner and I had been dating for a few months (like 3 or 4), and we were only about a month out from some god awful relationship drama. We're poly and went through a really rough time with both of our exes. I'd wanted to tell him for a while, but I didn't feel the time was right until a few weeks after things calmed down for us. I'm not good at holding things in, and not knowing how he would respond made me really anxious. So I sent him a long rambling text asking how he felt about exchanging "I love yous", and if he felt like that was something he wanted for us.

I was stressed TF out because I felt so strongly and I was worried that he'd want to keep things more casual after our long term relationships ended. But he responded by saying that he had been planning on telling me he loved me that same day. So we hung out that evening and everything went as usual, neither of us mentioned our text conversation from earlier in the day. But after chilling together on the couch for a while, he kissed me and told me he loved me first. Even though I knew it was coming, I still felt relieved when he said it. Our one year anniversary is in about a week :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 02:47:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You probably wouldn't qualify for any financial aid because your eligibility will be based on your parent's income until you're 24. 

Coming from a 25 year old whose parents couldn't afford to provide what you have, stick with it and finish your degree. Save whatever extra money you can so that you have an emergency fund if something happens and you need some time to figure out how to support yourself. Make the most of office hours and extra curriculars relevant to your degree. Get as much as you can out of your college experience, because you have the time for those things that someone working full time can't manage. 

Also consider that your parents don't have to know every detail of your life. I don't want to condone actively lying, but as long as you're being responsible and taking advantage of the opportunity they're providing you, you can easily withhold information from them if it's something you know they won't like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 01:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friends and I would pass notes when I was in high school, and I came home once to my mother absolutely fuming about something she read in one of my notes. One that I'd torn into 100 pieces and hidden in the bottom of the trash can. All I learned was that I needed to throw them away before I got home, and I still never confided in her about anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 00:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here, pretty much. I'll tell my partner I'm about to come and he calls me a good girl. It's so sexy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 19:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, sadly that's often the case. I got stuck in a loop with an ex who kept offering and then refusing to go to therapy for too long. It's definitely something OP needs to consider heavily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 17:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Part of making sure the progress continues should be holding him to his offer to go to therapy. His final conclusion that this is his problem and not a reflection of you is correct, and he should be focusing on that with his therapist. Any indication that he wants to go back on that offer should be a major red flag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-17 22:31:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Add a plunger to your toiletry list! Don't wait until you need one to buy one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 22:32:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had so many day 1s. I would drink at home, too. From the time I got home from work until I passed out.

I started out by doing little things in the evening every evening. I'd grocery shop, cook dinner. Pick a movie on netflix or a show and binge it. Make plans with a friend, even if it was just hanging out at home. I'd do my laundry, wash my sheets, clean my apartment. Listen to music or podcasts. I downloaded an emulator on my laptop and played super Nintendo games.

I'm still not good at being bored. But I'm better at it, and it's easier to be sober now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 00:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm poly, and my partner and I matched on okcupid before meeting in person by chance. He didn't get a response on the app simply because there were too many people to weed through and too many messages to respond to. And honestly, I thought he was a catfish because he's soooo attractive. 

For us women, there are too many matches for sure. I refuse to date monogamous people and there's still too many matches. Your SO should really up his dating app game, though, since nonmonogamous guys tend to have the opposite problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 23:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Life is not safe for women BECAUSE of the patriarchy. The creepy men who women need help defending themselves against often don't respect a woman enough to take her "no" at face value. But a "no" from another man is enough to make them back off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 23:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That can be avoided if you dont try to take advantage of the situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 06:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like monogamy isn't for me, so I'm openly poly. Feel free to message me if you have any questions about what that looks like for me, but I'm obviously not an unbiased source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 07:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chocolate/candy/fruit basket things are absolutely sent through the regular mail when you order from corporate websites. Same with flowers from 1800flowers and such. If it isn't a delivery from a local shop (which Sheri's Berries isn't) it's UPS or USPS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 06:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA, but only a little, leaning towards NAH.

I'm a florist and I have to deal with people trying to send "surprise" deliveries every day. Senders don't want to give us the recipient's contact information because it'll "ruin the surprise". What really ruins the surprise is when this kind of shit happens. Honestly, your husband is the one who dropped the ball here. It was a sweet gesture, but he should have communicated with you or with someone at the school (or Sheri's Berries, depending on how they deliver) to ensure you received the delivery. 

You were the asshole for being rude to the secretary. "I love when someone's solution to a problem they made for you involves more work on your end". Put yourself in her shoes and repeat that exact phrase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 19:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's definitely delphinium, though I dont know the variety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 23:36:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 40% of 70k is a lot of money to work with outside of expenses. What else does your money go to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 06:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not fair at all. It's morally reprehensible that this kind of thing is expected of people. There's no reliable safety net for people in her shoes. I'd respect her just the same if she wasn't doing it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 06:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand that completely. I don't think the idea is that more people should be in her situation, rather that she should be commended for her perserverance and resolve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 05:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not the healthiest, but it's temporary, and it might be her only option for supporting her family long term </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 23:06:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're making the assumption that he's single because that's what he's projecting! It's reasonable for a woman on a dating app to assume that a man is single if his profile doesn't mention otherwise. Or if he doesn't directly mention otherwise. He's being disingenuous and lying by omission when he asks these women out without clarifying that. 

Those of us who practice poly are the minority. None of these women are going to ask "hey, would you happen to be in a serious relationship with a partner who's totally okay with you going on a date with me?" And it's entirely unreasonable for him to put that responsibility on them. Their assumptions aren't flawed, his logic is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 05:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wanting "privacy" is an excuse. He wants to be able to break the rules you agree upon and go behind your back with no consequences. At the very least, he shouldn't be able to see anyone outside of the relationship at all until you are allowed the same right. If he can't handle it, everything closes until he can. He has no incentive to work on his jealousy issues because he can do what he wants, and you're sitting around waiting for him to give you an inch while he takes a mile.

You can't be ethically nonmonogamous with a liar. He's incapable of the "ethical" part. I know from experience. I tried for over 2 years myself. I was crazy about him, and he made me crazy with his back and forth. He agreed to rules and would break them constantly, came up with excuses, agreed to be better, nothing ever changed. You feel like you've gotten nowhere because you've gotten nowhere. And you never will. He won't let you. Ditch him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 05:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always urge nonmonogamous people to stay the hell away from closed marriages. You have the freedom to see people outside of your marriage openly, you have options. You don't have to lie and cheat to explore connections and get laid. So don't. It doesn't seem like you're too bothered by that, though.

However, do consider that this could hurt your working relationship. You'll continue to work and travel together after this I imagine. You can't be 100% certain that her husband won't find out. If he finds out it's random guys shes sleeping with at conferences, that's one thing. But if he finds out about you two, your job could be on the line.

I started seeing a coworker when I was open(I'm poly now). Her husband knew and was on board, and we had dinner together often. But then she started sleeping with my partner, who her husband had vetoed prior to the affair starting. It was a shit show. So so so so not worth it.

Go for it with friend B though. 100%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 03:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 12 year old me made charts, man. Memorized the locations of tons of the shards because what else do you need to use your brain power for when you're 12? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 23:01:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've found that it's hard to overwater peace lilies. Cut off the yellowing leaves and make sure it's in bright, indirect light. I water mine 2 to 3 times weekly and it doesn't get much light, if it's in full sun it'll need water more frequently. 

The drooping is almost always a sign that it's thirsty. If it's drooping and the pot is light, soak it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 18:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, I'm not sure how much help I can offer though. I'm sure luck played a huge role in my situation. I was on craigslist constantly scoping out places when I found the listing shortly after it was posted, and I still had to beat out 5 other people for the room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 06:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 roommates, one metro stop outside the city, a 15 minute walk to the metro, at the back of an apartment complex. Lots of factors that play in my favor. I got so lucky. Cheap rooms in HCOL areas exist but they're so rare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 05:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm in DC. Super HCOL, I'm lucky that my rent is under 1k. I feel for you. Hope you find some local resources to help, but its ridiculous that that's even necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 05:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's incredibly difficult to see these behaviors for what they are when you're in the middle of an abusive situation. The behaviors start small, and increase in severity and frequency over time as the abuser learns what has the strongest effect on their partner. They push things to a certain extent and break you down, just to apologize later and bombard you with love so you stick around. It's hard to see things objectively. Especially when you have no experience being in a relationship with someone who actually cares for you and respects you.

Learned this the hard way. A lot of people do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 04:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I make $16/hour. I'm incredibly lucky that my rent is much lower than average in a HCOL area (but still over 1/3 my monthly pay). I couldn't afford even the most basic health insurance plan this year. I make too much to qualify for Medicaid or any other assistance. I have to order my medications online. It's the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 20:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To add, as a poly woman, if you do decide to go this route, you should demand that she cut off the people that she was messaging prior to this. If you decide to try an open or poly relationship with her, you both start from square one. Part of being poly is open communication, honesty, and transparency. She can't continue those relationships that she started in secret. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 06:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The definition of agnostic is incorrect. The survey presents the definition as "belief in something, but don't know what" when the actual definition is "the belief that the existence of God or other spiritual beings is unverifiable and unknowable." Basically, the belief that we can neither confirm nor deny.

Agnosticism can apply to atheists and theists. Agnostic theism would be, "theres no verifiable proof that there's a God, but I think there is." Versus agnostic atheism, "there is no verifiable proof that there's a God, but I dont think there is." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 05:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont have any problems orgasming with my partners (but that did take several years of work to figure out.)

But I have a really high libido, and sometimes sex just doesnt happen. So what I really enjoy is using a vibrator on myself while my partner holds me/kisses my head/says sweet things to me/touches me a bit. He doesn't have to put in any work, and I can just do my own thing, but him just being there adds so much to the experience and makes my orgasms stronger.

Also, my favorite positions for using a vibrator during sex are doggy and reverse cowgirl. Reverse cowgirl is especially great if you're a little shy~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 00:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jacksonville, Florida is the largest city by landmass in the US. It's my hometown so it always comes up in conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 00:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men have their own unique struggles, and I have open conversations with the men in my life about the context of their experiences. But society as a whole is structured in a way that is intended to benefit (mostly straight, white) men. You came here, on a post about a woman who was assaulted, to argue that she did the wrong thing. I can come to some conclusions based on that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 23:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't understand sexism, then. You do not suffer as a result of your sex in any way, shape, or form. Sexism towards men does not exist. It isn't sexist for me to say that it is the responsibility of men to fix men's shit.

There are several absolutely fantastic men in my life who understand this. They listen to what other women say without saying "but show me the numbers tho??" Because they know that society is set up differently for us. They call other men on their shit. Because their privilege allows them to without consequence.

All we women can do is provide necessary context and experiences for you to draw from. But you're combative at every turn and question the validity of every statement. You think the guy who assaulted the OP is an asshole, but not a rapist. That's problematic. If he were your friend, and you found out he did this to a woman you dont know, would you continue to be his friend? Think about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 23:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't know if you hang around violent or problematic men. They won't show that side to you. 

As I've said, it's literally not my job to educate you. But rainn.org is a great place to start doing your own research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 23:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is the job of other men. Don't put the burden on us. We're burdened enough by your actions. You're the ones who can't act right. If someone punches you in the face, do you owe them a lesson in why punching people is wrong? No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 22:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I disagree. It's not a woman's job to teach men how to be decent human beings. You're saying we have to endure shitty treatment AND teach you step by step how to treat women with basic respect and decency? It is ABSOLUTELY the responsibility of men to be better men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 22:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yikes. Often times women do say no and end up beaten or killed. You won't, because you aren't a woman, but you could listen to women and try to empathize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 21:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worth a separate comment: your privilege is that you think you have enough context and knowledge to argue with people here about what women should and shouldn't do when face to face with coercive, predatory men.

Maybe push back less and listen more. Consider that you're talking to a woman who has experienced this treatment from men her entire life, starting from childhood. I've also never met a woman whose sexual experiences with men were consensual every single time. You haven't lived these truths and that's okay, but that means you have to listen to the people who have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 21:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /u/Hvidbergen

This post is spot on. Have you asked the women in your life about their experiences with men? Consider that they may not feel safe discussing it with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 21:08:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So the first time you were cornered by a gorilla, you would know exactly what to do? Women are taught from birth to go with the flow, not cause a scene, lest they be pegged as "hysterical" or "emotional." We are socially conditioned not to say "no." 

The correct thing to do is to say no, but it goes against the way we've been conditioned to act, and it carries the threat of physical harm. More experienced women are better at saying no because they've faced the gorilla many times before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 21:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your privilege is that you literally never find yourself in this situation, where telling someone to back off (even in the gentlest way) is enough to escalate the situation. 

Edited to add: real courage is still dating men and giving them a chance after so many of them turn out to be gorillas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 19:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Start listening. And start looking harder. You wont see it at first because the behaviors aren't directed at you. You don't experience them but that doesnt mean they aren't real. 

Edited to add: this is what privilege looks like. You don't get to determine what the reality is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 19:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing is, the men who do these things don't show that disrespectful side of themselves until you're trapped, physically or emotionally. They extend an invitation, and you accept under certain conditions. They say that it's totally okay that you don't want them to smoke! But once you're there, they do it anyway. They blow it in your face and flaunt the fact that they're doing the thing you asked them not to. They say, "what's the big deal? I said I wouldn't smoke, but smoking is so great, and you totally like it." They have the physical power and they've shown that they don't care about your boundaries or wellbeing. He seemed like a perfectly normal person to start. He had to, or else he couldn't have convinced you to trust him up until you end up in his apartment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 17:50:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men who don't know how to respect boundaries and ask for consent should absolutely leave women alone, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 17:47:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You seem to be implying that he would have stopped if she had said "Stop". Given what we know about his actions, that seems incredibly unlikely. The reality is, she shouldn't have had to tell him to stop, because he shouldn't have pushed things past her boundaries in the first place.  It's so difficult for women to outright say no when these situations happen, when they set their limits upfront and then find themselves vulnerable and being taken advantage of by a stranger. It's easy for you to say what she should have done, but I doubt you've had to worry for your physical safety in a sexual situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 15:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She told him 1. That she didnt want to have sex and 2. That she wanted to use a condom. He didn't give a fuck what she wanted no matter what she said. Maybe she should have said those things, but that doesnt change the fact that he knew where her boundaries were and had no intention of respecting them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 05:30:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad this is the only comment here so far. This is the perfect language to use. She may or may not ever take you up on your offer to talk about it, but regardless, she'll appreciate your thoughtfulness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 05:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so, so, so sorry this happened to you. I had situations like this happen to me even with lots of sexual experience. Guys saying it's okay to take things slow, then pushing boundaries once clothes come off. Taking off the condom and trying to say it's okay. The men who do this are disrespectful garbage at best and rapists and predators at worst. Their behavior is NOT a reflection of you or your worth. You were wronged in this situation, and you have nothing to be ashamed of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 23:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm polyamorous and this is my take:

1. If you aren't comfortable with this, you should leave her, because insisting on this when you don't want it is incredibly disrespectful behavior on her end.
2. If this is something you want to try to be okay with, you both need to sit down and do research on setting rules and boundaries in nonmonogamous relationships. She won't have the right to go to someone's house unless you agree, and you shouldn't unless you are interested in an open relationship yourself.
3. She needs to take things at YOUR pace. Even if that means going on dates with no kissing, no touching, etc. So that you can work through your emotions regarding her seeing other people before you add in factors like sex and STIs.

I personally think she has someone in mind already, which is a HUGE no-no in newly opening relationships. Plus she seems unwilling to compromise on this even if it hurts you. Unfortunately, I can say I was much like her a few years ago and when I was dating someone who wanted to stay monogamous. You aren't compatible, and she isn't respecting you. You should move on. It will hurt a lot now, but you will suffer less in the long run because her seeing other people will hurt you just as much.

Edit to add:
Opening up at a time when your relationship (and sex life) are rocky is a recipe for disaster. If she is unwilling to take weeks or months to make sure your relationship is rock solid before even considering this, then she is NOT cut out for a successful open relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 06:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are you getting that idea? You seem to be assuming a lot of details when OP's example was a cousin's birthday party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 05:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A very close friend of mine from high school and beyond asked me to be a bridesmaid a year ago and I said hell yes! I moved away from our home town and we didn't talk much anymore, but she's still my best friend. Her wedding was February 15th and I'm a florist. I worked 65 hours from Monday to Thursday, left work at 7pm Thursday, and drove a rental car 10 hours from DC to north Florida to be in her wedding.

I made it work because I love her and I respect our friendship. Wouldn't have missed it for the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 01:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey girl, I'm 25 and poly.

This guy doesn't want to be polyamorous. He literally doesn't know what that entails. He's been cheating on you and he's definitely trying to force a situation where he can have his cake and eat it, too. He wants to have an affair with her and he wants you to stick around while he does it.

I highly recommend nonmonogamy. I've learned what to expect from partners and how to build healthy relationships from practicing poly after years of dating guys like your boyfriend. But even if that's something you're interested in, this dumpster fire of an individual is incapable of it. The bare minimum requirement in those kinds of relationships is respect, and this shows that he has none for you. What an asshole, I'm so sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 21:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YWBTA. You would be rewarding your in-laws bigoted views and telling your brother that his marriage is less valid than yours by default. You would be turning a blind eye to, and even supporting, the discrimination that your brother faces every day just for existing. By asking this if him, you would be discriminating against him, too. Your own brother. 

Respect who he is and respect his marriage. Tell the in-laws to bite their tongue because he's becoming their family whether they like it or not, or they can stay at home if they can't show your brother basic human decency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 23:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Support her in cutting them off. They're no good to her and they'll never change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 02:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. If you have an ounce of respect for her, treat her as a friend. You've girlfriend zoned her. You should take a step back and reframe your relationship with her before you move forward, spend less time with her until you've moved on emotionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 02:38:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. He's definitely racist. Dump his ass.

Source: Grew up in the South </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 02:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. Yikes. She's still bi, and you're deeply homophobic. You are trying to erase her sexuality. She isn't less bisexual because she's dating you, and she wasn't any less bisexual when she was dating women. You're trying to Mansplain queerness to your queer girlfriend and that makes you an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 21:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner and I do this, except he kisses my head and I'll hug him and kiss his chest cause I'm 5'2" and he's 6'5" lol. We always at least touch hands as we pass by each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 17:23:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How the fuck is this upvoted? Do people really think suggesting lying and cheating is legitimate advice? 

You should talk to your friend about how you feel, but recognize that there's a good chance that nothing will come of it. If you do want to start moving things forward and see if a romantic relationship will work, you should both dump your partners first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 17:11:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's just their kink  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 16:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I buy my boyfriend flowers every two weeks or so. Nothing huge, just something $5 or under at Trader Joe's. He deserves it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 14:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing should be done behind anyone's back unless they've consented to a Don't Ask, Don't Tell arrangement. That's not nonmonogamy, that's cheating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 21:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been sexually assaulted and have had issues with sex off and on for years, this is my perspective. I don't think you need to tell him that you faked this once, unless it would make you feel better to talk to him about it. But you should speak up next time and let him know that you fell out of the mood. That doesn't mean you guys have to stop, you can take a few steps back and try to get turned on again.


It might be a good idea for you guys to have some toys on hand so you can help each other cum in these situations without having sex when you aren't feeling up to it. This is a common thing for my partner and I, if I'm not done when he cums, he'll hold me while I use a vibrator to get off and it's so hot and intimate. An awesome compromise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 02:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay!! No gold necessary, just doing my job  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 23:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Typically, yes. But it's entirely possible for the soil in the center of the pot to be hard and dry from chronic underwatering (likely before you bought it, if you haven't had them long).

I give mine plenty of water when the top bit of soil gets dry, enough to make sure it runs out of the bottom of the pot. I only soak mine when they look like yours do. They pop right back up within a few hours.

I'm a florist, so I work with lots of peace lilies lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 23:02:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it pot relatively light when you lift it? If so it's definitely underwatering. I don't think this would be overwatering unless it was sitting in standing water or overwatered consistently over a longer period of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 22:44:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It needs a good soaking. Let it sit under a running faucet for a while so the soil really soaks all the way through, and let it drain for a while before putting it back. It may need a bigger pot but the bigger issue is that it's definitely dehydrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 22:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dated a guy like this for 6 years. I did like to play games together, but I also wanted to be able to do other stuff too. He would join me only if I begged and pleaded and would hardly engage at all when we were out. 

I left him when I was 22 and it was one of the best decisions I've ever made. He begged me to stay and said he would get help and that he wanted to change, but 4+ years later he's doing the same things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 14:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not worth overlooking the bad to keep the good. There are people out there who will be consistently good to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 01:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They'll likely have to special order it for you and may have an order minimum,  but you'll definitely be able to find it. Good luck :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 00:23:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your local mid-high end florist or floral wholesaler. It'll probably be pricey! Amaranthus is typically used for event and wedding floral designs so there's always a price markup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-10 22:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amaranthus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 05:34:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When he gave me his spare keys and let me stay at his place for a month when my long term partner broke up with me and I had to find a new place to live (we're poly).

When I came back to his place drunk and belligerent multiple times because I was at the worst point of my alcoholism and my life was falling apart. He supported me, cuddled me, let me whine and cry about it, and was incredible to me when I was just embarrassing myself.

It's been 8 months since then. I'm 8 months sober and he's been supportive of me through everything. I could go on and on about how amazing he is. We're celebrating 10 months next week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 18:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At first it took a lot of therapy, things got easier but I still couldn't fully relax during intimacy. I had been with my partner for a long time and thought the problem was me, that I was incapable of having positive, enjoyable sexual experiences. 

I stopped feeling that way when I started to sleep with better partners. Partners that don't act like satisfying me is a chore, who are totally on board with accommodating my needs. Who are totally understanding when I need extra cuddles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 15:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been involved in many MFM, MMF, FFM threesomes. You're right that this is incredibly common. In my experience, it always got better with time when repeating the experience with the same people. Some of the partners I've been with have used cock rings to help them stay hard with mixed results. It worked really well for some and not at all for others. They're really inexpensive so definitely worth looking into! Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 15:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grocery store florists are a good place to ask this, too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 04:20:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your comment was yikes-worthy, that's what that means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 04:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing fucked up about being straight, but saying his partner can't see other men is problematic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 20:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My network had some breakups a few months ago because my ex started sleeping with a married woman after her husband vetoed him, and my current partner's ex was totally okay with that and eventually started sleeping with her, too. I told her husband and I have never regretted it. 

The biggest factor that separates Ethical non-monogamy and cheating is HONESTY! Your wife is telling you that lying and cheating is a laughing matter to her. There is no way that you can trust that she won't lie to you as well. 

This should lead to an ultimatum. You've already vetoed this guy and she didn't care. Stick to your guns. And tell his wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 19:00:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This law wouldn't have affected 17 year olds. Only those 15 and younger who haven't reached the age of consent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-02 20:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.removeddit.com/r/relationships/comments/aue6ds/25m_petrified_of_my_fiance_25f_leaving_me_for/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 02:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yikes! You're doing her such a favor by driving her to and from where she needs to go. She's so wrong to feel entitled to that. She has the right to dislike the car that you got, but a decent partner would be happy that it makes you happy. And she doesn't like your music or your style either? Does she ever tell you what she does like about you? Does she tell you that she appreciates the time you take to take her places? You deserve a partner who isn't mean to you and who likes you as you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-27 15:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IF you do end up moving forward with exploring being in an open relationship, that can only come after you've resolved the other issues you didnt elaborate on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-25 05:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happened to me, too! I wasn't as good at telling creepy guys to fuck off back then, but I was still being pretty damn forward about my complete lack of interest. The complete lack of self awareness was astounding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 16:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The OP does say they offered to try monogamy. But if the options are that OP changes himself or the relationship ends, which is what it seems like, then it really is a demand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 04:26:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would feel betrayed as well. Imagine the opposite scenario that people post about in non-monogamy subs all the time: When a partner in a monogamous relationships demands that they be able to see other people. That demand goes completely against the rules and boundaries that the relationship was built on and that their partner consented to.

It's entirely unfair of her to ask you to change. It's understandable that she struggles, non-monogamy isn't for everyone, nor is it easy for people who do seek it out. But the focus should be on finding a compromise that works for both of you, rather than there being an expectation that you completely change to accommodate her. Which is what it sounds like you're facing.

Maybe I'm extreme, but I wouldn't change such a large part of myself for someone, especially when they were aware of it for the duration of the relationship. I'd be willing to go to therapy, change our rules and boundaries in the interim, and do whatever I could to help them find peace of mind and reassurance. 

Therapy is a must. Shes had a lot of time to process the feelings that come up when you foster other relationships. Therapy can help her understand them and figure out alternatives to dealing with them that also work for you. I wish you both the best of luck, and hope you can find a happy compromise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 18:20:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It just wouldn't go away. I tried so many different things and it persisted. Some standard acne treatments made it worse, even. After discovering that fungal acne was a thing, I looked at pictures and some looked surprisingly similar to my acne. My worst areas were my jawline and the sides of my face. I figured, fuck it. Even if it isn't fungal acne, accounting for the possibility can't make things worse. I cut everything out of my routine that I had been using except Stridex (which is FA safe) and started a new routine from scratch. I started using FA safe products about 3 months ago, and it didn't get better right away, but I kept adding to my routine until I saw progress.

I was just in a wedding as a bridesmaid and I literally cried when I was shopping for color correctors and foundation a few weeks ago, but my skin has gotten so much better that the products actually worked to cover the blemishes that I still have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 02:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right, I didnt consider that. I'll edit my post and be more mindful of that in the future! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 00:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner and I have been together for 9 months, and were both poly before getting together. We're both solo poly but at this point we're like primaries in a lot of ways. 

Our rules are: Testing is mandatory before any exposure risks. After initial testing is done, oral and protected sex are okay. Dropping condoms is okay as long as it's been 3 months or more since they've had unprotected sex with another partner, unless that other partner has also been tested. We tell each other before things progress sexually with new partners to check in about their testing status.

Sometimes, due to weird circumstances, we don't follow these rules to the letter. Once he was with a long distance partner who had been tested but her results weren't due back for a few days. He asked me if I was comfortable with him taking the risk if it meant we stopped sexual contact until her results came back, and I was okay with that. But we always talk about the exact situation and weigh what the best compromise is.

Outside of that, we don't really have any other rules. It's just expected that we're open and honest with each other. I trust him completely :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 02:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner doesn't like to do oral. Which, in a lot of cases, would be a turn off for me. But he doesn't expect oral in return (but I love it so I do it anyway), and he uses toys on me to make sure I'm satisfied. So there are absolutely no complaints on my end because he has never said anything to make me feel bad about my body and he is always willing to find other ways to please me. There's totally ways to make this work if your partner is mature and respectful, but sadly most of the time that's not the case :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 15:15:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It may seem harsh to break up over something like this as this is your first relationship, but this is a pretty big indicator that he knows what your boundaries are and doesn't fully respect them. You should have a conversation letting him know that anal is 100% off the table and that you expect him to stop bringing it up completely. If he pushes back against that, or agrees and doesn't follow through, then you should absolutely reconsider this relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 03:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just put nonmonogamous on mine, not "open to" nonmono. But I am very openly poly in every part of my life including at work. I screen people that I go on dates with pretty thoroughly and I'm very picky in who I meet with. I have had issues with guys who think I'm always dtf even after having safe sex and mandatory testing conversations but for the most part, I've had good luck meeting other poly people on okc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 01:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been struggling with fungal acne for the last 6 months and I'm not acne free yet, but following advice I've found on the SkinCareScience blog has been a lifesaver. It's my skincare bible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 03:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nowhere near the most irritating thing about that whole relationship lollll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 00:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a pro at this after growing up with 4 little brothers. My ex liked to eat all of my leftovers when I would meal prep for the week and measure and count out my calories. My solution? Olives. Olives on everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 00:50:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And even if you hide it, and always hide it somewhere different, it will never stay hidden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-10 00:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hooked up with a long time friend and then immediately ended my 6 year long relationship that had been falling apart for ages. Not the correct order to do those things but once the damage was done I knew there was no going back so I ended things. He told me he broke up with his (long distance) girlfriend of 6 years as well.

3 months later, after spending damn near every day together, he was still weird about being fb official. I had some suspicions and his stories about his ex weren't adding up. They were still talking regularly and were still friends on social media. Turns out he'd never broken up with her and she found out when I changed my relationship status and he didnt untag himself fast enough.

My dumb ass stayed for another 2 years before he kicked me out to move in a girl he had been dating for 3 months. He was an awful partner anyway, go figure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-09 19:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If he has listened to you but wont make compromises to try to bridge the gap, like using toys on you or such, then he isn't worth your effort. Stop giving him bjs if he isn't willing to return the favor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-09 15:54:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  25 now, got out of a bad relationship, and I'm in two MUCH better relationships with people who genuinely respect me and care about me. I also quit my job and found a much better one. I'm hoping to go back to school but that's a WIP. Good luck to you, I hope you find your footing soon! Things will get better :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 03:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But can you make sour gummy worms?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 03:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/plantclinic can probably help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 03:05:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's so kind and supportive. He's honest and a fantastic communicator. He's cute and funny and intelligent. He's always looked out for me. This is my first relationship where I truly always feel considered and respected. I could go into detail about all the different ways he makes me feel loved but I'd hit the post character limit. This is just so easy and I'm so head over heels for him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 17:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right, I say that with the assumption that your needs are reasonable and healthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 17:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're right, I say that with the assumption that you're a self aware person with reasonable expectations and a willingness to meet your partner's needs as well. But that can't really be assumed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 15:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then they aren't the person for you, someone else will be willing to meet your needs without question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 15:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get better condoms and deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-05 15:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If he's an indoor cat, dont collar him. My partner's 1 year old cat died this way pretty recently. They might be able to get out of a breakaway collar if they get stuck but honestly it probably isn't worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 03:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a watch chain to me, but I could definitely be wrong. Any other suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 00:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crassula mucosa, watch chain :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-01 04:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP, this is a good idea! It'll be a little less of a surprise but your bf can ask them to have the delivery driver call your personal or office phone when he's coming up to make the delivery so you can meet them in the lobby. We do this for customers often when they don't want to deal with waiting for their flowers to come up from the mail room where we're required to drop them off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-01 03:47:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a florist and I've been so confused when I've gotten complaints about arrangements that were wrong for one reason or another, only to receive a picture and see that lots of product was taken out of it. I didnt know I was sending arrangements to your office 

Please report her for this! It's completely unacceptable, what an awful, selfish person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-31 22:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was a guy I had gone on a few dates with and slept with once. Hadn't gotten any bad vibes, he seemed intelligent and respectful and thoughtful. I'd been having some tough mental health days and rescheduled a few times for it, but he was understanding.

We finally met up again and, after a long talk over coffee, he asked if I wanted to part ways or hang at mine. I invited him back to my place because it was still early, and we had a deep conversation about my history of abuse and assault, and he said all the right things. I suggested we watch Netflix and cuddle, and part way through he just wouldn't stop touching me. Just would nooooot take a hint that I wasn't into it.

I asked him to leave and he did, and later on I texted him and told him he made me uncomfortable. He really wanted me to call him but I didnt want to. He alternated between apologizing and saying things like "WOW, just wow" and "Seriously, (my full first name)??" (that only my mother calls me and that isn't even on my Facebook page).

I told him I didn't want to see him any more and he told me how sad he was. He keeps messaging me on Facebook now cause I deleted him. Pretty tame compared to some of my experienced but damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-30 15:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a variety of mint! Mine freaks out the same way if I go a little too long between watering. They're thirsty af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 03:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First one is definitely a florist kalanchoe and the second looks like jade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 02:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spathiphyllum, a peace lily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 20:51:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally, before they even get a first date, they have to be poly and seem to be good communicators. I'll usually ask someone what they want out of a relationship and their answer matters less than how they say it.

First date I look for someone who's a good listener, who is open minded, and obviously physical attraction. Someone who is self aware and seems honest and trustworthy.

I'm incredibly picky about who I go on dates with. I'm also in two relationships right now so I haven't been taking the time to be active on dating apps. But my current partners are both soooooooo fantastic in every way so my methods definitely worked for me haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 20:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had no idea what any of my props were when I brought them home but now I have so many of these babies, roughly the size of yours! They're so cute and I didnt know their names until now so thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 05:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ordered from territoryseed.com, but I've never ordered from them before. I'm hoping it goes well so I can order more stuff for my indoor garden! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 02:04:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got one at a farmers market and it was amazing!!! It grew so quickly, it was so easy to take care of (watered every 3ish days, lots of light) and it was gorgeous. I dont quite know how to explain the taste in comparison because I never felt the need to get a standard basil plant. It was delicious. It doesn't flower so you have to root cuttings to get new plants. I ordered some online and I'm excited to get 2 new ones in April! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-26 21:43:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I moved away from my hometown where I'd lived my whole life and all of my friends because my bf at the time got a fancy job in a large, expensive city. Things were never awesome, when things were good they were great but he's selfish and lies and gaslights like crazy when it benefits him. But I was blinded by love and always did what I could to make things better and to be a better partner to him. He never tried to be better, of course.

We were in an open relationship and he suddenly wanted to become poly when he met this one girl. Three months later, he's kicking me out to move her in and he's sleeping with my married coworker.

When we broke up, I had been drinking heavily. I've always had drinking problems and always tried to manage it or quit entirely, and he refused to keep alcohol out of the house to help me. He told me "if you get sober, don't do it for me or to win me back" 

Instead of going back to my hometown, I found a room for rent that I can afford. I got a new job to get away from that coworker. I'm more than 6 months sober. I've made friends and I'm in a poly relationship with someone who is really, truly good to me. I'm climbing out debt that I found myself in trying to keep up with the lifestyle my ex expected me to afford. The people in my life are supportive of me and my sobriety. I even quit smoking cigarettes for New Year's. I'm trying to go back to college in the fall. Things are good now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-26 19:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took home a free basil plant from work that gave me downy mildew and killed off my amazing variegated basils  no more discount plants for me unless they're quarantined lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>