<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3135</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 19:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once saw a genius, eating chips with a fork. It changed my life. Never again have I had greasy fingers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 19:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why hello there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 23:29:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait. I'm legitimately colourblind, and now I'm starting to question if they actually are green and blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 09:29:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People would greet someone they havent seen in a long time by bumping their feet against each others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 12:55:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A container full of old, alchenical items. Some are dried, some are rotten/mouldy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 21:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. I remember once when I was hanging out with a group of friends. A friend had to leave because she discovered I had a cold.

Her father had just had a surgery of some sort, and as a result he had little to no immune system. She literally could not hang out with me because the slight chance of transmitting the cold to him could have given him blood poisoning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 18:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Small rant here:

Yes I understand that when a lot for people sat this, they mean it as a joke, but you should really be careful joking about this.

Let me explain. The reason we vaccinate is not just to protect ourselves from preventable deadly deseases, but also to protect those who can't vaccinate themselves, like children, elderly or other people with some medical condition that prevents them.

If an antivaxxer would stumble across arguments like this they would gladly agree with them, because if they get the option to not vaccinate, they would take it. But what they fail to see is that they're exposing other people to danger. Aka they're breaking the Herd Immunity.

As I said, I acknowledge that this is probably a joke, but it's a dangerous thing to joke about, because someone might be influenced to believe it's a good idea. And if the person saying the joke is one of them, well, then it's important to stress these points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 21:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats is a why I fancy this community. Its hard, but it also spurs thinking. You know, thinking of various way to word your thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 21:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right now Im actually watching a show from Japan, such as Toaru Kagaku no Railgun, whilst waiting for a 4th and final part of Attack on Titan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 07:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me, myself and Irene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 07:31:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a feeling several games fit this category: 

God of War

Assassins Creed

Dishonored </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 10:24:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Borderlands? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 09:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aquamam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 09:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> JoJos Bizarre Adventure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 22:57:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. I also encountered a situation recently where I realised just because I can interrupt the fight, doesnt mean I should.

I was on the train when I started to hear shouting. I checked and two people were keeping a third person on the floor. I prepared myself to jump in to break up the fight, taking off glasses etc. 

But as I got closer I realised that no one was in real danger. Yes, people were obviously hurt, but no seemed to have taken any serious damage. Also people around tried to calm both sides down and de-escalate the fight. So I stayed nearby, but made sure that cops were called and all that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 21:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldnt you normally want more directionality in your jammer, in order to reach your target without getting too close? E.g. using a directed antenna as opposed to an omnidirectional one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 23:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I... uhhh... dont know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A story about twins </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 23:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 09:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 09:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt realize that until I made a sacrcastic comment. I started getting downvited and I was really sure hy, then a guy replied that I forgot /s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 09:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My name is Infernova, just sent you a friend request </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 18:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 23:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever I see one, thats my first thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 23:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im still conflicted. Whenever I see the pattern I go, Oh fuck, not the spirals again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 18:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes. Whenever Im changing things on my server, the classical NotInfernova logs in and gets his roles reassigned, and hes always clicking everything about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 06:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Astral Chain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 14:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dayum. I just found it a few weeks ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Super Smash Brawl; Subspace emissary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 09:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbh I dont think you fucked up. Someone would have broken it to them at some point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 10:08:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that this game has loads of small easter eggs. I cant remember any specific ones right now, but I do remember there was one about Falloutboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually started reading it recently, and I must say it has drawn me in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone else mentioned in on this post. When voltages get really high, they tend to arc through the air, so he wouldve been unlikely to be able to fully grab the wire before the initial spark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 18:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Notice how the camera is perfectly set up, and that thr cheetah seems to be wearing a collar. It seems like its staged in one way or another </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 18:00:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/OneTrueBiriBiri </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 10:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> XCOM 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 21:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats true. When autoloaders first came out, they jammed alot. I guess as time went and technology improved tvey reached a point where theyre now reliable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 16:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> G </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 16:05:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 14:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 18:46:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its like wheres Waldo but a lot more infuriating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 17:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well now I need to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 16:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FIFA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 23:38:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. I mean now hes pretty much the strongest guy alive, but it would be interesting to see an origin story about hime, like a prequel series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 19:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is giving me Borutos Dad vibes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 19:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im getting Borutos Dad vibes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 00:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rhythm thief! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 00:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 00:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> JUST SOME NORMAL HUMANS USING OUR NORMAL HUMAN BODYPARTS TO COMMUNICATE </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 11:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 10:01:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look. Im a guy on the internet. Just trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 01:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guy with two eyes here! The two eyes each observe a picture which the brain merges togethe (which is how we percieve depth). 

Since her left eye is unobstructed, it will see just fine. But here right eye is obstructed in its top right and bottomleft corner, which means she will percieve her hair overall in those positions, not straight down the middle, like a cyclops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Woman rides furry and somehow ends up saving two worlds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 07:33:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 16:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanted to make a manga spoiler joke, but then realised that this is not r/TitanFolk.

I then read how to mark spoilers, realising that Im on phone and gave up on my joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 19:31:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read that chapter just yesterday. The chills went throughout my body and I was goddamn this is so good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 11:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ones I know:

Caught plague
 This is 049, the Plague Doctor. He will attempt to operate on anyone carrying The pestience, which we believe is what he calls the plague. People that he operates on may then become zombies.

Seen 096
096 is a dangerous scp sometimes who will kill anyone who has at any point observerd him. This is evident by a cobtainment breach where he suddenly started to rampage and broke free and then proceeded to go kill a man. It was later discovered that this man had seen four pixels of 096 in the background of a photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 15:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, it seems this video is actually a few years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 22:26:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its tekkit classic. Its fun, but it still have its great deal of bugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 21:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, as I was falling, I had already accepted my fate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I saw my whole life flash before my eyes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 21:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-11 22:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sg is a cmmon accronym for Singapore right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whats peoples stance on milk? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 15:42:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi fellow strong boned brethren. Like you, I have never broken a bone, but also, I havent drink milk since I was a toddler.

I am curious to what opinion on milk is.

On one hand, its good for your bones, but on the other its supposedly not THAT good for you.

I mean, I havent drunk milk for many years, yet I have never broken a bone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 06:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 06:08:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You go around shipping people, only to have their offspring find a time machine and help you. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 23:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 23:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Star baby makes me wanna say Kirby, but I dont know any of the games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 14:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okami </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 04:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Playing hardcore and using smoke grenades, I see youre a man of culture as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 03:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was these kinda clips that got me into the series. It all started with Chikas dance, and moments later I was listening to all the sounds of Chika </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 03:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats for sharper turns, when youre doing a really gradual turn, displacing the centre of mass is enough to induce a small amount of leaning.

When youre doing a sharp turn, you need to get the bike to lean more, and you do that by turning the opposite way, helping you getting the bike to lean more

Edit: Try getting on a bike, go and do something like a sharp 120 degree turn, that should stress the point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 02:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im dont know the exact details, but you would motice if youre ever riding a bike/MC.

When youre turning the front wheel one way, the bike starts falling towards the opposite way.

As your bike is falling, you turn the steering back and now its pointing the same way your bike is accelerating, making that direction the one youre going.

[Anyway, this video explains it better](https://youtu.be/llRkf1fnNDM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 21:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a skin that would appear in AoT wings of freedom 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 13:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The imperial system is wonderfully consistent and easy to rememeber /s](https://youtu.be/r7x-RGfd0Yk)

Edit: /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 00:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, european here. Wtf is a freedom wall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 03:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People say that, and yeah I understand the joke, but the problem is those guys are going to bring many more people with them. The same people who legitimately cant get vaccinated (babies who are too young, sickly people etc.) and that we are protecting with the herd immunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 11:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who's your favourite Strawhat Pirate?

Who do you think will be the next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Imagine being in a boat. And the next second there are eye-level sharks next to you looking you in the eye </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 09:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 00:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kyoto Animations recently had a fire (arson) and right now over 30 people have been confirmed dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-23 15:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its more like she was pushes and decided to bring him with her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 19:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (Not so)funfact: Wasnt thid the guy that accidentally deleted hus entire youtube channel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 10:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Out of pure curiosity, when roughly was this period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> They arent mans best friend for nothing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 18:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 11:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dreadful. Absolute shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 14:34:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the worst that could happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 14:33:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lettuce or any other type of sallad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 14:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally whenever you can. So, daytime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 15:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its like the song Cats in the cradle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 23:49:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually use them as standard, that is mostly because I play on lowlybpopulated servers, usually not more than 10v10.

But they are useful ol bigger stages too. I usually on switch to them if I play a very dense game (i.e. 64players on Metro and Im holding a chokepoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 17:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I accept our Lord, the ever insatiable Garfield! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 15:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Roses are red, violets are blue.
Theres always an asian, better than you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whats up with r/OhItllBeFine? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 14:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Their rules section:
[https://www.reddit.com/r/ohitllbefine/about](https://www.reddit.com/r/ohitllbefine/about)

The subreddit seems to have removed all of its rules, and people are shitposting everything.

I tried searching but didnt get any good answers. Did something happen or was there just so much low effort that the mods gave up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What happened to r/OhItllBeFine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 14:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What happened to r/OhItllBeFine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 14:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What happened to r/OhItIlBeFine? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 14:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm currently trying to learn some video editing and thought I'd have fun doing it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 02:06:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 03:32:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I keep getting pleasently suprised with all the easter eggs which keep popping up in this game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 23:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Monkey Island? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 20:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What even is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-28 13:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rayman raving rabbids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 09:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 09:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 09:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 09:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 12:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Half-naked man runs around burning stuff and collecting poop </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 11:48:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Your job is to navigate an old battlefield and to not get killed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 11:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 11:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Castlevania 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 11:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the Fire Emblems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 23:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ni no kuni? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 21:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 06:30:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To clarify, I was inspired by the orher post, but I didnt rip it off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 06:28:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> If you get the good endimg, it ends with a lively dinner party </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 23:54:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 11:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is literally a swedish series (it also got a movie mad later). 

Pojken med Guldbyxorna (The boy with the Golden Pants) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-08 08:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ! I have seen some very good answers, but I try to give my take on this. Im no expert on celestial navigation, but assuming the MC is smart.

By using knowledge of the stars, its easy to find out what hemisphere youre on. Its also possible to find out true North / South.

Next step is to wait untill dawn. When the sun rises, you calculate its angle of rise compared to the compass youve previously made.

At dawn is also the time you make your call. Think of dawn as a vertical line which moves across the globe.   By calling and letting them know its dawn they will know where this line is. By also giving them the measurements youve taken, they should be able to calculate where on this line you are.! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 14:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/nwordcountbot u/infernova99 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 09:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It can be a great challenge, but the rest of the party can really appreciate a well played one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-28 21:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-28 21:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hehe that was quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wingsuit-Spiderman blows shit up. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-28 21:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-28 12:01:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas, - Let Me Hear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 10:46:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 10:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Giant half-naked men launch people into space. Also, the main character likes to yell at people </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 03:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 03:22:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shiet. Didnt even notice that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 22:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 22:02:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 22:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Immortal rulers trying not to get nuled by India. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 17:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 14:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really enjoy the podcast No such thing as fish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-24 15:37:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt read what subreddit I was on, meaning I had no idea what to expect. I wasnt disappointed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 22:49:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha. You solved it. Getting isekaid and turning up in another world, except you manage to bring a gun with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 21:27:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 18:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It actually fits, but its not the one Im thinking of </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A president goes isekai and joins forces with a cat person and a dragonto save the world. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 16:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 16:34:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought itd be Super Monkey Ball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-21 22:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May I ask what the 45 minute rule is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-21 22:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for letting me off officer. Well I better bee on my way back then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-21 20:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That wasp a very clever joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 16:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You guys should just hold your horses and stop horsing around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-19 21:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There should be an option on the map selection screen to switch to the custom map page </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 15:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive actually heard it play at several hockey matches here in Sweden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 09:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 17:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that how gender reassignment is done, by cutting of a womans hair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 14:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about short hair? Or if there are two? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-15 09:21:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From a wrong readers perspective, the first two lines have a convenient space just above another that is also aligned with the space between the panels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 20:21:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And drink water too! You musnt forget to stay hydrated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 18:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is it even a fad? Where/how are all these kids getting this stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 17:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone who doesnt vapes apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 17:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the fuck is a JUUL Pod?

Edit: TIL that times are changing and kids are adapting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 08:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No! Crabs are people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 17:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/subsithoughtifellfor

Seriously though, how is this even a thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 19:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. A cleric had a wild night with a demon in disguise, got pregnant. Giving birth to a part demon baby, she could!t bring her self to raise it and left it with someone else.

2. Youre parents was killed by a passing by army, but you were lucky to be somewhere during the time of the incident. You were to young to remember this.

3. You were kidnapped as an infant and sold on the black market. The ones who bought you treated you very nicely however, and as far you recall, they are your parents, untill one day when [insert character background plotpoint] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 15:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont forget that you could also play fetch with them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 09:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While we mention Best Girl
r/ChurchOfFroppy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-17 13:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You dont have to engage in a fire exchange. Most MT have good mobility, flexibility, viewrange and often camo. 

Playing to your strengths, you could for instance pressure their flanks, forcing them to either take damage, or pushing them back into cover to help your team advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 10:05:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also places Ive been at have had a low ceiling forcing you to throw at a (really) flat angle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scientist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 09:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 08:54:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except for what people have mentioned, I recommend Aragami.

Also Ghost recon wildlands, even though its not a per say stealth game, it encourages and rewards stealth and tactical play (especially at higher difficulties) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 23:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im no expert either, but I think that the voltage slightly decreases as the batteries are being depleted.

At what rate I have no idea. Try swapping for a fresh pair and see the difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 20:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its pretty easy once you try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 20:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basically all the numbers point toward ONE of the two being a mine, but none of them specify which one it actually is.

So OP has been playing legit only to have his game rely on a 50/50 guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I thought you guys would appreciate this </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 16:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 14:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NANI?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 16:48:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No! Crabs are people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 15:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive put my monitors on top of several dictionaries(lotr books too bcas they thicc) just to get them up to a perfect height (ergonomics). Ive hade them like that for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 17:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know man. I mean, dont we all got this burning desire to make puns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 22:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has never happened to me on my experience, but, uhm... 

You know what. Ill just leave that to mr DM to decide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The lego-class of dice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 21:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-10 23:20:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why thank you. Good bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-10 23:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !1st door.

Those animals are indeed hungry. Really hungry. In fact, since no one has been to the castle for years, we can presume theyre so hungry that they are probably dead. Therefor, that will be the safest door.! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-10 23:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !1st door.

Those animals are indeed hungry. Really hungry. In fact, since no one has been to the castle for years, we can presume theyre so hungry that they are probably dead. Therefor, that will be the safest door.! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 15:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surely you meant seat-uation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 15:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt even realise that. Guess I was destined to roll down this road of mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 15:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a half-witted joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 22:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dam good arrest if I could say so myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 22:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You gotta AMP up your game officer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 22:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drakar och demonerar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 19:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I efterhand ja. Men nr man sitter dr, bilen framfr har stannat, och fraren ppnar sin bagagelucka. Sjlv r man fr svensk fr att a)sga emot (alt. Tuta) eller b) kra runt (eller backa/kra backt).

S dyker ett helt kk upp. Folk flockas, fotgngare, cyklister likvl som andra traffickanter, sen blir man gott vl tvungen att kpa ett par UTGNGNA semlor, fr att nr man rullar in p jobbet strax innan r du i princip tvungen att muta chefen.

O andra sidan var semlorna rtt goda nd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 18:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *spreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 17:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ecSTATIC abput youre arrest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 09:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbf, I can already picture myself the end </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 23:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is. That wasp a very well executed pun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 23:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine has a few layers behind it. 

Young 10year old me loved pokemon, and by then I was playing pokemon diamond, thus I choose the original name of Infernape Lover

Some years later I started playing minecraft (the cracked variant because teenage me cant buy stuff on the internet). It had a feature of setting your own nickname. As I was playing I realised my name was too long to fit on a single row on the signs.

Then I misstyped my name infernapenover which surprisingly was a perfect fit. So when I bought minecraft, that was the name I went by.

However, as I started playing online years down, noone ever called me my full name, they nicked me infer instead. I concluded that my name was still too long. I started tinkering. I wanted to keep the infer part as that was what people called me anyway.

Being 14ish I realised I could portmanteu inferno with nova (infernova) and that was the coolest shit ever. Also relatively unique, havent had too many troubles getting that username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 21:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Hz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 21:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hands off my brethren! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 21:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing like a good train pun to kick off some steam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 12:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best part is that Im not even afraid of those things. The thing is those pictures look really cool as long as you arent scared shitless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 11:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While were at it r/thalassophobia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 10:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Western countries do. For instance there is the SAS Killing House where they even invite [external guests to partake](https://youtu.be/qKHt4R7ByY0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 09:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then Im stupid. My fault </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just found this subreddit. Was immediately reminded of this one </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 01:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-27 17:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One session our party was exploring a dungeon. We got to a crossroad where our options was a small door to the left, and a big door to the right. Most characters were too big to fit through the smaller door, so we tried our luck at the bigger one.

I, playing a monk, asked the DM how tall the door was, and he answered I dunno. Big. Maybe like 200ft and the keyhole 100? I quickly realised I could easily dash up to the keyhole, walk throught it and continue.

Later in the dungeon I came upon a room with a lava pit (also som pillars sticking up, probably for jumping on). How far to the other side mr DM?
Oh, lemme look here. 100ft! You can guess what happened next.

Later on, in the semifinal room, in a big labyrinth, we stumble upon a LARGE lethal snake. We tried fighting it first, but it took me two turns before I was on deathsaves, so after the cleric had healed me, I picked them up and noped the fuck out of there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-26 20:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its fucking Toddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 23:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gee man. Im running out puns. I dont any more to spare soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 22:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does he have enough strikes for a turkey then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 21:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The question remains, was that his first strike? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 21:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A ban on jokes is worse than a sub belt punch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 21:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that was a SHITty joke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 16:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like youre take on the word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 16:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But then you realise youre a monk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 21:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As I was reading to myself I thought I wasnt seeing it. Then the last line hit me like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 11:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once had a situation were I slid down a 60 degree slope as I was trying to climb it. For the last few days it had been oscillating between freezing and melting temperature, as such everything was practically ice.

I almost got to the peak when I felt I was losing traction. I instinctively put down my knees and hands and troed clawing with all my might to not slide down the 10m I had managed to climb. Didnt work. Also carrying 15-20kg of equipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 21:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 21:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 21:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im surprised this isnt higher up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-31 17:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 11/10!  ? Thats way lower than what I wouldve given them

r/unexpectedfactorial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 21:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Det var lite lttare fr mig eftersom jag blev vrnpliktad. Det r nog lite fr sent 0 och ska nu, men annars blir det ett r med lite utgifter och en del inkomst, och s lite slipning person (och ven CV har jag hrt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 15:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember watching a video (by Veritasium) about survivors bias. Since that part already was ruined by that time in history, those are probably the more durable parts of the temple, and as such are more likely to last even longer.

By the same principle you dont see the less well built parts because they have already decayed long ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 14:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !Spoiler Clock/Time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 11:42:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Funny story. Once when me and my family where going to fly to London during the holidays. But the night we were flying our flight got cancelled and they put us on a flight to a nearby bigger airport where we would spend the night and continue flying first thing in the morning.

As we were lined up in another country for the check-in we stumble upon me and my sisters science teacher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 22:32:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I accidentally swiped right viewing this post, and the next photo in line was a cats arse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 12:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, I misunderstood the criteria </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 22:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One piece unlimitrd cruise!
(Two versions, SP and SP2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 19:21:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks like Sdermalm, Stockholm! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 19:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt even know that was a thing. I find the radius to just be the perfect size xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 19:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man it mustve been hard when you reached that day when you realised for the first time that your hands are never going down the tube again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 19:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My hands are not even small, just slim, I use medium sized gloves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 19:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. I mean, whos going to pick up the individual crumbs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who can fit their hand down the Pringles tube? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 19:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I noticed yesterday when some Pringles related memes popped up how people struggle to get the last chip down the tube and how you had to form your hand etc.

In the comments people would say how they eventually give up and tilt the can.

I realised then that I never struggle to eat pringles and can effortlessly pick up the last one (19 years old average size male).

I asked a group of friends and out of us 8, three could fit our hands, (even though one of them was a bare fit). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 15:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Desk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Shoutout to all tech supporters </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-31 16:22:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a story which happened exactly one year ago. Background: Being the tech-savvy guy in my class people would usually contact me when their computer acted up.

Anyhow it is new years eve and Im  in the midst of eating dinner, when I get a text on my phone from a pal. This friend of mine is a really nice guy, but hes also a workaholic.

*Friend: Hi Infernova! I was writing this paper when suddenly my keyboard started to act up.

*Me: In what way? Are buttons still registering or are the wrong letters being input?

*Friend: The letters. Some of the keys input the wrong symbol, (I cant remember the exact letters, but it was something  and some shift+letters)

*Me: Sounds like your computer thinks youre using probably an english keyboard, check in your settings which keyboard youre using.

*Friend(after some minutes): Shit I found it! Thanks mate!

*Me: Btw, how come youre working on new years eve?

*Friend: Bro I just forgot that its new years eve 

Apparently he got so into his work that he forgot what day it was.

Anywell, happy new year to all you awesome dudes out there

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2Mad4U </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-29 20:52:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-28 12:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But have gotten the bookshelves to the towers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-27 03:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not a father, im not even close enough to be old to eith (19), but I love the switch for the exact reason. Due to work Im barely home, so its a luxury to bring something with me to whip out during brakes.

And when Im home I usually dont have that much time either, so being able to pick up, play is golden.

Its also why I love the DS and its many reincarnations. It was a must for me while I was traveling (still is tbh), because I could just have it in my pocket, and when I suddenly needed to wait 30mins at this one spot I could just whip it out and play some fire emblem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 11:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had 2 friends who was in my karate group and scoutgroup. They were 2 girls one being 2 years older than the other. They always shiwed up together and left together. They shared surnane.

It took me a few years to realise they were sisters and not just really close friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-21 15:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are your thoughts and tips on social interactions between withing the gane (PCxNPC and/or NPCxNPC)

Within my group, and Im the next in line to DM, and I thought Id really like to give the world more colour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-14 22:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember awkwardly folding out my bipods only to embarassingly put my first salve into the rock Im lying on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-12 17:56:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was never risky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-10 12:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EOD Bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-24 19:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyday mans on the blocc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-15 16:11:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-12 07:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Communism is the superior ideology! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 17:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 15:32:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 14:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a teacher somehow write PORNCORN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-04 07:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Act!
Right time, right time, right equipment!
Yeah thats a roger
Faster!
Drink water, change socks

Im in the army btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-28 01:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still have troubles getting them to send different colour ripples. I keep getting the ripple that's on top of the layers be the only one appearing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Different coloured ripples depending on origin </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 12:21:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just got a new Cynosa Chroma (loving it btw) and am trying to configure the Razer Synapse Hue. Is it possible to have different origin button presses trigger different colour ripples (e.g. 1 always triggering a blue wave and 2 trigger red)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 06:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Miley Cyrus... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 13:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once when I had gotten stuck in a train jam, I heard music. Apparently the guy to the left of me was blasting Wrecking Ball on his phone speakers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 18:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alot of practice and really using my knees to have my body follow the motion.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First downspike </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 21:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive actively been playing with kendama for a year now. At first I quickly learned the cups and the easier tricks.

But today I reached a milestone, Ive done my first three downspikes. My friends didnt really pay attention but Im so chuffed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 19:08:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TOG! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tis the Superior Siege Engine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 21:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 08:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sm bivacker r bra fr vrme. Men akta s den inte bli fr liten, fr d fr du inte plats och blir blt o kall nd.

Och man skulle tro att jag borde vetat bttre om pressen efter 8 rs erfarenhet av bivackbygge, men man gr dliga beslut nr man r trtt xd

Nej men, se till att jobba p medans du kan (nr det r ljust eller inte regnar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 19:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Min tilldelade plats var p en mosstckt rullsenss. Det fanns f granar som erbjd ngot skydd alls. Efter lite orientering hittade jag en gles gran som hade ftt jorden under sina rtter bortgrpt. S dr krp jag ner och frstrkte tak, vggar golv och byggde en sjukt bra eldstad.

Problemet som upptod var att taket blev fr flakt och vatten brjade ansamlas p pressen, och s smningom tyngdes den ner det kalla taket mot mig, och brjade droppa igenom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 19:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nej fr fan! Det regnade mellan 1600-0330. All ved var vid det laget blt, ven den jag samlat ihop i bivacken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 18:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hehehe. Det hade nog kunnat g betydligt bttre. Platsen jag fick erbjd f alternativ s jag fick bli lite kreativ och bygga ngot okonventionellt.

Sen nr man r trtt, hungrig och inte s fylld av energi fattade jag ett felbeslut. Och sen s ett felbeslut p det felbeslutet.

Det slutade med att allt mitt materiel blev dyngsurt och iskallt, s jag fick varva med 15min vrmepromenad med 5-15min smn genom strre delen av natten. Men jag bet ihop och tog mig igenom det nd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 17:50:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag har hrt lite olika. Men exempelvis fick vi 5-3h smn och 1 ml om dagen. Ganska oregelbundna rutiner. En dag fick vi lunch, och minuten efter grvde plutonen ett 100m lngt stskyttevrn.

Uppgifterna i sig fr oss iaf var varken svra eller komplicerade, det utmanande momentet var bristen av energi och smn. (Hungern vnjde man halft bort efter 2-3 dar)

Nj, men alla i vr pluton klarade det strlande. Det viktiga r att ni fortstter lsa uppgift och peppar varandra! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 17:29:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha. Vi krde andra ordningen. Vi krde AGU frst. Kom sen tillbaka till kasern och brjade vrda all materiel, men observerade att vi aldrig fick vning avbryts.

S vi gr paranoida runt p kasern dagen efter, och sen blev vi pltsligt utslngda p soldatprovet. Men fyfan vad det var hrligt att ha gjort! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 12:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag sger som en kompis sa till mig. Dina befl kommer  ofta sga t er att dricka vatten (speciellt i brjan). Ni kommer tycka att det r skitmycket vatten, men egentligen r det inte tillrckligt mycket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 12:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vafan. D r vi ju p samma! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 08:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got my reddit account in order to interact with subreddits and ask some questions etc. Was a bit of a buzzkill at the moment to realize I couldnt do much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 16:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/absolutgalnapojkar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I think Ill take the side-entrance </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-15 18:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-14 10:09:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since neither of us have a d100, we use it as one, and anything above 100 counts as a reroll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-13 22:10:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It started with DnD. I thought itd be polite and buy my own set of dice as not to constantly borrow others.

Then I found a website which happen to sell more odd dice, (d24, d30, d60, d120), and odd shapes of the other dice. Tempted to own a (completely useless) d120, I obviously bought it, and since then  started to collect unconventional dice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-11 09:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Thrall on thrall fight (16min mark and forward)](https://youtu.be/k8XHoTCOvUI) 

[Zoey and Rythian do not have a good history with explosions (3:57) (followup 4:47)](https://youtu.be/svS0UbHIHaI)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is happening with the turkish currency? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-10 13:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just saw a post on r/europe about the Turkish Lira and how it had been tanking. People were discussing in the comments but I still have no clue as to how and why it dropped.

[(Post from r/europe)](https://www.reddit.com/r/europe/comments/963s6w/turkish_lira_has_sunk_by_over_10_in_just_five_days/?st=JKNWAAT1 sh=65a6aedd) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 12:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is no war in Ba Sing Se

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Roses ar red, storm cloud are grey </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 10:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 16:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Boss makes a dollar, I make a dime...](https://goo.gl/images/pkppkc)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 16:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You get more and more of a valid excuse to use back in my day... or when I was your age... etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 15:55:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a mobility scooter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 15:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shagging the dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 15:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not Walmart, but Target. Me and some friends and family were in NYC for vacation, and stumbled into Target to get some basic supplies (fruits, soda, snacks etc.) 

Its going to sound stereotypical, but as europeans we were a bit shocked. At the entrance there were permobiles anyone could borrow while you grab your groceries.

Then we had a laugh at lunchables, 10 litres ice cream buckets etc. As youngsters we were standing out a great deal fooling around Target. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 15:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Realistic MilSim airsoft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 15:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 15:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 15:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> According to this video there are about 80 324, but it also varies depending on where in NYC you start and where in LA you stop.

Edit: [Source](https://youtu.be/dQw4w9WgXcQ)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 14:51:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just like an actual trebuchet, r/TrebuchetMemes took a big swing in its contents for the worse (few weeks ago). There was a big war involving multiple subreddits and luckily enough it was eventualmy returned to its former glory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 14:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Skyrim sleeping system. Imagine being able to sleep anywhere between 1-24hrs in a single rightclick. And if youre sleeping in a bed you own, you will always wake up feeling Well Rested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 14:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/NoCapes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-20 06:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why isnt this higher? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-15 21:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a setup for an eventual spinoff or sequel series! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-12 10:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. As the party walks (anything but an open plain) they hear humans yelling every now and then. Should they stay to find out or investigate further they will find a hunting party. Because good weapons are expensive not everyone from this party can afford one, therefore all the money have been pooled to make/get one/few weapons and the rest have formed a line to drive the animals towards the rangers.

2. Here once stood a smaller village or town, but it eas razed a while ago either by a war or by any other conflict. But because of an ongoing war (or other crisis) refugees have started taking residence here once more.

3. The party notices a shop on the roadside. Upon closer inspection they find out that its inhabited by a mad scientist. Heres a list of some of his inventions:
         a) A swear. The man had an old shortsword lying
around thought that its range was its       shortcoming. So he put it on a long stick to increase its range.
         b) A two sided die. Its a flat wooden construct with a 1 engraved on one side, and a 2 one the other.
         c) A magic crystall which can store magic, and upon activating it will release it. Because of its low quality it cant tolerate anything stronger than a cantrip and they usually break upon use. Its not uncommon for them to break from smaller shocks either, resulting in a small firecracker-esque explosion not even strong enough to harm a bird. However because of the crystals rich potassium and phospate content it can be used as the most excellent fertilizer. This also explains why the scientists garden is completely overgrown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-02 16:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lowkey wants it to be an actual subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-01 09:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of this time back in the day. My friend was just about to finish capping and I was going around in my 300HP IS-3 looking for some extra damage.

As the cap was finishing I get pinced by a WT-E100 from the front and a Jgeroo from the rear.

Both of them fired and I realised a second later that I was still allve. Apparently one of them bounced, and the other shell never hit because the timer ran out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-01 00:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You wont be able to leave the continent because you would encounter Emus on the way off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-01 00:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Communist Manifesto by Karl Marx. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-30 21:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-30 21:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was once talking to my mum (who was out driving alone) and then she put away her phone, forgetting to hang up. I muted my mic and put on speakers and me and my sister were in for a ride.

Ive played toxic online games with people, but this was in a completely different league. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 11:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will start this with thank God I dont live in Norway.

In Norway they have a brand called Bamse-mums which are comparable to marshmallow bears dipped in chocolate. These bears, are the best and the worst food to happen to me. Why? Because once youve eaten your first, you have about 5 minutes to get rid of the rest before you will have gulped them all down.

The worst part isnt even the addictive part. When I ate my first bag I didnt realize how good they were, and in a really short span they were consumed, and because of their marshmallow like guts, those WILL clog yours.

I once had a bag and opened it in front of my friend, said Whatever you do, dont eat one, ate one for myself, and placed it right it in front of him, with the opening towards him.

He took one, tasted it and within a minute when he had eaten his 5th and realized how addictive they were he threw them in my face and we agreed to bury them.

So yeah, to answer your question. Bamsemums </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 03:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ei sa peit
M ikke tildekkes
Fr ej vertckas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 01:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Photosynthesis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 01:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP going to prepare a folder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 01:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trained </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 00:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never gonna give you up on either a harmonica or a kazoo. Imagine it. Wherever you are, whenever you want, you can whip out this tiny ass instrument and lay down the greatest tunes ever known to human knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-21 13:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just wait and see if there is a correspondi h r/TIFU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-06 11:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> var_a
var_b
var_c

... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 22:20:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See what bad things happen in baths! Baths are clearly a bad omen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 22:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knew exactly which clip it was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 21:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont really know why, but I have a softspot for Mk11 mod 0 with ACOG and canted ironsights.

I like the ability to engage in mid range encounters but also not be helpless in short and long range encounters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-03 18:11:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/recursion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 18:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least they dont waste cellular data... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 18:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on the person. Australians are normally upside down, but they do encounter a lot of tourists (who of course are right side up), and therefor they, being upside down are used to people speaking rightside up.

But when we consider Einsteins laws of relativity, we realize that from their perspective theyre right side up, which means to them (and only them) WE are the ones being upside down. Therefor, Australians can understand upside down.

Of course we who arent from Australia have little to no chance of understanding, because how often do you encounter an australian (try to remember when you last saw an upside down person, if you have at all) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 18:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obligatory  r/lostredditors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 16:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R/doingredditstuffwrong usully summons a bot or two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 09:43:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun fact: In Swedish we say kasta macka which translates into: throwing sandwich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-29 22:38:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What people miss is that it actually was a party-trick consisting of alcohol and a lighter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-29 21:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if Deku never got a quirk because All for one took it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-29 11:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Gol D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-28 15:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could be mistaken, but it seems to stem from a TV-show called Heidi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 23:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We must go deeper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 14:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id better be careful with that proposition. Imagine being on a bad spree maning bad decisions and having teams that doesnt help the situation. Thatd be very frustrating especiallu when youre not gaining anything. Itd probably be better to increase the reward of winning (or ever so slightly reduce one to increase the other).

In several cases, its usually better to reward the opposite of the behaviour you want to punish (even though the outcome will be similar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 14:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that they also realize that those entries are fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 01:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It happened me today. Me and some peeps were talking and I was going to bring up Yeah so [X ]happened, which funnily enough lead to [Y]. By the time I got to [X], they huh and then immediately went back to their conversation as if I never said something. Smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-23 12:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never realised how good of a tip this is until a friend did that to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-22 21:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Min kompis och jag gick ver till donkenbjudningar  l ~70kr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Love my shelf som food </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-17 21:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 16:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Cons-tits -ently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (0!)? But I thought arrays always start at 0? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-13 00:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 23:52:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isnt there actually one sang by the four swords misadventures Links?

Edit: [Found it](https://youtu.be/W1rmZjBmShI)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 09:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> META </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 18:04:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am sitting at the dinner table and this legitimately made me laugh out loud. Everybody was staring at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 08:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Paradox games does alot of what you just described. Theyre slightly different gameplay-wisd but theyre good games if youre into historic real time strategies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 18:36:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Endast en dansk skulle kunna ligga bakom detta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 06:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NANDESKA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 13:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remembered when I turned 18 and my bank finally allowed me to use their internet bank. Thing was I had to physically be present at the bank for them to activate it.

This usually isnt a problem because banks here have a norm of being open to 17:00 once a week, for us commoners occupied 8~16.

However this bank was only open mon-fri, 10:00-13:00. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 09:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used a colour inverter, and once the top two rows were inverted, I could see the difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-16 09:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the gotta catch em all mentality about it. In not crazy about the colours but rather the shapes and sizes of them.

Why use a regular dodecahedron (d12) when you can use a rhombic one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-12 21:27:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im literally hitting play right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-11 23:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw an ad on tv last summer (or the one before) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-08 17:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As we like to call it in Sweden; Norweigan Christmas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One very interesting DnD session </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 20:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is going to be a long one.

So our party has several murderous psychopaths who I honestly wonder are even close to being good.

After a long playsession were we almost killed ourselves several times without even being in combat our DM presented what he had planned for us.

His plan was as following: 
First we were supposed to speak with some old acquaintances and see if we could get a boat and sail towards the Big Bad Evil Guy (BBEG).

As we went to the harbour, there would be one functioning ship and a shipwreck. If we were to explore the shipwreck we wouldve found an injured girl whod been damaged by magic crystals, to teach us they are bad.

DM then thought we would steal the literally only available ship and sail off to fight the BBEG.

INSTEAD

We made pur way to the har pyr. There, we overdose on Arcana crystals and two of us got arrested and put in rehab.

Everybody ignores the boat and its captain by the way.

We got out of rehab and found ourselves at the top of a hill, with a straight line down to the harbour where the rest of our party. I, the cleric, was on 33/64 hp and the sorcerer was on 1/48.

The sorcerer is lying unconscious in a cart and I realise as soon as I move the cart, it would go rampaging downard. I also dont realise that hes on 1hp. The doctor ordinates sleep will do it.

I jump in the cart. What could possibly go wrong?

One crash site a few hundred meters below, and 50 damage later, the sorcerer is instakilled and we collectively pulled together to pump as much lifeheal into him, desperate to push him back alive.

250hp+ was dished out and we even tried turning him into a vampire hoping some undead might bring him back. After pooping out over 150hp myself I drop down on 0hp and start throwing death saves.

Our bald undead vampire tabaxi bard runs aboard the ship and starts pressing all the buttons. He rolls a critical 1, and DM said: You know what, thats it for this time. Well continue next week. Stood up and told us what he thought wed do.

Tl;dr: Instead of stealing a ship and sailing off fighting the bad guy, our party overdosed on arcana crystals, were put in rehab, resuciated our wizard by turning him into a vampire, and then probably blowing up a ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-06 13:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friends once did an economic union against me on monopoly because I built the first hotel of the game, even if it was on the cheapest possible street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Circle of Rust </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-03 11:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-20 12:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Over 100%! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-17 17:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No thats completely right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-14 08:46:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> f </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-13 23:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not with the UNLIMITED POWER that it will bring me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-13 22:35:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> S 399kr/(kg)^2 ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> At least I managed to view a 20 min youtube vid before I even started charging </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-13 10:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-13 08:31:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Put my spotify on private mode, listen on it constantly for a few days straight. Eventually you will feel that theres another song youd rather listen to, which will, of course, take the place of the old one in your head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-13 08:29:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rubiks cube and minesweeper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 22:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Super cynicalism. I have a hard time believing what anybody says, especially if its a lie. A bieffect of that would probably be me hating most stuff too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 22:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I realised he was a compulsive liar and probably one of the biggest racists Ive ever met </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 22:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Swedish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 21:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being bilingual is hard :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 16:42:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was in 8th grade and I went to a school with strict ruling. So I had brought an apple to school which I intended to consume as an afternoon snack. 

So our school had this policy that no one is allowed to eat or drink in the hallway, which is fair enough. So we had a somewhat long break, so I take my apple and walk outside and begin consumption.

But this was in the summer and the sun came out, and me being an edgy 14 yr-old went back inside with my half eaten apple to grab my cap and sunglasses. A teacher appeared and presented me with an ultimatum, go back outside and finish the apple, or bin it right here.

And if I uttered a single word of protest she wouldve given me a behaviour warning on the spot. All because of an apple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 16:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Emperor Palpatine.

Do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-11 11:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5/10, no disdyakis tricontahedron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-11 11:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So youre saying that you do not allow your kids to play with the caltrop shaped toys? How else are you supposed to step on them in the middle of the night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-11 00:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After a little use, its pretty easy to tell whats on top. We still havent got any use of anything larger than the d20, but the d24 + d60 can be used to generate time stamps.

The d120 can be used as a larger percent die. Some die throws use the d100, but we dont have any, so a d120 -20 can be used for instance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 19:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It rolls ever so slightly better, but I like that it has a more apparent topside. And its unconventional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 19:00:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww man, now I want some too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 18:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, technically it can be used as a golfball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 18:10:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or 20d6  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 18:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk. My addiction kicked in and suddenly I own a Hexakis Icosahedron

Edit: Me and my friend talked about it. It could be combined with a d6 to generate a normalised random number generator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 17:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One d120, two d60s, one d30, one d24, one d20, two d12 (a normal dodehahedron and a rombic dodecahedron), percent dice,  two d8s (a normal octahedron and a truncated octahedron), two d6 (one normal and a binary), and lastly two d4s (a tetrahedron and a truncated tetrahedron) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 16:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got the binary die for that (0/1) ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Since everyone are sharing their collections, I might as well come out with my addiction </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 15:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-10 14:37:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> German humor is no laughting matter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 22:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can map my entire party into that chat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 16:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Elesia, hill-dwarfen cleric

Her earliest memories are of her growing up with life clerics and there she learned of how to help those in need preserve life, but she never seemed to awaken any magic powers.

But that didnt stop her from traveling the lands and helping those on the brink of death. On her travels she met a devastated man whomd lost his will to live, and was starving himself to death on the street. 

Elesia then took time listening to this depressed mans story, and every time she came back to this town, she would stop by and visit this man.

Eventually she and this man would get engaged, and on the evening of their engagement, a mystic girl appeared in the crowd as time slowed down. This girl somehow altered Elesias soul and since then Elesia have been blessed with the power of magic.

Elesia thereafter joins a rebel army who are revolting against a demonic queen, whilst her soon-to-be husband (Orag) joins a small party, trying to earn money to acconplish their goal of building a hospital.

Orag gets drawn in to this plot to kill the demon queen, but sadly the queen hexes him, enslaving him. Orag being a formidable fighter, sadly berzerks and goes down in a blaze of glory, killing the majority of his party.

Elesia, saddened by Orags departing ups her effort to dethrone this tyrant and joins the elitesquad of the rebel army, along with three veterans and three new recruit, in order to dethrone the queen before she hurts anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-07 17:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the name of the podcast? Sounds interesting and funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-07 17:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like r/NotMyJob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-05 13:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Record everything and upload here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-26 23:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This reminds me of one of our earlier sessions. We had accidentally killed someones daughter whomd wed been tasked to rescue. She had been turned into a giant and noone knew so they just slaughtered her.

As we return to the town to report in, me playing an empathetic character informed him that his daughter wasdead.

When he asked how/why another guy answered; So yeah, we mightve killed her because we did not realize she had been turned into a giant

Smooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-22 13:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On the edge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-17 16:12:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesnt suicide equal -2 to deaths or still 1 death and -1 kill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-17 13:52:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whilst were on the unrealistic theme. It reminds me of the three towers (kings?) mission were you had several bossfights. At least one of them would pop his head out, and you had to him then.

Literally unloading bullethell upon his face and he was barely taking damage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-17 12:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I went plask plask plask, you man were jumping! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 17:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My character may have been killing the others during the time, and as we realised, that pretty much everyone were dying, we thought we kill off the others one aswell. It was all of ours first game and no character were agreeing about anything.

So we took this opportunity to start as new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 16:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was badly intoxicated and wanted to wake up and rush off to fight. Plus I think there was some curse in there too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 15:27:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend who had immense bad luck. He managed to get intoxicated and fall asleep in a house full of prostitutes. Eventually he started to roll for waking up. He kept rolling and rolling to wake up but never succeded. After a while he rolled a critical 1.

Apparently he fell in a coma and had to start rolling death saves. Needless to say he never got to roll a successive death throw, and without any of us knowing, his body was threwn out and rotted away in the gutters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 14:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just spotted tem and thought they were cute :v </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 11:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just thought they seemed quite and liked the additional details </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Was anyone else paying attention to the pictures in the background? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-16 10:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-09 15:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldnt it be fun if the shouts were shorter sentences or phrases rather than three words put together. And instead of adding words to increase power, the dragonborn instead learned to translate it more precisely and perfected the pronounciation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 22:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a math-test were I manage to get an answer to a question. Except my answer was negative but it clearly needed to be positive. So I frantically went through my solution to find the best spot to drop a negative sign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 16:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Som jag minns det s handlade det en del om samband. ven om man fr formelblad s kan det vara lnt att kunna t.ex. trigonometriska samband.

En grej jag vet med mig r att man fr se till att vara noga. T.ex. teckna din integral-uppstllning korrekt med dx osv och glm inte + konstant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 11:57:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Har ntligen slutat dagen efter 3.5h svenska tentamen. Nu ska jag hem, spela lite, och sen dra ut och kra DnD med polarna </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-31 10:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or it could be for ninjas. I like to imagine that it coulde be either or </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Its not crappy design. Its just not intended for everyone to use </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-31 09:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 15:28:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We did that once. We played it out as being another party from the same faction, who set out to do what our previous heroes could not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 11:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was playing a conflict avoiding dwarf by the name Orag who could NOT kill. If I did, who knew what would happen.

Thing was, since this was our groups first game and I was the only one who wasnt a murdering sociopath.

When a battle ensued within our party, when one of our characters were seriously going to slaughter another, I stepped in.

Roll for hit: Natural 20

Roll for damage: 30+

Insta-kill

DM rolls d20 to see my fate; Natural 20

Few moments later and Orag had slaughtered the majority of the party (fighter whod just learned maneuvers) and the two (LUCKY may I add) survivors managed to walk away with pretty much the entire party lying limbless on the ground </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-29 23:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> B u t C a n H e D o T h i s ?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-24 09:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SASUKEHH!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-14 00:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooooh. That explains alot. Ive always had stewards in my houses! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-13 14:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This has actually never happened to me no matter how many wives Ive married and houses built :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-12 07:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But the question is. Did you do it in one cut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-11 05:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basically how I described it to my grandparents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-11 05:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a text from a guy whilst I was celebrating New Year. Luckily I found the problem quickly and he could easily fix it himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-11 04:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just throwing some thoughts out there

Maybe differentiate between the open areas? I can imagine that closer to the cliffs its more barren, maybe patches of grass, but closer to the cities, I feel that you might wanna dedicate some land towards farming?

The cities have to get their food somehow, and only hunting (fishing for the coastal ones), probably wont cut it, especially for the larger cities.

Also: not everyone lives in cities, maybe add some smaller houses or clusters. So towards the coast you might have a large city, but inland one might find a small setlement living by a busy road?

Otherwise, amazing map! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-26 16:02:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know, I havent really gotten in to it, but I think it depends a bit on who you are, what language and what you are programming, but generally, a bit I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-26 16:00:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much does a polar bear weigh?

Enough to break the ice. My names Infernova.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-26 15:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive heard jobs like programming could be worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-25 18:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know. I never dared use it in fear of it breaking. I realised this friday, that my cleric might be able to mend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-25 15:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found a broken dagger (d8 -8) because I rolled a 1 one looting. Several character decelopments and plot points later, its my most prized possesions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-22 02:16:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool, Ill go ahead and check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-22 02:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you I will definitely try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Discord Automoderator </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-22 01:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-18 23:59:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A D60 isnt too bad a choice for ammo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-18 16:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So much better than good ol toxic world of tanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-18 16:21:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Twenty one pilots - heathens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-18 16:01:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Google Gandhi civ meme :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-18 11:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First things first: I dont see no [serious]

Second thing: Its a meme, which actually originates from a glitch in a civilisation game. It came to because Gandhi was so friendly it caused him to become too friendly, which made him loop around to the top of the aggresive scale, which meant, Nukes Galore! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-18 02:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all, an easy trick to make all your photos look better; be confident and dont be so nitpicky about how you look.

A genuine smile goes a long way (try thinking of a funny joke/memory and pop a small semi laugh just before to get into the smile). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 22:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It happened my laptopt too. It kept going for 20 minutes on 0% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 16:08:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ours probably didnt carry any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 13:41:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Running in the 90s - Max Covery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 13:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Running in the 90s - Max Coveri </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 13:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The great nordic memewar between r/sweden and r/denmark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 12:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once, a moose was hit by a car close by. As a licensed local hunter, my father was called in by the police to end its misery.

Now we stood there by the road with a dead moose. So we butchered it and ate roadkill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 12:22:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The world is the problem, the atomic bomb is the answer - Mahatma Gandhi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Finding tables and other informational charts about spectrography </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-13 14:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-10 20:53:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah. You see. Them doctors use their own unit system. Instead of referring to distances in metres, they would use legs.

In the same way they have another unit for temperature, Gastrichs. When they say 3rd degree, they mean 3 degrees Gastrich, (which is about 319 bne) they actually mean around the 634) degree Celcius mark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-10 20:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The director, God made 4 seasons initially. What the  happened was that a whole imperial shit tonne of drama appeared, factions were created, split, started crusading each other.

All this drama made the director filthy rich and famous, as such he decided to just kick back and enjoy his fame.

(Actually some local regions did get some spinoffs, seasons that dont really match what we others are getting) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-10 17:52:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The point with dashcams is that they always are filming, so you always have evidence for instance when stupid shit happens that your are entitled to insurance.

Or you know, getting funny clips to upload to the internetz and get som virtual score. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-09 00:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of Fire Emblem (e.g. Awakening), where children are copies of their mothers, but they need some fenotype from their fathers. Solution? Give em the dads haircolour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-07 10:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The picture itself screams r/babushkadogs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-06 01:03:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The intro from Running in the 90s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-06 00:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Minesweeper. Easily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-04 12:42:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I kissed a guy once. He smelled badly of alcohol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-04 09:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Points at it with a stick.
-Do something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Isnt it a little too early to be exited about (2018!) ? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-04 09:30:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-03 02:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its the same with floppy disks. Ive never even seen one, but I will always associate them with save. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-01 11:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats why theyre employed right? Ugh I hate those kind of people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-28 06:33:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (  
No! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 17:36:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use a pair of speakers which are really good with bassboost and all. One day the bass broke so I got  sad. 

Solution? I hit it just ontop the bass booster. Theyve held for another 3 years since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 16! ? I wouldnt call that only </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-22 06:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-20 01:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whole buncha hockeyplayers, both Elitserien and NHL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-20 01:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qi is a brittish tv-series, and they do a section called "general ignorance" which are full of these. They've also done books under the same name.

For instance;
Napoleon was never short
Goldfish do not have a 3 second memory
Krakatoa lies east of Java
Marie Antoinette never said "Let them eat cake"
Henry the VIII had 2-4 wives depending on who you       asked
Mt Everest is probably not the tallest mountain on earth, depending on you define "tallest"

And the list goes on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-20 01:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like that OP hasn't specified which political system, american, worldwide, or the myriad of european ones. And yet everyone assumes America (I would've, I'm just saying many more political systems need betterments) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-20 01:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Painting the picture:

I was a 16 year old guy, and had spent a larger portion of my life playing games, with a few geek friends.. Then I start [college equivalent] which means I have to meet new people, and my school partly did this with a party.

Only reason I went, was because my best friend, and my crush were going. Before I had even gotten there, a drunk guy in a blue morph suit came up and kissed me. Since then, I've never even been close to club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-19 13:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read Manga on an app called Mangateader (iPhone, probably on android too). It's clean, and they update quick enough. And yeah, the manga is awesome and lately it has just been jawdropping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-19 13:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't been following WoT news at all recently. What's compensation crew? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-16 18:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Benpress is swedish for legpress ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-16 14:07:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently I don't even know words. I probably wrote benchpress thinking benpress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My friend knows a guy who can benchpress a whole lotta kilos </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-16 09:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-14 10:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/theydidthemath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 12:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on what language I've been using mostly lately. I had a period when I thought alot in english, but otherwise I default to swedish, because it's the one I use the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 10:28:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had by the end of 9th grade crush on someone, without having realised it before. It was school prom and I realised that after this night I'd probably never see her again unless I did something.

So I tried telling her. Sadly the music was too loud, and it was really the last moment, as she had to leave immediatly, so she left without knowing.

That night however, I woke up having recieved a text from her asking what I tried to say. So I just said it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 09:53:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Socialise. You know. With people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-12 23:02:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/BamboozledButActuallyNot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-12 17:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't even need to click the link to know what it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-07 12:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually managed to kind of do this once in Civ V.

Me and my friend were playing with some AI:s. Because my location and military was enough to keep me safe, and from being a threat, thus I was never fighting with someone.

I managed to befriend ALL the ai, and I gt 4/6 of them to declare war on my friend (that part was just for shits and giggles). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-05 15:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Works better in swedish with Obi Wan Knubbi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-05 14:55:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a favourite question I got in a maths competition here in Sweden.

"A school has three classes, all containing boys and girls, and are equal in size. Total, there are twice as many girls than boys.

Class A has 18 girls, Class  B 8 boys, and the last class has more boys thans girls. How big are the classes?"

Firsy I was really confused, but eventually, it all felt so simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You don't think that's a bit too harsh? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-04 05:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-24 06:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something something Hisoka... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-21 18:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/dadjokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-21 01:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That the universe has an absolute velocity cap. Speed limit. You would think, that in space there is nothing to slow you down, so you *should* be able to keep acceleraring, but no. You will NEVER reach the speed of light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-21 01:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stress seldom works. Instead of freaking out and stressing over the situation, calm down, accept the current state, and calmly deduce a way to solve it.

For instance: You've missed your bus and will be late. Well there is no point stressing. Well shit you're late, but there's nothing really you can do. Wait for the next bus or whatever, but don't stress over the fact that you will be late.

There's a slight difference between being stressed, and in a hurry. I mean, you might as well *hurry* to mimize your lateness, but there is absolutely no point *stressing* and getting anxious about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-18 13:29:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First one that actually did the math and gave an answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-17 09:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trying to go indoors whilst eating an apple. Yup. I got a "behaviour warning" for wanting to continue eating my apple indoors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-16 17:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like r/dontdeadopeninside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-14 11:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes. It reminds me of the infamous "swedish busstop", or finnish depending. There's an unspoken rule that you keep AT LEAST 1 meter distance from strangers. I had once been waiting, and we spaced such, that between me and the guy furthest away, there were like 10 meters. And there were 4 of us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-14 11:03:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/maliciouscompliance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There a lot more movies to cover, if you wanna catch up to 2049! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 11:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-08 17:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Now you've planted your last potato"

English translations of saying, "you're fucked"

According to one QI-guest said; "shagging the dog" is something canadians say. (Why won't Alan eat Stephens noodles) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-08 17:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-08 17:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When people say "Aluminum". It seriously gets on my nerves. It's spelled "aluminium", and pronounced such!

Edit: I can't spell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 08:10:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But why not just use colours? That would make it both easier to read, but still get across the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 07:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It started really good, then it was just downhill from there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 07:00:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sauce: https://www.reddit.com/r/trebuchetmemes/comments/74g01j/heresy_in_our_high_school_textbooks/?st=J8FF92CN sh=818937e9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (r/trebuchetmemes) 270!!! metres is an awful long distance to launch a projectile. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 06:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 22:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's your favourite civilisation to play as, and why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 22:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a serious crush on someone. First we talked at all, but then it suddenly changed as we seemed to be interacting more and more.

After summer holidays, we got back to school, and it turned out that me, my crush, and my best friends from the other class, all had some classes together. She sits next to me during those classes because it's mixed and I'm the one she knows best.

My friends later pointed out that I'd been choosing to spend time with her over my close friends. Shortly after it struck me that she seldom talked about something personal, and that it felt as if I was always chasing after her to keep up. There had been times when she literally disappeared without saying anything, or waiting etc.

The final piece to the puzzle unravelled just a few days ago, when an friend of mine, (whom I haven't really been with at all recently) sat beside me, my crush, and my crush's friends. Then some time through lunch everyone left, except my friend, because she wasn't done eating. My initial reaction was: "I can't leave my friend, she ain't done eating". So Whilst the others (crush inclusive) left without even noticing two of us were left behind.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-04 15:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, the biggest difference is the mm. The T-44 was buffed with armour as far as I remember, but the t-34 should be the same. T-43 was a great fun tank with decent overall stats. I seldom fired gold, and the alpha was decent.

Both were awesome toptier bullies, and worked okay as a support in MT wolfpacks. Overall they were decent tanks I wouldn't mind playing for fun again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-04 13:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never had too much trouble with people spamming gold, obviously an e4 or jgeroo are gonna shit through it.

Whatever you do, just make sure to hide your lowerplate. Your ass has more armour than it. If you angle heavily, most tanks are going yo bounce off your superstructure.

You pretty much need the top gun though, and tha gun works wonders. I always try to get as close as possible, but not being frontline because not having a turret makes you inflexible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-04 12:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never three marked a tank, but the first I two marked was my 13 90 (whilst it still was T8), and I was hella surprised, and proud too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-04 10:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The t-43 was actually very fun as I remember it. It was the same with the T-44, but that was before they changed mm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-03 19:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Short info about me first: My hair is incredibly fluffy. Frontally, my hair has a larger width than my face.

Now to the story: I was going somewhere, usual stuff, and as usual I bike. As I pass a busstop, a random girl maybe 10-13 yrs old reaches out and just touches my hair as I wizz by maybe 5 m/s. It's not terribly fast, but it isn't that slow either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-03 11:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By the beginning of summer I had two tier tens, but I had been simultaneously grinding several tanks.

Now I've bought another three, have one unlocked, and am just about to wrap up the Jagdtiger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-28 11:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My Assassins Creed Unity freezes/crashes everytime I click "Quit to Desktop" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-27 09:00:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started reading this and thought that it was a REALLY weird r/showerthoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-26 16:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That word sounds like someone swedish tried to make up a spanish word for "kast granat" (swedish for hand grenade) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-25 08:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Some babies were dropped on their heads. You were clearly thrown into a wall" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-22 23:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Cough Da Vinci code cough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-22 11:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/theydidthemath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-21 22:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd rather be able to sleep whenever I want for how long I want. I can't stand being awake 23h a day. I mean, competely controlling your sleep cycle is going to refresh you enough as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-19 17:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hadn't gotten further than IS-3/T-10 when they removed it, and luckily never got to feel it's fury </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-19 07:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CrazyRussianHacker has all the gadgets and tools for general survival.

Colinfurze has slightly bigger and more specialised equipment such as a 600cc ARMED tuk tuk, or an underground bunker.

If there would be zombies and/or other survivors to rivale, Joerg Sprave has a literal arsenal or weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-19 06:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grille15. Basically the same as Swedish td:s, except it hits harder but not as often, however often and accurately enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-18 08:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like kill the assisstant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-16 14:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. I think the super heavy dilemma stems from this. It had been consensus almost that armourbwas going obsolete, due to "gold spam" and weakspots, and also new players who don't know how to use it properly.

So they buffed armour on some tanks and people grew mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-15 14:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> S1, cdc and t54mod1. Albeit I haven't played the t54mod1 after it was buffed, but otherwise it's such a boring tank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-15 11:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahahaha. You beat me to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-11 16:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found a place where they simply had a codelock. Except the code was written right next to it. Not obviously, but you would see it if you just walked past the door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-09 01:50:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is why i never visit self body improvement facilities! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 18:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the dark southern spot of southern Sweden that is Gothenburg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 06:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The entire Skyrim theme in dragon tongue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-04 21:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All places on a tank with viewport I think. For instance cupolas tend to have viewports, thus you are only required to put your cupola over the ridge.

That is also how someone can permatrack you by shooting rear-drivewheel e.g. without you spotting back because there is cover between yout viewports and opponent.

(There are usually viewports close to the gun too, above/below gun mantlet, I think the base of the gun even counts as one.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-03 17:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag hade ett krkort fr symaskin. Tog mig evigheter att skaffa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-02 15:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> T-54 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-02 01:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ALSO FIND IT HARD FOR MY TEXT ANALYSING CIRCUIT TO REGISTER INFORMATION DUE TO OTHER FELLOW HUMAN UNITS CONSTANTLY DISPLAYING THEIR INFORMATION IN A WAY THAT IMPLIES HIGH OUTPUT OF DECIBELS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-01 07:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fox really looks different in this HD-remake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-29 23:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am sad to inform, but I took the bait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-29 19:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The armour could be trolly too. People try shooting just as you pull back and hit your turret at a really steep angle. I bounced a Jageroo and Grille15 all in the same ridge pullback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-29 18:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say, no mods that are useful during the battle. Maybe last known HP, but things XVM. I started enjoying WoT again when I switched off XVM and decided to never more use it. My reasoning is, if a player is good, let them show that in combat.

I know some of these are bifunctions of xvm, but mods that lock gold and free xp are useful. There's also a mod which can show you after battle where and how tanks penetrated you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-28 23:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've done both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-28 22:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fv4202p prior to all it's buffs. I loved mainly due to my friends hating it, so I thought I'd prove them proved them wrong and after all that investment, I fell in love with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-28 09:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same happened to me on Mtn Pass. I managed to flip my 13 90 closer to the end and a Grille 15 were so nice to flip me up. I don't remember it costing use the game, so really nice of him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-28 09:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you done the missions as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-28 07:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt actually know it was possible to marry her. r/TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 67! Gold per turn? That's a whole lotta money </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-28 01:11:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-26 19:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Human idiocy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-24 07:32:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That map shouldn't really be t6+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-22 13:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now, let's see how long you'll have to wait before people call you reroll ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-22 02:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worst case scenario he would just have to get a mapping tool, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-22 02:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now I do.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-21 21:08:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finland: The country of the thousand lakes. Looks more like a big one now imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-20 17:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel this is a pretty r/CrappyDesign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-20 12:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wish I'd seen this before buying my 30b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-20 12:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a similar situation when I bought the 30b last week. I haven't been bothered grinding creds so I'm still running 11k creds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-20 11:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IS-3, Strv m42-57 and amx 13 90 are the ones That I find myself carrying in.

IS-6 too, but that was some years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-20 03:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Manufacturies are more worth it earlier on, I think they offer more production yield than a mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-19 17:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think thwre was a rumour going around that WG aren't too sure how treat the Grille 15, that they were considering some major remake, albeit it's recent nerfs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-19 12:37:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very cool video indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-19 02:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you're telling me that that psycho ISN'T photoshopped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 20:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of a story where a friend of mine where transporting garbage in a tv-carton, which they had secured on top their car. Then they went to an electronics store to pick up idk batteries or something.

When they return to their car they found out someone had stolen their box, filled with garbage, thinking they'd stolen a tv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 16:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The biggest supporting difference is that TD:s generally have larger guns, and thus more stopping power. You may have encountered some russian td:s su-85, su-100, su-152. These tanks can be equiped with rather large guns, or just rapid firing or high penetration. The 152 mm of the su-152 is enough to oneshot some tanks, so of course they're gonna be careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 03:24:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What confused me the most in the beginning was the whole garage. There was really little about how crews worked. What the percentage mean, how they are transferable but with some loss. Skills/perks etc.

I also did!'t by my first piece of equipment until like tier VI because I had no idea which ones were good / worth the credits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 03:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope they recorded for swedish too! That would be epic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-16 23:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "What should I do about it  //  Why should I know? Solve the problem"

-An old scoutleader I had whener He was asked a stupid question or was complained to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-15 13:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually wait for some small/mid sized pacakge, like 1-2.5k gold to be discounted.

The I usually spend it on premium for a weekend when I feel like playing a lot. 

I seldom pay for camo, but sometimes I will on a tank I like.

Otherwise gold is primarily for demounting equipment, because the credits you lose otherwise add up quickly.

If I'm in a really bad mood, I might free experience to make stock grinds less painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-14 04:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IMO:

My favourites are Malinovka, Redshire, Fiery Salient/ Prokhorvka, and lakeville.

Swamps, Westfield and Karelia are be fun too.

Kharkov, Fjords, Overlord and Westfield aren't too bad either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-14 04:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe some of the mods have become outdated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-13 17:14:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh. The more you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-13 13:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My computer managed to work for 20 minutes once on 0%, and it was not idle either, I managed to get some work done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-13 12:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are no proper differences. The only concrete fact is that EU 1 is almost always more populated, and this slightly faster mm, especially as people have pointed out, when there are few online.

One thing I've noticed, although it was months ago, is that there is a unwritten rule, that clan wars and team battles usually happens in EU-1, so the mm there will be way better.

Now I haven't done any of those properly at least since 2016, so I'm not 100% sure.

Edit: Auto usually puts me in EU-2, and I never notice any difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-13 12:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's just a tank which oretty much 100% fits my playstyle. My friend has tried goldspamming in it, and yet he never got above 1st class, and he's a good player too.

I just feel bad for him that he can't enjoy the tank as much as I do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-13 02:05:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do it like once a year. I always forget why my harddrive is so cluttered xd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-13 02:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The strv s1. I just hate playing it. It does not fit my playstyle at all and I can't even get good results in it even if I wanted.

The strv m42/57 on the other hand is an amazing machine. I ace it like every 4-8 battles and completely wreck the competition. It's also one of few tanks which I've gotten my second mark on too. (That's good for being me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 09:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember a time when IS-6 was still considered good, and they haven't even nerfed it since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 21:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They also use large(er) autoloaders too, so that will be acquired experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 20:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean they're better now, by a lot. I don't know how good you are, but I think it's educational to try every type of tank, to learn it's playstyle, strengths and weaknesses.

It might be hard not having any armour or hp, but it will be educational if you have patience, and an open mind, willing to learn and accept that you're not perfoming as good as you could.

What requires most patience (or money), is getting a good crew going, especially sixth sense, and some camo and viewrange.

You should definitely try light tanks some time though.

Edit: By the way, the elc was way better, and way more fun before 9.18 or 9.17. It was faster, and the gun was better. I did my first set of 15 LT missions in that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 19:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But far more superior </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 19:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The greatest medieval siege weapon of all, which can launch 90kg projectiles over 300 meters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 19:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a term in swedish. Sambo, or samboende. You're essentially living together as a couple, maybe even having a family, but you haven't gone all the way to commit yourself to marriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My use of alt tabbing went down with 95% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I interpreted it as he meant that they need to be trained for the tank, for the perks to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:30:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remove idiocy. Seriously. I hate stupidity. No more antivaxxing. No more stubborness. Nor more stupid accidents claiming lives because someone thought it'd be fun driving through a construction site. Etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Strv 81 right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First I cried. The I went into denial. Then I cried some more. This lasted about half a year maybe \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:23:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a hard feat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you a cigarette? Cus damn you got a hot butt!

Are you milk? Cos I'm lactose intolerant and you make my stomach funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Look at me, I'm in a stable! Moo I'm a horse!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perks too. If they're 100%, they will apply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 18:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say got average after 4k games maybe,. I really can't remember. But I do remember the time when I got the IS-3. Finally I was facing tanks of all tiers. Thus I was getting to know the last tanks, and took part of the high tier meta. 

Then I went against all my more experienced friends recommendations and grinded the french light tanks. After many painful games in the 13 90 I learned how to play in the flow of the battle.

Point I want to make, is that I learned a little for every new tank/playstyle I tried. I start bad, but grow more accostumed and never solely place the blame on my team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 17:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sixth sense needs to be trained to 100% on your commander for it to work. If it's 99%, it won't work.

If you do convert your experience to crew experience after every battle (the tick box above your crew in elited tanks), the least trained will recieve an xp bonus.

That said, everyone get's xp, but the least trained gets a bonus, but at the cost of convertible xp.

For every percentile progress you get on a skill, the more xp is required. You can go from 0-30% in one battle, but 98-100 may take over ten battles.

Your crew must also have 100% efficiency in your tank in order to keep training your skills. (This is counted without bonuses you get from Vents, BiA, Your commander or premium consumable) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 17:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Skills apply no matter the profficiency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-11 14:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A ricochet can still penetrate a tank if you're lucky, a bounce cannot then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 17:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is only common knowledge to SOME, but some people genuinely believe that Vaccine is redundant, a hoax created by the state/medicinal industry and that it causes autism.

(I'm leaving flatearthers for another day, they are at least not putting people in harms way) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 17:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a show/book for these kind of things, Qi - general ignorance.
 
For starters, Napoleon wasn't short. Goldfishes do not have a three second memory etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 13:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a general rule of thumb. Aim at tracks for critical damage, maybe gun if you're lucky. Tbf you're right though, especially since superheavy is quite meta rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 11:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Precisely. However, if you have a large ammo capacity there's no harm in bringing some extra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 11:21:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are three main cases:

When the enemy has thin armour. If you can penetrate HE, you will do alot of damage, for instance against Skorpion G.

When the enemy has thick armour, and you otherwise can't penetrate your silver/gold rounds. This is some guaranteed damage, but not as much as penetrating AP.

When you must do damage. This is a rarer case, but say the enemy is close to win by capping. Then doing 5 HE splash damage is enough to decap, and save the game. Also good for locking someone by tracking them for a teammate.

Usually, the larger the caliber, the more effective HE. (Compare Jgdpnzr E100 85mm with T-100LT 50mm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 11:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got steel wall in Skorpion G once. Skorpion op, plz nerf armour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 15:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I based this list upon a lix between how fun a tank is to play and how well it makes credits.

Strv m/42-57 -Really fun to play, and easy to perform well in.

M4A1 Ravioli - Comfortable to use, and makes good credits.

FV "Prius" 4202 - Ok at making credits. I personally get stable results. (I've got a good crew, probably why I like it).

Skorpion G - It's fast and got a big gun. Nail a few shots and you're having a good game.

T34-85m - Decent alround tank. I really need a crew trainer for all those russian meds

Tiger 131 (Heavy tank no 6?) - Really decent tier 6 heavy with an extraordinary gun. Really good in platoons.

Cromwell Blin - It's a good tank, but I prefer the Strv more.

T28 htc - Pretty steadfast tank, which can hold it's own surprisingly well.

SU-122-44 - Imagine the Skorpion G but at tier 7.

Pz 58 Mutz - It's mediocre. It's probably due to my lousy crew, but it's ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 14:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't watched the video yet, but suggestion: Make 30v30 optionsl (like encounter and assault), and don't have them count towards gun marks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 10:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it looks just fine to me xd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 09:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks alright to me on my phone \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 00:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean this one? \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 23:44:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> German too, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 23:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In swedish, the bishop is called "lpare", and the knight is named "springare", both of which literally mean "runner".  Although springare can imply "stead". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 20:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mathematics. At least most people around me hate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 14:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plugga grna, men inte fr mycket. Se till att plugga smart och effektivt och inte hrt, annars sliter du ut dig sjlv och ineffektiviserar din studietid.

Jag har klasskompisar som brnner ut sig sjlva fr att ka sina betyg ngotlunda.

Detta betyder inte att du inte ska lata dig. Ligg alltid enligt plan och plugga extra p det du inte kan.

Var alltid frberedd. Jag br alltid runt p min ryggsck, och dri finns alltid materiel. S nr ett prov kommer, s finns inte ens chansen att jag glmmer penna, sudd, stift, dator, laddare etc.

Slutligen r att ta hand om dig sjlv ocks. Tillgna inte all din tid t skolan. G ut, trffa kompisar, slappna av p exempelvis fredagar, och framfrallt, gympa, sporta och idrotta. G ut ngon eller ngra dar i veckan och jogga lite, gr ett par armhvningar.

Sport r perfekt fr att rensa dina tankar och ta hand om kroppen din. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 13:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dels ocks p innehllet p sidan. r/har du varit inne p en sida fr elektronik, kanske du ser extra reklam fr datorer. Om en video p youtube r taggad med bilar, kanske du ser en volvoreklam innan etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 13:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beror lite p var du bor, men t.ex. SL har ju app dr det str vilken linje, vilket hll, och hllplats.

Bussarna r alltid skyltade med minst en linje, nstan alltid slutstation ocks (beror var man bor). Vl p bussen str det nsta hllplats.

Nr jag brjade gymnasiet fljde jag bara de 50 andra p bussen, s om du har tur, lr du hitta fler som ska till samma stlle.

Gr bara inte som jag gjorde en gng, att frst inte kolla busslinjen, och ifrgastta varfr mina klasskompisar inte gick p, och sen stta sig p ett stlle dr jag inte ser nsta hllplats. kte p motorvg nstan hela vgen in till tullarna, och lyckades bara komma 30 minuter sent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 02:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> About the winrate. Sometimes, you're carrying your team more than you think. 

By placing a small, seemingly insignificant shot in the beginning, you may have just tipped the scales in your favour by forcing some guy to use their repairkit etc.

Hypothetical scenario:

You're playing redshire and you're team completely ignores the eastern flank, so you decide to go there. There you face 5 heavies and manage to hold them back 4 minutes, and take 3 of them down with the help of arty, and some TD far back. But you lose in the end. Yes, you did carry your flank, but in the end your team lost because they got surrounded.

Instead you might've placed yourself between your teams western flank, your 'basecampers' and the enemy push to the east. This might not give you the highest wn8, the highest damage, or most blocked by armour, but it may carry your team to victory.

I'm not telling you to camp, you'll learn this gradually by playing the game, by reading the map and adapting to the situation.

That's one thing I've learned. What's best for the team might not always be what's best for your stats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 23:02:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> About three fiddy. You might get $4.20 if you're lucky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 22:57:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you angle it, most tanks, excluding TD:s,  still won't. At least quick enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 22:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get warthunder ads on Wotlabs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 22:20:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I may not be the right guy to speak (1500wn8/2000recent). But I started playing quicker tanks, and try to stare at the minimap as much as I stare at my aim, just to make sure I'm doing what's best for the team, so either I'm usually in a good position to win, or I go down swinging, claiming extra wn8.

I never touch a tank tier 4 or below either, because those tanks are too unpredictable. And being a T-28 vs a cromwell or KV-2 isn't fun either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 22:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The IS-3 definitely. It's one of the best of it's tier IMO, even with all the new premium tanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-06 23:59:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suspect some people are latching on purely for karma too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-06 23:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of the nuzzle Pachirisu of doom from one Pokemon championship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-06 10:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People here have already described clans pretty good, so I'll describe my experience instead. Once we were up tilm 3 am singing soviet national anthem, eating potatoes and playing kv-2 running some ridiculous streak. 

And some other time half the team ragequit the clan.

If you're good, and find an active and serious clan, you may have the time of your life and getting alot of prems and rewards, or you just do like I did and said "Never again" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 12:29:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've already deleted the game, and am currently proceeding moving a siege machine 300 meters away from their hq, so they can expect a 90kg projectile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Write down words that begin with "TR". Just as Trebuchet was no acceptable answer, this is not an acceptable game. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 12:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 08:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag minns under en hemkunskapslektion nr min kompis ropar efter lraren ganska panikartat. Lraren sger "Du behver inte skrika eller stressa, jag hr, men hjlper nn annan just nu". 

Min kompis sger d i helt vanlig, lugn samtalston d, "Lrarn, det brinner". Nu kanske inte ni tycker att det r s jttekonstigt, frutom att vi lagade soppa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-26 17:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But haven't you noticed obj. 140 spamming apcr AND heat? (Implying they have one as standard)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-26 17:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The new AMX 13 90, is a blast. Same mm but with better characteristics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-26 16:11:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember from my childhood, when we made crustini with pesto (crackers with spread essentially). I asked my dad if I should do with basil or tomato spread, and he replied: "Mix them".

So I put them together in a bowl and mixed them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 23:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the same with TD. There should be heavy TD, and light TD, because Strv 103b and T110E3 do not have the same roles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sweet desirepath which saves 20 sec of my precious time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 15:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 15:34:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For that price, shipping is the least of your worries. Unless you're that guy who found that cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw one here about precision which reminded me of this: </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 01:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 01:53:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of this team me and some friends stayed up one night playing team battles. We picked an all soviet team with IS-3s, and me in the KV-2 (someone had to). 

I rush the hill on tundra, and lo and behold, a Blackdog tries rushing me. I put one HE in to him, he didn't manage to kill me in my reload, and I break his encircling and killed him.

That night we stayed up till 5 am, singing the soviet anthem, eating plain potatoes untill we lost, (took some time) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-21 22:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a game today, where someone toon hits for me when I was tracked, and I tried to repay the favour later, you know, if the opportunity would arise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-21 19:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is no such thing as fish! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-20 23:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our church has both wifi, AND a pokstop. Imma tell ya, we're real popular with them kids! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-18 17:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're no mate, pal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-18 17:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still pretty thin and would do decent splash at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-18 12:55:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I have to play tier 1, so still hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-18 07:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it Pain, or Pein? I've seen both been used on several occasions each. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-18 07:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel as that would definitely worked on r/floridaman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 23:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I won't! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 23:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A prank is at its best when the other part can appreciate it too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 23:00:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happens once a mobth that someone from our class (often me) has to help the teacher checking cables, input source etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 11:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of that guy playing overwatch with bananas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 10:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was back in ninth grade. By that time I was pretty bored by math as elementary school maths was easy to understand, thus not very challenging, and we moved at a slow pace.

Later that year I found out my school was giving out extended mathcourses. I thought to myself that I was pretty decent at math and was up for the challenge. So I took it.

During this course I fell in love with math as I learned alot of new stuff, and interesting applications that I'd never even imagined maths could be used for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 09:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 13 90. Because I was shit then, and it constantly met majority of tier tens, I relied on spotting and assistance anyway. The top gub wasn't really all that different since alot of the shits never connectef anyway.

The T-10 wasn't all that bad either. That grind was actually pretty painless, since the IS-3s gun carry iver, and you don't need to unlock the turret for the gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 08:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IS-3, amx 13-90, strv m42/57 and perhaps the FV4202 are my favourite tanks.

IS-3: It's russian, it's got armour, and that gun is absolutely killing it, slaughtering T34s who think they are safe properly hull down.

Amx 13-90: Get that crew leveled up and increase that camo+viewrange. It's now better than ever with improved mm, it's no longer always facing 13 tier Xs. The new gunhandling+pen is angelic too.

Strv m42/57: The autoloader is great for picking off same tier opponents. The small turret and great viewrange makes it surprisingly good at working ridges at ranges.

FV4202: It's versatile and the gun hits often, and inflicts damage too with that high pen.

Edit: Grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 07:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try to think, how much standard will I need to take to do a decent amount of damage without having to fire gold.

That's why my t-54 almost has 45/45/10 % loadut, because of the ammo capacity. I almost NEVER use the gold though, but if I am forced to, I have already fired 20+ rounds and probably am in a situation where I need to make my shots count to win the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 07:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or you could get Temair to blowbit all away, along with half the interior </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 07:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kv-13, t-43, t-44, were all wo derful tanks to play, and pretty much no gold fired either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 07:05:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See: "Cold War" and "nukes" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 02:12:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about creating a new account using the same mail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-17 02:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should try logging in on their website and resend verification email if possible.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-16 20:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's all about getting the knowledge (weakspots, angling, map awareness erc).

By tier 5 the game gets more standardised. Lowtiers are unpredictable with all the beginners who don't follow the map meta, as well as the countless sealclubbers.

I've returned to low tiers a few times, and they were essentially hell, so I draw the line at tier 5, (6 before mm change). I haven't dared ti touch tier 4 or below for half a year maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-16 20:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because you chew it, and then it's just a moist lump of dough. How does one even manage to cram a whole donut into your throat anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-16 20:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love to imagine Sasuke just dropping off some gifts by the door, knocking, then immediately leave xD

Edit: (Wow! That's a misspelling of sasuke I've never seem before) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 18:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That tutorial was super realistic. I got teams that did either fuck-all, suicide rushed. I got blocked several times and took tons of team damage. Super realistic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 18:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially since they would otherwise have pretty low. 5-6 is bigger than 10-11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 18:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That might be some graphical setting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 14:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha sorry. I hadn't read/seen since 2010 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 12:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That seems fair enough, especially because how easy it is to cast (even a dunce like Naruto learned how to use it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 12:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't they the same, except you're creating several clones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why is Shadow Clone jutsu forbidden? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 11:56:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see why some jutsus are, like don't mess with time-space or the dead, but shadow clone jutsu? I can understand that it's not commonly taught, but why forbidden?

Edit: Grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-09 23:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Jagdtiger is pretty fun to play now, more fun than since before the mm revamp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-09 20:54:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it would be as abused as the report function.

"Oh no that premium tank camped and sniped all my HP without being spotted; REPORTED for everything!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-08 19:40:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag minns nr jag var mindre (5?). Jag och min syster hade alltid gillat att kolla mellan trappstegen hemma, och en dag fr jag idn att stoppa igenom huvudet. Detta resulterar i att jag fastnar och inte kommer loss och drfr mste pappa komma och hjlpa mig.

En vecka senare r jag ldre, visare, och mitt huvud strre n ngonsin. Jag tnkte d att "Hur kunde jag vara s korkad att jag fastnade?" S jag gr om det fr att DEN HR gngen skulle jag inte gra fel!

Och jag fastnade igen.

Som tur r blev mitt huvud fr stort sedan fr att verhuvudtaget f plats i mellanrummet, som tur r. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-08 14:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a unicum whatsoever, but my Mutz makes a decent amount of credits. Same applies for the FV4202.

For a tier VI, the Strv m42-57 makes decent credits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-08 10:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah! I'd definitley marry Toon Link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-08 01:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adoption Wanted

Playername: Infernova (EU)

Stats: Overall: 1520 WN8, 52.67%
           Recent: 2020 WN8, 52.44%

Area of improvement: Tier 10 meta, especially meds. I have 2 meds (Bc25t and T62a sigh) and I just can't bring myself to have a positive WR in them, (40-40%).

http://wotlabs.net/eu/player/Infernova

Edit: Grammar and layout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-06 10:05:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe OP listens on other channels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-06 03:06:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of a game I had in the Jgdpnzr E100. I was bust angling towards a whole bunch of enemies pounding away on my armour, and I thought I just had to accept it.

He ended up ramming, and then shotguning me, thus splashing himself to death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-04 05:45:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those aren't really seperated and are in the end combined under assistance damage, and my friend made sure to track tanks when he was three marking.

I also remember QB saying that tracking tanks is a commant tactic when going for MoE:s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-01 13:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are hotkeys available, if you hover over a icon to the right, it will list the hotkey. Right clicks is used to quickly move and attack if I remember right. "S" is for sleep and spacebar for skip, etc.

The latter problem you specified can be fixed in the settings, and what you want to toggle off, is a setting which autocycles through your units.

This means you'll have to select every unit everytime you move, but the game won't change your camera to some faraway worker when you need your artillery to bombard someone asap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-30 22:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Took me too long to realise that it wasn't Majoras Mask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-28 02:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is one in Battlefield 4 though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-28 02:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The worst part is that my friend actually bought one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-26 15:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How tough am I? I took down a lvl 5 raid alone...








...with my CP 10 Magikarp! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-24 11:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I managed to be blindfired by a deathstar on Prohkorovka once in my 13 90, had 13 hp leftover, but I wasn't even mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-24 11:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 13 90 post-buff is one my favourite tanks ever. It was ok before, with goldspam, but now it's an absolute beast, even though they nerfed it's viewrange.

I can't say the same about the replacement bc-12t. I played 5 games then sold it immediately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-23 18:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, if you wait long enough, the next update will roll out, with the raid battles, I believe every now and then, a raid will come out, resetting all the gyms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-22 21:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as I know, I hold all lf the gyms around Amsterdam central. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-22 21:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Screenshot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As I'm posting this, I'm the only one holding a gym as far as the screen can see </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-22 21:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-22 18:20:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would someone mind translating the numbers for non-russian speakers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-22 18:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag skulle tipsa om att kolla runt dr du bor p t.ex. anslagstavlor eller internet efter mten eller andra typer av trffar.

T.ex. hller jag p med scouting och karat dr jag drigenom ftt jttefina vnner. Och har du tur kanske du hittar en ny, kul hobby p kpet.

Tips! Inga hrlurar eller mobil nr du ska socialisera, det blir s ltt att en person tar upp mobilen, s gr den andra det och sen sotter bda och r osociala. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-21 09:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag brukade se dem dr i Tumba lite hr och var, men har inte sett dem p ett tag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-21 01:02:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "As we all can see, the first roundabout stems from 1020 AD. Although highly impractical, it served as the foundation for centuries of engineering which lasts even today." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-20 23:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100 duck sized horses. Easily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-20 23:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it has to with sealclubbers. Since it is a lowtier tank, alot of players will have access to it, especially inexperienced players. Thus they drag the average xp down.

But since so many sealclubbers probably play it, they get great results, thus making it harder to ace. 

In oractice that means, 95% of players don't get above 650 xp, but the percentiles between 95-99 get between 650 and 954.

Edit: Right numbers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-20 23:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something something sealclubbers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-20 14:59:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always use Ballograaf mechanical pencils, it's a dream to write with.

The reason I don't use pens is because the lack of friction makes my handwriting faster, but more sloppy, thus harder to read and therefore I make less errors.

Whenever I make a small typographical mistake I can also erase and rewrite it, rather than writing harder over, or just rewritinh everything again, wasting space. They're also cheaper in the long run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 23:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Baserat p ditt anvndarnamn tror jag du ljuger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 21:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After actually reading I realised it's not a palindrome at any definition. Let's just call it an anagram xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 21:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you're allowed to rearrange spacing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 20:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Palindromes at their finest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 18:51:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Svar: Nej! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 17:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag har fru, men inga barn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-18 22:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kv13  T-43  T-44  T-54  T62a
This was one of the most enjoyable grinds that I've done. And I pretty much never fired gold. The awesome mobility and gun handling never let me down (let alone russian bias).

Sure enough I can't get the obj 430, but I thought I'd go down the lightline anyway. (This was before the lightank update) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-18 22:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, my last few days of WoT, I got the T62a. And driving that tanks feels like ghostrider </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-18 22:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is a result pretty much anyone would be happy with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-18 22:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of this time when I was trying the new Swedish tanks, the low tier ones. I was on Mittengaagd, and for whatever reasons he tracked me before going down, as in several shots. 

Eventually he got bored and stopped so we both drived down, but he, going real fast drove into me, causing damage, thus turning blue and getting banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-18 19:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found what was holding me back in my first games was knowledge. I had no knowledge of maps or tanks. 

The easiest way to solve this is just by playing the game and gathering experience. 

You might want to try watching youtubevideos. I find such as Jingles, Qb:s usersubmitted videos efucative and they usually feature several gamemechanics that are useful to know.

As people here have pointed parts of the community can be pretty toxic, so learn to ignore them. But still, don't be afraid to ask for help.

Last words of advice: Stay away from XVM. XVM and WN8 has never brought me anything good. You will see "statistically good" players and bad ones do extremely stupid stuff. The RNG gives worse players a chance to beat the statpadders and sealclubbers.

Lemme tell you something. Just play the game because it's fun. If it isn't fun, don't play it. I have a friend who cares about his stats. He is the one most likely to spam gold, check up a players stats afterwards and rage. And he hates the game the most and rages every game.

(Tbf he rages at every game, even in coop-minecraft) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-18 16:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you clearly don't need any of them except one xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-18 00:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/theydidthemaths ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-17 18:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the Ghandi one is an old meme which stems from an old civ-game where Ghandi:s peacefulnes caused a bug where he was the most aggresive one of all.

On a scale 1-10 I think he was a solid 10. Higher levels of aggresivness means they are more likely to nuke you. Civs never went that high pretty much, except Ghandi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-17 10:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to think of World of Tanks as chess. All tanks are like the pieces, they move differently and have different weaknesses and strengths.

When you play, make sure to read the minimap and pay in unison with ypur team in a way that benefits the team and not your stats (i.e. WN8). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-16 10:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. It's a bit situational, but those kinda tanks like being hull down behind a ridge or something, so with a little bit of rng and positioning, once every second/third shot you will hit under ideal circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-16 10:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maus got an armour AND hp buff. Type 4 and type 5 heavy both got derpguns, the latter does 1400 dmg with prem HE.

Arty is more accurate and annoying than ever with their stun, BUT they no lpnger have AP/HEAT rounds and will almost never one-shot you

This update also brought multiuse consumables that will be consumed by the end of the battle. Oh, medkits removes stun.

LT:s had a major update and their mm are the same as all other tanks and therefor alot of them have been tweaked.

MM is now in three forced formats with tiering. You will either have 3/5/7 ; 5/10 or pure tiered battle. (Hightier/Midtier/lowtier)

Quite some amount of tanks got tweaked. Too many OP tier 8 premiumtanks have been released. E25 was again.

Swedish tanks have been released. Heavy tanks have ridiculous frontal turret armour, but turret side can be overmatched. The heavies also have autoloader similar to the french heavies.

The swedish td:s (IKEA tables) have paper armour and rely on heavy sloping to survive. They have good camo and high speed, 50 forward and 45 backwards.

The IKEA tables use siege mode to tilt the whole tank to be sloped over a ridge to expose minimal of the tank. The gun itself is special. It gets about 300-310 base pen with APCR and prem rounds is APCR with a shit ton of pen. It's accurate af and gets a ludicrous dpm.

The german techtree got a new heavytank line. The vk 45.02B  now leads to Vk. 7 (something) and to take it down, just shoot whatever that's flat.

New tier 8-9 tanks, Vk100.01P and Muschen have been added and they lead to the Maus. These are very similar to Maus itself, but with cupolas.

Edit: WG had a fuckup and lost 3 community contributors, Jingles PointyhairedJedi and SirFoch. And pissed off the others ontop of that. (It was about youtube, copyrightstrikes and censorships) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-16 10:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not that often considering it's excellent gun-handling.

My first reaction was that it's gunhandling was comparable with that of tier 9-10 vehicles. Just let the circle shrink before you poke and you will be hitting whatever you want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-16 09:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. Against a knowledgable player in the right tank, few of the american turrets are always good. 

What I mean is high calibers pen them all the time (IS-7) by overmatching the turret top, which you therefor have to hude with gun dep.

But it's seldom I see people utilising this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-16 01:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Frra sommaren skrev dem bara "xxxxxx" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-13 17:41:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kommunen skickade i slutet av Mars ut brev till dem ungdomar i kommunen som skt sommarjobb, och detta med Postnord. Frn kommunhuset till mitt hus r det cirka 2km.

April r ver och jag utgr ifrn att jag inte blev erbjuden ngonting, men NEJ! 2:a Maj dimper ett brev ned i brevldan. Frn kommunen till mig, leverantr: Postnord... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-12 01:21:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People say that the T-54 has shite pen. Maybe it does. But I'd like to cliam that it's peb is very workable as it gets tremendous gunhandling.

It's super accurate even on the move, and combine that with it's decent mobility, and you can comfortably outflank your enemy and put ahots into their weakspots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-11 13:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually the cinemas in Sweden offer 3d-glasses, which are built so they could either be worn by normal people, or they could be clipped ontop you're regular glasses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-10 02:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People have already solved it mathematically, but I'm just curious if there is someone who wants to resolve the problem, and taking in other factors, such as baby-booms in November (or 9 months after valentines day hint hint).

Some cultures also have bias towards certain birthdayes, such as early in the year etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-09 20:25:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you build the prefollowing buildings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-09 14:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But with the new matchmaking you won't constantly be shat on by tier 10 tanks. If you're alone you will benefit the most from the new mm.

If you're in a platoon, well you're in a platoon, good for you.

Yes, Amx 30 is a sniper, but an aggressive one. I found that it's speed, hp/t, gun flexibility and viewrange allow you to find nice spots where you can outflank the enemy and spot and support your team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-09 13:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once you get away from the stockparts and get a crew which doesn't suck (which you probably will have, because amx 30 is the first medium tank in the tree), the amx 30 is pretty fun to play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-07 08:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never look at someone's statistics and don't even let XVM come near your harddrive.

As some people here said, someones super unicum stats says nothing about them until you see them play. They may just have sealclubbed at lowertiers and is then camping to max damage without being of use to the team.

Assume, that if you're not contributing to the team right from the start, that they'll collapse. I always make sure that I am in some way always helping my team win.

IF you get enraged anyway, DON'T chat with someone or rage somewhere, you will only fuel it. Try to stop the madness, otherwise you will make mistakes and do stupid things, die and get more mad.

I have a friend who more often than not gets real mad and starts spamming gold and curses at his opponents. And because he spams gold he thinks he's invincible and die because he lost his situational awareness and calm, logical thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-04 18:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the point. The keyword are "HEAT can be". More often than not, you will at least make up for all the tracks and space absorptionswith the extra pen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-03 18:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can still get a two-tier battle, i.e. 10 t7s and five T8s per team. But yeah I see your point. Tbf I feel tanks with preferential has alway been like that (At least for the two with pref. I have; the IS-6 and E25) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-02 21:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know how much of the camping experience you're going after, but something you MUST consider is fire. Some parts of Sweden are extremely dry right now (and will continue to be), as such I adivce being extremely cautious woth fire, and check with your region if there is a ban on fires.

We just recently had a forestfire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-01 10:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aaah. Thanks (y) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Request] "If bees earned minimum wage, a jar of honey would cost $182,000." </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-01 10:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Source: [r/Showerthoughts](https://www.reddit.com/r/Showerthoughts/comments/6ei2wq/if_bees_earned_minimum_wage_a_jar_of_honey_would/?st=J3E5DEXF sh=4f653c97) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-30 11:37:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend, his old expired Norton attempted to remove his other free antivirus program (which he has had for years) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-28 12:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He did answer the question. You can't just accelerate matter to the speed of light. It would requiring breaking the laws of physics.

(Fair enough he threw in fancy words, but still) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-26 13:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The IS-7 was my first tier ten, and the entire line is great, (except maybe for the kv-1s).

I have a friend who grinded the Leopard 1 and he loved every single significant tank on the line (except for the tier 7)

I'm currently grinding the brittish meds, and I've only gotten to the Centurion I, but I've played the AX plenty ol test servers and enjoyed it all

Soviet meds line is a bit trocky, but I always ended up doing good and got exceptional personal results </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-26 03:04:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My favourite score </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nn som har tips p kille som gixar ny id:s? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-24 17:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hnde igr p min fdelsedag. Det vanliga som hnder under en sdan dag r att man mottar grattulationer lite hr och var. Grejen r, jag annonserar inte fr alla att jag fyller r.

Men min kompis var noggran med att alla jag pratade med under dagen visste om att jag fyllde r. Lite pinsamt redan nu.

Hon sg ocks till att hela klassen sjng sista lektionen.

Men pricken ver i:et fr dagen var nr blev grattad, och svarade "grattis"

TL;DR
Min kompis sg till att alla grattade och jng fr mig. Svarade grattis nr det var en person som grattade mig </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-15 11:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag sg en frn /denmark fr inte s lnge sedan (inte s frvnande men det var en sverigeflagga p den) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hitta denna p /Norge , men den kndes relevant </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag knde igen skolan och blev skitexalterad i hopp om ytterliggare swedditors p Tullinge Gymnaisum. Sen sg jag att det bara var Sidewinder :( 

(Knner grabben sen innan) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:57:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Russian tenk OP! Plz nerf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The great nordic war: Sweden and the ottoman empire vs Poland, Russia, Denmark and Germany </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me being slightly in lead having a red shell chasing me. Guy throws it and I take te hit and trip just before the finish line and we were both cursing each other as I just about clutched the victory by the pixels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:51:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surely it wouldn't be too much of a hassle to fix? Just have the OTM be the tanks coordinates but +1m higher up along the y-axis or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Om du har tur s brukar vissa bibliotek ha sdant som man kan lna </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahaha. Jag och min syster var i en butik. Jag nskade Glad psk p vgen ut, och min syster: "Trevlig Helg".

Det var mndag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag har fngat tv p Tullinge-berg hr i botkyrka, samt hittade en clefable precis vid globen. Detta var dock ett tag sedan ( innan Jul tminstone) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag sg folk idag som gick runt med T-shirt i detta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends a bit on what tier you're playing. Sometimes I have days when just nothing seems to go my way and my team is just wiped, and I have WR=52.2% so it isn't entirely my fault.

This is even more likely to happen at lowtier because sealclubbers hang there and they max out their tank and just outperforms their opponents.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 10:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I remember this update but not it's name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rubicon? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been playing World of Tanks since Christmas 2014. I'm not really a 'new' player but I'm not one of them seasoned players who remember the Type 59. What's this "Rubicon" that I've read about seceral times in this forum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By your description it sounds line you're working towards the T28prot. KV-1 or T-150 might be the tank if you get into the right matchmaking.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's range. But also they get to choose between a large inaccurate gun, or a smaller but slightly more accurate gun, but IMO go with the big one because Stahlin will guide your shell eitherway.

They do have a narrow gunarc, so it can be somewhat frustrating havin to reaim, and shelltrajectory is nothing particular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reduces fighting capabilities
 
"LT:s should spot and support, not fight"
 
Reduces viewrange
 
Wtf wargaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But they could have premade comm-options, such as [Teamname]members, [Playername] is battling at [gym] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> De r dvstumma. Drfr har dem aldrig hrt ord uttalas och har ingen aning om vad det svenska sprket lter som. Sen kan de inte sga ordet heller, och drfr kan ingen ppeka att de uttalar fel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 10:51:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag brukade stanna till dr som liten, nn som vet om bollhavet r kvar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:09:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Patriot is not always availabe though.

Edit: Knowing WG:s need for money, it will probably be back soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't actually have it on the live server but I play it every chance I get o  the test server, and that's the Jgeru. Nothing says "Fuck you" quite enough as a 1050 dog shot into a noob heavy who thinks he's safe.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would be interesting to see a similar post for EU, mainly how it differs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:53:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adoption wanted

Server: EU

Area of improvement: How to properly play (and carry) in BC 25t and/or other high tier meds. (I have t54 and amx 30)

Playername: Infernova

Wn8/WR: Overall: 1437/52.67%  
                 Recent: 2100/55.35%
                 BC: 1777/39.56%

Wotlabs: http://wotlabs.net/eu/player/Infernova </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You might wanna add unsure as answer to some questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-12 11:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may have looked at tanks fitted with superheavy spall-liners. The superheavy ones add a lot of weight to the tank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-12 11:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Out of the tier 6 prems cromwell is certainly not slow. I believe my viewrange is maxed so I outspot pretty much all tier 8s, and the gun picks apart tanks real quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was hulldown in the defender against a 113. He was spamming HEAT at me, and I ricoched every three out of four shots. Came out of the game as top on damaged blocked (remember both teams had tier ten heavies) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Joking about these kind of stuff is just plane wrong :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yess actually. Tbf it was a humerous death, and I sent it in for the compilation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a game series called Wargame. (Three games so far)

If you use swedish units they will have swedish voices
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag lste hatt-troll frst... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jo men du ser. Det r hlften s mycket salt. Det r drfr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the best and worse things about lt. Being in the right spot at right time can yield tremendous points. I once got 4k spots and 1k dmg in the span of a minute on malinovka, but I've also hade games where I finish with 1k dmg and 1k spot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> T-54. Defender. Is-3. Cromwell. IS-7. SU-18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thing is some 'snipers' don't even know wherre they'll be able to shoot from where they stand. I have experienced several times when my team pressures me to spot.

Thing is, if I don't spot anything from this bush, then anything from beyond the ridge will be out of line of view for these snipers.

Prokhorovka for example. They want to you to go spot, but if you were to risk your life spotting (tier 10 tds are devastating) none of these guys would have a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend actually pointed out yesterday, when he stopped midbattle to look around at butterflies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:46:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Var d? Jag vet nu vad jag ska kpa i present till min syster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't there programs which can map those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> De gamla karolinerna under det nordens lejon krigade med gevr. Vi? Vi har helt enkelt moderniserat vr arsenal med tangentbord och mejmejs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jag och en kompis satt under middagen och bara fyllde i det (y) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kom igen hrni! Nu kncker vi dem! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Du fr nypa hrt i fingertoppen och anvnda ditt blod dom blck ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hej. Du kanske inte knner mig, men jag r en prins i Nigeria, som rkar vara avlgset slkt med dig. Skulle du kunna swisha sg 50 000kr s att jag kan kpa en flygbiljett och komma tille Sverige? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-30 07:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Efter ha sett era svar knns det som om jag r helt ute och cyklar.. 

1. Pokal
2. Vulkan sedd ovanifrn 
3. Tgspr frn sidan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tvggstvillingar :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Vi skall bygga en mur mot dansken! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:21:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men buss, tg, lastbilar, etc d? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Njaa. Salem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Det dr r ju Tumba! Jag sg ocks en, men den var betlydligt mer snderrriven xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-21 09:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aprilvger pgr som i regel iaf strre delen av April. S du har tminstone en mnad kvar av detta att frvnta dig </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-21 09:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tror detta r fjrde fr mig. I r! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pminner mig nr jag ska skicka hem trotsiga scouter nr deras frldrar r i kapprummet och vntar.

"Du kan ju inte lta dina frldrar vnta p dig?"

"Kan kan jag vl, handlar bara om jag vill". Allts vem lr barn sdant??!! Om du ska vara s trotsig, ge mig en anledning till varfr jag inte slpar ut och slnger dig i bakluckan?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-21 22:37:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obviously I would get (at least) a man-cave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>