<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9798</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 09:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Somthing that worked for me; that a friend said worked for her after 2 years of failing to find a therpist. Was to look at their pictures and then, read their bios. First see how you feel just by their appearance and then look at thier bios for things like their word choice make it much easier to choose. 

Also a correlation I've seen, often is the really good therapists don't take any insurance. But still tend to have competitive rates. Useing these 3 thing helped me narrow it down pretty quick and find a very good therapist.

(GA, USA is where I'vealways lived so keep that in mind) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 11:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didn't bolas also create the Amonkhet gods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 11:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm def no expert but shouldn't this also ask if you are or are not medicated?

Ex) Such as i used to have hypersomnia and would sleep 12-16 hours a day.
But now i only sleep a few hours during bad mental health days. It changes quite a few of the answers i would have given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 04:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 12:47:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quite alot of Companies have finally figured out they do much much better if their employees are happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 22:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My wife is a world top 500 raider in WoW it's pretty cool to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 09:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love that card way better than arcane denial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 13:46:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Control beats combo.
Combo beats stax.
stax beats control.

at least the closest you can get to a rule of tumb with cedh IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 02:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> #truefacts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 20:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also it's black and you have ritual effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 05:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I believe it probably stems from the existential dread. I'm in the same boat op. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 05:32:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same as most posts here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 06:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I def get it being annoying if drugs is all people talk about. Like drugs are def fun but your life doesn't need to revolve around them. Im guessing most of these people are in thier late teens early 20s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 06:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't follow like they are in your house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 06:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Op if it upsets you so much why do you interact with these people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I was excited for the future for the first time today. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 06:42:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A little context 
I  have had depression since i was around 11 now 27 
I was diagnosed with severe atypical depression and generalized anxiety along with a slew of traumas  2 years ago after i tried to kill myself.

 Since then i have gradually learned to take care of my mental heath in a healthy way, as well as found a solid combination of drugs. While at work today i noticed i was day dreaming about how to achieve a financially stable future and i was actully excited about it!  Just wanted to share. 

PS - If you are still in that dark place know that it's worth fighting off the depression you got this fam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 20:33:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They also are getting a second prints run next month right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 20:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also professional chefs is a hugely male dominated field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 05:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [[Sudden spoiling]] card is nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 02:48:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was a huge movement in the late 90s early 2000s to change it but it never caught on. For the most part i agree with it but swapping from miles to kilometers and gallons to liters would fuck with alot of people's brains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 06:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [[Mikaues the unhallowed]] i love the amount of shenanigans you can do with him. Kver the past 5 years it's gone went from control to combo and now is being made into zombie tribal. Just a really flexable fun reanimator card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 05:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my experience stax and chaos are way more hated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 22:02:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Godamn this is a good story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 21:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has there been an attempt on your life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 05:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also [[grand abolisher]] [[hushwing gryff]] [[tithe taker]] [[kataki, war's wage]] [[sanctum prelate]] [[remorseful cleric]] [[runic armasaur]]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 05:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [[Spirit of the labyrinth]] , ashiok, narset, thats all i got off the top of my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-11 02:13:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's fuckin diabolical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 09:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly i think this is more of a sociological thing than a mental health thing. For some insane reason it's cool to have to ALWAYS be doing work or school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 08:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awww shit i want updates if even they aren't slutty confessions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 18:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn you are my go to fap material now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 09:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn girl i hope you got your polio vaccine cause you won't be able to walk when i get done with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 09:22:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck i didn't know i could get this hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 08:52:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I spat out my beer. That was fuckin great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 08:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally my exact thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 08:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I this k my fav moment with this card was when my wife turn 2 equipped it to an inmoth nexus and proceeded to 1 shot someone. (Yes they milled 11 cards) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 08:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may want to checkout /rnsfw411 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 08:10:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn you have perfect nipples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 00:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (Male here) i would probably cry from how happy that would make me. And if i bought you slippers in return would 100% feel like garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 09:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In 3rd grade someone stole my zapdos card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 15:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mikaeus the unhallowed deck is really fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 16:00:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is def alarming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 15:59:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm not sure if this is a troll or not... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 11:01:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 08:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 15 years ago in high school i was working on a project with a girl i had a minor crush on. Anyways i was super focused on doing something i think i was makings and outline of a molecule or something. But she got really close to me for a second and she said "do you wear contacts"?  me-"no why?". her- "not even colored ones?"me -"nope".  She got even closer for a second then sat back and smiled and said  "wow you have really beautiful eye's".   I wasn't an ugly guy back in high school but the only thing i really had going for me was that i had put on alot of muscle that year so i occasionally got like an oohh you're really strong.That's the only time that a non relative complemented my eye's and it still makes me feel good about it.   So yeah we are pretty starved for anything other than being handsome or cute or strong.

TLDR; 15 years ago in high school a crush told me i had beautiful eye's and it still makes me happy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 07:59:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had the same worry but just using flonase or some kind of saline type nose spray once a day made the allergies almost a non issue. The reason i got it done was is i started to get sleep apniea. And it is unbelievable better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 07:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would also recommend that you don't say things like "it looks great trust me" and *then* do things like rub his chest i literally never believe my wife if she does it in that order.  If you touch him like you want him and then just say "mmmhh". Or any number of ridiculously sexy things women can do it will probably put him in a really good mood or embarrass him to the point that he thinks your messing with him. Will 1000% work if you "follow up ;)" later that day.  


Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 07:34:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> legit probably thinks you have a crush on him, or need somthing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 07:31:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 15 years ago in high school i was working on a project with a girl i had a minor crush on. Anyways i was super focused on doing something i think i was makings and outline of a molecule or something. But she got really close to me for a second and she said "do you wear contacts"?  me-"no why?". her- "not even colored ones?"me -"nope".  She got even closer for a second then sat back and smiled and said  "wow you have really beautiful eye's".   I wasn't an ugly guy back in high school but the only thing i really had going for me was that i had put on alot of muscle that year so i occasionally got like an oohh you're really strong.That's the only time that a non relative complemented my eye's and it still makes me feel good about it.   So yeah we are pretty starved for anything other than being handsome or cute or strong.

TLDR; 15 years ago in high school a crush told me i had beautiful eye's and it still makes me happy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 07:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are def people and 2 holes isn't even accurate they have more than that. like damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 07:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah like ii think if you really are that passionate about a hobby if it really is a passion then you should never be shamed for it. BUT if you are angrily describing/bitching about thing's wrong with your hobby or getting really sexual about things with it.  ex) Tifa is so hot i would fuck her all night. Then it's alarming i think mostly because it shows you have no sense of shame or self control which tends to = scumbag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 06:57:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah just from your post i can tell  that you aren't that type of dude.   
The type we are talking about tries and fails to use pity as a means manipulation into getting laid and then they get SUPER SALTY or Murdery/rapey when it doesn't work because they are "nice" it is what they deserve . That and the way they talk is generally very very objectifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 06:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like it's a virgin raging hormo's thing. So yeah it's WAYYY worse when you see it after HS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 06:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's kinda fucked up how often i had to threaten dudes or pretended to be a BF at bars/ and the mall for some reason, in my early 20's because i see them harassing the hell out of my female friends (or in some extreme cases strangers). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 06:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've learned that some of my friends have one or 2 (both male and female) and for each of them i was actually surprised. i imagine it's more common than people think but the stigma makes it so only creepy ass dudes talk about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 06:41:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah all this plus  most literally everything i've read about terrible first dates made me cringe super hard. I feel like it was just a fine to sucker punch someone once in the face alot of this would be less of an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 06:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can get the inside of you nose reconstructed for surprisingly cheap as long as it's nothing cosmetic it's pretty affordable. Helped me wonders after the 13th and final time i had my nose broken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 06:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not creepy but annoying is when they constantly talk about how good of a guy they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 06:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My advice would be treat them like you want to be best friends not lovers, if you change parts of yourself to please friends too well then it may be an idea to try therapy. I had the same issue as you until i stopped actively trying to get women to like me. Just trying to do things you love with people that you like/love and do things that they love too and you should find a very healthy relationship.   


TLDR; Treat them like they are your best friend that you would be happy to fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 03:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah my increased does lexapro has made it hard for me to reach peak as well  but my wife is always very satisfied. Helpful tips i've found is that some studies show that lexpro may decrease the amount of salt in your body (moore common the younger you are) and makes you dehydrated easier. I now try to drink 1-2 zero cal sports drinks a day and while i may not always get there it still feels alot better than without the gatoraid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 02:37:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Top comments are on point but i would also like to mention making sure if you are sexually compatible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 02:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having sex with a mostly but not completely erect penis is actually pretty dangerous much high chance of "breaking" your dick. This chance is farther increased if you aren't the one moving.  


Edit:typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 02:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eispcally when she's like "you're so big"  
, "oh but this isn't even my final form!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's probably unfolding as we type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I'm dumb i meant [[scour from existence]]
Also there is [[perilous vault]] [[Karn liberated]] and both ulamogs. 

I've mained a mono black deck for 5 years and this card can be good if your deck wants to swing alot but personally i think its lack luster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 01:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [[Return to Dust]] and [[Meteor Golem]] are way better choices and oh and [[Steel Hellkite]]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 11:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get help the depression Is real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 10:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Call of duty modern warfare 2. Holy shit those characters were so well acted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What does your S.O.(s) do to support your mental health? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 10:55:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-17 00:45:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would recommend listening to this podcast by the laboratory maniacs guys. The problem with playing a tournament for EDH is collusion. 

You get 2 people in a pod that know each other and have powerful decks in most cases one of those 2 are going to win that pod. 

If you are going to do it. My recommendation would be to split the prize 2 ways 1 prize for first place and one prize for the most interesting deck. Preferably have the most interesting deck have a slightly larger prize. 

Have each person in a pod vote on the deck they thought was the coolest. After 2 or 3 rounds whoever has the most votes wins the prize. (I have no solution for ties for most interesting deck.)


https://youtu.be/FfH13xLfovo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 21:12:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree i think you mostly just need more draw engines. And probably the green enchant that turns a thing into a basic forest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 20:58:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man the borderless makes me realize how great that art is. Nice job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 20:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [[Derevi, Empyrial Tactician]] tempo toolbox. That deck always had an answer for basically anything and just slowly punched you to death. (No it didn't run winter orb or the like.) Man that was a fun deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 21:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please kill him and give us a new blue walker after this for the love of bolas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 18:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have an appt in about a month. I'll make sure to bring it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 01:47:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah i have it's not suicidal or self harm thoughts just so meh.. My wife wants to help but doesn't really understand as she doesn't have depression herself. So i figured i'd ask y'all. Ty for the advice as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 21:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm nothing jumps to mind but I'll try to see if i can think of somthing. Also I've tried some other stuff just nothing seems like i really want to do this. Just more i guess this passes the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> None of my hobbies are fun anymore </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 19:45:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bit of context I'm 27 and have severe depression, anxiety, adhd and some mild ptsd i am medicated for all of it.  I Am married in a good relationship.

Normally i play video games with friends and my wife at night and play Mtg (magic the gathering) on one of my days off.  But lately nothing seems fun or interesting i pretty much just work eat and sleep now. I also seem to be tried alot again. Even the idea of sex is just meh. Not sure how to break this cycle, advice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 22:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They should lose their licences for this shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-01 18:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 03:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quite good although my only criticism would be the arms look too long on the vampire(?) in the chair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 03:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fallout 3 a bought it summer of my junior year and dis nothing but play that game for 3 straight weeks almost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 19:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm trying to get 3 more arena codes for my brothers and wife if someone will pm me 3 i would greatly appreciate it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 08:27:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly keep going for now antidepressants take a bit to work. Encourage him to talk to his therapist but. If he continues self harm and seems even remotely more unstable call 911 and get professional involved to have him forcibly treated in a safe environment. That's what it took for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-21 20:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The american government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 05:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The end of mass effect 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 20:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same used to happen to me frequently.  found out it was Actually severe anxiety after 12 years of it.Turns out i was just able to work around it and remain a high functioning member of society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 20:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same, don't poke it to Hard or it will hurt your balls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-05 19:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bit dungeon 2 i got it in a bundle deal and played it when my internet was out for a month. That game is by far the best $1  game I've ever played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-05 19:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean i felt the same way ended up getting treatment in october, turns out i had been severely depressed for about 15 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 02:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Permission to use this concept art for my upcoming dnd boss?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-26 00:30:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now its all about those hand drawn games lookin at you cuphead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-03 21:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A little girl that killed her parents and siblings and now they are undead puppets taking care of/fighting for here. The twist is the father was the necromancer on the council but the girl has her own plans. And none have yet noticed the father is actually dead.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 22:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-21 16:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love me that Wellbutrin feels nice that walking no longer feels like I'm pulling a car behind me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-21 16:46:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There wasn't really any one thing for me at least. I just received my first treatment from professionals in my life. After going to the E.R. because i could no longer fend off the emotional need to end my own life. Turns out I've been depressed and horribly anxious since i was around 5 (25 now)and suicidal depressed for almost 12 straight years. I will say that meditation and exercise are great and help a bit.

 But the true and real reason i have been able to survive so long (until the wonderful people at the hospital helped me). Was by really 3 parts A) cutting toxic people out of my life yes this means toxic family too.B) having real friends that are there for me when life get way too real and too much.C) Pet's. 

Also found group therapy in the hospital was very very helpful most city's have free programs that are similar to aa for people with mental illnesses.

P.S. if these things don't help you after a few weeks months at most. YOU NEED PROFESSIONAL HELP. it's ok.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-21 16:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean they suggested meditation as a coping skill while i was in a mental institution. It helps with anxiety but can be dangerous with major depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When you (Domino's Delivery Guy) and the Papa Johns delivery guy, deliver to the same house at the same time. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-27 10:26:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 05:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neil is a self important dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-03 22:26:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Writing and making dnd campigns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-01 23:39:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to ask where did you get the tiny easel stand? Also your work is super crisp =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-01 13:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Money cant buy happiness but it can buy a knowing feeling of a financially stable future and man that is alot of stress gone forever. Also it can by drugs that make your brain think it's happy, so it can buy synthetic happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 02:43:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pre or post 2009 market crash? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 02:38:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not free trade when laws literally prevent competition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 02:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it didn't we killed that industry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 02:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey diamonds are useful and worth every penny; for lazers and drills And surgical equipment. Not for rings /jewelry. Fuck that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 02:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How millennials are killing (insert bad business model here)

Them - How dare they kill americas treasure!

Us- You mean a business not supplying what its consumers want and going under as a result? That's capitalism.

Them-How dare they want handouts! Gives- grossly irresponsible banks and investors bailout money even though it literally broke how our money works.

Us-  we just want Affordable schooling, healthcare and homes so we can simulate economic growth somthing that wouldn't be a problem if your generation didnt interfere with it consistently.

I think we may be more pro capitalism than baby boomers. By you know bankrupting shitty business and understanding basic economics.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 02:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well i would love to have 5 roommates and live in a shithole house so i could get the fuck away from you. But that county beatification  bill you were sooooo proud you voted for made it illegal to rent out homes within 20 miles of the college. So here is a hot iron brand, please, shove it up your asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 01:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My god i hated that shit growing up ill pay you 5 dollars an hour to help in the yard me at 11- ok what do you want done on the yard? Blank blank and blank. 4 hours later mom  " this is as far as you've gotten? I know you can work harder than that" 11 year old me-"why would i work hard or efficent if you are paying me by the hour?" 

Now if my mom wants me to do any work on her house i quote her for an amount of money and it will take as long as it takes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 01:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Abzan is a magic the gathering color combination. Named from the magic the gathering "Khan's of Tarkir" block in the lore and the game the realm of tarkir was made up of 5 tribes each using three diffrent colors of magic.  "Abzan" is a tribe using white green black color combination. So an Abzan deck is a deck consisting of the said colors and is extremely popular color combo in the modern format of mtg currently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 00:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are some papers out there thoerizing that stress can effect things like predispositions for cancer. Much like how "heartbreak syndrom" can literally kill people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-31 00:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adrenline Pumpkins new album: Raging Pie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-30 21:54:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jeez , this is great paint it yourself?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-29 13:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2001: A Space Odyssey 

it just wasn't very grabbing to me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-28 06:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol i did the same when i woke up from general though i was 13 maybe 14 at the time.
weirdest part with mine was that my liver was functioning fine just really really scarred up. 
the moral of this story is unless you will die if you don't. don't take part in an experimental drug trial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-28 01:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude holy shit i had the same thing though i had to get a renal splenal shunt put in and mine luckly never fully burst before they were found and banded over the course of a few months (37 total). *Lived through extendes internal bleeding five* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 15:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want a really long time killer and like mid fantasy Wheel of time series is pretty dope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 15:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chemotherapy and experimental drugs fucked my brain up in weird ways. Like some day's i just feel no emotion, and most days i lose 45 mins or so of time mid activity and my mind just goes blank I'm completley unaware of what my body is doing and the passage of time (according to my wife It's mostly pacing) until somthing breaks me out of it. Honestly terrified its gonna happen one day and it will be years later and i have no memory of what transpired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 15:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's "the blood of the covenant is thicker than the water of the womb" not blood is thicker than water.

Honestly people go on and on about how family is everthing in the media your family ,people who are close with their families, its bullshit. don't be with toxic people even if they share genetics with you. I cut off really hard from the majority of my family many years ago ( see them maybe once every 3 years and rarley talk in that time) though for different reasons than yours, and in that time i learned that your home and your family are where your heart is not where your genetics are from and I'm far happier for it. Get yourself some breathing room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 15:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Drive like everyone else is blind,drunk,stupid or any combination of the 3"

dont trust turn signals (or lack of) as meaning someone is going to do something you expect. 

Always check before going through a green light has saved me from 2 t bones

avoid other cars blind spots

laws don't dictate physics

My granddad gave me this advice when i first started driving and I've never crashed in my 11 years of driving.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 14:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gentle and kind people

"There are 3 things all wise men fear, the sea in a storm, a moonless night, and the wrath of a gentle soul."
-unknown(?)
(Heard it a long time ago and remember it to this day) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 14:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Live together first.

In my opinion have sex. You should know if you are compatible Share your fetishes\fantasies.

Know that you will fight amd be mad even somtimes hate each other maybe for a few days or even weeks it's not all sunshine and rainbows. But it's worth it.

Know if you want kids or not.

This mau be the most important one of all

YOUR S.O. OS NOT A MIND READER 
Your partner will not always know why your are upset or that you want sex ect ect if you don't make it clear and you shouldn't expect them instinctively know these things.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 14:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Learning how to cook non boxed meals actually can save alot of money. 

Perpacking a few days worth of meals to heat up in a microwave (kinda sucks too though).

If you have an elective taking a cooking and/or nutrition class helps as well for the above thimgs and it's great life skills.

Sams club or Costco.

Aldi has off brand everything and will save you a ton on groceries.

Enriched rice and rice cookers are your friend, Espically in a dorm.

(As previously mentioned) Chegg.com buying your books on campus is criminally expensive.

Roommates and living off campus in many areas is cheaper. 

Bike/walk/public transit if it's safe/realistic.

Spend time digging for scholarships

Change jars if you use cash can add up to alot over time.

Never shop at publix

This last one may be the advice that has saved me the most money.
Legitimately find a really cheap/free hobby like DnD, World of Warcraft, League of Legends. 

Having somthing fun to do that doesn't involve leaving the house has saved me from spending a shitload of money over the years. (Just make sure you actully study too.)









 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 13:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chegg.com, rent/buy your books off of it, you will save an insane amount of money per semester. My last semester i saved 800 dollars. Total for 2 years probably 2-3 grand saved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-27 02:23:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is really strange I'm 27 as well and grew up in a suburb outside atlanta that exploded in size as i was growing up. used to just walk around /bike to my friends houses. But during the summer around middle school my parent's would let me leave or even use the stove while they were at work but they let me bike 2 miles away.. A mere year before. Then when i hit highschool especially when i was 16 and got our really old gas guzzling truck (had a cellphone now as well). during those summers i would spend actual weeks without seeing my parents they would just call every few day's to make sure i was alive/not in jail. Was funny when my friends who had jobs but no car and i who had a car and no job took a trip to FL just spur of the moment. Good times. But still it was weird having that super overprotective phase. I can't imagine what it would be like to live like that my whole childhood.

Edit: did just occur to me that it was right after i finished chemotherapy and was in full remission that that weird overprotective time kicked in.. Still from a child's POV it was super weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-14 21:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo got a growlithe adding now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 19:29:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Add me plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 19:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 19:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yup yup
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> looking for rock Friend Safari with Rhydon. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 19:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 14:44:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plz add me been trying to get eevee all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 14:06:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Add me plz as well =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 06:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Got some fires here for that eevee =D
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-13 06:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-12 22:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i keep going offline to add more friends i have to leave to work for a bit now, but i'll leave my ds on and connected for you peeps i've added already.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-12 21:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and Slugma has flame body for breeding =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-12 21:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> certainly
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for Eevee and ditto but adding all </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-12 21:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-12 21:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>