<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8497</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 19:34:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Depression "attack"? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 20:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yesterday seemed normal. I had a string of good days, so I was just pushed myself to make breakfast and watch some tv. I don't remember how it started but soon I was trapped in my bed crying. My pillow was soaked. Whenever I thought about doing anything (like asking a friend for help or brushing my teeth), there was such a torrent of negative thoughts and I would start crying again. I was so violently sad and scared I would be stuck for the rest of the day, maybe the week. I was so focused on not crying that I was stuck laying there. After a length of time (I lost track), I pulled myself together enough to watch a movie. I felt so agitated after what happened to me. I couldn't enjoy the movie, I was so uncomfortable and sad that I couldn't stand just laying down and watching the movie. Then, after the agitation, I felt drained. It was miserable, but I was able to finally talk to someone and feel a bit better. 

I rarely feel this out of control. I've felt hopeless, numb, and suicidal before, but this time was so overwhelming. Has anyone felt the same? I don't notice this specific feeling described often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 19:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think so. Otherwise, I wouldn't go to therapy. I used to feel really hopeless and suicidal during the worst, but now I feel like I can manage better so maybe I could still live a fulfilling life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 02:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. I've been tracking my moods recently and now I see all my emotions in a greater context. Now I feel like I can't fully enjoy normal days because I'll feel sad again soon enough. Before they were unexplained surprises, but now all I just feel like a waiting for feel shit again. It's very disheartening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 01:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anger. It's not too bad, but I have a small reputation for getting pissed easily/semi-often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 03:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tragic. You just have to be creative then. My school has a couple of corners that people rarely visit. Sometimes I cry during stretches in PE or similar times when everyone is distracted. 

Still, the whole situation sucks, I hope it improves for you soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 02:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I go into the stairwell, I don't if your school has them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 19:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just got a fannel from a thrift store thinking of Wayne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 17:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 01:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't push yourself to be 100% open at the first meeting, it's a process. I was really nervous during the first meeting because I was stressed about discussing my whole mental health history in one hour to someone I just met. During the second session, I was able to mention a couple of panic attacks that happened recently and that started a conversation. Try to write down the concerns you have before/in-between sessions and then try to bring as many as you can up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 00:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link: [https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/dbfps4/tifu\_by\_ruining\_my\_best\_friend\_hiv\_diagnosis/f21w9ma?utm\_source=share utm\_medium=web2x](https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/dbfps4/tifu_by_ruining_my_best_friend_hiv_diagnosis/f21w9ma?utm_source=share utm_medium=web2x)

Me and friend recently started using Letterkenny jokes after I recommended the show to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> To be fair... in r/TIFU </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 00:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 00:32:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. I never realize how depressed I am until the episode is over or I have one day that isn't as bad. It's honestly night and day, yet I will never be "depressed enough". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 00:30:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of people in my school are similar. It fucking sucks because no one who is LGBT can be respected or comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 00:27:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know, I'm pretty good at math. Maybe because bisexuals are more comfortable being artsy and creative and people who lean toward humanities usually don't like STEM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 05:01:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are *soooo* satisfying because of all the little crunches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 05:00:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt that way for a long time about my depression, my friend helped find the courage to reach out to the therapist. It's awkward, although I've seen one in the past for recurrent panic attacks, and I don't know if it's working yet. Still, I can't imagine my life being enjoyable or worth living if I continue to go through depressive episodes or deal with anxiety. I just hope it works, I own it to my friends to at least try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 04:46:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ignore it or laugh it off. It's so much easier to make fun of these people rather than engaging. I've been pissed *many* times before, sometimes I show it but I don't want to be confrontational to the wrong people, dangerous world. 

Usually, I get through my day fine. There are certain days that make me want to move but it balances out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 04:29:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently got some birthdays gift so I'm in the gift-giving mindset. Think about: hobbies and interest. My friend likes action/adventure games so I got him the whole UnCharted series. My other friend expressed delight when she found a Muji pen, so I got her two of those. Think back to conversations. Maybe get him a nicer version of something he wouldn't think to splurge on or buy in general. Examples: wallet, coffee/tea, belt, cologne, skincare, posers, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 04:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in New York so I can say yeah there are a lot of assholes. There seems to be a culture of aggression and asshole-ery (couldn't think of a right word). Still I can't speak for all parts, I usually stay confined to certain areas. 

I would always choose New York over anywhere else because under the shock and commotion, there are small pockets of community and relationships everywhere. There's a lot of culture and life that exist in New York and that's why a lot the residents stay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 15:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When sock shopping with my mom, I snuck in some socks with pride on the bottom.

Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Had a freakout in front of a friend eariler (possible derealization) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 09:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started freaking out when my friend was over, which I'm not too ashamed about, my friends have seen me in rough places before. I've had a small history with anxiety (panic attacks, moderate yet undiagnosed amounts of social anxiety). I  also have a decent-sized fear of the supernatural and "not being real" . I am usually pretty reasonable but I have a ton of ridiculous fears I can't shake. Today I was already nervous/stressed since I had a coffee and a small freakout earlier (over ice cream of all things), so my regular fear was multiplied by a hundred. I just felt like I wasn't real and everything she said seemed to hint all me soon having to wake up to the "real" dimension or being dead. Her eyes looked fake/wrong and mine did too in the mirror. I was in agonizing anticipation of the act of finally uncovering the "truth", this anticipation became fear when I realized I didn't want to look behind the curtain. I felt so uncomfortable that I had the desperate urge to be safe, but I didn't know how. I was hyperventilating at this point and my friend tucks me into my bed and holds my hand. I felt a separation between my body and "spirit"/consciousness which created a strange discomfort that couldn't be fixed. Eventually (I don't know how long this was), I began to feel normal again and calm down.  
So she starts playing music to lighten the mood, the first song starts like, "nothing is real, nothing is real". We are both shocked but laugh it off.  The situation was so ridiculous. The sharp distinction between my normal mindset and this paranoid one was so stark, the way mental health problems can change mindset is so crazy to me. Overall, that was awful. I hope it never happens again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 05:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think humanity is selfish, but most people don't have an appetite for the destruction of others. I believe the people who enjoy hurting others and/or lack empathy are the real outliers. Pressure justifies the action. For example, killing an armed robber out of self-defense. Unless you meant a different type of situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 05:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5'6" I'm not crazy short but enough to where it gets pointed out sometimes. I wish I were taller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 03:04:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to sleep on planes, makes the ride pass so much faster. It's a lot easier to sleep with the shade down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 06:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweaters/hoodies in earth tones and primary colors. Beanies. Straight legged jeans and corduroy. Doc Martens, Vans.

Go into a store and pick out the more interesting item there, push yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 06:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't get suspicious, but I have a hard time conceptualizing the fact that they might miss me if I died. Yeah, I may be fun 20% of the time, but that's not enough to actually care about someone. They all would just forget me and move on with life. Which would be fine, I rather that over causing immense amounts of guilt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 05:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You seem to be overthinking, but you can use location as a search if it really bothers you. 

I've haven't had a chance to use the website through, got my therapist through my school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 03:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/therapists](https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/therapists)

I can't guarantee that you can trust everyone on this website, but I'm sure it will make the search easier. You can sort by gender, age, insurance, specialization, etc. 

Your primary care doctor can recommend someone.  You can go directly through your insurance, asking for someone covered by them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 01:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use google docs or tape it to my wall in visible locations. But I've lost some notes too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 17:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's nasty as hell. Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 15:18:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Furries are weird, but they don't deserve the hate they received. It just became popular to hate them, continues to be perpetuated because it is an easy joke that works on a lot of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 15:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is very true. Kids have a *way easier* time getting weed than alcohol. Legalization allows for regulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 04:05:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe because being tired is associated with depression?

Last year, when I was incredible depressed I alternated between less than 5 and over 10 hours for months. I was exhausted every day and every other symptom was intensified: crying, angry outburst,  headaches, etc. Could have been part of the cause or a result, I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate that! Right now, I'm doing well considering the past couple of months. But I know all it takes is one day for me to wake up wrong. It all flips then I'm back in the cycle.

It's fucking harsh. I hope you're alright or will be alright soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> School is disgusting. I hate the "too young/overreacting" comments too. Just because they had normal childhoods doesn't mean no one else struggles. I don't doubt adulthood sucks, but child/teenhood sucks too. Also, I hate "high school is the *best* time of your life" more. If *this* is the peak of my life, I am actually afraid.  I want to get better so bad. I can only find the energy to drag myself through a day at a time and try not to be miserable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 02:31:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Society </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 00:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the e-girl/boy trend. Also, soft people, if that makes sense. Like, flowery, feminine, artsy.

I don't have a preference on race or hair color. If they are reasonably attractive and have good style, I'm interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 00:06:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with you. I notice that there has been an increase in "white hate" and it's unhealthy. My white friends  (I admit this group is limited, so it may not reflect all white people) have expressed guilt because of their race, internalizing the toxic behavior directed toward them. Any race can be racist and problematic/aggressive attitudes shouldn't be as accepted as they are currently. 

But nigger is not equal to cracker. I think most people would agree it has a stronger impact because of its ties to slavery, past and current racism. Not all slurs have the same impact. Still, I believe they shouldn't be used to attack others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 18:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it should be mandatory but instead *way* *more* accessible. I don't believe it is important enough to devote resources to and will be boring to most kids when they are forced to do it. That being said, I was in comp sci and advanced STEM classes and I think I understand some of the benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 18:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to watch it as a kid, but I don't find it funny anymore. 

I don't see why it's making a comeback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 15:50:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would the paparazzi be able to defend themselves with this law or is their only option to get beat up or run? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 03:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't enjoy warm liquid. Cold drinks are refreshing, hot drinks warm you up. Warm drinks are just *disgusting*, especially dairy. I don't care what cereal is trying to disguise the taste of *warm milk,* I simply refuse. This is basically sugary soup, I am appalled! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 02:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I disagree. Most people I know with younger siblings are burdened with extra responsibility and older siblings tend to get distant/problematic when they get pass mid-teens. I can't understand that being a positive experience even if they say they love each other. I probably don't understand because I've never really experienced that "sibling love". The loneliness is really only an issue with kids, past a certain age, it is better to be an only child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 02:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. No matter how much I sleep, my eyes feel so heavy and my head is a little foggy. I just feel like a switch flicked in my head and I do know how to turn it back on. I just had my first therapy session today, I *really* hope it works because I don't know what else to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 20:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH

It was unnecessary for you to snap at her, before that you seem like a great roommate. Her rules seem reasonable (no drinking, not eating her food, going to bed early), but her attitude is a BIG issue. 

I don't know if her attitude will change but I suggest trying to make an effort with her so you know you tried to remedy the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 20:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get that too, but I can't really enjoy it because either: I feel I'm faking because I was able to experience "normality"/happiness/contentment or I will go bad to feeling sad/angry/empty soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 07:57:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a good board on LetGo for $30. You could also look on Facebook Marketplace or ask around. I educated myself on brands and parts before so I didn't just buy an old Walmart board. Just use your best judgment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 03:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, tucking my legs in really helped my ollie get off the ground </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 02:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's so frustrating because of the learning curve but progress is rewarding. I find that I get the mood benefits similar to going to the gym. It's also faster than walking when I want to get around and it's another hobby to enjoy with friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 22:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They expect to be happy. They just live. They start off days normally and only feel sad due to life situations. They are content with mattering to their small circle of friends and family. Life is not horrible so they don't see a reason to stop it early. 

That's what I understand from asking friends. And sometimes I understand it too, but then I go back to feeling like shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 21:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes, but it's always an afterthought. I try not to linger on it though because either they wouldn't care or whatever pain or regret they feel would be tenfold in friends and family. I still wish I was less angry, so I wouldn't feel the need for revenge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 05:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate that too. They seem like they're having so much fun but I just can't seem to join in (even on good days). I feel weak in a way because I can only deal in smaller groups. 

Maybe one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 05:08:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never tried any other skate shoes, but vans feel good to me. It might be an issue with your feet. If you need more support you should buy shoe pads. 

If you have some durable shoes that are comfortable you can just skate in those. I wear my converse sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 04:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I went to my old school counselor in my sophomore year, she gave me a place to calm down after panic attacks and we had a couple of therapy session (CBT, I think). The school year ended before we were able to finish so I can't comment on how effective but she seemed to care a lot.

I'm a little scared to talk to my current one, but a lot of people go to her so I'm assuming she is helpful. I'm just forcing myself because I want/need a therapist and my mom won't help. Maybe tell someone (friend or family) and have them encourage you. Or give yourself a deadline. Also, try to think of possible positive outcomes too. Maybe they'll help with mental health days or homework extensions. Could even be a good therapist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unexpected Letterkenny in r/AskReddit </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 18:51:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  #x200B;

https://i.redd.it/5ym1l215kzm31.png

[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/d4yzjt/parents_of_reddit_at_what_point_did_you_realize/f0iwhid?utm_source=share utm_medium=web2x) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 04:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took mech eng last year. Me and the whole class were doing pretty well until they introduced Solidworks... Needless to say, it was a nightmare we all suffered through </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Skating on Fresh Sidewalk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 03:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was skating home today and noticed how good it feels to glide over smoooooth sidewalk. Ive obviously noticed it before, but I was so tired and it felt like bliss to not push my board over rough or cracked concrete. Next time you find some beautiful sidewalk, skate it for the boys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-14 17:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been feeling so tired and down recently despite my attempts to be positive, eat, and sleep over 8 hours. I don't want to relapse again, but I feel it's inevitable. 

At the same time, I don't feel valid because I am able to have some good days.  I'm just trying to make a therapist appointment before I talk myself out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-28 21:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Your" 

That makes me so uncomfortable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 19:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try to give them a bit more respect because I feel bad for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 16:25:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like it too, but I get stressed about the shower demon (as \\u\\FatThrobbingBigDick called it). So I use this speaker with rotating lights that I got a couple years back when I have time for a longer shower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 16:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shaming people is wrong, but everyone should at least have some idea what is going on. The people around me don't care at all, and they just join the majority. I'm not the best at keeping up, but I want to make sure I know current issues and 2020 candidates.

The people that you're describing are crazy tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 16:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get so pissed when people are limited by race or gender when cosplaying characters. 

I hate this cultural appropriation trend as well. It's so restricting and causing people to justify overreacting to issues that often don't exist. People deserve the chance to express and share culture without worrying about some dickhead getting mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 16:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like there is a limit to how far to you can darken your skin. A light to median tan shouldn't be a problem. Too dark and it looks wrong and is reminiscent of black face. I doubt your intention is to mock people of that complexion, but we should all are be moderately sensitive of history 

I also think it's weird for a black person lighten their skin significantly for a character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 15:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love artificial fruit flavors. If I wanted a fresh cherry, grape, strawberry, etc. I would eat it. I eat candy so I can taste sugar and citric acid in levels that real fruit can't provide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 02:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This game is so beautiful. I wish I was able to get out more, be a bit more rugged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 01:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get annoyed pretty easily. Everyone I've known has been bothered by it, but I don't really know how to fix the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 00:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Popular

I also just like bland foods in general. I feel like I need a balance of intense and more muted flavors in my life, they both complement each other. I'm not trying to be attacked by a spice fest in every meal, sometimes I just want to eat a plain dish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 00:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **Unpopular**  
It's been so normalized as a greeting that isn't really taken too seriously. If you really care, just start a conversation about in an appropriate place. Or get into the habit of talking about current events and emotions when you initially see your friends. That's what my friend group does, then we drift off into other stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 17:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I skate with friends if I can. I also just practice where it's empty. I live in the city and I can find a couple places where barely anyone is there.

 #x200B;

Edit: Also, try taking your board with you. It helped me become more comfortable being seen with it and I practice more when I have the option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 17:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the combination of both twist made season one so great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-21 13:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would get some. I haven't broken my arm or anything, but I feel a bit afraid to when learning tricks. Also I keep skinning my elbows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 21:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really enjoyed this scene. Feel like it completely captured how a good day feels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 21:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The holes would make sense to me but I don't anything about science. I believe the holes are created on impact. Like the outside of a bulletproof vest being blemished, but it isn't penetrated. The clothes are a thin layer covering his body, which is the part that actually defects. 

 #x200B;

Or he is absorbing them because the bullet seems to disappear. It's stupid, but would be funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 19:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've also noticed that a lot of the world's rules are broken. 

Like entering and exiting hell:

* When Lucifer first dies (shot by Malcolm), he uses the Pentecostal coin to leave hell.
* Then the second time he is killed (with defibrillator), he is able to leave by getting over his guilt.
* Finally, to get Abel's soul he just flies down. 

I don't know if I'm the idiot, but I wish it was explained more, and these issues are not only with hell. 

 #x200B;

That being said, I like the show's characters and although it can drag on at times and make me angry (Lucifer is a bit of a prick), I want the satisfaction of Lucifer and Chole together. I've invested so much time in, I want to see the end of the story. 

Also, the closeups are pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 18:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree. I don't hate the guy, but I am jealous of him and his work ethic. It's so hard to try and become a better and more productive person, so a lot of people don't  (I am one of them).  Instead, they resent people who are putting in work and succeeding or they act like it's impossible for them to reach the same or similar level of success. Maybe if I was more motivated, he would become an inspiration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>