<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2667</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-14 07:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're doing great, please continue to bless the world with this wonderful foam technique </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-14 07:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on how much you spend and how difficult your drink is.  If it's a standard build Frappuccino, then being a polite person is all I need. If you're a regular then a buck or two is good. If you ask for a secret menu drink or a bunch of drinks (+4) then 3-5 bucks would be ideal. 

Please do keep in mind that this is my somewhat arbitrary system based on what I'm used to at my store. 

You're probably doing okay since you actually care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-14 04:53:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be happy to make this drink when the customer is polite and tips for the time and effort.
So basically never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 16:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever one of my co-workers goes on a milk run, he yells out to the Kroger employees " I GOT A LOTTA OREOS AT HOME, AND I RAN OUT OF MILK"

Nobody ever says a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 16:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always had this but I've never known how to talk about it. On the rare occasions that I cry, after a little bit I'll still be physically crying but I stop feeling anything and start wondering why I'm even crying in the first place. I've had this ever since I can remember, and I can totally relate to this experience, if not the trauma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 16:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know we're all thinking it so here it is



Ok boomer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 15:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My store got a new one after one of the ovens caught on fire twice, that's all it took. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-10 23:20:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's really good! You deserve all that karma! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 18:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You get to see the next day and see the possible outcomes. This way you can never get caught in a traffic jam or have a fatal accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 14:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm one of those broken sad people and I almost wish that I had anger issues because then I'd at least be able to have some kind of motivation in my life. I know the grass is always greener on the other side, but man I don't know how I'll get through life without wanting anything out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 00:47:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can we start an Erin can thread? I feel like she gets overshadowed a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 03:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 02:38:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it does, sign me up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 02:36:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm thinking more about social media addiction and the instant gratification/stimulation problem that's arising, bit whatever floats your aquatic craft, my dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 02:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But is the social media outlet influencing how we behave on a daily basis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 02:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A ton of people are a-holes but less of them are racist. You have to deal with both parties, keep fighting the good fight.

May the Siren smite all the Karens in your district </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 02:15:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More helpful comments please. I'm here too and I'd like to want to get out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 02:07:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tenured partners are awesome, thanks for teaching ten years worth of new baristas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 02:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ....And may the Siren make your coffee hot and kill the scourge of Karens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 02:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It all depends on tone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 01:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you don't miss those days anymore, huh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 01:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would make our lives easier, of course there isn't an app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 16:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't want people to see the real me. People who know me and love me think I'm great, but I always think that there's something awful about me that people shouldn't see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make sure that when you're training that your trainee is the number one priority. Work with the shift on duty to be placed where you need to be on the floor, or not on the floor at all. Sometimes managers try to make trainers train while at another position and that just doesn't work. Give your trainee all of your attention so that you can give them the best start they can get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pumpkin spice just isn't that great of a flavor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you do something irl together then it's not that weird to text her about it later. If you're in a group with her it can be as simple as complementing something that happened or asking about future plans, then make your move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ataaaaaaaaack! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In that case, call your DM and let them know. The sandwich thing seems a little overkill, but it's not cool to have only one person in the store after close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can totally call FCC or Partner services, but in my experience they usually don't do too much even when there is a legitimate problem. 

If you do report it, don't let anybody know you're doing so. Once word gets out that can look badly on you if they're innocent but just neglecting rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The manager will immediately know if the cash count is off and the partner is stealing. They might just be trying to play it cool and not show their hand so that they can compile evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be interested in a Democratic monarchy if King Croc has an opinion about Healcare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Find events that you can join with people of similar interests. If they're at an event, they'll probably be fine with talking with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 15:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine how you'd respond if they treated somebody you care about like they treat you. 
Channel that feeling and make them realize they have better things to be doing with their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 14:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh heck no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 14:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no doubt, that shift was being a total butt. However, it's better for you to call off ahead of time and let them try to get coverage than to show up sick and unable to work. When you have a legitimate reason to call off, nobody can blame you for following the health code and respecting your fellow partners and the customers. As a shift at my store, it's so much better to have a notice in advance so I can plan accordingly than to learn that somebody's sick when they come in for a shift. 

The shift is was a jerk, but you put them in a tough situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 14:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> According to the pic, apparently not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 14:40:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are you doing this to me?

Because we're Starbucks, and life is a fucking nightmare.

Any other John Mulaney fans in the thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 06:29:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like this wasn't properly assesed either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 06:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One time some higher ups(2-3 degrees higher than our DM) visited our store and started walking behind the counter and interacting with DT customers during a rush when we only had three people on the floor. When I asked them what they did they said "Oh, we're partners."
Like we're a ducking Starbucks cult or something.

All hail the almighty Siren 
May she bless peaks and kill the scourge of Karens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 06:20:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always get Splenda and Equals stuck on the syrup so it forms a disgusting crust until I get a 10. Anybody else want to petition for 15's?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 06:17:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After a few months you can start to juggle between the window and the speakerbox naturally. You have to make once or the other wait a second or two when you take an order/receive payment and then switch. It's a rhythm thing that you CAN do, it just takes time and dedication.

Also you don't have to deeply interact with customers this way and if you're a super-introvert like me, that's a win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 06:08:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't agree more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 06:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 06:01:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Au Ag Pt they're all metals, so boring! Let's get some more electronegative element based rewards going on up in here! Can I get a Chlorine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 01:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Made me actually smile today. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 01:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh the internet is a skeleton because we're all secretly dead inside. I see you, meme-maker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 01:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *cries because of scary math food* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 01:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do it! Then you'll have a badass story about how you got your inspiration once it's done.
Then if you make it big you'll truly be living the dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 01:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thorsday-god of weekdays is the next contestant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 20:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in a similar battle against anxiety but when I got a job it really helped me with some portions of it. After a while I stopped caring about what my co-workers thought of me and just had fun with some of them when I could. One of those coworkers is my best friend now and we text every day. You might not have the same experience, but it was really helpful for me.

The battle is worth it, keep fighting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do I really need friends? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 20:37:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a college student and I don't have many friends. I have some friends back home that rock, but none at my college.

People keep telling me that I have to make friends and get a group, but I don't feel like I need people in my life. I'm much more comfortable being by myself, however I feel strange that I'm not with people like the normal people here.

I suffer from anxiety so I feel weird and out of place with people but I also feel weird without anyone here.

Any advice for making friends halfway through the semester is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 20:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know if I can finish my first semester at college. I'm getting A's and B's but my mental health isn't great and I don't know if I can do anything, much more have a functional life. 

I'm supposed to choose classes for next semester but I haven't even applied for the loans yet.

I'm supposed to want things for my life but I'm numb and I don't want anything. I'd rather just stay in my room and eat/sleep/not think about how badly I think I'm doing.

People say that with determination you can do anything, but I'm all outta determination juice.

Occasionally I get somewhat motivated, but I still don't believe that I can do this even though literally everyone in my life says I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 18:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sew, a needle pulling thread! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 18:19:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this Break'NEnter thieves emporium? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 18:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either Santa is way to fricking late or that man's handwriting is the worst ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 17:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My heart is melting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>