<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5949</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 20:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.electronics-notes.com/articles/ham_radio/amateur-propagation/moonbounce-propagation-eme.php

Here's the basics of how it works. Just looked it up myself and it's interesting. You can do it with a decent ham radio. Go try it and see what you think. You can use it to pick up long distance radio signals from other places on the globe. Kinda neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 22:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Almost all of these I have multiple answers that apply but i can only choose 1. For instance i watch documentaries on YouTube AND streaming services </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 17:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True. Mostly saying that if you say no to the first question you still may be interested in the product, but the survey says skip to the end if it's a no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 13:45:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link to the survey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 13:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this is only for current houseplant owners you should mention that in your title. Also note I currently do not own a indoor houseplant because I have difficulty keeping them alive which may actually be a niche for you as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 09:40:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or a pit orchestra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 22:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If someone makes a meat alternative that has a similar or better eating and prep experience (taste, smell, texture, ease of cooking/flavoring) at a same or cheaper price point I will happily never eat meat again. But honestly I'm not that swayed by cow emotional capability. I already know pigs are smart and empathetic and I eat them without issue. I'm better swayed by ecological or economic impact, but that economic benefit needs to pass on to the consumer too (which I realize currently is an issue of infrastructure, demand, and novelty) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 20:21:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pst... Look at the question that's the title of this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 17:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7749 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 15:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On mobile or I'd shop it, but results fit too well to ignore. 
Ystalyfera Transmiting Station "All lead to God"
[Album cover](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Martis_Chiesa_di_San_Pantaleo.JPG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Witch-mafia encounters/flavor/fluff ideas </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 16:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some background real quick: My game's a modern (1999) set game with secret cabals using magic and legendary creatures/myths to influence and control various societies. My PCs have wandered into Sedona, AZ which is controlled by a group of 3 witches using a combination of transmutation/animal control, diseases/necromancy, general scrying and sympathetic magic for a general racketeering and blackmail scheme where local businesses pay "protection money" through offerings. The witches themselves hide behind proxies/minions, and the PCs don't know everything going on yet.


Any ideas for flavorful events/encounters to hint at the witches control. So far they've investigated a series of animal infestations that forced the health department to shut down businesses and destroyed an extremist church (that was harboring/training a witch hunter that may be an obstacle/reluctant ally). I also plan on a proxy trying to steal hair clippings/blood/etc in some way. Any ideas of similar surreal events/counter attacks/etc from the witches? Ideas for their lair(s)/front businesses/other mafia-like activities would be appreciated as well.

TLDR: I want ideas for witch lead mafia encounters set in modern times. Surreal/spooky appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 19:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might have answered my own question. I found on the [kickstarter](https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/sonofoak/nights-of-payne-town-a-new-story-arc-for-city-of-m/posts/2480468) update it's saying end of may hopefully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any idea when the expansion pdfs release? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 19:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I preordered about a month ago. No word from Sons of Oak and the website still says they're due in April. Is there an announcement somewhere I missed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 19:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The OneShot podcast did a series where they played a scenario with some of the pre-gens. I liked it's blend of fate and PbtA as well as the setting and now I'm playing a game with regular group, though it's gotten decidedly not city based by virtue of their world creation in our first session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 22:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of shredder from TMNT. Looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-19 19:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice, that was actually a strategy I was thinking of. Thanks for the answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 23:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or, Hens Going to Wager </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 23:14:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you not aim the dog for the dog drop? That move seems much less worth it if you cant aim(from a foot above  obviously) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 23:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. Including pawns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 16:16:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I agree with OP, I've done both off and on through my life and always feel better eating junk. I get depressed and angry pretty frequently when dieting (no matter what form that takes) and often crash out after about 1-3 months in. It's gotten to the point that I'm scared to diet cause I feel so horrible and feel like I have to sleep all day (though I'm doing well on my current plan so far). I've never felt better eating healthy than when I eat whatever I want other than very short term stuff like feeling over full or something. I wish more than anything else that I did feel better on a calorie deficit, that's why it's so hard to do.

Similarly, I've been lifting for about 6-7 years and very rarely feel good from workouts, but I continue cause I like the results (getting stronger) and sometimes I feel accomplished.  Overall, it's very much a chore and not "fun". Again, I'd love it if I got some sort of high from working out, but doesn't seem in the cards for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 15:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With any tougher cut with lots of connective tissue/collagen you will render that tough stuff into gelatin making it much more tender. Basically anything you'd cook low and slow via another method (smoking/braising). With sous vide though you can do much lower temps, though you'll have to go longer in the bath. Basically longer=more collagen break down=more tender. There's gonna be limitations and preferences as with anything else obviously. Some people like 12 or 24 hour short ribs, others shoot for 48-72, but there will be texture differences with each level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-04 21:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was deciding this myself. Besides what the other guy said, I just wanted to note that you can get a few bucks off if pre-ordering both off the city of mist store (it's 30 for both pdfs). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-02 17:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh. Awesome. I guess I should have done a quick look before asking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Virtual tabletops or the like? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-02 06:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, I'm looking to start up a new game soon online with some friends and was wondering what people use online for keeping track of all the statuses, story tags, etc etc. Any particular virtual tabletops/programs/whatever people have found effective? Any screenshots or video of how people have laid out their virtual tabletops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-19 20:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MDIC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-16 01:03:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like your foam rocks and snow and shrubbery. I dont love that dang tree kinda pulls me out of it. Just looks faker than the rest. 

Also, minor, but some of the smaller rocks kind of merge into the base part of the foam. Maybe carve in a little more or add snow or dirt or something to add a little contrast and delineate the small rocks better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-03 19:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Corn tags </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-25 13:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Funky Spiderman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 00:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not important. Just a dumb observation you're getting way more into than I expected. No worries. I'm done. Have a good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 19:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which would put you, I'd guess, over 45 as it came out 39.5 years ago.

I've seen it, but only due to it being featured on MST3K. Also a few years after The Island came out so age seems irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 19:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pst.... That movie's actually 40 years old. I'm sorry for you loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 04:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People think it's real, but it's really just extreme pirating or a natural obstacle like the edge of a flat world or something cool. Or vice versa! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 21:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or lack thereof, cause it was highly improvised leading to the shittastic dialogue. I'd blame the director primarily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Patrick Carney - BoJack's Theme </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-27 14:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-02 19:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know right? However, having done some research into Thelema and Crowley before coming across the podcast it's pretty apt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-02 19:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You got it. Hail yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-01 03:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It be very impressive if he did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-31 22:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>   Sex partners are the absolute most valuable items.

It wouldn't be famed power-bottom Aleister Crowley if that wasn't in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 23:34:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you saying Boo? Or Buuuuuuuuuurns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-01 23:20:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would also  suggest gumshoe potentially if you want it to be more investigative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-01 23:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or cursed AND enchanted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 19:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Proof Hillary is a ROBOT!](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/La1oMBgphEk/maxresdefault.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-08 14:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Macadamia oil is decent for high heat cooking too as its pretty low in omega 6. Lowest of the nuts in PUFAs in general so youre not getting a lot of omega 3s either. Its a easy to use neutral tasting oil so I end up using it as a staple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-08 02:38:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  That sounds awesome! Id love to see it when youre done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-07 21:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty out of the loop cause I had no idea. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any good setting/conversions out there for this system? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-07 21:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this has been asked before, but all posts I can find on it seem to be from at least a year ago. Any toolsets/conversions to fun settings anyone has come across other than the obvious "Edge of the Kingdom" one? Anything for Spy/action, cthulhu mythos, superhero, star trek, or really anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-14 17:55:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For one character? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-03 14:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rubbin the ol weasel eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-31 16:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has a small hole even when closed so its gonna allow some release of poopstank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-23 14:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [The theme from Bojack Horseman](https://youtube.com/watch?v=2moynDt9Fq4)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-23 14:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Preacher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-14 23:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They saved jazz once, now theyll have to do it again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-16 22:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ours is "The FlooNetwork" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-11 19:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The problem being, those require good writing, directing, and acting, while gore-fests can get away with much more mediocre everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-09 14:50:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, volcanoes should erupt more often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 21:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> #\#MugatuDidNothingWrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-01 16:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean that was Office clips played over Avengers, so that's part of it. And I'm not sure Spader really won any awards with those roles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-01 14:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [And he plays the same character in the Avengers](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tf-_230SjbM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-25 16:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/interdimensionalcable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-24 15:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, share with the class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-12 18:18:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did the same thing. Mine comes tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-07 22:27:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought Jess doesn't have an ept slot...

EDIT: R2-D6! Realised after I posted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-24 12:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a cool idea. I'm glad I was accidentally on r/all today to bump into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-21 04:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Pretty much what I was going for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Starviper and Scyk repaints </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-19 01:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-15 05:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember these on Newgrounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-15 03:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is amazing! You don't see enough duet style mashups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. Guy 5'10" lowest at 145lbs. 8 years of college and I'm at 270lb. I have been lifting like three times a week for the last 5 years so a chunk of that is muscle, but I'm probably 80lbs worth of fat over where I'd like to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:34:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I have a basement office in our town home and despite what temperature the house is it gets pretty cold. Normally I actually enjoy this, but in the winter it can get a bit ridiculous so I'd bundle in blankets and things. Noting this, my wife (then fianc) made me a fantastic faux fur lined night's watch style cloak that I could wrap up in to stay warm, but wouldn't have to take off if I had to do things around the house. It's the best and I still use it all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're saying this youtube is HAUNTED?!~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Homing missiles on the Inquisitor are a bit unnecessary as you already have a pretty strong attack from  range 2-3. Prockets can be nice as they discourage people getting in real range 1 of him. Lone wolf is usually redundant as you'll probably be TLing every round anyways and you cant Errol twice. PTL or juke both work well instead. Autothrusters are nice as well if you have them or maybe stealth device if you don't. 

If you're doing Ryad with a cannon put the TIE/D title on. Or drop the cannon and put on TIE/x7 which she excels with. Consider Vessery for TIE/D builds as his ability works well with it and he synergises well with others wanting TLs like inquisitor (though you have to not use it before he gets to go, VI can help). Marksmanship works okay for TIE/D due to the double attackbut if you go x7 predator or PTL gets more mileage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play around with that sweet super-slamming, bomb dropping, regenerating craziness. I'll bring the space jam slam on my buddies! Also, connor nets and TLTS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're like maybe 2-5cm by 1cm maybe 2mm thick. I have no idea where to find it in Europe, but in the US you can find it in like the specialty flours in grocery stores or in health food stores. You want to make sure they're unsweetened for paleo as sometimes they add sugar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Savory Coconut flakes.](https://www.ourpaleolife.com/savory-coconut-flakes/) Sometimes I switch out the seasonings. Salt and pepper, curry, lime, various vinegars, taco type seasoning and logical combos of the above have all been pretty good too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:04:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started about a month and a half ago, buying a used collection on eBay to get me started

The subreddit has helped me fuel my obsession building new lists and checking out new strategies, builds, tutorials, repaints etc. Overall it's been great to have a subreddit that helped pull my attention over constantly reading toxic political threads which I had gotten stuck doing constantly with the election. 

I so far love all the factions. I've mostly played empire, but I'm crazy about building lists for all three.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And doesn't even look her in the eyes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So is /r/peoplefuckingdying actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:45:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're not going to use missiles on the A-wing, there's no reason not to take the Chardaan refit which will give you two more points to spend. 

Edit-a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:23:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> X-wing would work pretty well these days too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My first list I ever made was basically this build, plus Ten Numb with a mangler cannon and Biggs to keep them around a bit longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That bubbly-hex pattern on the front and wing tips looks amazing. Airbrush with a stencil? Or something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Geez. That's amazing, but so tedious. I feel you should just play armada if you want that scale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-19 06:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, he did get Harley to provide the "Phantom's Own" laundry service truck hint which *subtly* influenced batman to think about the phantom zone. So, not entirely unorchestrated IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Apparently there is](https://www.flickr.com/photos/57174319@N07/6321476357)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:54:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely something I'll eventually get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the one, but I guess lambda spam could be fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:25:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a really good point. The only one I saw there last time I dropped by was a plain starfield one. Is the official one great quality or are there better options out there both for looks and grip?

E: forgot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I haven't seen strikers in action much yet. I'll have to look into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:20:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's def a contender too, forgot to mention it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help me blow 40 bucks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit: grabbed a shadow caster and some imp veterans(going a bit over my original plan...). Thanks for advice everyone. 

So I just realised I have a Barnes and noble gift card with about $40 on it from Christmas and figured it's a good way to throw some money at xwing without feeling like I'm actually spending anything. 


So, what should I spend it on? Currently leaning toward a large ship, either a scum ship or one of the yt-1300 options. Also maybe a quad jumper cause they look fun. Any suggestions? Willing to spend a little more than the $40 potentially 



Current collection is:

3tie/fo (including a blue starter

3 tie fighters (inc red starter)

3 tie interceptors ( imp aces)

1 tie bomber

1 tie punisher

1 tie phantom

1 tie defender

1 tie advanced

1 tie advanced prototype

1 firespray 31

1 lambda class shuttle

1 yt 2400 freighter

2 b wings (reb aces)

1 k wing

1 a wing

2 y wings

1 e wing

2 x wings

1 t70 x wing

1 hwk 290

3 z 95 head hunters (most wanted)

1 m3a interceptor

Thanks guys!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's one I was thinking about. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome man. Looks great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:58:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm totally okay with any of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any fun lists you can make out of this collection? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi everybody,

After playing a few times I took the plunge and bought somebody's pretty sizeable used collection on eBay. A buddy is coming over this weekend and I was wondering if any of you wonderful people have fun lists using these ships or basic ship combos that are fun to try out. Fun/interestingcompetitive in general. 


Here's the ships:

3 tie Fo

3 tie fighters

3 tie interceptors

1 tie bomber

1 tie punisher

1 tie phantom

1 tie defender

1 tie advanced

1tie advanced prototype

1 firespray 31

1 lambda class shuttle

1 yt 2400 freighter

2 b wings

1 k wing

1 a wing

2 y wings

1 e wing

2 x wings

1 t70 x wing

1 hwk 290

3 z 95 head hunters

1 m3a interceptor


This includes one of each starter, an imperial and a rebel aces set, and Most Wanted. 

Thanks guys, and sorry for such a vague/daunting task, I'm just a bit overwhelmed and thought the Reddit hivemind might already have some good ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:01:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks great! It's like in game when it moves from your normal walking model to a pre-rendered cutscene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have not seen that one. Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Somehow with the contrasting text or something my brain is really oscillating between seeing this as an innie or an outie cube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to nitpick too much, but West Point is free to any who are accepted (plus I think you get a stipend). That said, it is an incredibly rigorous and selective school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doing a wash will certainly help give some definition. Also, not using absolute pure white except for some highlights. Mix in some light grey. 


All being said, I like the lab rat idea for a Skaven blood bowl team. Personally I'd try and find/modify a mini to look like brain to add to the team, or at least for the sidelines as a coach or something. (Disclaimer: I know very little about blood bowl. ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May want to read the title again.  There's [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l8U0IaMsRf4) of him boasting of it, whether he actually assaulted people or not is not contained in that headline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The haven/heaven thing always bugged me at my local popcorn place </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the irony of the composition of these photos. It shows a picture of several "liberals" having all sorts of different reactions during some sort of protest and labels them as all the same. Then it says conservatives just want you to think, but shows all the "conservatives" striking one of two poses. Not exactly an image of thinking for oneself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The heavy metallic look gives a bathysphere vibe to the TIE cockpits. Almost steampunk. Probably not my thing for imperials, but I do like it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just bought a pretty sizable fleet off of ebay to get into this(30 small ships 3 large), and I've been looking for storage solutions so this is great!


Looking into the 1374 plano, I keep seeing reference to finding them for 20-30 bucks. Has anyone gotten them that cheap? Best I can find online is like 45ish. Is that a price at some brick and mortar store or do I just need to wait for an online deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you're saying in an alternate universe our Lord was in Dumb and Dumber, allowing it to win an academy award? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be c-ware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:58:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> #\#getoffmylawn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-18 06:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can get it in the chicagoland area. However, personally I couldn't get into that flavor. I really like the lime, cherry-lime, tangerine, and (after some getting used to) coconut flavors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FYI, molecular bio is usually quite math and chemistry heavy, so it may not be what you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries. I only knew cause I was reading the top posts for some spooky Halloween fun this last week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:59:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the [all time top post](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/3iex1h/im_a_search_and_rescue_officer_for_the_us_forest/?st=IUZMCXRP sh=27b28637)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did they use to fail at a higher rate though? That's really the important part here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-04 21:10:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So... neither easy nor reliable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:49:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That indeed would be a racist statement if he thought they were crazy *because* they are latina. It doesn't necessarily mean the person is racist, but it does mean the action they took is based in racial prejudice. However, if he just thinks this specific group of latina women he knows are crazy, then that's not racist assuming he doesn't then think *all* (or most) latina women are crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 02:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Find out, after the break! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries, I get you.  I know you weren't really trying to be a dick about it. I just thought it was funny saying this judgment is not elitist while at the same time saying they've probably only had shitty, cheap, or badly prepared steaks. You see the elitism there right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your explanation certainly didn't make it sound less elitist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:29:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Well, you got the first part right, but the second part is just a myth.](http://www.snopes.com/risque/homosex/sagging.asp) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a sign! Like those waterstains that look like the virgin Mary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be having a satire stroke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Semen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's just a stupid internet slang thing, like IMHO or ITT or all those. Don't know what to tell ya. It "makes sense" as long as you know what it means, but that doesn't mean it doesn't sound dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-02 17:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> inb4=in before. As in they typed something prior to some expected response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If they got all the way to 9 it seems like they can count pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats! I'm jealous cause I'm at 14.8!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's some redditor's compilation of fascist Trump things if you're actually interested](https://www.reddit.com/r/EnoughTrumpSpam/comments/4teoxl/a_final_response_to_the_tell_me_why_trump_is_a/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-02 04:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gambling, especially on completely non-skill based and non-predictable outcomes (lotto, most casino games, etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-23 01:59:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most? Also, do you happen to have a source for that, cause some people above are shedding some doubt on that concept and I'd love to know the substantiated truth on the topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Psh, I WISH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a white male doctor that scored 49/100 (not priveleged).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-16 15:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like yours btw. Especially the tentacle pool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-16 15:49:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Must have warped. Is definitely angled more down than yours. No big deal, I'm gonna base her a bit later and make it look better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-16 14:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Honestly, I kinda stole it from a [google searched image](http://forum.reapermini.com/uploads/monthly_03_2015/post-13800-0-28148500-1426564780.jpg) of a two toned version of this guy. But then I felt like it would be extra "reptile-y" if I did some red-orange in there like a lot of poisonous snakes and the like have on their scales. Also kind of an inside joke with my pathfinder group as my bard mis-identified a baby green dragon as a blue dragon. I thought I'd make it primarily green and teal to make that seem reasonable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The pose does seem a bit funny from that angle, but that's how he model comes and I don't think I could change it much with bones stuff. Might be my bad photography angles, as I was just trying to take a pic for my wife. 


The horns are offwhite, but I did want more of a transition from brown than I really ended with. So I'll probably go back and fix that sometime. Thanks!

Edit: phone autocorrect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My first post on here I think. Reaper Bones dragon "Nartrax" CC welcome. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:23:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-08 17:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was a hard impact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, I feel ya. I've backed like 8 kickstarters and have more minis than I can probably ever paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-06-04 02:17:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An instrument... OF OPPRESSION!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-24 00:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No worries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-23 23:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, why? Think I'm someone specific? Don't like Zoolander quotes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You serious?! I just... I just told you that... A moment ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-06 21:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who are invariably princes, so feel free to kiss them to turn them back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-04 02:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand your point, though I feel it would be hard to hit much of a bottleneck unless you were doing some very heavy handed selection. For instance, if we were just selecting for autism it would have a very negligible effect unless autism confers some sort of immunity or survival advantage currently unknown. Depends on the depth we are going here. If you're going for a "completed version of humanity" then you are indeed likely to hit a bottleneck. But seeing that I can't see a way this would be possible on any sort of species wide scale, I doubt it matters if the completed guys get wiped by future malaria or something similar. 

So while I feel that for the theory of eugenics the bottleneck may be the strongest argument but for implementation, I doubt it would be much of a hurdle as long as you controlled for it. Social and political issues I feel would be a far bigger obstacle for actual implementation because populations wouldn't accept it. That is of course is all speculation though and depends on a myriad of details. But either way we can agree to disagree. 

Btw I'm not particularly pro or con for eugenics, just offering a Hitler-free counter argument of the first thing that came to my head. Also, not angry at all, so I hope it didn't come off that way. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-02 23:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By the time we understand all that I feel like we'll be able to simply use gene therapy to change anything disease related in the genome. I feel that'd be a more ethical way of doing it than classic breeding eugenics, though it could still be abused obviously if this was authoritarian state enforced, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-02 22:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We were talking about the movie idiocracy in this case which is a movie that assumes the premise that intelligence is pretty much entirely heritable and the unintelligent outbreed the smart. 

I see where you are coming from for your concept and do not disagree completely, but currently it would be entirely uninforcable without some extreme authoritarian government overhaul. 

Also, we don't understand genetics nearly enough to be effective at this. Epigenetics, or how environment including diet, stress levels, etc effect gene expression, is just starting to be understood and is a huge component of how complex genes function. Similarly, gene therapy is becoming more reliable. If we can just turn a gene off or control its expression for a genetic disease why bother sterilising the individual?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-02 22:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My personal opinion is more that I don't trust the people in power to make a utopia or to share goals with the general populace. I also don't think you can breed a utopia cause behaviour, I feel, is weighted a bit more toward nurture than nature, especially with factors like epigenetics where it's nurture effecting nature. 

Genetic bottleneck would be somewhat hard to come by unless we're talking about some very extreme eugenics here. Are you talking about breeding humans to the level we do for dogs where individuals are assigned mates and/or are likely to be somewhat incestuous? Or just light eugenics like manditory abortion of people with certain genetic/developmental disorders (which was my assumption due to the context of this thread)? It's unlikely the latter would cause much of a bottleneck. I like that it's arbitrarily the "best" argument according to you though just because it's the one you most agree with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:55:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen enough smart people make idiot children and vise versa to think that you can fully breed idiocy out of a population. Seems more nurture than nature to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never heard of it. 

Seriously though, this I guess could be a weird sarcastic statement but I see no indication of that. More likely it's a troll and/or a mid to late teenager with "edgy" ideas IMO. On the off chance they were serious I spent two minutes giving a non-Hitler answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the most basic reason not to support eugenics is the general human rights issue of not allowing a basic function of life (reproduction) for consenting individuals based on whatever criteria those in power decide upon. If you're not the one determining the criteria that's a scary thing and easily abused. In terms of racial or even demographic based eugenics (AKA Jewish people and folks with autism can't breed and must be castrated) it is basically a form of genocide, albeit a bit less direct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-07 02:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hah. Nice ending zinger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-04-07 02:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. That may be the worst person I've seen on the Internet. I'm sorry you had to deal with such a malicious person. They're trying to tear you down to feel better about themself. They are the worst kind of person and you were right to try and stand up to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-29 15:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Noah's McArk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-17 01:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TIFU by crying into my gf's blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-16 15:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zombicide: Black Plague.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-03-01 18:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, set that to 0.5 speed and it kinda sounds like Hugh Jackman!

^^^^^^^but ^^^^^^^not ^^^^^^^really... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-22 21:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you mean the picture in the heading, that's David Schwimmer. I guess this could be David Schwimmer's blog, but probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-20 18:55:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is literally black face.
Edit: /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-15 21:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They also missed the opportunity to say "*mash* together" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-15 21:37:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Avocado? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-15 21:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, check in every once in a while a post some weird stuff on here.

edit: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:46:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/BetrayalVideos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:14:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/coaxedintoasnafu  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-01-08 21:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, check your white privilege. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-31 14:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you wouldn't mind, please add me as well. I plan to stop eating junk when I'm stressed/bored and lose at least 40lbs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-31 00:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Get your ass to Mars!](http://m.youtube.com/watch?v=fpUVPvsIF5w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-23 20:50:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like this person needs more RAM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:47:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't tell, probably because I can't read the original, but I'm pretty sure this is satire. Seems along the lines of An Indecent Proposal from the awkward translation (IMO) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, so was I. Just looked like a humble brag. 

It is though. It's also entirely possible to have no sex with opposite sex friends and keep a friendship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-11 21:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Subtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-11 20:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So... you want to prove their point that doctors wouldn't know how to treat fat people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-12-05 02:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not even close. 

Next week it'll be "These 31 Root Vegetables are Kicking Cis-Heteronormativity's Ass"

Featuring: This spud knows just because zhe has phallic protrusions doesn't make zher any less of a Womayne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-24 20:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Hooooly shit...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FPKOSvo3AJM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-24 03:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My fave is Leap Day Williams starring Jim Carrey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-24 02:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like he was looking for some fingering instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-21 07:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So Tities come in pairs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-07 02:45:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, it's a group of terrorists that took over the Big Shell led by Fortune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-04 00:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone know what Kojima quote the SJW was mentioning? I'm curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:18:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Auto-murder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to have arguments with a woman's studies major on facebook similar to these, though slightly better backed up. There seems to be a SWJ movement to revert to a small community, tribal "anarchism" where everyone would just be responsible and have tons of free time somehow. She basically said it could only happen after a semi-apocalyptic situation or revolution which killed off most of the population (and what she was rooting for). She said laws would be unnecessary cause basically community opinion/implied mob rule would hold everyone in check. When I asked about what she thought would happen when the neighboring tribe that found an old military depot came through conscripting and enslaving her tribe with superior force she had no answer and ended up very mad at me. I gave up on the arguing cause it was too deep and now I just post crazy articles she puts up here on TIA periodically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-29 02:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This kinda hits home for me.

I knew a guy like this in college. Roommate turned arch-nemesis due to reasons unrelated to the story. Years later, he did this to a very emotionally vulnerable (depression/maybe a PD) friend of mine by buying her a bike and an iPad using school loan money. Because of the mental state she was in the guilt actually did lead her into a relationship with him, which turned somewhat abusive. In order to "help" her overcome some issues with negative behaviors  she had he would withhold sex and/or affection. Really, just an awful person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-29 02:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Racist... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [TW: Not tumblr] Everyday optimistic phrases=Gaslighting (x-post TumblrPls) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 21:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (TW: Not tumblr) Everyday optimistic phrases are the equivalent of emotional abuse! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 21:50:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-28 19:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever they mess with language like this I get serious 1984 vibes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-22 19:58:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But why male models? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-16 02:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing. Everything is equally the worst, forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-10-16 02:07:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [There's even a song about it](http://m.youtube.com/watch?v=5g196vURUDo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-29 07:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [They wouldn't agree apparently.](https://www.google.com/search?q=vegan+social+justics oq=vegan+social+justics aqs=chrome..69i57j0.3981j0j7 sourceid=chrome es_sm=93 ie=UTF-8#q=vegan+social+justice) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-25 20:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fine with it. Wife is fine with it. Doesn't really happen often outside of group settings for either of us though (drinking with mixed gender friend groups).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-22 18:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, really. Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-17 02:13:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they were talking more about welfare for poorer single mothers. Which really isn't any better, but slightly less hypocritical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-16 18:05:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chiropractor (M), electrical engineer(F), bank teller (F), CS guy (M), Locksmith (M), and waste water treatment chemical engineer (F). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-15 20:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But Zooey's a [Zelda.](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=2 cad=rja uact=8 ved=0CCcQtwIwAWoVChMI3_TU1tX5xwIVybgeCh09-Azu url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3Dqb80Hexd1Aw usg=AFQjCNG1d6X2PgpKP5yHYgNk2VAKets5gA sig2=enjpJ624MS28jklmn4T5VA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-11 21:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Human bystander effect right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-11 21:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [And to reduce pain!](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hypoalgesic_effect_of_swearing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-10 20:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For what? That sweet sweet 20 points of Karma? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-10 20:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No real clue. Don't know him or the wife very well. He joins my workout group sometimes cause he works with a couple of the other guys at a repair shop. I was surprised to hear he was a RP as he seems like an otherwise ok guy but one day he just started telling down on his luck gym buddy to try RP stuff cause it worked really well for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-10 19:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I may have seen this girl at the ren faire this weekend. Whoa! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-10 02:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only red piller I know IRL went on and on about how the process of getting his wife pregnant was terrible because it meant a few months of "boring, terrible [non-anal] sex" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-10 02:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Odd your getting downvoted. IMO they're very similar except /r/niceguys tends to be a bit less depressing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-09-09 19:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eh, Kojima's kinda all about going overboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-28 23:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I've never seen someone offering a archive to Jezebel downvoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey! Cracked seems to be making some actually entertaining articles again! That's good news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was a correctional officer. I choose to take this possible typo as an amazing play on words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys, he's Chaotic Neutral. That simultaneously means he doesn't give a shit about your social standards and is just misunderstood. He's just playing his alignment. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-27 18:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She-bagging? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-14 15:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw this one coming too, but the facial expression and push still made me laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-13 19:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's 4h. But it's real time so you don't have to be playing the game that entire time. Timers keep running while the game's off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-13 15:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nowadays I think they even bring the celeb in and do multicam 3D imaging to get everything right. 

Source: I think I remember that from the Colbert Report episode where he was made into a wax statue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-12 16:41:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's on the back of his shirt. Clearly he doesn't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-03 19:52:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vagintionary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-08-02 16:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Thug: I don't know where the drugs are! I s2g!*

*Batman: s2m!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-31 20:58:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saw [this](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ldWf5Yj-RnI) earlier this week which suggests differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-28 20:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think he meant the scene from Always Sunny that is at the beginning of this comment tree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's white though, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 19:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've done a lot of different things, extreme(ish) and not. All seems to do it or I just kinda fall off the wagon of it cause there was no real plan/stakes/rules/whatever. Thanks though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 19:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totes jealous, but congrats on all the success. 

I cook and like healthy food in general (as well as unhealthy ones). Just seem to crash and burn after about 20-30 days of dieting (up til then I'm usually happy and fine), then all the sudden I just want to sleep like 12h a day and not do anything productive. That's when I get crazy needs for junk food and weird stuff like anger responses to smells food that's not what I want. I feel like some sort of out of control animal rather than my normal self.  It always seems like I have the opposite reaction as everyone else too, food cravings and emotional stuff is always fine for the month or so and then I just go crazy with it. I don't seem to really get hungry at any point, just cravings for specific nonsense. I lift, walk and dance regularly for the past 5y whether dieting or not. I'm a chiropractor with a B/S in biochem as my undergrad so it's especially frustrating to me as I know the science and studies and strategies that are successful for high percentages of people, but it doesn't seem to work for me thusfar.

Sorry to vent weirdly. It's honestly the biggest stressor in my life now that I'm out of school so it somtimes wears on me a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get depressed after about a month of dieting (so far every strategy I've tried that has worked has lead to this in the past 5 years, and its the only time I'm ever depressed). Still a lame excuse and it's not stopping me from trying, but I honestly have a bit of a fear response to it and that stops me from moving forward with weight loss. I end up not really being able to function though and it continues until about 10 days after I start eating junk again, so until I can find a way around that I'm probably staying bigger than I'd like to be unfortunately. Not one who usually buys into food addiction junk, but honestly I don't know what else may be going on. Done supplementation and lab tests and shit, so far no insight from that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah, gotcha. You can certainly do that but it's not entirely fat loss (mostly water) and usually not a permanent or sustainable change. 

Wrestling is kinda notorious for causing eating disorders and stuff. I work out with a few HS wrestlers from time to time and hear this stuff constantly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 17:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, you understand that you can increase the calories spent and achieve a difference there as well, correct? That part is usually done via exercise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right, it's possible, just not gonna work for everyone or even probably like 20% of people. That's all I meant, and that usually the problems more with diet rather than lack of motion. That's a crazy amount from just workouts in a month btw. Glad it worked for ya! Mind if I ask what you did?

Edit: Just to clarify. The ideal is to do BOTH diet and exercise obviously. Studies mostly show diet works better for loss if used exclusively, but people who exercised as well had an easier time sustaining their weight loss afterword. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:32:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First guy did. I assumed you were in the same boat as I thought it was implied by your response. My bad I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-22 16:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eh, no offence but you're pretty wrong about minimal exercise being the only thing you need. My guess is while you eat "bad things" you're still only around your bMR. Most experts say it's gotta be at least 80% diet to get weight loss results. Admittedly my diet is probably even shittier than yours, but I've been walking 2mi with my dog for 5 years, doing heavy lifting with a trainer 3x per week for 3 years, and ballroom dancing about 3-5h per week for the past year with my wife. While this has certainly lead to me becoming much stronger/graceful/able in general, I've still gained about 60lbs in those five years. High stress of my school drove me to some bingey behaviours and I still haven't really beaten them now that I've graduated. If just a tiny amount of exercise works for you then that's awesome, but if most people won't change diet too then nothing will really happen for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-20 18:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AH! I'm watching this episode RIGHT NOW!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-17 06:28:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lucked out and picked up a Kaladrax in box for 13 bucks about a month ago from a "garage sale" at a local gaming shop. Really happy about that one. Got the clockwork dragon for $6 too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-16 02:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He  *finished* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You probably haven't heard of him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:07:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine a peanut butter and jelly sandwich. 

Was the jelly in the sandwich grape?

That's FuckinGrapeCulture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 22:02:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/infectiouslaughter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 16:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're kids and were probably just expecting to be able to push him around and bully him a bit. Serious fight probably threw them off and likely none of the aggressors wanted or expected any sort of real fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-07-10 02:15:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are decently high paying jobs for the education requirements, and honstly probably does contribute pretty heavily to the perceived "wage gap." I know around me at least garbagemen get pretty great benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh she gets it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's how I always sing this song in the car with my wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-19 02:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BTW [Here's a source for some tubes!](http://www.amazon.com/K-S-Engineering-320-Assortment/dp/B0006MZMHS/ref=sr_1_4?ie=UTF8 qid=1434672616 sr=8-4 keywords=metal+tubing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 17:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Harry Potter and the Neuromancer. 

A highly magically augmented Tonks approaches a down on his luck, drugged out Harry 15 years after Hogwarts. She offers a job to help free a magically enhanced AI that was broken into six pieces all placed inside of objects and creatures across the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-18 02:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Psh, neurotypical psych students? That'll be the day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 18:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had the same thing with an overweight couple sitting right next to me. Also apparently had lots of trouble with everything they ordered (eat in theatre). But yeah, just wouldn't shut up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 17:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is wonderful
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-16 16:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this needs some obnoxious Ash mumbling noises.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 22:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You must not know very many atheists then. People are all over each other's shit from every creed/race/etc. Hell, half these SWJs seem to be atheist and they're *all about* not minding their own business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fish you! Right in the pond! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fish you! Right in the pond! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:40:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think in a previous post with either the same or similar metrics it was discovered to be a 4chan joke now taken too seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well this was 11 years ago back in high school. So I doubt the teacher even remembers it, much less me. 

Edit: a letter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:56:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Futura: Ghostbustress of the Future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A friend of mine got in trouble for writing the word "negro" (in quotes mind you) for a Huck Finn essay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:50:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least there's mostly sanity in the comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [TW: HuffPo, Darling] Apparently Emma Stone owes everyone an apology for being cast as a half Hawaiian. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [TW: HuffPo, Darling] Emma Stone owes everyone an appology for being cast as a half Hawaiian. BONUS: Everything ever is whitewashed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Diet is usually like 80% of weight management. So it'd likely have to be a LOT of gym. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 03:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's just the Greeks. Couple of real party houses on campus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-21 03:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's just the Greeks. Couple of real party houses on campus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 18:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been reading too much tumblr. I read that as "*white people* like this are generally unbearable[...]" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [That's Numberwang!](https://youtu.be/qjOZtWZ56lc?t=31) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-19 07:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was probably more the first statement on the meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, as long as everyone agrees not to write any more blog posts and novels until we've written a perfect tax code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-17 17:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, at that point taking care of an animal will show that you have compassion and will come with certain levels of prestige. So the farmers will sell their animals and make fortunes. Eventually, because it will be concidered unethical to breed them, animals will become an expensive status symbol and also express ones wealth culturally. At that point companies will release "electric animals," basically an(imal)droids, for a cheaper alternative to a real animal
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-15 06:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mashup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 08:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He just wants to be featured on this sub.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-05-11 07:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That took the cake for me too. 

Speaking of which, happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 20:00:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you just ignore that rule and keep playing? Haven't played this specifically, but I know they started adding that to some longer games like risk seemingly just to make them shorter. We always just ignored them so we could just keep playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-23 18:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had something similar where I ended up driniking way too much mountain dew and just shit like 2 liters of bright yellow liquid. Fun times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brigadoon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spoiler alert! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [I love this one](https://www.google.com/url?sa=t rct=j q= esrc=s source=web cd=1 cad=rja uact=8 ved=0CB4QtwIwAA url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DxYc4DT18EJg ei=uvY3Vb6pJvaCsQTE54CgDg usg=AFQjCNGXVQ-JMVVhLJ-BAOutuXkW2Zu5wg sig2=-sc7DEdOsOPwMutM6bESeg bvm=bv.91427555,bs.1,d.b2w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-13 18:08:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoa. I am currently watching the Sonic '06 Game Grumps episode in which Arin makes that same joke.  Weird coincidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-11 16:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Rape college campuses" 
In 4-8 years ya'll have to start calling me Dr. Rape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mostly words, some abbreviations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 19:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man, I have Doctor priveledge. I hear ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-03 06:26:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just in time for Easter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-04-01 18:41:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are four lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-20 04:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Horg is my choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-17 14:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Classic power move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 16:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, one of my favorite parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 16:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are absolutely right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:33:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And let's try a quick switch-out on that. 

***Black*** fragility

***Jewish*** fragility

***Female*** fragility

...and hooray, now we sound like some sort Eugenics Eddy or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Showed up on my facebook. Mostly full of classic "all degrees are equal"statements and crazy double standards </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:07:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-03-12 18:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure. She's Dwor-Kin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NZIRK4G_Z7E#t=180 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-02-13 21:02:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's like your heart beating in your throat, but OP had Chic-fil-a so it went the other way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-26 17:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well then! PM me later (   )  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-25 23:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> o_0 "Man creme." Punctuation is important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2015-01-13 01:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine too. She even does it if we go upstairs to bed sometimes so now we have to tell her when we do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-12-10 20:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Diesel's "I'm a median system" link, Diesel adds a few more pronouns stating "We're still exploring ourselves." Hooray?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-25 19:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a biochem background, so I kind of understand where you're coming from and I just graduated from National a few months ago. A very evidence based curriculum and has a research group. However, possibly due to the opening of their newer campus in FL there seems to be budgetary problems and I didn't see much in the way of research while I was there: One prof. works a lot on meta-studies for nutrition, a few others have pet projects, and I was researcher for a study that was backed by Foot levelers (I think there was one on Vibram "toe shoes" as well during the time I was there). In the past they've done a good amount of research, but I saw less "quality" studies than I would have liked while I was there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 19:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, some of us are misanthropic assholes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 17:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is like people showing off their drug stash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-14 00:46:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FlooNetwork </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 22:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No you're right. Really just speaking of my experience with a few friends who were competitive and any time anyone mentions brawl around them. I'm quite aware that there's players without these opinions. But semantics aren't funny.

Also, for context, this was at -8 karma when I made my original comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're one of the good ones! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-13 17:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair, this is what a competitive SSB player would say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-12 23:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just crazy good looking. Love the highlighting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-11-09 22:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh... That kind of busts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 05:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or it's taking into account situations where people are driving under the speed limit but there is still a pace of traffic. There's just different options. Like if most people were driving the speed limit  (say 55) and one guy wanted to go 50, then he better be in the right lane. That's all the law said. Same works if, say due to traffic, the average speed is 35 in this 55 speed zone and one guy is in a tractor or is hauling something so he's wanting to do 30 or something. He should stay in the right lane again. In that situation, no one is speeding and the law still makes sense and is adapted to the situation by that language. All I'm trying to say is that the two laws are completely independent, and the phrasing is to be a catch all including going below the speed limit and thus doesn't suggest that people are "supposed to be speeding" though it would also include if they were I guess, though then the speeding laws would also be in effect. 

Blah blah blah, semantics and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 05:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heh, could be. Don't know if that means you're "supposed to speed" though

Edit: Didn't see the re-posted Oregon statute. See my above statement on that if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 05:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was not a question anyone asked as far as I know. I was just talking about the basic speed limit laws. If you were supposed to speed why would there be speed limit laws? The question you posed earlier of why there would be slow traffic on the right laws if we weren't supposed to speed is moot as people driving below the speed limit would still be held to that law without also having to break another law (IE you can follow that one or break that one with no speeding involved by either party). 

That curve is interesting and was a cool thing to learn, but is not really relevant. According to that chart average speed is better than both slow or fast so if the hypothetical "person going slow in the left lane" was going the average speed then they are a safer driver than the individual wanting to go faster behind them. Just depends what the average speed is, which we do not know in this situation we're discussing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-29 04:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a speed limit not a speed mandate. You can go *under* the limit as much as you want, as long as you aren't obstructing or going below a minimum. (Or maybe you were being sarcastic, can't read tone). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-23 17:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like sauteing veggies and/or veggie noodles and finishing it in a curried coconut milk kinda sauce. I personally like sweet potatoes, various squash, spinach, carrots, sometimes beets (turn things red), peas/pea pods, stuff like that. Really any veggie's will do, but season them well and remember different veggies cook at different rates.

Edit: I also really like cauliflower rice in general. Food process the cauliflower and then it cooks pretty quick either just with oil or with a bit of liquid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-13 14:43:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also for the schools of magic and sins/virtues of ancient Thassilonia in pathfinder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 23:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It unlocks a broken power basically where you get infinite focus and fire arrows for 15s or something. I've only used it in that fight, but it seems to be pretty much just dependent on making enough coin and maybe doing one of the quests. 

Edit: it's the three slots on the upgrade page below the rest of the upgrades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 22:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I did some. Do not know if it was all of them, but I'll assume it was. Wasn't really paying attention to those quests and just doing them as they came along, so I'm not sure I did all of them.All that seemed to be needed in my menu was the right amount of money.

I looked just for you and it seems that there is one bow quest left, so I guess you don't have to finish all of them(?). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 21:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think so. I know I spent about 2500 or something on top of that in the upgrade screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-10-03 21:52:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had the same thing so I bought that super bow and just nailed him in the head like 20x. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some songs from video games you can dance to? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-26 01:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I dance at a local Arthur Murray and they're about to do a series of parties based on video games and I was looking for some interesting songs or covers of songs to bring. The different party's themes are Sports games (including racing), "Combat" games (by which I assume they mean both fighting and general action games), Classic games, Fantasy games, Rock band/music (probably have this one covered), and "Mario Party." Any help is appreciated!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-11 04:09:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, just to give a data point I learned from hooked on phonics and did not fall for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 08:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's](http://chestofcolors.com/lava-tutorial) a decent example I found of what I meant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-09-01 08:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have done basically reverse highlighting. Where I start with white and go through yellow, orange, red layers (whatever color you want or all of em or whatever) leaving a little of the previous behind and then stack on some grey/black/metallic black to make some solidified areas.

Or you can do that in reverse, and just highlight up from black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-29 19:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope she's Liz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 18:03:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, then you are almost certainly in the wrong job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 05:23:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that why they're called the BEATles? Cause of wife-beating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-28 05:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This came off as a kinda funny joke the first time I read it, but then I read some more of his tweets. Now I am just sad. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-27 19:57:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, ideal weight is usually calculated on a linear scale, which is kinda weird. BMI is a bit better, but can still be still be unreliable for a "fatness" scale if the person is heavily muscled. Both are pretty usable for large groups though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-24 01:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Food, alcohol, most consumer goods, gas (due to subsidies), probably some other stuff. Taxes are pretty low. Not sure you wanted a real-ish answer, but there's one anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-08-08 23:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like the home alone music in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-28 02:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't goblin's allergic to books?
Looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-05 03:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link? This sounds awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-06-04 12:35:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oscar Wilde  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-07 19:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *vacccinations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-05-07 19:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jeez... 25 dollars is the lowest suggested donation... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-04-16 18:04:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for reminding me this song exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-03-19 15:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No waifu in the club. Gimme twenty dollahs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2014-02-25 06:39:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The owlbear's cuter cousin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-12-19 17:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Prime directive guys... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 20:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least she's aware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-11-12 17:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If all squares are rectangles, then all rectangles must be... HITLER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-17 19:28:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reading that I first started thinking "invisible T syndrome" was something to do with testosterone, like those low T commercials... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-16 14:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're a fat admirer. They probably wont be all that old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-15 17:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To fight anecdote with anecdote, my fiance is a petite, blonde Electrical Engineer who's professors helped her figure out her plan for a master's and later find a great job. 1 year into her job and she was hired on as the only salaried employee other than executives (everyone else is contract work). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-14 23:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah... I had a friend of a friend on facebook get one of those and post about it a bunch a couple years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-10-10 16:51:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been watching some breaking bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 23:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is an example of canon of course, and not head canon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-30 22:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that not appropriation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-26 00:35:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit-Lord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-25 23:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It can happen, especially if you have a mutated alcohol dehydrogenase gene (which breaks down alcohol for you). This is especially common with people of asian descent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-19 00:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never got the henpecked imagery of this until just now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-17 20:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except that arguably eating sapient/sentient beings (or feeding them to others) is an evil action. Worgs, with an int of 6 and being able to speak, probably count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-05 20:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a black eye from a friend wii tennis-ing my eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 22:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sugary and fatty maybe. Like milkshakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-09-03 22:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Upvote for the pun, intentional or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-06-23 06:24:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Part of my weight loss problem is that I have the opposite of this... :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 06:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My god! He could be any one of these things. Words, you've failed me again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-16 06:24:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean... that's one of the definitions... Right above that one is  ["an expert at programming and solving problems with a computer"](http://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/hacker) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-14 06:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have to make your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-11 04:05:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks friend. I also needed this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-09 18:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I was fucking a girl up the ass last night and she turns to me and asks 
"Why are you fucking me so furiously" 
So I said, "Furiously? that's a pretty big word for an eight year old" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-05-03 22:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you get sick of him over doing it, have him steal cursed things. Bag of Devouring maybe? Or I remember there were some sorta little creatures that looked like gold pieces that ate gold. Fun stuff with that. 

Other than that, if it's something he really wants to do, use it as plot hooks. Have him take a clue off a random bystander that leads the party into dealing with a cult. Have him steal from a wizard that vows vengeance. Have him steal from someone who really needed it, and see how it ruined their life. Whatever speaks to the player and helps advance your plots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-24 17:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasn't big on it, but was working with a trainer and a small group which made me go 2-3x per week. Eventually got to where I feel weird if I don't do it, but I rarely get some crazy high from the actual workout. Workouts are lifting 3x/week, for the last year and a half or so. Huge gains that I like, but no real high.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-15 06:14:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, you're thinking of Miss Cleo. I'm pretty sure this was in reference to a prevalent lyric of *Old MacDonald Had a Farm.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-15 02:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's completely based on preference. There's a grading system that goes from "rare" to "well done". Only really done with steaks and similar meats (rack of lamb, duck breast, some fish like tuna).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-15 02:23:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Link to cheap foam.](http://www.thefoamfactory.com/packagingfoam/picknpluckcr.html)  Though probably only if you buy quite a bit, dunno what their shipping is like... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 06:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually for bipolar disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-09 06:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In some states and countries, this is the five second law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-04-06 03:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The pound of dice by Chessex I got (this was years ago) had a lot of "factory seconds" in it. This one claims not to be all "factory firsts." This included some badly printed dice, and even some custom 1d4s (the 1 said D'oh), with numbers that didn't line up on all sides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-28 22:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pathfinder, it's a faster paced, better balanced 3.5 which is what I played most my life. 3.5 is great, but gets weird with so many supplementary rules. Especially if you have power-gamer munchkin types in your group. Pazio also makes some great campaigns (called adventure paths), that are wonderfully written and each one is very unique so you can choose the right tone for your group.

4.0 played too much like a MMORPG for me. A lot of the flavor/fluff was weirdly changed as well, though  I haven't played it since years ago so it may have changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-28 22:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, need them n-3 meats/eggs/fish. But she's doing what she can on the budget she has I think. Better than nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-28 21:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can also ask him any questions you have. Any good doc will be happy to explain things to anyone interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-27 15:13:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What game system? (or which version of Dnd)? Classically in like pathfinder and 3.0-3.5 here's the stats. Only real useful if poisoned, or maybe for sneak attacks and stuff. Hope that helps.   
http://www.d20pfsrd.com/equipment---final/weapons/weapon-descriptions/blowgun .   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-22 15:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Work like a paranoid schizophrenic! Those guys get lots of great things done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-20 15:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deus Ex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-18 14:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that other people see these things too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 18:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I'll try keeping these things in mind more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 18:02:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry if I'm being kinda contrary, just a little frustrated with it all. I do appreciate the advice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 16:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've thought the same along the energy lines and run several blood panels. Metabolic/lipid, a pretty complete thyroid panel, and some other stuff. Only thing that ever comes up is slightly high cholesterol. I've done some elimination diets cutting gluten and milk and some other stuff for a few mo and then re-challenged with no real effects (same with simple sugars for a general dysbiosis sorta test.)

My family's not too overweight, and they do have healthy stuff in addition I just tend to fall into the trap.  

I don't have to eat in the car, I just end up buying ice cream cause it's on the way and I feel stressed and talk myself into it. Doesn't seem to matter if I'm full or anything like that either. I rarely get hungry at all, just cravings for specific things.  I generally eat similar to what you're talking about , I just also get ice cream or soda a few times a week (or more if tests, or less if I can force myself).  I know how to eat well, just not how to not eat bad stuff in addition. 

I'm trying to lifestyle, but I've found if I set limits I can stick to eating well for longer. I'd much rather adopt it to a lifestyle change, but it hasn't be something I've been able to manage so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 13:35:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am down about 10lbs currently, and have been down as much as 39lbs in the last 2 years, but I bounce around a lot. Also some lean mass addition as I've been working out quite a bit in this time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 13:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chiro student here. Which makes it worse, cause I'm well aware of what I'm doing to myself but still can't stop it. :\  

While I don't buy anything bad to keep in the house, I do tend to buy food to eat in the car during my commute (often ice cream things). Probably my main source of bad food is me actively seeking it, which is what bothers me about it as I can't seem to stop for long. I split my time between my family home and my fiance's apartment (and school). While my fiance usually eats well, in my family home there is usually at least soda around which I cannot control. I usually have less trouble with stuff in the house as opposed to grabbing things on commutes or when out to lunch.     

One other slight issue I've found is that I rarely have more energy when eating healthy than when eating bad, and tend to use that as an excuse. Feel more tired/angry/depressed, even for months in.  

I feel I know generally how to eat well, and have tried several different mods to my diet all to the same effect: calorie counting, paleo, more body-building inspired cutting diets, etc. I can usually do these for a set goal of time or weight assuming it's relatively short and doesn't hit a midterm/finals session. I've heard a lot of reports of increased energy and such in both literature and on r/loseit and the like, but have not experienced it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need some advice on stopping stress eating and such please. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 04:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello,  

This is my first post other than my new person intro, so please be gentle ;)   
I'm currently in a heavy duty, year round schooling program and every time I hit midterm season, finals, or holidays I seem to crash off my diet and eat all sorts of junk. The main culprits seem to be Ice cream (with mixed in candies), soda, bread-y foods, and various holiday naughty baked goodsDuring these times I feel my thoughts going to these things all the time, planning out the next cheat. I also really enjoy eating out with my fiance and play dnd weekly which often leads to similar snacking if such things are at our game.  

Any advice on stopping such behaviors? Anyone in similar situations that figured anything out?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-14 04:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello lose it!

I've been a lurker for a bit, but here's my introduction.
M/24/5'8"  Starting weight 248  Goal weight 180 Current weight 236

I put on nearly a hundred pounds through college (with very very little drinking surprisingly). Through the past two years since I finished undergrad I have fluctuated all the way down to 209, but always seem to fall back into old habits and am now back up to 236. I'm currently a chiropractic student, so while I feel like I know how to diet and exercise I have a lot of issues with actually sticking to it. I'm in a very hectic school schedule (~30 credit hours per trimester) that goes year round with only short breaks and seem to have some stress eating issues, especially during midterms and finals. 

Through these nearly two years I have also been weight lifting 2-3x a week and have seen a huge difference in my strength and muscular size, so there is definitely an increase in my lean mass as well. In the last 2 weeks I have been trying to slowly add in some HIIT and rehab type core work on 3 of my off days. I'm determined to defeat my hatred of cardio.

I'm currently 12lbs down from my high and am working to improve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-08 15:39:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very complete and well done. Helped to inspire me to start getting serious again. Thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-08 15:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It'll never get past the Star Wars missle defense system! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 18:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second Citadels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 18:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **Pathfinder** Friend ran a short campaign while other players were unavailable, after that finished we moved on to some boardgames  

**Last Night on Earth** We played one round of it, my first time playing as a hero. I heroically sacrificed myself several times.  

And a few rounds of **Citadels** (the card game which is a quick, fun, little strategic mess), which was the first time for the rest of my group. They seemed to enjoy it a lot and want me to bring it along next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 18:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're willing to wait till Sept to get it, the Zombicide season 2 kickstarter is out and comes with lots of goodies. http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/coolminiornot/zombicide-season-2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-05 05:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Backed as well. Found this independently and was planning on posting it myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-04 17:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Logistically, assuming the baby's the same size when it hatches, the egg would probably have to be bigger than a baby... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2013-03-04 16:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TLDR The queen of England is British. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>