<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3688</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 22:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. In a moment of perfect clarity, you finally understand. You're amazed how you had never before noticed the superior comfort and durability of flannel. You are completely mind-blown by the generous cargo room and the all wheel drive, go anywhere capability of the Subaru Outback. These revelations change your life forever.

 Whenever your friends or family try to have a conversation with you, you only talk about Subaru's zero landfill plant in Indiana. You lose all your friends, and your family have you committed to a mental institution.

At the institution only female doctors are allowed to see you, and they must all be, or at least pretend to be, lesbians. This is because you have said that they are the only ones you trust and the only ones who get you.

You spend the rest of your days in the institution. You constantly pester the staff with questions like "Is your favorite cloth brushed flannel or unbrushed flannel and why?" You're also known for randomly screaming out bits of trivia, like the fact that all Subaru Outbacks come standard with raised roof racks and enhanced tie-downs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 16:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the amputation thing, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 05:00:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. After countless reports of breaking and entering, police finally get the suspect in custody: an old man named Kris Kringle.

During interrogation Kringle not only cofesses, he also admits to stalking little children and watching them as they sleep. When asked why, he says he wanted to see if they were "naughty or nice". He continues on, telling police that he brought toys to the children he liked and often ate food from the victims' homes, turning the b e into burglary.

Parents are outraged when the news gets out. Protests break out worldwide as people demand justice. News outlets cover nothing but this story.

After the longest and most expensive trial in history, Kringle is found guilty on over a billion counts of burglary, stalking, voyeurism, and sexual grooming. He is sentenced to life in prison without the possibility of parole.

The other inmates find out why he's locked up. A large group jump Kringle in the shower and beat him to death. During the beating his belly shakes like a bowl full of jelly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 02:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. You now have a free subscription to every porn site. This includes illegal child porn sites. The police are at your door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 01:28:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I could upvote you twice for the Hawking radiation. Nicely done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 01:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. Now they blow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 01:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. Drive-bys are no longer carried out with guns. Now they drive up slowly, throw an improvised explosive at someone's house, and speed off.
Militaries quickly lose all their small arms. They can't risk putting troops on the ground without guns, so they rely more and more on explosives to fight the enemy. Civilian casualties skyrocket. Some militaries, out desperation, resort to nuclear weapons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 00:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. With over three hundred thousand subscribers,  it's virtually guaranteed that some of us are pretty terrible. Most of us go for a stroll in the park or enjoy some ice cream during our nice day. Some of us, however, spend our nice day getting away with crimes and causing bad things to happen to innocent people. One or two of us may even have a lovely day of murdering others. We had a nice day individually. As a society we had criminals go free, an increase of pain and suffering, and maybe a couple of homicides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 00:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. Pay is adjusted down to whoever makes less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 00:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. Your wife gives up everything in her life so that she is available for you to have sex with. Don't get the wrong idea, though. She is not happy about it. You see her struggling to talk through her tears as she declines every invitation she receives. She misses births, graduations, even funerals because she can't risk being busy when you want sex. She suffers from depression and breakdowns. She refuses to get help because you might want sex while she's at the docor's office. She is a broken husk of her former self. But, hey! You can have sex with her more often. Congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 23:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. You do not die, but you continue to age. You still feel pain, and you still get sick. You just don't die. You slowly lose mobility and cognitive abilities, becoming an invalid.  Medical staff try their best to care for you until you have so many incurable diseases they cannot continue without risking everyone's safety. They have to seal you away in a room that no one can enter. They go so far as to plaster over the door. 

As time goes on, you are forgotten. The huger pains are intense. The lonliness is soul crushing. Your mental and physical health continue to deteriorate. One at a time, you lose different abilities. Sight, hearing, speech, memories, they all slip away. The diseases relentlessly attack you. Pain and sadness, darkness and silence; you just don't die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 18:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. Nothing you want to happen ever happens. For example, if you want to be around people you are instead alone, and when you want to be alone, you are constantly bothered by people. People you like suffer, and those you hate prosper. The internet goes out every time you want to use it, while reseraunts and grocery stores are always out of the food you want. The only people who are interested in you romantically are those you find repulsive and are a gender you are not attracted to. Etc, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 18:06:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. The games don't get better. The ads just get worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 02:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Takes off pants*
So, Ash's mom, do you want to be the boy or the girl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 15:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It happened to me a couple of months ago. I ended up uninstalling and reinstalling the app to get it to work again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I wish bad things only happened to bad people. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 16:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 15:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. In fact, they grow back so large they can no longer be used for their intended purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 15:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. The wings can lift you one inch off the ground, and you have the stamina to use them for two seconds. You require 48 hours of rest after each use. 

Also, each wing is 20 feet long and does not fold or retract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 15:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I was on tv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 15:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. Karma becomes the only currency in the world. Everything you post gets downvoted. Meanwhile, reposters become billionaires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 14:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. When you take it out of the groud, you break a water line that causes $20,000 worth of damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 14:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Granted. You find out there is an afterlife. It is exactly like this world except there is no end or escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 11:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This will install a generic USB driver.

Follow this [link](https://zadig.akeo.ie/downloads/). 

Download zadig-2.3.exe. Don't get 2.4. I run windows 7 as well, and 2.4 kept freezing on me.

Have the miniSNES connected to your USB port. Turn it on by holding reset, turning on the power, then releasing reset.

Run zadig. In the drop down box there should be an unknown device listed. This is the miniSNES. If it's not listed, click options, then choose list all devices. It should now be in the drop down box.

Under the box, make sure WinUSB is chosen.

Click Install Driver.

Let it do its thing (less than a minute).

Open hakchi, and follow whichever guide you are using.

It should now work fine. I hope this helps.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mods are asleep. Post ten d's </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-16 06:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dddddddddd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 23:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They would name them after their competitors, of course. Probably still better than the public naming them. I don't want to die because of Hurricane McHurricaneface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 20:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi. You could add roasted tomatoes if you have the time. Cut either cherry or grape tomatoes in half. Put them in a glass baking dish cut side facing up. Drizzle a little olive oil on them, and add a pinch of salt. Bake at 300f for an hour to an hour and a half.

As far as seasoning, I like putting a little black pepper in cheese sauce. Just remember that a little goes a long way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-28 05:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My speculation is Mueller is filing federal charges against people who can also be charged with state crimes. If they accept pardons, state charges become a lot easier, and they can be compelled to testify. Manafort is an easy pick here.

Mueller may also be forcing Trump's hand when it comes to pardons. How many pardons need to be issued before a case can be made for abuse? I don't know the aswer, but there may be some lower level people indicted to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-03 22:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got the letter as well. I'm glad more people will get to see the shows. I hope they aren't getting rid of some shows in the change, though. For example, there have only been a couple of Cult Classic episodes so far, but they have been very good and Casper Van Dien rocks. I want all the shows to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Blonde Joke] Why did the blonde get fired from the M M factory? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-14 16:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She kept throwing away all the E's, 3's, and W's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-09 22:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like my chickens just how I like my lollipops.
That's it, I'm a co- Wait! I mean, um, nevermind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-09 08:04:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The quiet game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Request] TV Fights episode </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-06 20:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love to see a TV Fights: Cartoon Edition. Everyone can wear their coolest pajamas and house slippers. Billy Biz could rock a respectable flannel set.

Some sample questions:

What is the best Saturday mornig cartoon?

Name two cartoons that should do a cross-over episode.

Which cartoon teaches kids the best lessons?

(Speed round) Best channel for cartoons, Disney or Nickelodeon?

What do you guys think? I think the fighters and fans love cartoons. Let's make it happen!

P.S. Mike Carlson should be a fighter. Given the costumes he's worn on Movie Fights, his pj's would be epic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My guess/hope/dream is that this box is so limited and so expensive because it contains a numbered, autographed item. Imagine we get something signed by Stan the Man himself. That would definitely increase the value without increasing the size of the box </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>