<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4396</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 12:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you arent already flooded hmu would love to make a new friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 17:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jiraiya, god damn that anime... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 15:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I relate to this doctor more than I care to admit unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 01:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is exactly how I imagine my Stellaris campaign when I take on fanatic purifiers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 02:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True blue legend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 02:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 13:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Im from Australia feel free to hit me up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 15:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so cool!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:34:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice tats, fellow GCer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 05:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could never remember the order in which the months went until I realised that July - Novembers initials spelt the name Jason, have never forgotten since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 16:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well theyre gonna have a lot of work to do now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 15:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That or YouTube, its the only thing that keeps me from thinking about stuff and I hate that I have to resort to distracting myself just to not be sad for 5 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 16:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mash that avo, put some salt and lemon juice in it then spread it on toast and that shit is amazing, fight me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 15:48:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres no real way to tell if this was because of him, you or the girlfriend. In my experience Ive had to give up friendships with my female friends because of a jealous partner and that shit really sucks, Im sorry youre in this situation but dont give up on making new friends there is still a lot of good people out there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 16:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you live in the Wild West? How did you survive without water for 2 weeks?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 16:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I have a bad habit of doing this too, yet I love my friends so much but I cant help but just go into solitary mode and thinking that everyone hates me and Im this and that and every other bad thing under the sun, makes me feel like Im going crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 16:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The rest sounds interesting and possibly hilarious but how does someone talk about water? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 16:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might be worth trying your local game store, good games is all over Australia I think and they usually run games on Wednesday, Ive only played for like a year on and off as a barbarian so I really have fuck all experience unfortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 16:00:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no worries mate, good luck! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 15:50:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When are you planning on starting this game? Im an Australian and dont have a lot of experience but I may be interested if our schedules line up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 11:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wish I couldve been apart of this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 10:52:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rosetta Stone 2 electric boogaloo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah never planned to turn 18 let alone 21 but here I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 16:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey you seem pretty cool, feel free to hmu! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 18:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think discussing it is probably better than the typical noooo we love youuuu but I cant blame people for reacting the way they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 18:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I play guitar and minecraft too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 16:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Throwing it inside the guitar is just as effective...if you can ever get it out again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 15:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it with my own friends sometimes let alone strangers, IIRC its something to do with social anxiety at least it is for me. The best thing to do is to remember that 9/10 its all in your head and no one thinks about all of our flaws half as much as we do, but if it gets in the way of life and your enjoyment of it, it might be best to see a therapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 17:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah should be 18 and over here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 17:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im keen, feel free to hit me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 15:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre actually pretty cute, keep doing your own thing and a relationship will find you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 17:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not an American but I agree white people should have pride in where they come from, as should anyone, and of course that doesnt give anyone the right to go around hating on people for their heritage, that goes for everyone regardless of skin colour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 15:34:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes me smile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>