<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3848</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 17:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 18:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i support this statement 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 17:54:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beautifully said! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 17:53:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you said this really well! im an INFJ married for years to an INTP.  We have had to work at communicating a bit better but it is so worth it. i finally feel mostly understood and appreciated. and i think he would say the same. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 17:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brilliantly said! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 17:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  i think i say it this way for this exact reason... i have no idea how i said before hearing... lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 05:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why are people down voting this??  my mother mentally and physically abused my brother and i... but no one knew until after they divorced ave my brother and i refused to live with her. we told my dad and some family members...my dad knew some hence the divorce... .. and to this day my dads side of the family still treats her with respect and sometimes invites her to family gatherings...

so yes forget that shit and call his ass out in front of everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 23:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> on vacation as a stowaway in my suitcase </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Zorro wants to go too! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 21:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 12:21:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i cant tell you how much i love this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 20:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I played with my son off and on for a few weeks.
After I bought the game for myself it took a few hours to beat the first boss... and I have yet to beat the second one. But its fun and I love the challenge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 15:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My eyes!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 23:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god... why did I click on this... I e been reading it for ten minutes... I need to bleach my eyes!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 19:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/whyweretheyfilming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 02:47:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaassss!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 02:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 05:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yasss!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> YALL!!!!!! That laugh, though!!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 05:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 20:23:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think maybe because the majority of cults out there base their beliefs around Christianity. And the Apple is a big symbol of sin and fallen man in Christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 20:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Mississippi. I help my husband run his construction business. We hire employees and independent contractors all the time.  

This church was treating you like an employee and paying you like an independent and that is against the law.  You mentioning it probably was the reason they fired you. 

Im not sure if non-profit like business (like churches) can get in trouble for this or not. But I do know that a regular business can and the federal government takes it pretty seriously. 

They could be required to retroactively pay in their share of the Medicare/social security.

Like I said though, Im not sure how churches and the like are treated when it comes to stuff like that. 

If you have a written contract that quotes scope of work and your bid for the job, then they might be able to get off by saying he was a contractor but we didnt like his work so we fired him

Unless you were punching a time clock and there was a record of your hours... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 21:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well it got the other guys comment upvoted... so I guess it was perfection...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 15:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im dying!! I cant believe people arent upvoting this comment...  I guess they arent real fans.. jk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two loaves for the price of one! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 05:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> He might be hilarious... but that laugh though!!!  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 19:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 14:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bicardi and bubly! Sooo good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-11 04:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I was just thinking, how is this awwee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-11 04:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So beautiful it looks like a painting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-10 14:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats the best!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-10 14:43:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  this is the real story here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-10 14:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Say it louder for the ones in the back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Baby Batman turning on those Puss in Boots eyes! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-10 03:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im dying!!!!  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 04:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 23:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/subsyoufellfor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 06:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude!! You hit the nail on the head! I wasnt even thinking in this direction but yet... bam!! Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My introverted Burrito makes a special living room appearance. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 17:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 17:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What beautiful eyes!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My introverted cat, Burrito, makes a rare appearance in the living room. Shes a natural. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 17:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-14 20:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I Took A Picture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 03:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dressing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Happy Memorial Day! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-27 19:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 17:45:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This vacation feels like an ad! Too perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-23 14:43:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No he has the regular number of toes. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> He wakes up like this.. literally. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 22:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I coughed. He woke up. I think Im in trouble. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 22:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 16:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know who you might be thinking of... he did look like he could be Quicksilver. But is the little boy from Ironman 3 all grown up. Its even the same actor who played him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 21:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the exact same way... I feel like I have this big void in my life now. It really feels like the death of friends. Ive been a funk since Saturday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 17:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 03:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yass!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 03:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yasss!! We needed that!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 03:29:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very much more hulk.. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 03:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, Jesus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 13:14:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reverse reverse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 13:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hail Hydra  loves that! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 13:06:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Lebowski! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 12:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Odin decreed that whomever is deemed worth to wield the hammer shall have the powers of Thor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 12:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because when Tony snapped his fingers,maybe he dusted them back to their original time... just a thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 18:37:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That statement about having to avoid going back to certain places because you struck up a conversation with someone... I thought it was just me and my anxiety... Im so glad to know Im not the only INFJ that does this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 04:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are there mods on this sub... cause yeah... this needs deleted... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 15:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My stomach hurts... but otherwise, Im good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 15:22:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/likeus  but seriously this just made my whole day! I cannot stop laughing!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 05:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dying!  did he have an online degree? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 03:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont breath in silica if you set the anchor bolts before you pour the concrete... like a normal person  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 10:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Cosmo Brain!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-10 14:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband and I use Merrells hiking boot. 

A version of these: 

https://www.merrell.com/US/en/moab-2-mid-waterproof-wide-width/27934W.html?dwvar_27934W_color=J06058W#cgid=women-footwear-boots start=1

They hold up super well, keep your ankle supported, and have great grip.. at least on metal, which is what we install.

I absolutely love them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-10 13:40:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 16:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say the exact same thing!! That gramma got gams!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-05 00:46:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, this, a thousand times this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-04 00:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have only been playing for about 45 days. I have the Silent Swordsman, 2 ss lv 3, one ss lv 5, and one ss lv 7. I have the silent swordsmans spell cards that help, and I use warriors and noble knights along with the Nobel knight spell card that gains the knight 500 atk and gain 500 lp on your main phase. I also have the cosom brain which I love and two cool dragons. And some other trap and spell cards. 
Im silver rank 2 right now and Ive won over 25 times.  But I dont get to get it on and play just a whole lot and the first 30 days I spent doing stage and character unlocks. :) anyway Im sure non of that is what you meant by build but it was my best guess to what you were asking. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 17:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made a SS deck that I love and I didnt use real money, just the gems that I had been collecting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 17:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For reals!!! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-19 21:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you!! I came here just to make this friends reference!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-19 21:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And this is my ring tone for my husband!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 01:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the tip!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 01:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I use Merrills and I love them! Feet pain went to 0 when I finally got a good pair of work shoes!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-25 17:02:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats actually soo awesome!! Ive never seen one like that!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-25 16:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaaasss!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 16:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yasss!! These!!! I just do not understand their logic behind their beliefs!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-14 20:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That comment deserves more attention!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-11 05:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is such a great response!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-11 05:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. All day long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-11 05:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For reasons Im not a liberty to say, I cant do Facebook. But I could easily text once every two months... except all that catching up on lives seems just... exhausting... even though I do love all of them.  I wish I could just be the one they call when they need something but are totally ok with me never calling them... lol 
I know how fd up that sounds...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-11 05:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im soooo bad at this!! How do you do it?? Im not Facebook so I feel like its nearly impossible! Because emails are soooo much work! Oh dont get me started on the dreaded phone calls!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-08 03:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally though... if you zoom in and look close... is this not that little shit from the Green Mile that married that 16 year old when he was 50 something??   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 21:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  genetics  and I never wear make up. I think it ruins your skin. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-28 05:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-25 12:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude! Self evaluation/growth is so important! And extremely mature! Good for you for not taking what I said harshly! I really appreciate it!
I have to constantly reevaluate myself and Im always making mistakes and some times I can be very wrong about things... thank you for taking the time to reply!
I hope you and your friends and family have the best holiday season!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-25 02:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 16:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can promise you that,  to her, you trying to tell about the new girlfriend is somehow coming across as I have a girl, so that HAS to mean I dont like you (but secretly Im hoping this puts you at ease so I can spend more time with you because I have feelings for you.

I dont think you enjoy hurting her. I also dont think you are hurting her. She is desperately trying to keep you from hurting yourself. Its what we do. 
You say you only had feelings for her on two occasions... but my man, feelings are not a light switch. You dont just turn them off and on no matter how much you might wish to. They are there and they are unconsciously coming to the surface when you are around her. 
Even trying to keep this relationship alive is telling her how badly you like her. 
Shes ignoring you because she doesnt want you to fall for her more just by being around her. (Cause thats what happens when you like someone.) especially now that you have a girlfriend. Now more people could get hurt and infjs really dont want to hurt people. 

Be honest with yourself.  You love being around her and just a text from her would make you light up,right? 
If she changed her mind and texted you out of nowhere and said Ive been ignoring you because I realized I had feelings for you and didnt know what to do.... would you leave your new girl to pursue this new avenue with your friend? Be super honest.  If the answer is even remotely a stop and consider before I answer then you have feelings for her. And she is picking up on that even if you dont even realize your feelings yourself. 

Give her the space or confront her in person when she gets back.  But I would definitely stop texting. Thats just pushing her further away because she can smell your feelings all over it.

Im an internet stranger and I can smell it. 

And Im so sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 16:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not really sure. Sometimes he seems to get enjoyment watching people assume he is not very bright just because he is quite. And other times he expresses what seems to be disappointment that other people cant immediately see his intelligence. 

I just have to remind him that the people who know him and love him know his worth, personally and intellectually. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 16:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We are not in debt. But we also dont make a killing farming.  

I also think your container idea is very interesting and could be profitable... on a larger scale. On small scale (say one container) its not going to be as super lucrative. Not saying it wont provide income or provide personal enjoyment. 

I really am very happy you are interested in farming!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:58:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please do this. Please get into farming. And do so following the latest phase. And tech. And all the other stuff. 
I would love to see you succeed. Because this world needs more farmers. And more people with their hand in the dirt (or water in your case). 
So they can understand. And then they can help us advocate in our all our favors (those who do it old school and those who do it up to date)

Farming isnt cheap. It doesnt have to be hundreds of thousands either. But it isnt something to be gone into lightly. 

Thank you for at least finding farming interesting!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, your job sounds nothing like my dream job... 
it sounds sucky.  (Not putting you down.. it just sounds terrible)
As an INFJ I dont think I could tolerate it long unless I had zero other options...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. Blunt honesty is my favorite because then we can be blunt back as well. :) 
Definitely another route!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:44:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude. I own a small 60 acre farm... 
with old outdated equipment...
The man is not over exaggerating the cost. You dont have to go into debt or invest multitudes of capital to farm... 
however to make money at farming... you do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I for real think, after looking at your profile, that you have concluded INTP must be the initials of some drug or gang or some such thing. 

Dude its stands for a personality type. 
Introverted
iNtuitive
Thinking
Perceptive 


Something like that. 

Its a sub for people with that kinda personally type.

Some probably drink. Some probably do drugs.
All of them think your posts are shit. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude Im having fun just reading yours! And of course his asinine comments just make it better!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/shitpost  also for real dude you are r/lostredditors  


Why this sub?? Just why??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats my dream retirement job... to own a bookstore... just a quaint hole in the wall place that the locals go to for quite reading and, of course, the sage advice of the bookstore owner on their next selection. Somehow she always seems to know the perfect book for everyone... :) 

*deep sigh* I wish working in a bookstore could pay my bills right now... :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get out of my brain!!!  No but for real stay... its nice to have understanding company in there..:)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 08:04:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude.. she is an INFJ. You have done/been doing several (probably unconscious on your part) actions, phrases, vibes, and the what not to give her the Im still into you as more than friends feelings. And shes trying to nip that in the bud.

Read up on us INFJs. We pick up on EVERYTHING! Especially nonverbal and verbal  cues from people.  Then later our minds mesh it all together and we have the answer! We have been seen as mind readers or psychics. In reality our brain is taking in all information from not just one interaction but several and then putting the pattern together.

You already told her you had a crush on her. So thats a big umbrella for her to file every little nuance you do under. Which then apparently said umbrella declared you were raining feelings down on her.

Give her space. Be a real friend and dont force interaction. The ball is in her court to continue this friendship.  Be careful you dont become off as pushing a friendship relationship on her... the INFJ doorslam might  be on the horizon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 03:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you are dead on with this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 15:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree with everything you said! Perfect!

I was just making a commentary (dissertation is probably more like it, considering how long my reply!) on what OP meant with his post. Because as you pointed out, a lot of INTPs start off feeling what OP is feeling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 15:19:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre so right about us NF types! I constantly have to check myself because Im always called out for sounding very r/imverysmart 

Whilst my INTP husband is super intelligent but usually comes off as the quite dummy in corner. Thus, hes constantly doubting his intelligence while at the same time feeling mentally superior inside! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 15:13:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/lostredditors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 15:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most teenagers feel misunderstood because the older generation thinks the things they are into are garbage. 

I think OP is referring to the way a lot of INTPs feel about the general population. Mindless chatter. Narrow views. Nothing of substance to them. Just shallow wells not worth dipping into. 

Because most INTPs are highly intelligent and are constantly looking to learn new things. And connect old ideas to new ones in interesting ways.  

And the general population has a hard time understanding their ideas and thoughts. So most of the time, they dont bring them up, because whats the point. So they feel very lonely.

I say all this because my husband is an INTP and constantly expresses the emotion behind that titanic quote. He feels like hes surround by idiots and shallow people when he steps out the door everyday. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 15:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just let him be him. Im married to an INTP (Im an INFJ) and the thing I love the most about him is that we dont have to fill every moment with words. Taking a road trip, for example, is so relaxing. We can talk and then we can go for hours in silence without the awkwardness. Just the comfort of each others presence.

But... we do talk. A lot! People outside our marriage think hes such a quite and reserved dude. Totally the opposite!  

Heres the trick... they are afraid people might judge them for all these crazy and random and awesome things they think about...because they never ever stop thinking...they have sooo much going on in their head! And they are use to people not understanding them at all so they never open up to just anyone.

So..dont push him to communicate. Maybe ask pointed questions about his ideas or thoughts when he does say something. Or like another redditor suggested, ask him questions about past life experience, or his thoughts on certain theories or topics. let him gradually over time start communicating more. And you just listen. And dont judge. And contribute meaningfully to his ideas giving the insight that only an INFJ can bring.  And he will love it. To finally feel somewhat understood and to be able to hold intelligent conversations with said person is like the holy grail for them.  Because they mostly deal with people that couldnt understand what they are thinking or couldnt be bothered to care about it. (At least they think thats who they mostly deal with). 

Anyway, good luck with your INTP! Ive been with mine for about 11 years... hes my best friend! (Also the person that aggravates me the most but still my best friend!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 14:39:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant wait for my bookends!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 17:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude just telling it like they told me! (and how it actually is... lol)

Also I just google the big 5 test and clicked on the first link and went right to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 15:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I scored high on Factors 3, 4, and 5. Lowe on the first 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 15:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Married to an INTP.  What you just said is the basis for our wonderful relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 15:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This!! We always love and appreciate a gift! Especially if someone spent time and energy on it. We know how precious that stuff is! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 15:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im an INFJ and I dont like journals. Never had. Feels like work to me.  Now, I dont like talking on the phone, I would rather text. If someone has a real problem, my advise is usually better when I type it out.   But just s journal for my own thoughts... nope. I got them just fine in that big Rolodex in my skull. :)  but I agree with original commenter, I think this is more straight personal preference and not necessarily a standard INFJ trait. ( to like journals)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-20 14:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My best friend and my sister!!!!!  

My best friend and my sister!!!    

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Me and my best bud, Baby Batman, just chillin... waiting on the bat signal.. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-11 04:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-26 05:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaasss!! We just got one! My grocery bill went from around 250 a week to 100-150!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-18 21:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooooo!! That sounds worth a go!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TIA.. vanilla ice cream drizzled with honey... best thing since peanut butter met jelly! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-18 16:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-17 02:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im an INFJ married to an INTP. I love the shit out of that man. He is literally my best friend. But my lord... miscommunications abound! Misunderstandings abound! Him getting tired of my feelings abound! Me getting tired of his aloofness abounds! You get the idea. But we love each other so damn much. I feel like he is seriously the only person that gets me. We have so many inside jokes (were going on 11 years together) its ridiculous. I love that he has actual things to say when he talks and he loves that I can actually understand what he is contemplating. And so much more good stuff. But you have both have to be open to understanding each other and trying to work with each others different styles. But I think if you do, its a fantastic match. 

On the other hand my very best friend in all the wide world (other than the hubby) is an INFP. And that takes no work at all. She is the peanut butter  to my jelly, the apple to my pie, the remote to my tv, the password to my wifi... you get the idea. A friendship match made in heaven!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-15 19:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so true! (INFJ).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-12 22:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mr. Lee, I dont feel so good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-11 06:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aquarius! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 19:56:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree. Since you already sent the more trite message, I wouldnt want to send another one anytime soon.  But thats just my opinion.  Maybe wait a couple of months and then send him a version of this post and see how he reacts. If he doesnt respond or has a basic unfeeling answer, well then, you will know for sure he has or is moving on. Or is working out his issues. Or whatever. But at least you will have borne out your heart and made all the efforts you could. And you can then move on without regrets. Again this is all just an opinion of an internet stranger. Please dont take it as cannon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 19:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im an INFJ and I support this response 100%! 
I dont think you can be a true INFJ, or maybe just not a healthy one, if you arent constantly trying to see the other side of the story. You should be wondering about what makes them the way they are, or perhaps be wondering if they too are INFJ or ENFJ and are using their chameleon personalities to just get through the interactions. The last thing you would be doing is making a blanket one size fits all assumption about charismatic people. (In my opinion).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 19:20:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also my comment is showing up on my phone as a huge text all in bold type... I have no idea how that happened or why. It was not intentional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 19:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> #6 and #3. Ive got to work on #3, but I wish the people in my life that love me understood #6. Sometime the very thought of being around a human being makes me exhausted and anxious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 19:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dear God, this. It didnt even occur to me till you said it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 19:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you should say to him exactly what you write in this post. Copy and paste it even. Its direct and vulnerable. And you know us INFJ do not expose our vulnerabilities to just anyone. And when someone does that to us we respect the bravery that it took to do it.  If you were afraid you were too aggressive and that it looked like you didnt care, sending him a copy of this post (or a version of it) will at least let him know the headspace you were in at that moment. And it will let him know exactly how you are thinking and feeling and trying to respect him. I think he would value your text and if you still mean anything to him, he will respond. And then maybe establish a NC timetable. Or maybe he just really needs to know you care and is ready to start again. You wont know unless you text him. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 19:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So whats the question? Not being rude, I just couldnt find a specific thing to latch on to answer.  But I do know from my own experience.. being too needy will definitely drive her away. We like confidence. Its sexy. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-10 18:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Way to go! And thank you for posting! I come here to lurk and get motivation when Im feeling unaccomplished... I love reading things like this! Helps me get my mind back on track!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 15:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 15:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell probably go for a walk now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 15:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And your father smells of elderberries!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 14:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And if you come near me again, I shall taunt you a second time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-08 15:00:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A Facebook buy, sell, trade group. You can list the clothes as a lot and sell it in bulk. If you have 50 items list it for $50-$70 dollars. Take pictures of examples of whats in the lot.  People who own consignment or resale shops will buy it up quick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-08 14:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  for real though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-07 05:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This also feels very r/sadcringe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-03 02:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chandler proved that he likes to maintain her. Whats more special than that? To know you have an obsessive, perfectionist, A-type woman and you love her and all her issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-03 02:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just kidding, Chandler, your my favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 21:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like it! Send away!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> They had a 2 for 1 sale at the shoe store... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 19:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-28 14:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have a link to evidence of your claim? Not being rude, just really interested in the real story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITAP of the sunset across the back forty pasture </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-21 05:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 22:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh, sweetie, this conversation is making me a little uncomfortable.  -Ross  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 22:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We poo poo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 22:20:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could... if I wasnt going COMMANDO!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 22:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I could up vote this more than once!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 22:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hummus hummus hurry people what gets out hummus!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> View of my daddys farm from my tractor seat... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 14:41:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-05 06:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/thathappened   Not that I dont support other women... but yeah...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 20:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaass!!! Drop Dead Fred! Ive been looking everywhere for this movie!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 06:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 24 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 18:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the hope for the future!! lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 15:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 15:13:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So Im not crazy?? This bathroom problem Ive been having is from IF??? This is a thing?? Please tell me this is a thing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 17:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/thathappened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 14:58:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 14:57:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BACKLESS DRESSES!!! Yasss! I love the way the look... except I will never be able to wear one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 06:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha. Ha. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 06:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best comment so far!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 06:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously though...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 05:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 20:32:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit I love pony o and I havent found anyone else in my rural area that even knows about!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 18:38:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/thathappened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My baby Batman... taking a break from saving the world... drink responsibly my friends.. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 17:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 01:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally r/catsareliquid !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 01:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Zorro doing Blue Steel better than Zoolander himself! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 01:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 00:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This baby wins the internet!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 00:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please tell his name is Rico!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 00:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its so fluffy, I wanna die!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 00:24:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So schmexy!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 17:29:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say the same thing! Dont know why you were down voted!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 17:17:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/sweatypalms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 18:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have high arches and have been dealing with this same problem!  My husband suggested I try the same brand boot he wears, Merrell. He noticed a significant reduction in foot pain since using the brand. So I bought some Merrell for woman boots and this week has been amazing! I didnt even have to put my inserts in them! I havent had achy feet all week!  (We own a steel building erection company... Im on concrete all day!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-14 20:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus Michael Keaton is just the shit! :) lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-14 19:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes yes and more yes!!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-14 19:44:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-14 19:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaasss!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 14:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reflections on my life: 

read the name Kim and immediately my brain said, thats not even remotely a Kardashian.... 

now I want to Hemingway it up with a glass of whiskey and a shot gun. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 05:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought about it being preplanned... after I commented... lol 

This is going to sound stupid.. what are car spotters?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 00:08:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/whyweretheyfilming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-06 02:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Cross post on r/quityourbullshit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 22:42:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/lostredditors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-03 22:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-02 16:27:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 07:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Yasss!!! Almost needs to be on r/boneappletea !!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 21:45:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An African swallow, may be, but not a European swallow...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-26 17:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive never been so jealous for over a food item in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-26 17:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This!!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 15:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/perfecttiming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-20 23:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-20 16:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Band nerd! (The good kind!!) loves to travel, has read all the Harry Potter books, has two best friends, quite but would stick up for one of those friends in a heartbeat!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-20 16:57:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 17, soccer, and its either one from South America or Spain.  you look like a sweet hearted, well rounded, loyal friend!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-20 16:47:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-20 16:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 29 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-17 17:07:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty close!! 38 in October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-17 17:06:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So close! 38 in October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-16 16:54:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom says are you ready freddy at least 10 times a day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-16 16:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got more problems than Carter has liver pills!

What has that got to do with the price of eggs in China?!

Hold the baby, were all going to die! (This is when driving and braking-like normal braking) 

Hand me that doomaflautchy! (Her word for literally everything) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-15 04:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 38 this October!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 15:02:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also belongs in r/trashy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 15:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/oddlysatisfying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 15:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  r/catsareliquid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What? Its a box... you expect me NOT to sits?? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 06:14:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Even at 2 years old, Zorro is still just a big baby... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 06:06:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-10 00:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is by far my favorite comment!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 06:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude for real! You need to post this on r/quityourbullshit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 18:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I am 38... so...    But my colloquialisms usually only come out under extreme duress or pain... probably that hellboy of a splinter triggered it...    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 18:38:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it be obvious...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 18:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Ive always said it.. its a phrase that was/is used around my area a lot... so it just became part of my lexicon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 14:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 13 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 14:13:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lord have mercy... my finger started throbbing just looking at it!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 14:03:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not only my own accidents... but my sisters accidents also... she was/is our moms golden child. Im the older sister. Whenever she accidentally spilled/dropped/broke anything, Im the one that got the beating/punishment because I must have not been watching her well enough.  To my sisters credit (and even though out 3 children total she is the only one that has contact and actually loves our mom) she never used her position to get me in more trouble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 17:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the worst Ive ever seen! And on top of that they didnt even use the right colored caulk!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 03:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/catastrophicfailure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 19:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know! Crazy disappointing! Same thing happened to me with the Enders Game movie, also. Ive waited over 20 years to see my favorite book on the big screen... and they destroyed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 18:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Enders Game by Orson Scott Card. And literally any other book by Card. Oh and the Enders Game movie was SHIT! Pure unfiltered shit. So read the book!! (And then read the next 3 in that series... then read the prequels... and the books told from Beans perspective. Cause once you read Ender, then you love Ender,  and you never want to stop reading about him.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 18:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! This! The movie is fine... if youve never read the book...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 18:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Brandon Sanderson, especially the Stormlight Archives!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 18:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but way beyond Harry Potter! This like Harry Potter for adults! One of my favorite series!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 18:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man! Its blessing and a curse... my husband gets asked about his daughter right in front of me way too often... lol  and once at the airport, because I had him hold my ID and boarding pass (and it didnt help I wore my hair in braided pigtails ) that the TSA agent asked me if were were taking a secret trip and did my family know where we were going... it also didnt help that I didnt change my last name when we got married. He almost always refuses to go through the line standing next to me now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 05:06:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything about you is killing it!!! Love your hair, your look, and your tude!! You are #goals!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 04:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This might be the weirdest yet somehow most  oddly satisfying comment Ive read yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 01:57:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel you on this.. Ill be 38 in a couple of months.. I still get carded.. and people always ask my husband (who is the same age as I) if I am his daughter..  I agree its a blessing a curse!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 18:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 18:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 24 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 18:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 18:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally!!! I was wondering who was gonna pick up on  that!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 18:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just call me Dorian Grey...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 17:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 22!!  I wish!!! 38 this October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 17:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boy do I miss 23!! 38 this October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 17:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im legal thats for sure! 38 this October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 17:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this why I still get carded?? Lol thanks man! 38 this October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 17:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You were closer!! 38 this October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 17:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude!! So sweet!!  38 this October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 17:53:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your answer is my fave! I just love you!! 38 this October!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 16 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:48:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:46:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 21 :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:44:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 24?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Guess my age (but not my ass.. hes 15) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 05:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 15 American :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 18:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude! This! You are a FRIEND!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-23 15:09:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally a compliment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Followed u/ErgodicVeld recipe and made some succotash! Delicious! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 17:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-21 15:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude... If Pete Davidson can walk around all engaged to Ariana Grande.. well then, my man, you are equal to anyone you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-21 15:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a mom. But more importantly I was once a teenage girl with an abusive mother who was raised by her dad and brother. I will say that, unlike you, my dad and brother and extended family loved the mess out of each other. My dad tried crazy hard to fill the mom role.  But there is nothing that can take the place of that ache of wanting a mother who cares. Nothing. And so, sweetie, I understand wanting to open those cards and feel close. I tried desperately hard to forgive my mother and have a relationship with her (doctors say she is bi-polar) for years. But oh my God, it hurt. She disappointed me every time. She seriously doesnt know how to love. So I cut it off completely. And yes, still, at 38, that longing is there. So I just want you to know Im terribly sorry for you. You can message me anytime about anything. It wont be the same as a real life connection but I promise to answer you.

You should know, though, I never learned how to do make up either. Ive never worn it and I guess at this point I never will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-16 13:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude! I got the same curl in the same position! lol just posted it yesterday  oh and I use SM low porosity line also!  

Your *curl* is gorgeous!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-16 03:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look at you! Im so proud of you for even recognizing you are part of the problem. A real narc never does. Maybe you have some learned behaviors from your mom, but you at least see the problem and are reaching!

Show your husband this post... show him your willingness to accept responsibility and seek help.  Maybe he will understand thats not a sign ova true Narc. 

Then suggest individual and couple counseling!

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-15 23:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it has been a life a saver! Especially the leave in! I dont how it works, but it soaks right into my hair and makes it so soft!! I usually have blobs of product all around me by the end of the wash day because my hair just wont soak it up... but the Shea Moisture low porosity line is completely different! I would try it for sure! At least start with the leave in conditioner... if you like that (and by like, I mean you will love it!) then you will know you will like the shampoo and conditioner! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-15 18:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now if I could just get the rest to follow suit... lol

Todays (terrible) wash day routine...
Shampoo and condition with Shea Moisture low porosity no protein 
Shea Moisture low porosity no protein leave in
Jessicurl Rocking Ringlets
Curl Keeper Original
Miss Jessies jelly soft curls.

Squished that all in upside down
Diffused side to side then upside down 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My one tiny ringlet in a sea of waves.... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-15 18:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-14 05:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. Its like I dont actually have a childhood. I cant remember it. Most of my memories are the ones told to me. But over time, and the more I think of it, and the more my brother (with his crazy photographic memory) talks to me of it, the more(little bit) I remember.   (Mentally/physically abusive mother) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 18:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-10 01:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats the recipe? Do you just mix all those (really delicious) looking veggies together? Do you cook them together or separate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-01 17:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally also belongs in r/nononoyes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-01 17:23:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/childrenfallingover  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sisters, Zorro   Burrito! From cute and cuddly to fat and happy!  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 20:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trying dry my hair... but my Zorro thinks I make a better lookout tower...  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-24 01:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-20 21:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This totally belongs in r/ATBGE !!! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-18 00:52:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep... lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-18 00:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watching John Wick with my teenage boys... theyve somehow never seen it... I must be a terrible mom..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-16 20:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like I literally stopped reading after I read this line and immediately posted the same as you! 
MP fans for the win!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-16 20:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is the air speed velocity of an unladen swallow?  
African or European????  

Can you be my new best friend!!!!! Lol  not only a Monty Python fan, Im a fellow shorty.. (53) 

Anyway kudos to your process and you posting it! Im feeling more encouraged by the minute!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 20:30:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, this! Just let her do her thing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 20:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>   love those names!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 20:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, thats precious!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 20:15:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like hes wondering what your doing in his bed... lol  what a cute scumbag..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 20:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In addition to the stuff the previous redditor said... be careful not to mess with babies very much or try to pick them up and hold them.. at least for a week or so... because the mama may move them around to avoid to much interaction. Just place all the stuff next to them and let her do her thing.  (Also they like dark quite places). My boys kept messing with the babies our cat had and she kept moving from the box we gave her to any open closet she could find... lol. I had to teach the boys to let the babies be at least for a while and give that mama cat some peace. Lol 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 20:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my gosh... precious adorable indignant face!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My handsome Bad Kitty... winking it up for da ladies... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 20:08:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-09 05:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every single moment with my grandfather... young me had no idea what influence he was being...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-09 05:29:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I miss my mom...  I cut her out of my life... and its made it better... but I miss having a mom... even if it was a sh*tty one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-09 05:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This also belongs in r/assholedesign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-09 05:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This...  I feel you on this...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My adorable Bad Kitty. From super cute lion baby to super handsome tiger boy... and he still sleeps as weird as possible! Lol </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-09 05:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 04:14:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Naked lunges... or opening the pickle jar... its not good naked... 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 04:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 04:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahaha! Truth!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 04:05:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude! For real!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 04:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yasss!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 04:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You stole my post! Seriously, shaped my childhood/teenagers. All the Ender Wiggin series books did. Actually readying The Swarm now.. I cant get enough of that universe... even though my favorite guy is no longer there....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 04:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always carry my towel... just in case..,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-08 03:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On the tomato plants, your yellow flower is supposed to die and fall off. Look inside one that recently died... you should see a super tiny green tomato! I can totally assure you, there is not a problem with the tomatoes! They are looking great!

We dont grow zucchinis on my farm... so I cant be sure, but it could be bad pollination or a disease. I would call your local county extension agent and ask them. He/she should be able to tell you. 

For reference I live in north ms. My dad owns Wise Family Farm. (He used to be a county agent, too! ) 


Edit: I took a closer look at your tomatoes... this has nothing to do with the flower bud dying and falling off...
The tomatoes are starting to look yellow in the bottom leaves... you could have southern blight in your soil... which will mean that your tomato plant will die over time before producing much fruit. Southern blight follows the flow of the water under the soil... if you have any tomato plants that arent yet turning yellow from  the bottom up, you need to take some tin foil and dig down about 3 inches in the ground at the stem and wrap the tin foil around the stem of the plant. This will prevent the southern blight from moving up the plant. It will not help any plant that is already yellowing (the leaves are yellowing) at the bottom. 
This might also be the same thing thats destroying your zucchini but I cant speak to that for sure. And since I cant see your plants in person I cant be sure the tomatoes have southern blight. 
If you do have it though, its best next year to plant in raised beds with compost or potting soul. Or plant in hay bales like we do on our farm!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 14:00:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean you couldnt have written a more true statement!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 02:32:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would be a fitting post to r/trashy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 02:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very clear! She gets anything she wants with those big blue eyes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 21:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! We thinks so too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> She just showed up in our yard one day and hasnt left two months... obviously her name is Pretty Kitty. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 19:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-23 22:02:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That thing is more manipulative than my mother....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-23 15:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your curls are on point!!! Beautiful!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-23 15:46:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gorgeous!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 16:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, your hair is super beautiful just the way it is right now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 16:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe use more gel to get a better hold? Dont worry about it being crunchy... as soon as it dries completely you can scrunch out the crunch! I also use curl keeper original as the final product on my hair and it really helps with the frizziness! 

Also... most of the time frizz is your hair reaching out for moisture. When you must some water on it, use a spray bottle that has a little bit of your conditioner in it.  You can also use a bit more gel after you spritz with water. 

Also try a deep conditioning treatment once a week... find a deep conditioner that you like (I like the garnier fructis one minute miracle (the one with papaya extract) and I leave it on for 20 or 25 minutes. Then rinse out and do the rest of your routine. It seriously changed my hair after one time of doing this! Its like my frizz disappeared! 
Also a good leave in conditioner would help! 

Every head of hair is different... just keep experiment and researching and see what works! My curls were super uneven but the longer Ive stayed on the CG method the better and more uniform they have gotten!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 16:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your curls are beautiful!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 02:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 02:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/FyMW6Hf

My hubby!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 01:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A link to a few more pictures 



https://imgur.com/a/KleY659 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 00:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see her as a match!

https://www.buzzle.com/images/halloween/nerd-girl-halloween-blue-skirt-with-hat-costume.jpg

Or her!

https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQVXrdvqFBZFpQpa4V6B9eT3DZpEkWpCg2_LJ77EvrxMxDgEyDK

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 00:26:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see her as a match! 


https://jorgefarah.files.wordpress.com/2014/04/reasetree.jpg

Or her!

https://diversejapan.files.wordpress.com/2011/07/maria-rainier.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 00:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god, this!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 00:05:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This!!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-20 20:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I do too! But Im only 5 weeks into the CG method and I have more bad days than good ones. So its nice to know if I have an important event I can do this the night before to ensure a good hair day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 23:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not gonna lie.... Ive had quite a few hair days that me feel very Henry the VIII...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 22:45:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 21:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude! When I first pulled them out I was like... what the ***** is on my head!! Lol 

Oh and I always consider behead an option almost everyday! I totally hate doing anything time consuming with my hair!  Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 21:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are like under$10 for a big pack of different sizes on Amazon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 19:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I was worried about sleeping in them... and no lie, it wasnt the most comfortable... but I found a more comfortable side and went with it and once I finally fell asleep... well I was asleep and didnt feel them! 
Next I may drink some shots and maybe Ill pass out and not feel a thing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 18:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see lots of progress! Way to go!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 16:40:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can see from my previous posts that I have naturally curly/wavy hair. My normal wash routine is condition with the Shea Moisture, apply a little bit of the Shea Moisture curl enhancing smoothie, then curl keeper original, then Kinky Curly Curling gel. I plop for a while and then either diffuse or air dry. Im at the end of week 5 doing the CG method.

For the bendy rollers, I was on day 2 hair. I sectioned it off and sprayed each section with a water/conditioner mix and put a small amount of Herbal Essence totally twisted gel in each section. Then I put in the rollers and went to bed!

When I first took them out... I was like, oh my, what have I done! But after separating out the curls and SOTC and fluffing... well.. I gotta say I kinda like it!

Next time Im gonna try the giant rollers and see if I get larger curls! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tried bendy rollers for the first time! Trying to get my curly hair under control! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 16:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 04:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No... you are Beyonc!! 5th day hair and you are looking on point!!! I love your curls!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 02:28:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I stalked a bunch of curly girl Instagramers  lol... then I googled protein overload and it told me how to test for it using a strand of hair. It also told the physical signs... like limp or stringy curls, very dry hair that feels brittle and prone to break easier.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 17:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before pic was taken maybe 5 days before the after... I was working out of town and forgot a few products. Picked up some new ones without carefully reading the ingredients! Two products had silicones and I had been using them all week! On top of that, I figured out I was protein sensitive and everything I had with me was loaded with it!! 
Got home did a wash with a sulfate shampoo and used Shea moisture no protein conditioner and leave in. Curl keeper original and then finished off with Kinky Curly Curling Custard gel... gracious it was a vast improvement! And the after pic is my day 3 refresh from wash day! (Just a little conditioner mixed with water, diffuse, and SOTC!)

So happy to have my curls back!
Im on the beginning of 5 weeks CGM!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Protein and *gasp* products with silicon vs almost no protein and certainly no silicon! (After pic is a Day 3 refresh!!) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 17:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 03:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do the same as the reddit user above. Shea moisture no protein shampoo, conditioner, and leave in. And I use Curl Keeper original for the humidity and the Kinky Curly Curling Custard gel.  It seems to be working for my low porosity protein sensitive hair. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 00:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my gosh! A beautiful hair victory! Your curls look amazing!! So shiny!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-14 23:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was having the same problem with LA Look. If I used too little, I had no hold. If I used the right amount to hold it (and trust me I experimented lol) I could not SOTC. I recently switch to Kinky Curly Curling Custard gel and it works wonders! Creates an awesome cast that keeps frizz away and then easily Im able to SOTC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-14 23:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are making more than slight progress! 

One thing you might try is the protein overload strand test. Google the method and you should be able to tell whether your hair is protein sensitive or not. Also google other ways to tell.  My hair was protein sensitive and had a hard time curling all over if I used too many  products with proteins.  So I tried some cheap versions of some protein free ones and maybe one product with a protein and it completely changed the life of my hair! 
The only reason Im even  saying it (because its hard to tell just from a picture) but deva curl, while awesome, is pretty protein heavy. 
Maybe trying using only one or two of the deva products in your routine and change the others to ones without it. 
But google protein overload before you buy anything cause Im just a random person on the internet and you will know your hair better than anyone else! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-14 20:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful curls!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-14 20:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the title of your picture! Lol 
I use a spray bottle with one part leave in condish and 3 parts water. Some days (day 2 usually) thats all I need if I put enough product in my hair on wash day. The other refresh days I use the spray bottle mixture plus some gel.  

But humidity and your wash day products makes a lot of difference also. Also a satin pillow case made a world of difference in the amount of frizz I get! 

Some days I just embrace the frizz and go on. Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 07:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This! You took my heart and put it on reddit! Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 22:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats awesome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 21:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow!! Its beautiful! Do you trim the ends or is a for real no scissors near my hair?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 21:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude!! Just 2 days in!! Officially #hairgoals!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-10 21:31:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks amazing!! What an awesome and inspiring transition! I may just stop hunting for that straightener I had my husband hide! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 20:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gorgeous ringlets!!! Im having serious feels over them!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 05:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gorgeous! Hair! Everything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 05:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Girl!!! This hair!! One day!! #hairgoals!!! Its beautiful! Cant wait to see your hair a few weeks.. months... year... into CG method!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 05:30:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does this have protein as an ingredient? Im desperately searching for a deep conditioning treatment, but Im protein sensitive and have yet to find a good one without protein...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 05:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This process is a journey! Im only working on week 4 of my CG journey... and Ive had more bad days than good... but I have learned so much about my hair... and Im being inspired by people whove been doing it a year or more (thank you Instagram!) you wont have awesome curls everyday overnight... just keep researching about your hair and learning what works for you and what doesnt. A lot of newbies keep a hair journal detailing what they did each day and whether it was a good hair day or bad... so you can learn what is working and what isnt!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 04:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This! 100%!! You are !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 22:04:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im still struggling to figure out what curl pattern I have... a lot of my upper hair is wavy and a lot of the underneath is coiled and springy... 
but I found out I have low porosity hair and that seems to have helped when researching new products and methods.
Google the strand test for porosity and it will tell you a couple of really simple ways to check the porosity of your hair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 17:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the EXACT same way... some days I love it other days I just wNt to cry because I think its mess and just too wild... 
Im trying my best to stay with it at least for a year! But who knows... i find self looking for that straightener my husband hid from me... lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 12:14:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks amazing even if it wasnt in a ruined castle... the location made it even more epic!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gorgeous!!! #hairgoals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So like zero products?? It looks awesome and is exactly where I would like to be! Is this wash day or refresh day? What did you was/shampoo with?? Sorry for all the questions but I would love to a zero product day that looked like yours!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up on you tube Squish to Condish... I have very low porosity hair and it can and be dry like in a second.. but S2C has really helped work the conditioner into my hair before I rinse it out. I really think it has helped my hair moisture wise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My hair hates too much protein.. and I have heard devacurl products have a lot of protein... my hair got much healthier and more bouncy once I eliminated products that have proteins high up on the list.
Also my hair is low porosity and is always desperate for moisture! I have recently been using Aunt Jackies Curl la la Curling Custard a d it has so much moisture that I dont even need a leave in conditioner when using this product! 
But also... remember this is a journey and it might take a few months to figure out what your hair likes/needs... dont give up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By the way... your hair does not look greasy! It looks amazing!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:07:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same... I really want to dye my hair completely one color... I think my highlights and my curls dont see eye to eye!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:06:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also... isnt LA Looks (the blue one) da bomb!!! I just tried it a few days ago and I cant imagine my hair without it anymore!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks amazing!!! Gorgeous! 
Arent all those products CG approved?? Just wondering because I use or have used several of them!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats one awesome curl right there!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay!!! You will be so happy when you find the right products for your hair!  It already looks great!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 05:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like for real #hairgoals!!! Im only three weeks in! I cant wait for the 2 month mark!! Your curls are gorg!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 04:57:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your hair is #goals! So pretty!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 04:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay! Thats a hair victory!!! Keep on keeping on!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 04:53:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre right... looks amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 15:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its wicked hard to do... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 15:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I said I got belt whoopins... not that I gave them...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 15:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Mississippi... on a farm... its age 10 skill requirement... lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 15:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, Im old and blind... probably too many belt whoopins... lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 14:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you just say punishment smacks?  Belt Whoopin gotta better ring to it... at least thats what my daddy said...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 14:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How to back up my truck with a trailer on it... scratch that... Im still working on it...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 14:12:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dr. Katzenstein (or Dr. K as we called him). My high school chemistry teacher. Short slightly overweight mostly bland northern Jewish guy. Oh, but his brain! He had such a passion when teaching... his eyes just lit up! And man, if you ever approached him wanting to learn more... ah... his eyes... 
Im almost 40 and still think about him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 14:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow!!!! Thats a beautiful plant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 03:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also on the CG method you dont wash it daily. On refresh days most spritz with water or a mix of water and leave in conditioner and add other products... so diffusing or air drying takes a lot less time. Most CG method people only actually wash their hair 2 or 3 times a week... some even less!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 02:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does feel like forever.. but it is less time than when I use to blow dry my hair and straighten each section by tedious section! 
Also I dont diffuse it to 100% I diffuse it to about 60%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 00:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He looks so seriously majestic!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 00:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds about average according to the stuff Ive read. My hair is bad low porosity so it takes like all freaking day to dry if I dont diffuse it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITAP of a tiny rainbow across the street </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 15:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 14:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gorgeous!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 14:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One day!!!! Thats amazing!!! What a hair victory! Your curls look beautiful!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 14:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gorgeous hair! I cant wait to be 6 months into my journey!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 14:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  commit! Do research! (YouTube videos, instagram, the actual book.. etc..) and then on the days it isnt working... just keep at it! I have a post from just a few days ago on my profile where I tried new products and lost all my curls... I wanted to give up and go hunt down my straightener! But then a few days later and boom! Hair victory! This process is a journey of discovery about your hair and how to care for it and if you commit I promise you will fall in love with your locks all over again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 14:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Im like on an ego trip floating on cloud 9 right now... I thought I had a hair victory... apparently I got a skin and youth victory as well!! Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 14:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scrunch out the crunch! The gel creates a cast over your curls (which is great for no frizz!) but once its absolutely dry, you gently scrunch out the crunch and you are left with soft, fluffy, volume curls with minimal frizz!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 14:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Just watch some you tube videos stalk some curly girls on Instagram and then do this thing!! Lol you will have bad days and feel frustrated but just keep going! Its been worth it to me so far!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 14:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not any longer than when I used to straighten... its maybe a 5 minute or so longer shower than normal. Diffusing feels like it takes a while... but it doesnt take any longer than when I used to blow dry my hair straight and then take the straightening iron and section by tedious section flat iron it out.  And refresh days are even shorter! Maybe 5 to 8 minutes max!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 06:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your hair looks amazing!!! Love it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 06:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gracious! Your hair looks amazing!!! Way to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 05:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks awesome! Im thinking about the big chop also! This gives me encouragement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 05:58:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gorgeous curls! Im so jelly!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 05:56:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  thank you! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 05:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im dying... no Im not hiding a hiding a covered painting! Genetics and a no make up regimen are all I got! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 05:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It means Curly Girl... and its method is outlined in a book by Lorraine Massey..., or google it and watch you tube videos like I did!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 05:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously guys... its genetics! And a no make up regimen!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 02:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep 2 more years and Ill see the big 4 0... as my user name suggest, born in 1980.. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 02:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Curly Girl... its a book by Lorraine Massey... basically the Bible for curly hair... or google curly hair method and watch the videos!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 02:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Curly Girl... its a book by Lorraine Massey... basically the Bible for curly hair... or google curly hair method and watch the videos!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 01:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too much!! :) but since Im nearly 40 and rarely hear that, Ill take it!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 01:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a homeless chic kinda way...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:40:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I literally just use the diffuser than came with my hair dryer!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also... look up curly Susie on you tube. She actually co washed her hair every day. And it looks amazing! I actually co wash mine about an average of every other day. But my porosity is so low, I really need the moisture. And I think its helping! (Who knows... in a week it could be back to being a mess again!)
Also pay attention to your ingredients... make sure its free of all the stuff a CG doesnt want. Also my hair tends to not like too much protein... I found that out earlier this week... (You can see a previous post on my profile and what it did to my hair). So I cut out most of the products I was using that had a protein ingredient too high up in the list!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I struggle every day! I cant claim hair victory every time! But Im learning a lot about my hair and what it likes and doesnt like. And I too have rewashed on the second day more than once! Its seriously a journey with lots of research! Just dont give up! 
I do the pineapple at night and have a satin pillow case as well. Also if I refresh my hair, I make sure to diffuse it while hanging my head upside down. Diffusing helps a lot with volume! Also google about clipping your roots when drying (both air drying and diffusing). And google Medusa clipping. I dont go to bed with wet hair and I make sure to really scrunch out all the crunch at the end of the day! 

But seriously! Google curly girl methods and volume for curly girls and watch you tube videos and stalk those awesome girls on Instagram! You will learn so much!!  My husband thinks I have a curly hair obsession but my research is finally starting to take off!  Like todays results were from researching my hair porosity (its low... so low) and then researching what low porosity curly girls do and then modifying that for my hair. I honestly think that helped me get the results I did today!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh God, I thought I had that scene good and repressed... thanks a lot.. now Im all up in my feels  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:22:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugggg all of these!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mr. Stark, I dont feel so good...    right in the feels....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:15:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you look great! I dont like the slim fit suit jacket either!  Comfort = Confident = Hott   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Squish to condition is a technique where you scrunch and pulse to get the conditioner into your hair. You squish each product in separately. I sometimes even use a spray bottle of plain water to spray on my hair between product applications because I like to STC (squish to condish) on soaking wet hair. Plus I have really low porosity so my hair needs all the help it can get with getting the conditioner and product into it. Some wonderful curly girls have some awesome videos on it! Just google it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-06 00:01:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously! Do it! I was on the fence forever... I used to straighten my hair nearly every single day. Everyone could tell when I was running late because I would let it go curly. But I hated it so much, that was a rarity! After watching countless you tube videos and stalking Instagram curly girls I finally decided to go for it! I have more bad hair days than good... but Im till a newbie trying to figure what products and techniques work best for my hair.  And my worst hair day now would be my best curly hair day before I started the method!  Im actually excited about my hair now and I cant wait to see what a years difference will make!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 23:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  thank you! I had to have my husband hide my straightener from me... and today is the first day (in 3 weeks) i havent felt the urge to find it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 23:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  thank you! I cant wait to see what they look like a year from now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 23:22:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy smokes! What a beautiful kitten!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 23:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Different gels do get out of the crunch phase while I diffuse... but this LA Looks does not. I had to SOTC! Lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 22:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  it means to scrunch out the crunch! If you use gel on your hair, as it dries it creates a cast on your hair. Which is a good thing as it helps eliminate frizz! Once your hair is 100% dry, you gently scrunch your hair and the crunch goes away! Leaving  frizz free crunch free hair! Google some videos to see how some awesome curly girls do it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Im so happy with it.. today... lol tomorrow could be whole different story! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I swear you will get there... I have more bad hair days than good and Im still trying to figure what works the best for my hair. I love this sub for all its tips and encouragement!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:27:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly is just the ole genetic roulette... lol Im glad you found something that works for you! It will pay off in the end Im sure!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Co wash is the act of washing your hair without shampoo, just with conditioner. Squish to condition is a technique where you scrunch and pulse to get the conditioner into your hair. Some wonderful curly girls have some awesome videos on it! Just google it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant wait to get where you are!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Im still a newbie and have really bad hair days... but the before and afters are what keep me going! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! The side by side is what keeps me going on the days I feel like reaching for my straightener! I use to think my natural hair just looked crappy... and that I couldnt do anything about it..,3 weeks after accidentally watching a you tube video... and Im like oh! Snap! Where has this been all my life! I cant wait to see a year from now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaasss! Its my next Nook buy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Give it a try! I have no regrets! I use to feel the same way about my hair!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know!! Im loving the CG method! Even on my bad days! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 21:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  not really! Im almost 40 and Ive never worn make up.  I moisturize every morning and thats it.  Nerium day time cream has been my moisturizer of choice for the last few years. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 19:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Todays routine:
No poo, co wash only with Bella Curls Coconut deep conditioning masque as my conditioner. Squish to condition after detangling, then rinse out. Used Aunt Jackies Curl La La defining custard, squish to condish, then LA Looks Extreme (the blue one). I squished that in also! Plopped for about 10 minutes... then diffused until 80% dry. Once 100% dry I SOTC!  

So super happy with todays results!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3rd week into CG method! Ive had my ups and downs already but today is my best wash day yet!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 19:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 17:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jeezz!!! Thats awesome! Im so jealous right now!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 17:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im excited with ya!!! Thats an amazing haul!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 17:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I wasnt looking at it well.. I was hoping it wasnt a car/farm equipment accident. We get those a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 15:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 23:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mississippi gets it right every now and again... lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 20:14:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! The $80 dollar fixed you mentioned... will it fit a Nikon 3200? Ive been researching prime lenses and other lenses trying to figure out which one I want to go t next.. I hadnt thought about camera stores... I live in rural Mississippi... pretty much Best Buy is the go to, but Im quite certain if I actually looked I could find a camera store or two! Seriously, thank you for the tips!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 18:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you love it, you can make it work! Look up agritourism and see if its for you! Its a great way to bring life to a family farm and let it be sustainable for more than one family member. You can even turn that nursery into an agritourism business! And a business degree of any kind couldnt hurt no matter what type of business you would like to run!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 18:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a 1953 John Deere 40. My whole life, Ive called it the putt putt tractor. Because thats the sound it makes running!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 18:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love a different lens, but Im using the kit lens. I cant justify spending a lot on a new lens until I learn to master the camera and lens I have... lol

That cat is a new one for us and hungry for affection... she wouldnt stop moving and twisting and turning so I did the best I could! Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 18:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 18:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much! I was pulling a wagon load of families back from our pumpkin patch last october.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 17:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We dont have anything newer than 1980 on the farm! My uncle and father miraculously keep them all going!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 17:37:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it!!!  thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My view this past October... cant wait for fall! (Yeah, I know, we are old school on this family farm!) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 16:51:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When the Irises just started to bloom </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 16:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Focus, composition, post editing... thoughts? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 02:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITAP of the irises in my yard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 02:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITAP of my blue eyed girl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 02:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 02:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? I can try it! I just like the bright blue of her eyes... :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITAP of my backyard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 01:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Focus? Post editing? Anything you think? All will be helpful! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 01:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 23:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having to actually go to the library research section instead of the magic google in your hands...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 23:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dial up internet..... insert horrific noise and wait time here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 23:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 19:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you!!! It was advice from this sub that helped!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 16:34:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted an update post with a picture of my resurrected curls! Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 16:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Refresh routine: sprayed my hair down with my spray bottle of water mixed with Cantu leave in conditioner until it was pretty damp/wet. Then smoothed over a little Herbal Essence totally twisted gel and then scrunched it in for a while. Then diffused a little.  Look at my other post to see how bad my curls looked after trying a new product or two! (And my normal routine is posted in the comments of that post). Definitely sticking to the products I know work for some time to come!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 16:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I refreshed my hair this morning with my spray bottle of water mixed with Cantu leave in conditioner till it was damp/wet. Then I smoothed over Herbal Essences totally twisted gel and then scrunched for a while. Then diffused. My curls came back!! I wish I knew how to put another picture on this post!   I think maybe my hair didnt like the Eco gel or maybe I didnt use enough?  Either way Im excited to see my curls again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 04:18:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your fur baby is adorable!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 03:57:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will do!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 03:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Monopoly..... it doesnt end well...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 03:10:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally understand!! (the editing problem! Lol) Thank you for the heads up and the link!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 02:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you serious!!! Dear Lord!!

Wait I just read the packages, they say no sulfates, parabens, mineral oil, etc...  which is the exact same thing the rest of my CG products (shea moisture and Cantu products) say.... am I supposed to be looking for something else on the packaging?  If so, for the love of curls, tell me! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 01:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I love this sub! Everyone is so helpful!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 00:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the tip and encouragement that itll go back!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 22:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im using Bella curls coconut oil deep conditioning masque as my conditioner, Miss Jessies leave in condish, Cantu for kids curling cream, and Miss Jessies Jelly soft curls. Then I just STC and plop for at least twenty minutes, then diffuse.
Today (a real wash day) I did all that except i used Shea Moisture strengthen and restore treatment masque (last night, I left it on for twenty minutes then rinsed it out) and then instead of the Jelly Soft Curls gel I tried the ECO style olive gel.

I cant believe I lost my curls already! Im only three weeks into the CG method! Any advice on what to do now would be really appreciated!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need help! I had curls a few days ago and now theyre gone! Routine in comments </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 22:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITAP of some flowers in my backyard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-29 22:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-29 22:06:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nikon 320O iso: 100,  1/500, f/4.5, 26mm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Close up of flower bud. Any constructive critiques? I literally just started using a DSLR, so any thing you have to say would be great. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-29 22:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-29 07:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 53 and yaaasss! Same! You could not have described it better!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 19:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the tip!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 18:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I phone 7, no filter, just the late setting sun. I normally like to use my Nikon D3200 (Im just a beginner) but I was working out on the farm and didnt have it with me.  It wouldve been such a great shot with that camera! (Sharper and better focus) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITAP of our sunflower field last October </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 18:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 18:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like the light in this photo! Actually I love the overall feeling of it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 18:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt know my parents had another child! How great is Dad, though?!  

Had an ex husband tell me I will always be disappointed in love because my father loved me too much and I expected him to do the same. 
My dad loved me the exact amount equal for 2 parents.  The only reason Im halfway well adjusted!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 02:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 23:19:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is a great picture!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Straight out of the camera (Nikon D3200 w/kit lens). To edit or not to edit? Is it even worth it? (Just got my DSLR and am practicing!) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 23:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 03:26:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for the help! Can I ask, what ingredients should I be looking for that signify humectants?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 23:29:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im using Bella curls coconut oil deep conditioning masque as my conditioner, Shea Moisture curl enhancing smoothing as my curl cream and leave in. And then Herbal Essence totally twisted curl scrunching gel. Then I just STC and air dry.  Im loving the results... except for frizz. I got lots and Im not really sure why or what to do. Ive tried plopping and I like it. But its not helping the frizz. :) still loving my hair through this transformation though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One week in to CG METHOD! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 23:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>