<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6175</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 02:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Count me in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 16:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Baby steps, we got this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 16:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im glad too. I havent been able to bring myself out of that cycle in a while. So yeah, I guess Im doing better than I though lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 15:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ive just come back from walking my dog and am now sitting down to finish a blanket Im making for him. Its funny that you mentioned writing as well. I just put a new blank leather booklet in my work bag for tonight. I guess this is just me attempting to really start making a change for the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My head is so loud right now </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 14:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bpd is screaming in my head. It is so loud at the moment I can barley drown it out. Im trying so hard to respect your boundaries to give you what you need to heal.   

Ive been an moron in the past. Ive been selfish and mean and I own that. Its all on me.  Youve been nothing but kind, understanding and loving. Even when you couldnt be.   

This is so hard for me to do. I love you and I want you to be as well and healthy as you can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is one of the hardest things </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 13:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bpd is screaming in my head. It is so loud at the moment I can barley drown it out. Im trying so hard to respect your boundaries to give you what you need to heal. 

Ive been an moron in the past. Ive been selfish and mean and I own that. Its all on me.  Youve been nothing but kind, understanding and loving. Even when you couldnt be. 

This is so hard for me to do. I love you and I want you to be as well and healthy as you can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-23 20:38:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is the binge eating I find very difficult to control at times. I try to binge on healthy snacks but Im a sucker for chips. Eating more protein seems to help keep it a bay though. Not eating too late at night may help as well. I try not to eat late but its difficult with my work hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-23 13:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im on a 2mg dose of abilify to take the edge off some of the anger, mood swings a depressions. For me, it has helped. I find Im a lot more stable. However, I have had some side effects like gaining a bit of weight (which I can control by going to the gym) and the small muscle twitching is annoying, but I feel for me its working over all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-16 03:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would like to take the time to thank everyone who has responded. I wasnt expecting this at all. All your words of encouragement, warmth, concern and compassion. I am truly overwhelmed. 

I do have a therapist and it was his idea for me to do this. He thought it would help and it has. 

Im an ordinary girl trying to make it one day to the next. But all your words will stay with me as well. So thank you everyone for helping me cope and get through this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-15 15:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for taking the time to say that. It means a lot especially coming from a first responder. Thank you for all that you do as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-15 11:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I ran to your aid </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-15 08:15:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You died on Friday. You were hit by a car seconds before I stepped off the bus along with another gentleman. I saw you every morning walking down the street as I went to work. I ran to help you when no one else did. I did compressions on you before fire department and ambulances got there. I hope you know I did  everything I could. May god keep and rest your soul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-17 05:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey thank you for your response. Ive only been in his medication for a short period of time. I was also diagnosed with chronic depression, social and general anxiety.  Ive had a suicide attempt as some years ago and was hospitalized again three years ago. 

I was told the Abilify could take the edge of the extreme anger and aggression I feel. I was warned about the side effects like the potential for diabetes and weight gain. The first blood tests will be done in 2 weeks. 

So far I think I feel less anger and seem to be thinking more clearly. Or maybe Im over analyzing. However, I also dont feel as hungry. 

I go to therapy every week but I was not thinking that Abilify would be a quick fix. Ive only recently come to terms with a BPD diagnosis. Honestly the class of medication was making me anxious. 

You are right though, I think I will seek a second opinion. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 07:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my, Im sorry to hear this. Ill be careful. Thank you for the input.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Abilify </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-16 03:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is anyone else on Abilify and how do you feel its working for your BPD?  Im curious. I just started with this medication and Im not sure what to expect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 20:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy birthday!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>