<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9452</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 09:52:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry I'm not a child anymore, I drink my juice straight out of the glass, no straws used </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 09:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 09:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not American so I don't have a social security number but the Italian equivalent is the Codice Fiscale which is a tax code if that helps I'm down for sending it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 00:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes he's single!
+39 391 188 0140 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 00:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually it was when he was 20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 00:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R/wosh CrInGe normie reeeeeeeeee go back to Instagram </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 18:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No but there were vegan options </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 18:16:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On jah? Religion bad though right guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 18:00:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes he's jewish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 17:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand what you mean now, and I do agree that they don't deserve to be burned alive, but at the same time they don't not deserve it. The protester seemed to have thrown the molotov in their general area and it hit her. You can't fault the protester for doing that as he feels that change needs to happen, and sometimes it needs to happen through violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 17:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, english isn't my first language so I might have misunderstood what you said. Can you show me how I am wrong here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 17:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not one of those "acab" people. In my country (Italy) the police is quite brutal but most of them aren't. I don't condemn violence towards all police as they usually do more good than bad. 

There are circumstances where acab is applicable though. A government that uses its police force to gun down protesters is pretty shitty. I'd rather be a "tankie CTH (idk what this is) idiot than a person trying to defend a police force murdering random civilians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 17:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you realise that even if you are a cop you most likely can't sustain your family (in chile). A cop earns probably minimum wage and with the situation in Chile it most likely means that they can't support themselves and their families (thus the protests). The only reason why a government like Chile's still has power and control is because of the armed forces and police. By just sitting there idly as a police officer, even if you don't personally shoot anyone, means that you have no regard for human lives as you keep on helping and supporting a corrupt and terrible government. 

I don't understand why you say you'd just show up and not be effective, do you realise that workers can be fired right? If a cop friend is getting beat up and you sit there and watch don't you think you'd be in some kind of trouble? The same trouble you said you were afraid of in the 1st line. 

Personally, I'd like to think that I wouldn't just sit there idly while my own citizens who I am tasked with protecting are getting gunned down by the police, but hey maybe it's just cause I'm a random zoomer on reddit, and apparently a "tankie CTH idiot" (whatever that means). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 17:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't you think that if you are aware of your own police force shooting unarmed people they'd feel some kind of remorse and quit? You know, being a decent human being and all that. Of course that one person probably wasn't guilty of shooting anyone, but they are still associating and being part of the police force that does do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 16:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> police: shoots at random protesters
protesters: retaliate by throwing molotov cocktails
reddit: *surprised pikachu face* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 16:01:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad is fat, if it helps. I'm non-binary and my grandparents, aunt, and mother are religious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AITA for saying murdering random people is bad? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 15:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi guys, on mobile so sorry for bad formatting, also using a throwaway yadda yadda.

So last week I (M17) went to a restaurant (genderless6) to eat out with my mother (F54) my father (M55) my grandparents (M86   F74), my aunt (F51) and my dog (M9). 
At some point through our delicious 5 star meal, the man sitting next to our table said he felt like killing random people. Of course I immediately stood up and told him that it's not right to do something like that. 
Everyone immediately clapped and started cheering as they thought I was NTA. The restaurant manager apologised for that guy's rudeness and I got the meal for free.
After getting back home my dog (M9) told me that he thought I was TA because I shamed an innocent man in front of a whole restaurant, so am I the asshole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 23:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't worry I'm Italian, you don't have to teach me how to avoid paying taxes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 23:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should try avoiding taxes instead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 13:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The graph above is about people's qualities, not about positive things and thus I don't think Gandhi deserves a spot in the love section at all. I understand Buddha being there as he was loving to all people, but a person like Gandhi who was wildly a racist, sexist and homophobe doesn't deserve a spot there. 

As for your quote, it's one of the dumbest things I've heard. Should we remember Hitler for reducing unemployment or the holocaust? We remember both the good and bad of people cause that's how we form opinions on people. We can't simply ignore all the bad that people have done just to look at the good they did. Winston Churchill is considered a war hero but he also diverted food supplies from the Raj to British soldiers which led to many famines. 

Sure Gandhi played a huge role in India's independence and for that he should be rewarded but he was also a horrible, nasty little man and instead of ignoring that part of him we should educate people on it.

A person can't really be both loving and not loving at once though can they? A person that is loving wouldn't call black people dirty animals like Gandhi did. Was he a patriot? Sure. Did he love his country? Sure. But he sure as hell wasn't loving overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 11:56:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But he is not an artist. He managed to liberate india from colonial rule but it doesn't mean he wasn't a pos. Everything ranging from calling black people animals and very dirty, calling hitler a dear friend, giving enemas to young women and making young women sleep naked with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 11:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was fundamentally a dick head overall though. I don't see how a racist and a pedo can be under "love" in any way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 10:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gandhi: a racist pedo but apparently is the best of all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 10:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll take a lethal punch any day please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 02:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No please tell me you're joking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 00:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/lostredditors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-03 01:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To add on to this, I've been spinning for a while but only know the 4 fundamentals. I don't really enjoy sitting down and watching tutorials so I don't really have the chance to learn new tricks but I've been happy at the level I'm at currently. Sometimes it's way more fun to figure stuff out on your own instead of tutorials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 02:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was out on a day trip in Mantova and I captured this shot while walking around a park soon before having to leave. I thought that the composition with the branches around the frame and the statue in the centre was very nice. I took this with my Canon EOS 200D and the stock lens. I'm only a beginner in photography and would appreciate any feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Parks are wonderful </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 02:12:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 00:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA then your wife has no say over the tiger's body and wishes, it's all about consent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 22:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Info: was the tiger okay with going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 12:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did I really just forget that melody? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 22:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He lost his finger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 22:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit is partially owned by a Chinese company

yeah so we shall keep using reddit and giving this Chinese company more money instead of stopping to use reddit, cause otherwise how are we going to get our daily dose of memes!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A new friendship is formed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 00:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 07:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't those two timelines only audio and video too? It means he added no sound effects or any kind of extra detail or work in his editing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 10:07:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But then that isn't a passion, just something you might be interested in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 08:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you think that a couple hundred thousand of people with 3d printed guns would do anything to the Chinese military? 
China would just raze Hong Kong to the ground if they wanted to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> discord_irl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 23:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 10:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A wood fired pizza costs like 5-7 euro here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 09:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who "just wants to relax" in a public bathroom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 18:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am Italian and can confirm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 00:22:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The whole of Italian reddit just cringed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 21:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crit chance is the chance you have of critting on your attacks so no it won't chance if you have 100% or 102% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 21:16:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but he's asking for a real one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 19:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come to Milan and you'll see many wankers buying like 2000 shoes or other super expensive clothing items that don't look good or any different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 19:15:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure Bape is the Japanese equivalent of Gucci or some other high fashion brand, not saying their stuff looks good but it explains why it's worth so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 19:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blue cheese (such as Gorgonzola) is common on pizza here in Italy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 19:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine there's a huge terrorist attack and since the terrorist hasn't been sentenced you never find out stuff about it. People would miss so many things that are going on in the world. A better solution would be to write as unbiased as possible, not censor the media </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Guy wants a free $500 hoodie in exchange for a shoutout on a YouTube channel </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 19:07:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 19:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goodbye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 19:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 19:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A scout is a support, just not a healing support </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> American Ice Cream sucks and is overpriced. Here in Italy, a 2.5 euro ice cream would be more or less the same size as the one in the picture but in the US the prices were more than double that for a smaller ice cream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't be OP! Just as long as you enjoyed it the calories don't count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Raw or do you prepare them in some way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 14:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if that's a carbonara but it sounds good anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 07:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm not the only one who got that song recommended to me while doing my philosophy essay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 20:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With that grammar seems like she got the stroke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 19:22:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GG jungle diff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 17:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, using your logic, all a rapist has to do is claim they have never done said action and we must immediately believe them. I was wrong to say that cause there's no reliable source to prove that she did sexually assault them but just cause she said she didn't do it doesn't mean she's telling the truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 16:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly I feel like I may be the only person on Reddit that likes her music. I've heard that she also had sex with them but clearly I was wrong so I apologise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 16:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or the genocide of native Americans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 09:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She said she would fuck men after drugging them, meaning they cannot give consent. If a man roofied a woman and then fucked her the media would be going crazy but since she's a famous celebrity woman no big media is giving a fuck about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:13:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rap more liek crap amirite lads music was better when John Lennon beat his wife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 09:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The brown one looks like a huge turd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 00:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/justlearnedthefword </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 22:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although this is a nice comment it's really not what the sub is about, he's asking for advice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 12:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm Italian and I've lived abroad for around 6 years and after I've moved back to Italy I've just started hating it more and more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 15:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm Italian and I'd never heard of Alfredo until a year ago some streamer mentioned it on stream. My grandad used to say that the most important part of any good Italian dish is the highest quality main ingredients. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 09:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh oh I go to that station every day but this is the first time I hear something like this happening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oh for fucks sake this is so unecessary and cringy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 07:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 00:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is pretty recent but 
I was coming home from school and my dad picked me up at the metro to bring me home. He starts asking the same question and every time I answered with "no thanks" . After I told him there was no reason to ask me the same exact thing 8 whole times in a row and he just goes ballistic. He tells me that I shouldn't be treating him like shit etc.
When we finally arrive home he tells me that I'm a schitzo and that I need to go back to my "schitzo doctor" (basically just my psychologist that I go to cause of anxiety and depression). 
Skip to 3 days later and I told him that I thought it was pretty rude to call me a schitzo since I didn't do anything wrong and he tells me that it's no different than calling him rude cause he was asking me the same question. 
He has since not apologised (definitely not the first time) but I'd acting like nothing ever happened and that we're best buds


Sorry for the long post I really had to get this off my chest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> League of legends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Badass guy will fight anyone and boil their children! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 13:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 19:07:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Essential oils *can* be useful but it's definitely not for healing / curing cancer or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 16:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Terroni gang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 22:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are those Balenciaga's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 18:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/accidentalitalian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 16:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can find used s10s in great condition for less than 650 dollars so this isn't that bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 01:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I'd think you'd look really good with a man bun but it would take a while to grow your hair out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 21:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, it was just a regular supermarket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 19:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah those really look like them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 18:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be making pickled peppers tonight :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hey guys I just rescued this plant from dying in a supermarket yesterday and was wondering what type of pepper plant it is. Any info about it would be great (how often I can water it etc). Thanks! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 15:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 12:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly, "suck me" or "suck your mum" are very common insults at least in the UK and I've heard them plenty of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saw this huge guy at a renaissance fair in Italy :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 00:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 20:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *gets on my knees and unzips your pants* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 19:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does this fit here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 00:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just saw the first iPad so I assumed they were all the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 23:43:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah i didn't see that, thanks for clarifying. Don't have any apple products so I didn't really know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 16:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boomer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 21:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La canzone  pure carina ma non posso dire che non hanno delle facce da cazzo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 20:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boomer rap more like crap amirite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 20:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This pizza looks really tiny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 19:05:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So at the moment you claim you couldn't think of anything which is why you didn't go and get the ice pack on your own but at the same time you went to him and unplugged his pc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 18:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Giaime e Lazza, la canzone si chiama Fiori </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> These two rappers from Italy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 16:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Owl unit spotted in Italy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 15:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 13:19:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one cared who i was until i put on the mask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Donald is watching you </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 17:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Brther you must accept the sofa </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 17:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 17:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Took this with my Huawei p20 pro while I was visiting Dublin's Japanese gardens. Thought the flower was really pretty so I gave it a shot :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just a flower </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 17:39:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 12:36:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't it like that for every game though? In league you can't buy less than 5 worth of RP. Skins don't add anything to the game so if you don't want to spend the money on them then don't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just a flower :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 21:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 19:26:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sent a discord friend request! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 08:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A number of clues: exactly the same camera angle

Exactly the same plant growth

The same shadows

The same vehicle and other objects in the background

The single foreground figure is in the first pic, in the same place relative to the slightly taller man in the front row

There seems to be the shadow of one of the other officers head, in the same place... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 22:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you read the article you'd see that only very recently the countries finally started returning it. Before the waste was not able to be recycled and probably was thrown in the sea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 14:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lots of developed nations send lots of their trash, including plastics, to poorer Asian nations and most of that trash is usually not recycled and instead thrown into the sea.

[https://www.bbc.com/news/world-48444874](https://www.bbc.com/news/world-48444874) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-11 09:27:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/sneakybackgroundfeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mumble rap bad, Eminem good, upvotes please </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 02:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 22:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'm guessing it's in Fortnite and 12 kills is pretty good imo. In the couple of weeks I played I don't think I ever got more than 4 or 5 (although I'm not a pro). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 21:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello I'm in the same time zone and would love to learn TFT as I am really clueless on how to play it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blurry picture of a cat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-13 18:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 14:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hasayo#4467 for my discord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-10 21:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I'm pretty bad at league (high silver) but I'm not toxic so we could play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> gggggg </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-10 17:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 01:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Speak for yourself sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Winchester 3 best game because of Geraldo. Upvote this or you are a fan of EA </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 15:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 20:45:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Semen died :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 20:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> R5: my King's name is semen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This does put a smile on my face </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 20:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 13:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well maybe r/sneakybackgroundfeet would fit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 00:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been here since day 1 buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 22:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We don't have guidance counselors and teachers here don't really give a damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 22:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so glad that it worked out more or less well after all for you and that gives me so much hope for my future. Thanks! \^\_\^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 22:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much! Several friends and my SO are what have been helping me these past months and I can't thank them enough. I wish the world wasn't as shitty so that no one would have to go through this. Lots of people in foster care here are beaten and mistreated so I fear that it wouldn't be too good for me. I just have 2 years left and thanks to people like you I know I can do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 22:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad has choked me out two times now, one time because i closed my bedroom door while I was hanging out with my friend. Other times he has tripped me on the stairs for no reason other than enjoyment and I had to get stitches cause I hit my head pretty hard. I'm afraid to call the cops or do anything as I do not want to lose my chance in life to do good and I'm also afraid I'd lose all my friends and especially gf (we're long distance). All I have is two years left and then I can finally get out of here. Thanks so much for the support. As for the rest of the post I totally understand why people were calling me TA and I understand that i shouldn't have assumed when they'd be back etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 22:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand, I should have not expected them to be home when i wanted or make any kind of assumptions and it was wrong of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 22:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree with being TA cause of expecting them to come back home early and that they didn't check my phone, I only added that part when people asked me why I didn't prepare food on my own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 22:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much, you have no idea how much this helps me. I'm planning on leaving for university as soon as I finish my school and to find a job for the next two years. I plan to essentially cut them out as soon as I can and go live with my girlfriend in Ireland at 18/19. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand that I might seem entitled but as i answered before " I'm 16 and all there was left in our house was some fruit, apple and  some pasta. If I had eaten the pasta instead and not eaten the sushi  they would have potentially beaten me or yelled at me / gotten very  angry for it which is why I didn't prepare anything" so I had no chance to eat anything else or I would have gotten in trouble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As I replied to someone else above " I'm 16 and all there was left in our house was some fruit, apple and  some pasta. If I had eaten the pasta instead and not eaten the sushi  they would have potentially beaten me or yelled at me / gotten very  angry for it which is why I didn't prepare anything " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:54:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, they often punish me for extremely silly things. One day my dad said all chinese people eat dogs and some other racist stuff and when I said it wasn't true he left me to walk back home on the side of the highway and it took me about an hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I definitely wouldn't beat my 16 year old kid like they do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They weren't by themselves, they were having an appetizer thing with their friends and also a couple of my friends (including my bff) and they didn't invite me as they usually do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I forgot to add, i asked them beforehand and said it wouldn't take too long. I don't mind so much about not answering my texts as the consequences that could have happened if I had eaten something else before they came back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course I didn't expect them to be that fast although it was only an appetizer which consists of crisps and snacks. I asked them how long it would take before they left and said it wouldn't take too long, I totally understand if they wanted to stay more but at least tell me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 16 and all there was left in our house was some fruit, apple and some pasta. If I had eaten the pasta instead and not eaten the sushi they would have potentially beaten me or yelled at me / gotten very angry for it which is why I didn't prepare anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AITA for getting mad at my parents for making me wait? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 21:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 20:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you check the brother's twitter everyone is so supportive of her and I've read comments saying that the mother suffered enough... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 16:41:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes finally I found someone who plays EU4, I'd be down to play, also 16M and CEST </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 16:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PM'd you, would be down to play minecraft sometime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 11:34:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can confirm that's how we are
Source: am spaghetti </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 03:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FBI yes hello </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 18:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This picture right here makes me want to buy a birb of my own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 17:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This might be weird but he looks so soft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 19:56:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean photographic memory right? Cause on wikipedia it makes a distinction between the two and says that eidetic memory has been proven. Also that doesn't really answer my question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can a person with an eidetic / photographic memory still get Alzhaimer's? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 17:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like do the two conditions cancel each other out? If they can get Alzheimer's would it affect the person slow than usual? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-04 11:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madonna Italian representation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 18:34:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although Arnie was in much better movies Dwayne was also in Moana and Jumanji which were quite good overall, but still can't compare to Arnie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> OMG I'm literally shaking and crying my 4 year old son with cancer just painted this before dying. Upvotes to the left </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-30 12:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 17:26:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so confused, I was stating the fact that it's not true that men will experience less violence in their lives and that it doesn't matter if they do or not because it's totally fair to feel in danger from a man at 1am regardless of your gender </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 17:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly, a man at 1am is scary for anyone really, man or woman, her gender doesn't change the fact that she did something to protect herself from a potential threat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 17:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not saying women aren't likely to get raped or assaulted sexually or robbed or killed, I literally said that her reaction was normal in that situation cause bad things happen, but saying that men don't understand fear is silly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 16:30:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yeah it's more likely to be a woman, but that doesn't change the fact that men are statistically more in danger than women. I think the OP is NTA cause her reaction was normal, but to say that women are in more danger and that men don't understand is silly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 16:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I might be wrong but men are more likely to get robbed and murdered right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-27 20:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely gyros and saganaki from Greece and pierogi from Poland and also I love me some oliebol from the Netherlands and quite strangely also Yorkshire pudding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 22:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well on quora they get paid to ask popular questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 20:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd prefer talking pretty much anywhere else than on Reddit since it's pretty crappy, you can dm me your discord/Snapchat/ whatever else you'd prefer to use </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 19:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello you seem quite cool and we could definitely chat some time. I'm 16 M and share pretty much the same interests so maybe we could chat sometime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 22:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as she's still fresh enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 22:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As user u/TheManInTheShack said on a previous thread " Tap on the user icon in the lower-right corner (the one that takes you  to your account) then tap on the Settings icon (the gear in the  upper-right corner) then tap on Text Size. "

He says it wasn't available on android but the original thread was a year ago so it might have been implemented by now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 21:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can try showing them stats of unemployed people and how many of those don't have any highschool / university diplomas if you can find those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 21:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very good cat loaf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Would it be fine to dry clothes in an oven or microwave? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 21:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So for my slippers to dry up it will take roughly 3 days cause of the cold weather. Would it be fine to dry them in my oven or microwave? If yes why don't more people do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-24 00:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 192 pieces of geomag are about 100 euro on Amazon ($118) so it should be cheaper than 800 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 22:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 1st Italo-Ethiopian war started in 1895... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 20:00:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct me if I'm wrong but didn't Mussolini do that years before in Abyssinia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 01:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had to censor clap though it's a family friendly subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 16:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it might be mobile data plan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 11:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slightly longer version [https://www.reddit.com/r/pussypassdenied/comments/ai1tgi/girl\_slaps\_boy\_and\_gets\_payback\_found\_on/](https://www.reddit.com/r/pussypassdenied/comments/ai1tgi/girl_slaps_boy_and_gets_payback_found_on/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 16:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He then said 

 I'm of Italian decent you ignorant dipshit 

Which not only is rude for no reason, also proves he isn't 100% Italian like he claimed to be. He also spelled descent wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 16:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you call Donald Trump "our President" you must be American since Trump isn't Italy's president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> America is the only country that recycles plastic! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 15:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 15:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also most pizza in Italy is already considered "cheap" in some places in south Italy you can find pizza for around 5 or 6 euro, sometimes including a drink too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 15:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/GoodScumBagBrian commenterd this

 I post at t\_d all the time. I support our President and am a lifelong conservative 

He's clearly bullshitting about being italian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 01:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I'm not mistaken showering that often isn't good for the body </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-16 00:50:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate to this. I love debating about politics or anything really and seeing the other person's view point and other ways of thinking. Unfortunately I've lost quite a few friendships cause people think I'm always looking for an argument and am being annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 07:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing there's dead people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 07:43:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Italy: exists
UNESCO: it's free real estate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 22:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Carthago delenda est! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Stinky butt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 18:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 14:52:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How long have you been learning Italian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 14:48:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually words that end with "a" are feminine (sedia = chair) and "o" are masculine (tavolo = table) and when words end with "i" means it's masculine plural (tavoli = tables) and "e" is feminine plural (sedie = chairs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 14:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well no, formaggio is the singular for cheese in italian while formaggi is plural, so formaggi is the correct word here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 13:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry to correct you but it's quattro formaggi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 11:54:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> H-how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 14:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 14:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But the Armenian flag is there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 22:13:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A dick without skin on it looks like a huge flaming hot cheeto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 20:50:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the sound of the skin ripping off my dick after I pull too hard on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 14:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 14:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh hey that's me! I'm glad you enjoyed our trip and I can't wait to see you again 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-19 22:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone said that the game lasted 15:11 and vayne had more than 100 farm so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 18:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/cursedcomments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 10:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The art of the deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 01:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello, I'll also be starting the IB next year and have exams after Easter (I'm assuming you're also doing IGCSE exams) so we can chat on discord if you'd like to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Black people can't be racist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 17:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's a New Zealand? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 23:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> GAMERS are being MISTREATED time to RISE UP </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 17:20:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Food critic Itay </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 17:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thanks discord, very cool </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 16:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 23:13:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cheap pandoros are much better than cheap panetonnes but expensive pandoro is worse than expensive panettone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 11:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He did his research </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reply to Suzanne Moore saying she'd rather prioritise crimes of misogyny over burglary. Fatality </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 11:27:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-07 21:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Such a cute boy! :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found on a Sunflower violin cover </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 23:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 23:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mashed potato is a sauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> cursed_opinion </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 18:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 18:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/cursedcomments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 20:44:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well he has an anime profile pic so you never know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> He's not like the other "dumbass dudes" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 20:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 10:15:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last year I wanted to try out one of these sites so I deposited the minimum amount you could. From there I managed to get to around $25\~ starting from $1. Then I went all in to get an AK skin and lost all my money. Never bothered again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 10:10:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't know if this counts but I put spicy maple syrup on waffles and fried chicken last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 09:30:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It might be hard to prove that you put a warning on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 09:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> School uniform </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 09:23:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/ComedyCemetery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 09:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful eyes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 08:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Couldn't you call the airport / police and say there's a bomb or danger on that flight and ruin her trip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 07:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So? What does u/CorrupetMeth do thats so significant? Why does it matter if someone kills it? Not like were losing anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Mitty is on the roof :o </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 21:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 19:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 13:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those can't be removed

Then in the same sentence 

when you finally decide to remove them

Also I haven't found any news articles or sources that say that you could die when getting tattoo removals. Many people do not regret their tattoos and like them, now I don't particularly like OP's idea for tattoo but if he likes it then I don't see anything wrong with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 23:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly I don't really see any way people could stop it happening seeing how it's so easy to have access to these things. Personally I've never smoked or drank anything but everyone around me seems to be doing that. Here teenage (16+) drinking isn't super looked down upon even though imo it's really bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 23:16:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  [https://www.amazon.it/Sigaretta-elettronica-Cigarette-serbatoio-vaporizzatore/dp/B07GZP217M/ref=sr\_1\_3?\_\_mk\_it\_IT=%C3%85M%C3%85%C5%BD%C3%95%C3%91 keywords=vape qid=1554153318 s=gateway sr=8-3](https://www.amazon.it/Sigaretta-elettronica-Cigarette-serbatoio-vaporizzatore/dp/B07GZP217M/ref=sr_1_3?__mk_it_IT=%C3%85M%C3%85%C5%BD%C3%95%C3%91 keywords=vape qid=1554153318 s=gateway sr=8-3)  Italian amazon link for a vape. Most of my classmates have fake IDs too or just photoshop their ID birthdate so they're old enough if they need to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This isn't how this works... This isn't how any of this works </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 23:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 22:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of my classmates (I'm 16) buy vapes and liquid from amazon or other online stores that don't ask for verification  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 22:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They can't just let it grow out forever  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 22:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 22:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 22:09:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/ComedyCemetery you can't force a meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 22:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the fuck happened to this keyboard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 21:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Young Thug STS or Relationship maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 21:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hills are clearly part of the governments plan to make people think the earth is a sphere! 

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flat earther believes that the "Wall Of Ice" brainwipes you... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 20:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hermes is in the deep fryer :o </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 17:40:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 17:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much! I am actually subbed to this but just forgot the name. Solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [TOMT][SUBREDDIT] A subreddit where I can post a picture of a cat in a box. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 15:40:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember there being a subreddit called cat trap or something similar which was made for pictures of cats in boxes. I can't find the subreddit anymore or i just forgot the name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 11:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or the spelling of babies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Irrefutable proof that the earth is flat according to this guy, also a piece of ice wipes your memory when you see it! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 11:24:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 11:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He seems to be really into flat earth subreddits and has been saying that reddit blocks free speech. I also would like to believe he's a troll but you never know with flat earthers anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Those darn globalists killing our babies! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 11:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 08:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well in Finland breaking the law is illegal so no one can commit crimes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 21:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably to switch the outlets on/off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 21:44:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buffalo Wild Wings

I'm not from the US and we don't have that in my country, I've seen buffaloes before in pictures but for some reason I just never realised that buffalo wings weren't actual wings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 21:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolute unit of a daisy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 21:41:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For basically my whole life (I'm only 16 but ok) I've, for some reason, always thought that buffalo wings came from the wings of buffaloes but then I realised they don't have wings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 21:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last night I dreamed that Gandalf put a bounty on me and the bounty hunter from the TV show frontier showed up to kill me but I befriended him by offering him a deviled egg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 21:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/titlegore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Epic joke xd </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 19:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oh gosh </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 18:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 17:17:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No you're right, I meant to say 6 million Jews and I was wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 16:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly, according to the US holocaust museum, around 6 million Jews died, then 312,000 Serb civilians, up to 250,000 People with disabilities living in institutions, 220,000 Roma , 1900 Jehovah witnesses and hundreds possibly thousands homosexuals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 15:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus Christ 17 million in the Holocaust? Where did you get that figure from? Most sources agree at around 6 million but the precise amount hasn't been found, but 17 is way too high  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 14:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well uhh egypt is in Africa  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 12:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Op said that he is in the middle East as well  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My girlfriend's grandmother has this shirt cause she likes horse riding, so that apparently makes her different and special </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 19:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 01:16:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry! Didn't know this is a repost and will delete the post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 00:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cOnTrOl 


/S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 21:42:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% agree, their children will have pretty much no choice other than to believe what their parents teach them and will believe that the earth is flat too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hermes is a sleepy girl </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 19:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 17:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly I feel like they don't even realise their own stupidity to the point where they literally think the earth is flat and believe their own lies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 14:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Prego! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So apparently NASA isn't a competent organisation and the cold war was faked!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 12:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 19:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's totally fine to act differently due to such a huge hormonal change, but I dislike when people do not own up to their own actions. Certain girls in my class use periods as an excuse to act bitchy and judgemental and generally not nice and that's the kind of people I don't like. What I was trying to say is that I wouldn't agree with women or men using hormones as an excuse to their shitty behaviour

 #x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-18 13:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you don't see men blaming the fact that they have more testosterone for being more aggressive. I agree with the fact that it's just something you can't control and it sucks, but you can't just blame it for your actions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 12:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "This is false! For fucks sake do your research people. She was convicted of drug and prostitution(pimping) charges. She was released almost immediately on the larceny charges." Quoting u/spark0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 19:37:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some places in London, like in Chelsea, charge more than 50 pound for men's haircuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 15:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure the girlfriend is the person that made the post but I'm not 100% sure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ILPT request: how can I get every monthly edition of the Economist for free? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 13:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm quite broke but I'd like to read the economist every month but the price is quite high. Is there a way to get it for free? Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 20:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rabbit is great for youtube and netflix, if you need any show reccomendations about what to watch feel free to ask! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 19:55:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I'm one day late but you can try Chrome extensions like rabb.it or netflix party to watch stuff together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Me and my fiancee (just proposed) are both HUGE Nintendo nerds, and after coming back from our trip in Japan, our bags were filled to the brim with these goodies!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-16 20:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 10:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks OP I'd like Zelda botw if possible!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-11 12:52:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Charles II could barely speak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-11 10:50:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man you're really kind!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Some guy was talking trash to my duo queue partner so I had to do it to ho, </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-05 19:55:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-30 11:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But take Walmart for example, they have hundreds of stores across most states, each state of even city in the US can have different taxes, so they just print the basic price without the added tax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-25 21:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He doesn't eat or drink 

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-25 21:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm 16 so of course I'm no expert on this but 150k sounds a bit too little to retire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-25 18:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 150k invested nicely is an extra 6k a year, I don't think you'd be able to do that much with it, let alone live off it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 00:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We get to see each other pretty much every month but we do video call every day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-18 00:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For sure. We talked about it and she apologised and said she didn't really think in the moment and made a mistake. Imo the fact that she can acknowledge her own mistake and own up to it is very important. Now we've set some ground rules and things like these won't ever happen again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 23:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you gatekeeping relationships? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 23:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I'm not too sure as we live in different countries and so we don't go to school together. I'll ask her next time we speak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 23:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The topic came up cause she was doing a survey on sexuality for her class and since her grandma is a lesbian, she was wandering if there was anyone else that she knew what was not straight

 The topic came up cause she was doing a survey on sexuality for her  class and since her grandma is a lesbian, she was wandering if there was  anyone else that she knew what was not straight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 23:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have told her that I am not comfortable with anyone knowing. The topic came up cause she was doing a survey on sexuality for her class and since her grandma is a lesbian, she was wandering if there was anyone else that she knew what was not straight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 22:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot man! We've been together for almost 4 months now and it's going great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 22:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I know she didn't do it to hurt me or offend me, we love each other very much. I agree on respecting the comfort zone part and we've talked about it and she said she won't share anything without asking me first (and I'll do the same) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AITA for getting upset at my girlfriend told her family I'm bi? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 22:36:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 1 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 23:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-31 21:28:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now he gets to skip the queue at Disney world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-25 00:24:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love to gift this game to my girlfriend so we  can play it together. I've played 500+ hours of it and can't wait to play it with her if I win the giveaway.
Merry Christmas Reddit from Italy!

Her steam ID:
https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198271624833 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 19:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've literally been here for two hours telling these people how much of losers they are for liking overwatch. You're a really bad attempt at a troll  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My friend back at it again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-15 22:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My friend trying to spell away </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-11 13:44:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 15:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah definitely, I'm 16 and she's 17, as far as I know she isn't interested in me and I'm already in a relationship so in my mind there was no reason for her to send me that picture  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 15:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks diddledbydad, I thought the same but I just feel bad that I stopped talking without any reason why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 15:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well her feet looked normal but I got woken up by the notification and first thing I see are two feet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AITA for ghosting a girl after she sent me pictures of her feet? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 15:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I started talking to this girl from Reddit and after a few weeks of talking on and off on discord (not voice chat) she sent me pictures of her feet at 1 or 2 am. After that I told her that I didn't really appreciate those pictures and I didn't write anything to her after that. She sent me a message a while back saying hello but I never answered. AITA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Necklace I found on Etsy. Missing a lot more than just New Zealand </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-01 18:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-30 09:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Racketeering conspiracy and firearms offenses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 22:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> character - fran, username - hasayo, profile https://osu.ppy.sh/users/7374449 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-24 16:55:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/foundthemobileuser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-24 16:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My thoughts are completely in English, except sometimes they're in Italian but never had any in French  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-24 16:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that big accounts have notifications off, but as usually celebrity accounts aren't managed by the celebrity themselves, the person managing it would probably continuously check other celebrity accounts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-24 16:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also speak 3 languages (Italian, English and French) with Italian being my mother tongue, but i speak in English cause that's the language I'm best at </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-16 15:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't call someone making a silly, inappropriate joke creepy, it's definitely inappropriate and not everyone might like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-14 08:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, just a fancy name for toilet in Italian  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3 in a row </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-11 16:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 19:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Rock? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 18:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry who are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 16/M from Italy looking for some long term friends! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 18:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been on this subreddit for a long time but never made a most, so here it is

My interests are:

Gaming, watching TV and movies (mostly netflix), watching anime and eating food. 

I have social anxiety and depression which makes it really hard for me to make friends irl. I'd love to make long-term friends that I can trust and talk to regularly to distract me from my day-to-day life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 19:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing it's a throwaway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 09:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In her last post she claimed she was 18 and in this post she's 17 hmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 19:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, not for children, they are usually enthusiasts of a certain animal with human characteristics. Google it because it's hard to explain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 17:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tony Hawk killer? Nah you're gonna be killing EA and Ubisoft with those skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-16 17:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who dress up as animals  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 18:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello, we can talk! I can PM you my discord if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 18:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/excgarated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 19:12:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I'm sending a PM right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 17:02:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sent you a message! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-09 17:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basically it's kind of a fetish / kink / thing people do where you voice chat with someone and then fall alseep together still on the call </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 17:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey i PM'd you but you never added me :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 20:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sent you a request!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 20:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey we can talk, do you have a discord or twitter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 20:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sent you a message on here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-07 18:17:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sent you a message!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 12:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I also was confused by what he meant when he said sweet calzone. It's literally just a pizza folded in half  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 08:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I'm only 16 and I've lived abroad for 6 years, so I might not be as knowledgeable food wise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 08:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm originally from Milan but my father is from Bari  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 08:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Calzone is an oven baked pizza that originated in italy, don't really know what a stromboli as it's not Italian and I've never seen one before today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-04 08:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Italian here, calzone does mean pants but it's a very old term and not really used by people as much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm pretty sure that's not Milan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-29 22:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-27 20:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Toight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 12:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 08:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you have access to making a Reddit post but not googling the patch notes? Hmmm  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-19 13:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude you asked, why should he be the one to read the patch notes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Throwing steak at napoleon is the best aesthetic </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 23:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-14 16:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's meant to be capocollo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nagazaki and Hierosyma </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 14:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 23:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's what I thought but they left all of Europe though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 21:37:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/MapsWithoutCorsica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 21:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/MapsWithoutTaiwan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 21:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oof brother, you can still do some </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 20:58:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Already did that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 20:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/mapswithoutsicily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 20:06:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/mapswithoutmadagascar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 19:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/mapswithoutJapan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 19:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/mapswithoutsrilanka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 19:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/MapsWithoutIndonesia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This map is so wrong on so many different levels. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-01 19:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-26 03:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro you have to link the video for us to check it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-26 02:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No but free karma for OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 14:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you have an internship at NASA you should know who Homer Hickman is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 05:13:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's not a random dude though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 01:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The kid is holding his hand near the metal bar so that the old lady doesn't hit her head against it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 00:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nani </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-23 00:43:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are welcome friendo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 16:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There can only be one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 15:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting, is there a pp crab for mouse players? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 15:04:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that their natural habitat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 14:59:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a meme that started from a call of duty game, where you had to press F to pay respects to a dead soldier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 14:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In or around the sea, they're often found on rocks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-19 22:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He joined Reddit today  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-16 13:56:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough, it's not a game for everyone, imo I like osu streams but I understand why it's not for everyone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-16 06:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's wrong with OSU? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 00:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ironic this is that I'm actually dyslexic. Also I'm not shitting on you for a typo, everyone makes those, but for your lying about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 00:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone's unnecessarily mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 21:32:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First you said it was autocorrect and now you said you typed it wrong, so which is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 20:48:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You clearly cared enough to lie about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 05:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ligma balls lmao gottem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 05:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I'm in the US currently, if you'd like to talk I can PM you or you can PM me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 21:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I'd like to get to know you and we can also duo on fortnite (not that i'm any good at it), you can PM me so we can share discord profiles :). Have a great day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-02 10:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take a seat right there sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 23:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 19:03:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I struggle a lot with social anxiety so that would be very hard, but even if I tried I live far away from any big city so there aren't a lot of things I can volunteer at. I also don't like Church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 18:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done and done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 18:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wish I could find other places to meet friends as I've none now, hopefully the next people I chat to on here are less of pedophiles. I'm not on there to meet a partner, just to make friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 18:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been on the "Make a friend chat" and so many people were asking if i was a female and wanting to see pics of me although I am under 18 (and a male) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 17:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I blocked and reported him to kik and I am trying to get in contact with the Police in his country. He sent a picture of his face as well so hopefully they'll be able to identify who he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 17:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, this guy was being weird and asking me if I was ok with me sending pictures of myself and then him sending pictures back. I was on Kik to meet some new friends but I guess not everyone is like that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First day on Kik, so this is what it's like eh </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-01 16:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 21:05:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot for the replies everyone, hopefully I'll visit in a couple of years as next year I'm visiting Korea  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 21:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Italy is much better in the eyes of a tourist than a citizen. The politicians are shit and people are usually acceptant of lgbt or minorities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 19:13:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately I am currently living in Milan, Italy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 17:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot, considering also moving there when I'm older but it definitely looks worth a visit imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 16:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This might be completely off topic, but how is Toronto, I'm considering visiting it and other cities in Canada. Is it visit worthy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 00:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's about the Sugandese people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-27 00:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They will be pushing  the pregnant person down the stairs to kill the fetus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Instagram is a gold mine for wooooshes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 19:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-21 14:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That friend's name? None other than Albert Einstein </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 02:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oof deleting that now sorry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 01:25:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uh I sure hope it does  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 00:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem man. Thanks a lot for the cake day wishes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 00:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The scope was added in post production, he doesn't not actually have any scope on the gun. This is very common among paintball/ Airsoft YouTubers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 14:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That epic moment when someone steals your shoes so you basically murder him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 14:06:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure they've been in porn for quite some time now, just depends on what kind you watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-02 19:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry to hear that man  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Request][Steam] Black Desert Online ($4.99) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-28 19:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here is my steam [profile](https://steamcommunity.com/id/boboboboboboobobob/)

I am currently posting this again as my other post was deemed to short, so here's my effort to write a bit more.

I'd like to request the game called Black Desert Online. It is a popular MMORPG that has gone one sale as the steam summer sales began. The game's description is as follows:  Black Desert Online is a sandbox, living-world MMORPG. Experience fast-paced, action-packed combat, hunt monsters and huge bosses, fight with friends in a guild to siege nodes and conquer castles, train your life skills such as fishing, trading, crafting, cooking, and much more! 

I'd love this game as I've tried it once at my friends house and loved it, for the past weeks I've been researching a bit more about it and how the game works and I am currently very into the premise of it. Personally the fishing and conquering castles is the most fun part for me as it differentiates it from the other MMORPG I've tried. I've wanted to try and get into MMORPG's but never had the time to (school and weekly therapy sessions), so now that I'm soon on summer break I hope to have the time to get into this game and enjoy it! This game currently has mixed reviews but having it tried it once, I can say that I positively say that I enjoy this game and will play it until I'm somewhat of a decent player.

I know I will be able to run the game as my PC specs are good. If anyone else has this game already then you are welcome to add me and maybe we can even play together sometime!  
Thanks to anyone that would even consider giving me this game, you are a very generous person and I seriously thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Request][Steam] Black Desert Online ($4.99) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-28 18:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-22 15:26:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you can get a steam refund as it's not on sale buy I am not so sure. Try and check to see if steam will refund part of the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-19 16:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bad, now I look dumb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-19 16:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention that doesn't look like the flag of Nigeria  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Apparently my phone has been charging for more than 48 years </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-10 21:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-06 07:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my bad, didn't realise  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-06 07:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not 100% crit chance, I just like the burst and it helps me kill the enemy adc faster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 18:55:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had my fair share of success with that build and haven't lost a single game with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 09:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer ER into stormrazors, pd, IE and then rfc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-04 11:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Er first is better imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-31 09:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because you played a good game with him doesn't mean he's OP. Wait until the pros decide  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-22 19:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's fair, it's still in testing and beta so I'm sure they'll improve it before it gets fully released  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-22 19:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never lagged on my PC, may be a software/ hardware problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I actually like the new Reddit redesign. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-22 19:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel as if it's much cleaner and modern looking. I like that the pictures automatically expand. I much prefer browsing now on the redesign rather than on the old design  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 01:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll get back to you in 3-4 days with an answer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 22:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm ok with hanging out with you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 16:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-28 16:41:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks satire to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 22:37:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to really cringe, check the boogiedown hashtag on twitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 21:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Fortnite "boogie down" competition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-26 17:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's not wrong, is he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> u/subject9452's circle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-04 19:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-08 17:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't know if this is possible but I'd give it to the Bill and Melinda Gates foundation, they've been doing a lot of good in the world and they seem to know what they're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 16:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as a company pays the right amount Facebook will have pretty much any advertisement  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-21 00:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the heck is happening in this thumbnail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 16:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Living the good life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 01:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or a relatively healthy life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Health is subjective and being obese should be CELEBRATED </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 01:04:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 01:02:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 01:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This whole thing is going way over your head  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 00:59:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never said you were </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 00:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really aren't understanding  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 00:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's gay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 00:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nail biting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 00:47:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing it's a scam, I wouldn't accept anything unless it's from a trusted person  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fucking Brutal  </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-03 00:43:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-29 13:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Via BlackBerry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 20:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stop comment these things on your own posts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-27 20:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are you commenting that on your own post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-27 18:33:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tree house  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-25 14:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  https://primitivetechnology.wordpress.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found this on "learn something" page on twitter </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-09 14:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-06 21:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> League of Legends  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-06 21:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Babysitting and dog sitting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Saddest/ most tearjerking animes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-02 16:31:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never cried watching any movie so please suggest the saddest/ tearjerking animes, possibly with a good story and likeable characters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-01 20:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally I had my laptop built from a German website, but I know that alienwares are too expensive, try looking at MSI's or Dells </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-01 02:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just write a comment that goes against Riot ToS on the official league of legends subreddit, that's a smart move  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-31 18:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if you die?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-31 11:19:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on what kind of videos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-27 09:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's a lie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 01:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think rating your own channel a 10/10 is a little biased </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-01 19:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I see is a guy with low self esteem trying to show off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-17 01:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too lazy to press one button? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-17 01:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do think that the hate for this mod is because it makes certain countries overpowered (Germany).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-17 01:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At this point, when the picture looks so crappy there is no point in even trying and bothering to upload  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-17 01:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's more than halfway through 2017 and people still don't know how to take screenshots  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-13 11:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still have it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-13 11:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He isn't wrong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-13 11:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ears getting blocked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-13 11:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found French really easy but out teacher was an ass. I really enjoyed business but I didn't really understand it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-13 11:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just started reading Ready Player One as I finally found it after I got it from a lootcrate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-13 11:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really bad headaches from my brain damage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-13 11:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beware of cute puppy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-29 14:20:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be there or be square </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-23 21:23:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 23:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's definitely an *interesting* way to do it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 23:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guy jumping off a building  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 23:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm still too young but, I have brain damage, meaning that my hands constantly shake, meaning I can not become a surgeon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-09 23:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucky you! My doggo hates being anywhere near water, he despises the water and will never go inside it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 20:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had a Dell laptop that was very bad and the customer service was incompetent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 18:54:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks but I said that I don't want a Dell laptop  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 18:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That doesn't justify shit posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Want to buy a new laptop for school and gaming. Budget of 1200 (Italy). Maximum 15" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 15:16:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> * **Total budget and country of purchase:** 
1200 in Italy

* **Do you prefer a 2 in 1 form factor, good battery life or best specifications for the money? Pick or include any that apply.** 
Would like decent battery but good specs for the money

* **How important is weight and thinness to you?**
Not too important, just I don't want a super thick laptop

* **Which OS do you require? Windows, Mac, Chrome OS, Linux.**
Windows

* **Do you have a preferred screen size? If indifferent, put N/A.** 
Maximum 15"

* **Are you doing any CAD/video editing/photo editing/gaming? List which programs/games you desire to run.** 
Probably will be using Photoshop and maybe premiere, would like to run League of Legends at 60fps on at least medium/high

* **If you're gaming, do you have certain games you want to play? At what settings and FPS do you want?** 
League of Legends medium/high at 60fps, CSGO medium/high at 60fps and The Sims 3 high at 60fps

* **Any specific requirements such as good keyboard, reliable build quality, touch-screen, finger-print reader, optical drive or good input devices (keyboard/touchpad)?** 
Would like for the computer to last a few years without breaking and would like for it to be silent when using word/ browsing on the internet.

* **Leave any finishing thoughts here that you may feel are necessary and beneficial to the discussion.**
Would prefer if it had good ram and isn't a dell laptop
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 13:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could have cropped the picture  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-06-22 19:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> England is my city </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you mean letter not alphabet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:42:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for those circles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:56:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bayonetta  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:26:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do we know this is your post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This pray for Stockholm sign </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lazy town mod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How many times will this be reposted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How many times will this be reposted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't get stunned if you are already dead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm guessing because the thumbnail has the same text as the title  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank for helping me as I'm currently through my first playthrough of the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a noob with only 26 hours I didn't know you could have more than 3 rivals  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can do that by 10AD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so I'm not through only one who read it like that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What mod is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the reply, I'll check it out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Europa Universalis 4 mod help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:15:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only started playing EU4 (50hrs), and I'm looking for a good map graphics mod. Can anyone reccomend any good ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-01 12:55:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It happens to me too on pc I just close the page and it's actually uploaded  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-31 12:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1920x1080 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-30 12:14:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes it is possible but be careful when going up or down with the helicopter as the car might hit you and blow up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-27 12:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you read like that? Because if you read the "correct" way you'll understand it just fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did jew wear it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> New setup? Loving the 15 fps  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I salute you with my 100 bytes per second download speed and 500+ ping online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-25 13:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know the stairs that move  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-23 11:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-08 12:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ritual Armor of Boethiah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After 30 mins of research I found out its not the best armor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks but does it have the highest armor rating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Immersive armors help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone of you guys know what is the best light armor in immersive armors? Thanks in advance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:51:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As the guy who also watches you, going to a doctor might be a good idea since I'm pretty sure it's not meant to look like that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:44:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> White privileged male scum piece of misogynistic trash  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just whip it out, don't need to be discrete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That might be because the earth is flat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As the guy who watches through your Web cam, you seriously don't have to do it so often  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which computer is the best singer

A dell  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice try KGB, nice try  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> STOP FINISHING ALL OVER ME  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What else do you search for that starts with a "p" in Google? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just call me the doctor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:11:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And egg probably  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> During his presidency the US national debt doubled  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Life. Or so they say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:08:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THERE HE IS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FeelsBadMan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Motherlode  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are your actual thought on Harambe? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But can you though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:16:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to (and still do) play tennis everyday for a few hours. I then went to participate in tournaments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Old granny midget bdsm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:13:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We waited for 6 months to get into Gordon Ramsay restaurant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My skyrim was bugged out and when I created a new savefile the carriage started flying everywhere and all the guards were dying for the fall  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that the baconian theory which states that Shakespeare didn't write any of his works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remember to make all the eye contact and then glaze him like a doughnut  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:02:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try and post this on r/earthporn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I'm on a highway to hell" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uncle Jeremy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:52:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I see is a blank paper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whiplashthesnake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-14 12:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All aboard the train to hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-12 12:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The lightsaber mod exists on pc and is called magica sabres I think  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:49:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing really strange about that, here in Italy they are mostly crown sealed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He used the English to dolan translator probably  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Green </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Steal their computer mouse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *insert born to feel meme here* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *insert sad pepe picture here* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I be head memer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as they don't reproduce by holding hands they'll be fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And if I do what are the chances that they will be uncles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Made me laugh there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This girl in my ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The letter 0 is also 0 when turned upside down  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd go with Bill he's been pretty douchy lately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Username checks out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Black, black and more black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:49:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I have sex when pregnant will my baby become pregnant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:47:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice try FBI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:46:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Stay the hell out of MY way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:45:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once had to call the restaurant to order the food because none of the waiters could see my table as the restaurant was full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oreos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an Italian I have to say no chocolate 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vsauce, Primitive technology, Joerg Sprave and Crazy Russian Hacker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The first ring doesn't have a hole </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 23:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm also Italian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Incest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 11:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy to help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 11:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is still a bit burnt and without any mozzarella  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:51:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nerdcubed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:49:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See you in hell  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you mean the elder scrolls?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lawyer is standing in a long line at the box office. Suddenly, he feels a pair of hands kneading his shoulders, back, and neck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Italian in me just died a little </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:42:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Titanic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y'know Nathan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oreos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Though it was going to be a blatant repost but was surprised </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was younger I threw a rock at my friends back because he stole my gameboy while I was playing pokemon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:32:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am no expert but I'm pretty sure it intentional 

Edit: I just checked on my phone and yes it is a feature  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-30 11:23:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit: I had no idea that this was already posted on  here, my friend sent me this pic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but how are you going to post to reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then they'd get bored after my daily fap n6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-10-29 21:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where I left my God damm keys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Near Lake Como, Italy 4032x3024 [OC] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-29 17:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:22:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You forgot nutella pasta mafia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-15 14:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah didn't know that thanks very much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-15 13:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grammar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-15 13:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's because you're on ps4 and you can't compare it to PC  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-15 13:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think WoW is not worth the money since it costs 15 every month  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-15 13:27:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And he is also at work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-13 08:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't the f12 button for steam screenshots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-11 22:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cracked game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Noob here that needs help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-10 00:04:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was wondering how often should I go to war vs other people? Any advice is much appreciated. Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I wasn't grammar nazing him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But don't downvote me for no reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You try them on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i dont know let me check </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My first dacia playthrough (extended timeline) managed to capture rome </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-07 17:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should we go for a pink or blue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-04 01:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do know 1 thing, you'll need a flamethrower or a nuke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 23:52:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice game, only thing is that it's hard to manage money  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 18:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Played it for about 2 hours now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 18:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 15:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit: I don't know what I did but it's now working, thanks everybody for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 14:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So did that and it said everything was ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 14:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok how do you do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 14:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't find the option 
http://imgur.com/a/UURA0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help I just downloaded EU4 and I can't select any nations and the whole map is grayedout. Currently only running the Women in History mod. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 13:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A flair is a short word/s that describe your post, and each subreddit has their own flair. Furthermore if you are on mobile you can't add a flair but on PC you can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ehm if you are born in most countries you would read this normally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-28 12:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you know if a subreddit is owned by a black or white or whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-28 12:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Butt hurt much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-26 14:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll ask my grandpa if he knows what this is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can anyone identify this? It's from Italy FYI </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-26 13:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-26 09:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So the things on the right are fried olives, then some cooked veggies and a potato and veggie cake thing. To finish it off there is some tiramisu and some bread and butter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Surprisingly good food on an airplane </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:14:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-25 14:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A settlement need your help I'll mark it on your map </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So he can't buy bicycle cards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:10:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The downvote are coming  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:08:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I could send you some I'd do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3edgy5me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha I have at least 90 potions and 50 super ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *dough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only stairs m8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-23 10:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually this is a repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well maybe it's exaggerated that he destroys everything but better safe than sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try posting this at /cityporn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The witcher serie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of the Tom Clancy books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Triggered feminazis incoming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:31:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What did you expect, they just write a bunch of numbers in the command prompted and then he magically has money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:30:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like who? (Serious question, I haven't watched any matches) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:12:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha my friend is the great grand daughter of the King haile selassie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:53:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try looking for his name on the player search but otherwise I don't know 

P.S don't downvote my comment just because you don't agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get in the van </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ehm lizards in an auction lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:40:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Title doesn't make sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> M8 the house I used to live in was 10000 a month so with that you can't really afford some houses in big cities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At the end of a game click on the report icon next to someone's name on the top right corner and select the appropriate box, in your case I think it's "unsportsmanlike behaviour". You'll tick that box and then write a brief description and then BOOM you just reported him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The title doesn't really make sense since Pokemon go is a game that's already out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes it was just a joke dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never saw a goldfish in the wild tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should a wall get an assist if a hero hides behind it and then gets a kill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's just a standard Italian  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought you only ate kangaroos and crocodiles M8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No but the small roads and buses remind me of it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> London, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 13:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 10:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like to be a mod on this lovely subreddit, I've spent a lot of hours playing HOI4 and although I was never a mod on Reddit I was of another site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-22 10:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah especially when you attack Saudi Arabia and it decides to join the Comintern  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rrrrrrepost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you make the map? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-21 12:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why u do this 2 my eyes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-21 02:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah ok i thought of something else  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's so funny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-20 22:29:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *evil laugh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-20 12:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you blind, it looks much more like a stegosaurus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-20 12:38:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Download assets then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-19 17:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Augustus ceaser was 4.6 trilliion
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-19 17:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw that his net worth was 4.6 trillion
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-19 13:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better than my shit hole of a town </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-19 03:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, doesn't exist although there is a spawn cheat but you need to be a developer to use it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-19 03:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THANK YOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-19 03:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ?Why is this a question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-18 13:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was not my idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-18 13:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When did I say sexual abuse? Never. I said sexual assault </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But OP never said anything about Rio 2016, it was just you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:29:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I don't think that it's sexual assault as she didn't assault her or anything BUT it's not normal for your parents to watch you masturbate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-17 19:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:25:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bush or plant after me please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-16 12:09:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But OP never said that they were the same creature, he sated he looks like an ancestor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-16 03:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct me if I'm wrong but don't they have tentacles and that creature also has them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-15 00:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I live in the centre of London so there is nothing to explore, it's literally the same in a few km radius </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Living in London is as great as you'd think </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-14 23:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-14 13:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucky you my first planet was all rocks and no plant, and I couldn't leave it because it didn't have zinc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never watched it, maybe I can watch it online or somethings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Not mine] This looks like a praying mantis and a crab. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-13 18:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:13:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks dude I'll see what I can do
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:33:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well anyone would be good since I'm silver 5 and I've lost all my matches recently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude how do you make maps like this one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-12 22:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Form italy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn you got more upvotes that the post itself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or is it just Fanta sea  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A mix of Macedonian's flag with a Kiwi in the middle [Made with FlagMaker 1.7] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:20:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a joke dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 18:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 17:46:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I said blue-green because I'm not good with colours and how do you add flairs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well the upvotes on his comment disagree with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nepal of course  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does that DLC add? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two things: how did you get that blue-green"diplomat" next to your name and second: thanks for understanding  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah sorry my bad, I've only just started my first campaign so I didn't knoe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's the El Dorado DLC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing in the middle doesn't fit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about if you want to play as Luxembourg or Paraguay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 12:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THANK YOU. First of all its fat and second of all its unhealthy for him to be that fat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 12:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When is their mixtape coming out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or we didn't have a garden, or hoses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:49:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP watch the GradeAUnderA video on the racist test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct me if I'm wrong but isn't the 19th century the 1800? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially when you start with 1-2 military factories  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-09 00:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try and improve it by adding a higher quality sickle and hammer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:51:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't get the debug mode to work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-08-02 22:46:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boosted animal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-30 01:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well let's say she becomes a (naked) 80 year old woman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I also hate people wasting money on random shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 23:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know what happens next in the show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 23:50:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you're bad with money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 23:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure that is a great idea and could you please tell me your YouTube channel name please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BUT you can switch off many visual effects from the options and the day-night cycle from in game to reduce lag
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1) it was a joke 2) you'll never be able to play at 60 or even 30 fps  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:15:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stop playing on mac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 11:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cute doggy pt2 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 00:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 00:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much captain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-29 00:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah thanks so much dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you please tell me what are core states? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [BA, Italy] Found this beautiful bug what is it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It will run really low since my Gtx 980ti can't handle it at max graphics at 60 fps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cute doggy chillin </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-28 11:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm just a beginner at HOI4 so I sent all my troops away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I played a game in which Denmark managed to fight off the Germans and take a HUGE chunk from them

P.S I was playing as the UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-27 11:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Step 4. Profit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I luckily got one today too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahah thanks for the encouragement bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So jealous since my strongest Pokemon is 200 CP and I'm not good enough to to capture anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 14:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy hunting from italyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 13:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Need one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 12:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you get the writing next to your name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 11:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude try and go in airplane mode before opening the app then when the red thingy appears from the top, switch off the airplane mode, worked for me and many other people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 11:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 11:16:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks dude  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 01:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 00:53:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP as an Italian I have no clue what this is, it looks raw, please explain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 00:50:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He said he hatched the lapras, but he never said that exact one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-25 00:16:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you are calling him a liar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He never said that he didn't max it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My weedle is stronger than that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:32:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a huge vagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahah I feel bad for you, I found those Pokemon in the south of Italy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks and I believe I'm a level 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know that feeling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My 6 strongest Pokemon after a week of playing! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> please do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The outside world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:07:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for how long did you cook the pasta? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it has anything to do with your specs, its your keyboard that might be damaged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe try the Total War Series (Total War Rome, Shogun etc...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>