<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9999</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 03:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the most uneducated question ever but...

Growing up my (conservative af) parents always spoke against Muslims, some of the things they would mention were "the quaran teaches muslims to kill nonbelievers" and other similar things is that true? Is it one of those things how the bible technically says dont eat kinds of sea food and where certain clothes and stuff but isnt practiced any longer? Are my parents just dumb (I mean they are anyways but...)?

I've always wanted to ask this but didnt want to offend someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 22:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why dont you keep your baby in your bedroom and share that room at first as it will be easier to have the baby close anyways. Then once the adoption is processed they could share rooms. Its such a simple solution that I feel like you have an entirely different reason for thinking this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 05:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So would you rather the government continued to tax women more than men and continue that inequality or...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 05:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you have too many geeky knick knack things around the house maybe get some stuff for his car? I got my husband spiderman car coasters for his birthday just a bit ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 05:51:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you think this is kid friendly? Considering going but don't want to leave my baby for 2 nights in one weekend and I already have plans for one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 01:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The berry bursts into a ton of weird little pod things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Growing on the wall outside, what is this? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 01:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 22:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow that was fast, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 22:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would probably give this to my sister but my favorite accessory would have to be my knock around sunglasses. Between my husband and I we probably have like 60, currently I am wearing the eclipse pair which is entirely black. I always forget to take them off when I get to the office and end up walking around all day with them on top of my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can anyone please remove my husbands hand? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 22:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 18:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially with the beard! It would look great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 05:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of monsters and men - little talks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 05:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The civil wars - falling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 00:28:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make sure your first picture is your best one of you alone (unless you're with a dog). Dont have more than one group photo and make sure the photo isnt you looking like youre in a relationship with anyone else in the picture. If you have any pictures with filters, make sure the first picture does not have a filter. Try and include a picture with you all dolled up. Try and include a picture of you doing something you enjoy or with a pet or something like that. 
While jokes are kinda of a risk, make sure you have something in your profile that would be easy to respond to in a message, it can be a joke, favorite movie book, etc. Something that someone messaging you could play off of- if its easier for them to think of a response then they're more likely to message you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 19:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say this On Writing helped me improve my writing immensely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 19:43:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While you shouldn't let this chick get to you for sure and stick to being yourself, one thing I've found helps me shape social interactions is quite simple. Ask questions! I bet she loves talking about herself and her life. Plus it will make her feel like you care about this and her well being. It just shows in general that you're considerate to others and interested. Every Monday ask how her weekend was! And then if you can think of something you did over the weekend you can share that too. Then ask plenty of follow up questions too, slowly this will build up to conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 19 year old affecting rental applications? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 06:27:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasnt sure a good title for this.

Basically, I'm moving apartments in a couple months here. It will be me (22) my husband (24) and our newborn daughter. Along with that we are having my younger sister (19) move in as well. She is still in high school and doesnt work or have any credit history. She has a disability that prevents her from being able to work and she hasn't graduated high school anyways. (In exchange for living with us she will be taking care of our daughter while we are at work. It will be a safer living arrangement for her as well so all works out.)

The issue is that since she is over 18 apartment buildings want her on the applications as well. I understand why but I'm worried having her on the applications will affect our ability to be accepted. Our credit scores are average and credit history is on the lower side but all of our payments are on time and we dont have anything bad to be reported. Our previous landlords will be able to vouche for us as well if needed about our on time payments and such. So we're already a little iffy on 100 percent being accepted or not regardless of my sister.

How should we handle this? Should I be worried we wont be accepted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not saying this is what's happening here by any means. I'm just saying it could potentially be the problem here and he seems to be ignoring the advice given by the counselor and I wonder if that's such a good idea for his relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt say get in the mood. I said help her mood e.g. help her be relaxed happy and comfortable with him and life in general. Not horny... for instance if he was trying to help her relax by doing the dishes or something, but every night he did that he asked for sex every time and so in her head she thinks "wow he thinks doing the dishes = he gets sex, nope". And so eventually he gave up on asking for sex but that means he also stopped doing the dishes, that reinforces in her head "wow he thinks if he does the dishes he gets sex". That's not the way relationships nor sex work in a healthy relationship. Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 23:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He didn't say hes still trying to help her mood though just that he stopped asking. Besides it's not gonna take just a short while of not asking for the issues to be fixed, this is gonna take time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 20:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think he didnt get much out of the therapy as he himself said it came down to him needing to be nicer and him not agreeing that that was a problem and therefore it wasnt entirely successful. How would it come up in therapy that he needs to be nicer and such but at the same time not be the truth. This sounds like a concern that would have come up in therapy from the wives perspective and he is ignoring it. 

I dont think it's wrong to want sex from your partner but if you are being nice to your partner NOT to be nice fo your partner but to get lucky later that night then that is the exact definition of an ulterior motive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 19:29:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This kind of thing might be happening here. He says that he does nice things and such but my question is, is he nice for like a day and then that night tries to come on to her? Or does he sustain these behaviors for longer periods of time, long enough that when hes being nice and such shes had enough time that in the back of her head she isnt dreading going to bed that night and having to reject him again. That kind of anxiety in her head would counteract the nice actions and not relax her at all. I think he could try putting sex out of his mind for a couple weeks entirely and just focus on the emotional aspects of their relationship during that time to make sure those are going strong without making her believe there are ulterior motives and then revisit sex then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get some practice by making some female friends online! Itll help you realize they arent all that different, especially if it's all through chats. I know its falling apart a little now but if you're willing to put up with the sucky parts of it you can go on omegle. Another way I made internet friends was through kik chat groups. I know both of these have bad reps, you gotta be willing to dig through the weeds for them but either way chatting with women online in a non romantic way will help you become more comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 04:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Night Circus? Maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 02:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I Want by Kodaline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 06:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Night Circus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Shopping is impossible! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 22:59:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Background: I've struggled with social anxiety for as long as I can remember but have made significant progress especially the past year or so. 


Basically, I had a baby a month ago and this has made me relapse a bit and I'm in a rough patch. Its horrible timing because post birth none of my clothes fit and I have no idea what size I am.

I have no pants that fit anymore but shopping is torturous I literally cant do it. I hate going in, feeling squished, having to try stuff on until I find the right size and going back and forth from the fitting rooms till I get it and its different for every dang brand! I hate taking up space, feeling like I'm bugging the workers and am in everyones ways. It's even harder now that I have to bring the baby with me. Today my husband and I drove all the way out to the mall and when we got there I saw through the store windows and couldnt do it. My husband let me give up and I never even stopped the car we just turned right around and went back home.

I go back to work in a week and need clothes before then, please help!!!!

Any advice on how to get through a shopping trip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 18:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly what I was gonna say!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 06:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved solved solved! Thank youuuuu!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Childrens book about a family of farmers with many children </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 05:46:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember my dad reading this to me when I was pretty young so he would have been reading it to me in the early 2000's but I believe the book was older than that.

In the book there was a family and I believe they were farmers. They had quite a few kids and I think there was some guy who didnt like them. He would do things like mess with their crops by throwing bad seeds in I believe. The kids worked together with their parents to do farm work and such.

The most memorable thing is that the farmer would often say to the kids something like "johnny bella Ann Gregory and bob" (totally made up the names, I have no idea what they actually were). Reading it allowed it had a definite flow to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 04:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh Wonder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 07:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> House of leaves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 07:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have always lived in the castle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 07:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> House of Leaves, the story itself is quite sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 23:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the end of the world as we know it (and I feel fine) - REM probably not but worth a try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 20:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alt J? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 07:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt like the girl power moment was just Marvel trying to take a short cut to get away with how terrible the female presence in that movie was. It was like a "oh hey we didnt forget about you guys have a cookie okay bye" moment. To me it felt more insulting and dismissive than anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 02:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dan Vs. Maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 02:02:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Zombie by the Cranberries OR the cover of it by Bad Wolves or both maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 01:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hollywood Undead is my angry listening music, Kill Everybody, Undead, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> IIL Come on Eileen then WEWIL </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 19:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have yet to find a song so perfectly fun, upbeat, unique, and just perfect or even close. Dont just reccomend a ton of other music from that time period because of the time period, while I do enjoy music from that time period anyways, to me Come on Eileen is a specimen of it's own and a song for the ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 18:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Night Circus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 13:32:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oooh this is a good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 01:50:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It

Carrie

The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon (my first, a shorter nice little taste, I'd recommend starting here)

The Shining 

Cell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 23:00:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Night Circus gives me a very fall vibe
It or The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon by Stephen king give me fall vibes as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 19:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> House of Leaves, it took me a little bit to get engrossed but once I got there it was great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 18:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The old dude tells him not to kill his son. Both books are about the colonization of that area from different perspectives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 18:23:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure how relevant it is to the human mind etc because I cant remember but a great side along read to the heart of darkness is things fall apart by Chinua achebe (probably spelled that wrong). It shows a different perspective to basically the same topic that really opens up your eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 17:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Artemis Fowl by Eoin Colfer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 05:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh Wonder might be a good one, check out Drive and without you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Starting young </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 19:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 09:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SOLVED SOLVED SOLVED !!!!! Thank u so much, that book was creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 07:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 07:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cell by stephen king </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 06:25:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a great suggestion, my husband and I use an app called tinybeans for sharing pictures, videos, milestones, etc. I like it because you have a lot of control over who has access to it and who doesnt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 19:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup I'm the exact same. I grew up in this are and have been to almost every store restaurant whatever and I still cant connect them. I gotta whip out my GPS a lot of times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 19:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exactly how I am. I'm just terrible at all spatial reasoning in general and I've never been very good at it so I'm not concerned. It's just not a strength for me, my husband is great at it though so we even out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 11:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordan - shorter and far more psychological
Cell - shorter side
It - longer side 
The Shining - easier to get through than It, more psychologically based than it and cell but not like the girl who loved tom Gordon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Children's book about a witch? A claw footed bath tub, a dog, and very distinct illustrations (90-00) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 09:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember reading a childrens book when I was little and would have been reading it around the early 2000's so it could be from then or earlier. I believe the illustrations were black and white and I'm a drawing like style. 
The story was about a little kid who is kidnapped or like runs away or something and ends up like captured by a witch or something out in the woods. I think the witch plans to eat the kid but the house and the things inside the house help the kid to escape. I'm pretty sure at one point the kid uses a bone to convince the witch that she (?) Is super skinny and I think a dog gave the kid that advice. 
One thing I remember distinctly is the fact that there was an old fashioned bathtub that was the claw foot style. The child is made to clean themselves in it I believe and I feel like it talks to the kid or runs away with the kid in it or something and that's how the kid finally escapes entirely at the end of the storybook.
Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 04:59:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Along with that she could be grey-sexual which is a bit controversial but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 02:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not saying that's not true but you were saying if that didnt happen and they were to go into the foster system it would be a worse scenario than the one they are currently in and that is not true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 01:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These kids are so young that's not a concern and I highly doubt these kids would go the permanent custody track anyways. You're judging the entire system off of your one personal experience, I'm looking at it around my about 70 clients I've had the past years experiences, some werent great and even those are highly better than the experiences these children are enduring due to their home life right now. I'm sorry you personally had a bad experience with the system, that's a shame. But your experience is one of many and just because you had one bad experience doesnt mean these children should remain in a neglectful home. And besides the fact that you're not taking their ages into account here shows you dont know much about this as you would hope your own personal experience would have taught you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 00:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... I'm a foster care case manager and these kids are in fact being seriously neglected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 00:26:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Based on the description here I'm pretty sure these kids would do much better in the system anyways and besides they're young enough that theyd be easy to place if it came down to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pregnancy is hard </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 20:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey everyone,

Like the title says pregnancy is hard. I hit 40 weeks yesterday and had an appointment scheduled. I went in and they told me my blood pressure was high and sent me to the hospital where they took tons of blood and did all this other stuff. In the end my blood pressure was getting higher every time they checked it but it never got up to severe and all the blood and urine tests came back fine so they sent me home. Now I'm stressed about having to pay 2 hospital bills instead of one and the fact that it was getting higher not lower but the worst part is no one seems to care. All anyone asks me about is the baby, no one cares over whether I'm okay and healthy just the little one. 

I know the baby is super important and stuff and I know I ended up sent home and being okay but I wish I still had contact with my mom because as terrible as she is, at least she would fuss over and be worried about me too. At least that's what I keep telling myself. I just want someone to be concerned about me and my health too and to stop just asking me about the baby but ask about me. I want someone to be the kind of worried where I'm telling them "no I'm really okay" and they are taking it almost too far but it's just the fact that they love me that much and really want me to be okay. The kind of overbearing love/concern that at the end of the day is nice to get sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 17:35:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this from the wayside stories series? Maybe the "wayside school gets a little stranger" book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 07:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thirteen Thirtyfive Dillon? Probably not but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 04:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although maybe not because it doesnt match the time you set </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 04:33:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hush hush by Becca Fitzpatrick, its gotta be I love this series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 23:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're feeling nervous go ahead and tell them. They're super understanding and are great and walking you through what's going on what's going to happen and going at your pace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 20:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit out the YTA for the bot please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 07:02:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds a little similar to Carl in Shameless U.S. but probably not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 04:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drive by Oh Wonder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 06:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably not but Jolene? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 06:08:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably not but fuck up by Shane dawson? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 00:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lasagna actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 20:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna go against the grind and say 
 NAH BECAUSE I am a foster care case manager and in our county at least it breaks a TON of rules to take pictures of our kiddos and post them anywhere. It's against a ton of privacy things and such and if you guys were interested in posting the picture anywhere it would no longer be possible. It's a rule a lot of people tend to overlook but it exits for good reason. Along with that if the kiddo ends up reuniting with bio fam that's actually a lot more difficult on foster parents than these parents may not realize if they havent yet gone through it. Displaying pictures with the kiddo in it could trigger them emotionally and make things difficult and these are pictures that most people would want to display. 

Option: get some pics with kiddo and some without that way kiddo is included but simultaneously if the kid ends up reuniting there isnt a mysterious kid in the pictures in ten years and you can post some, and if kiddo isnt reunited then you have pictures with the kiddo as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 19:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH mainly for not fighting for more primary custody of these kids who are in the care of a mom who is unable to provide for them. This is punishing the kids too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 18:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband is dealing with an issue like this, mind if I PM you some questions about how you fixed it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 00:46:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure if Brookeville's shelters are bookable but that could be an option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 03:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I literally felt that exact same way my first time going there, I hadn't had any females to help me figure that stuff out until then and had cried in too many department store bathrooms trying to do it on my own before I found that piece of heaven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 03:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SOLVED! THANK YOU!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 02:15:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's NOT little monsters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [TOMT][MOVIE][90/00'S]CHILDRENS MONSTER SOCIETY THAT LOVES MESSINESS, SMELLOVISION, AND STEALIMG SOCKS </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 02:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *repost because I messed up title formatting*


I was watching this movie in the early 2000's but it could be earlier than that. It's a kid/family movie. In the movie I dont remember a lot but there is a monster civilization that lives beneath human society. The monster society travels up to the human world to make messes and steal singular socks to mess up pairs. In the human society there is a teen girl who is a main character. In the monster society they have something called "smellovision". There is a young boy monster who doesnt like being messy and stealing from the humans so hes kind of looked down on and has to hide it. One day I think his dad takes him to the human society and from there it gets hazy but I'm pretty sure the teen girl and him meet and she ends up coming to the monster society and they have to hide her? I dont believe the girl was animated but was live action and I dont remember much about how they did the monsters. This has been bothering me for YEARS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 00:26:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Add in a good admittance essay about your struggles and you're fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 00:14:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Larosas for pizza maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-10 18:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 37 weeks today and I'm so torn between the two. I'm so over being pregnant and tired and uncomfortable and im also super excited to actually have my baby here and see my husband parent and everything! At the same time I'm dreading labor, and I'm going to miss my job while I'm on leave and keep thinking things like "oh I want to wait until this date so that I can get this done before leaving". Then the second I'm too tired at work because of pregnancy I go right back to "nevermind I want to leave right this second". Its such an emotional roller coaster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 02:53:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The exhaustion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DAE else experience this? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 22:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey bumpers,

I'm 36 weeks and am SO tired. Earlier in the pregnancy they determined I was pretty anemic and put me on iron pills and I remember before going on the pills I was so tired all the time but after going on them I felt better. Now I'm starting to feel how I did before again. It's not just normal tired, its tired to the point of struggling a TON to get up in the morning for work and then struggling to get my work done and then struggling to stay at work till the end of the day. I feel like I'm in a fog almost constantly. Take today for example, I fell asleep at 2 in the morning (a little late for me but whatever) and slept until 12 noon today waking up once every 3-4 hours to pee but falling back asleep after quite easily and sleeping deeply. Today when I woke up I was still exhausted for like an hour, I ate around 1 and was fine until like 2 when I felt dead exhausted again and fell asleep until just a little bit ago (4:30ish) and I'm STILL a little tired. 
This is how I felt before the iron pills and now im wondering if this is normal third trimester woes or if this could mean my iron pills stopped working or aren't working enough? Does everyone feel this way third trimester?
 I'm going to have them check my levels when I go in on Wednesday but ugh this is terrible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 19:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Essential oils, hear me out. Not in the these will heal you when you're sick kind of way but in the these relax me so that I can actually fall asleep at nights much faster than I've ever been able to before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 19:11:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Claritin and a humidifier, growing up I was constantly sick with sinus issues and my parents would only give me benadryl/nyquil. Now that I've started claritin and my humidifier I can breathe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Employment advice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 22:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi teachers,

I'm new to this sub so let me know if I'm breaking any rules or asking something that's asked a lot and I'll delete or something. 

Anyways, I'm asking this for my husband who graduated 2 years ago from a pretty well known college for teaching in my area with an English education degree and is licensed for 7-12th graders. 

My husband is a part of a ton of websites with teaching job postings and applys to everything applicable- in my opinion he gets a lot of interviews during the hiring periods (at least like one a month). He made his resume with a lot of help from good standing people for education at his school and has quite a few good references. Despite this fact for every interview whether it be part of a 3 step interview process or just the one, he never makes it past the first interview and I can tell it frustrates him a lot.

He dresses appropriately and goes above and beyond researching the schools before hand and their missions and values etc. He even matches his ties to their school colors. Financially being a sub isnt a good option for us right now but he does other things on the side education related (teaching weekend classes to kids, along with something else I dont full understand). He just cant seem to make it past first interviews.

I was wondering if you guys had any tips or any things he might be doing wrong. This is in the SouthWest Ohio area if that matters.

TLDR: husband cant get a job teaching never gets past the first interview HELP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 18:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was about to reccomend Lacy Green as well but I couldnt remember her name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-10 22:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I once peed in a Gatorade bottle to avoid walking through my common room to the bathroom as my roommate was mad at me and had a friend over as well and were in the common room. I'm a girl so it a difficult feat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 02:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA are you dating my ex? Hed be failing even without putting the blame on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 19:10:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah theres laundry basket porn, Google it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 20:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does everyone act like engineers are scientists? Maybe bio engineers sure but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Recipes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 05:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey moms,

For those of us who dont have moms of our own who do this kind of stuff for us-
Pass down a favorite recipe 3

I really wish I had a mother figure to do this kind of thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 19:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> INFO what does your sister view the responsibilities of a godparent as? A religious guidance or a future potential guardian or both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 06:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA but that last text you sent her about fixing your fuse was just fueling the fire at that point especially knowing about all of her car problems that were stressing her out at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 07:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me it never fully went away but got more manageable with the occasional relapse depending on life stuff. I got to that point by mostly exposure although I coupled that with some thought management of forcing myself to not think that I'm a burden or whatever and trying to think as often as possible that other people are genuinely nice people who are happy to help me. Mostly thought it was just the exposure exposure exposure. (And faking it till I made it- if I pretended like I belonged/was being normal/whatever then it could be true). Getting a job working with customers helped with that as well due to the fact that since I felt my uniform gave me some authority I could feel less like a burden and self conscious and more like a boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 07:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH but only because you didnt handle it well.

I had someone close to me have a surgery for scoliosis that resulted in this person being in near constant pain and being extremely depressed due to it (and being switched to home school for the surgery). I dont know what your brothers recovery has been like but it took me a year to understand fully what was going on with the person close to me and be more understanding. Maybe try and do things with your brother that wont cause him too much pain but can cheer him up some. Or motivate him by asking to do work together saying you work better with a study buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Finally confronted Narc Mom </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 05:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After NC for about 5 months my narc mom texted DH (I have her blocked) inviting us to Easter and I guess this whole time I've kind of had hope she could change or something because I was really considering it. DH didnt agree but was willing to respect my decision.

Well after milling it over I really thought about it and realized nothing she had done or I had heard about her would suggest she had changed at all and the last time I had been around family she and Edad spread a ton of lies around and bad mouthed me so I decided enough was enough.

I basically called her out on everything and she responded how youd expect of course, tons of lies, manipulation, gaslighting, rug sweeping. Only 2 things surprised me. 1. She admitted at one point she was in the wrong for not respecting boundaries BUT obviously she didnt apologize and also pretended like she had stopped doing that which she hadn't but okay. 2. She didnt express even the slightest interest in having me back in her life or in meeting or being involved with my daughter who is due in July. She basically said it was my loss and didnt even try one bit. 

I guess I should have expected it but I've noticed most parents on here are kind of crazy about the whole grandparents thing and the way my parents had talked in the past I figured they would be too. I guess not. Hopefully that doesnt change after LO arrives though.

Edit: Needless to say were back to NC and I have finally given up hope that her or the rest of my family will ever change. As freeing as it is in some ways, family holidays will be very depressing and lonely for awhile. Just looking forward to spending them with LO and DH next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 21:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the Woodlands, it's in Cleves so depends on your location but it was a super reasonable price and staff was amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 00:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA you kinda effed up but your girlfriend could have stood up for you at any point here leading up to this and a person can only be insulted so many times before standing up for themselves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 22:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA but a simple apology for your action and lack of knowledge in etiquette can go a long way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 22:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same even if you want to look at it more prolife hes the asshole because he feels the fetus is "our child" yet is in support of termination as well. So whether prolife or pro choice dudes TA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 22:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He refers to the fetus as "our child" but if he truly felt of the child in that way then why would he not at least try to advocate for it. Instead he seems to also want the abortion despite viewing it as a child already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 22:15:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA and the edit made you even more of one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 21:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd reccomend checking out /raisedbynarcissists or /justnofamily (sorry idk how to link to stuff haha)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 05:43:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To avoid creepiness/awkwardness I would add her first, if she accepts I'd react to some of her posts maybe a like or something and then message her using said post as a slight segway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 14:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With parental consent yes? And they aren't kids. The 17 year old wasnt drinking the only ones drinking were 18... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 14:43:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my state it's legal to drink on private property where the sale of alcohol is not happening with parental consent. Which they had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 19:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been in a similar situation (watching my parents abuse or neglect my younger siblings) basically my whole life. At this point they're futures are extremely bleak but the youngest one is 14. Basically all of them have dropped out of school and all this stuff and at this point I think it's too late to call CPS, but I wish I had when they were younger. Some of your siblings are still younger. Calling CPS because your mother isnt getting your brother the care he needs with his emotional mental issues aka medical neglect wouldn't necessarily get them removed from the home but it would potentially get someone in there to help guide your mom towards better resources and make sure your siblings are being better taken care of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tempted to end NC because I'm mad </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 00:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm currently NC with my narc parents due to a LOT of reasons, driven by the fact that since I'm pregnant it's not just about protecting myself anymore but my baby. I've been VLC to NC for about 3-4 months now.

During that time I had to fix my relationship with my sister that was heavily influenced by our abusive past and was very codependent. We've fixed our relationship since then and were both doing a lot better with boundaries and just communicating better, but I will feel a lot less worried about her once shes moved out of my parents house.

I'm 21, shes 18 and isnt currently in school and has one year to finish. The reason she didnt finish school is she was hospitalized due to an eating disorder. She got out went to a in patient center for a week or so was doing well for a few months  but then relapsed and ended up back in the hospital.

At that point they recommended a more specialized inpatient about 4 hours from us  that we've been waiting on insurance to approve and preapproval they were acting all for it. The issue is she has officially been approved and now they're constantly trying to convince her not to go, at first they were telling her she didnt have a ride there so I offered. Then they changed the date,  so I adjusted my schedule and it would be fine. Then NMom started pulling some BS about the chicken pox going around and I cant be around sister due to the pregnancy. But I wasnt having it, so now they're trying constantly to convince her not to go or to push it off (knowing this would make insurance reject it). Theyve switched to telling her if she goes they'll kick her out and wont drive her to therapist appointments etc. Telling her everyone else there will be thinner than her even. Calling her names etc.

This is a very hard decision for her and shes being very brave agreeing to go but dealing with all of this is making her consider not going.

I'm so mad about it and she needs to go that I'm considering breaking NC just to go off because I am going to scream. Shes planning to move in with us in October but until then her moving out isnt an option unless they officially kick her out. 

TLDR: narc parents trying to convince sister to stay sick and not go to treatment and I'm mad enough I'm thinking about pausing NC to go off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 20:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For hearing more, ask questions about how the baby stuff is going but also let her be more than just a "pregnant person" ask about her typical normal stuff outside of pregnancy as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 03:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I went NC I left a few messaging avenues open to my parents for the same reason and my nmom especially didnt respect the boundaries I put in place by constantly a few times every day blowing up my phone switching from sweet to mean to inviting me over etc. Nparents cant respect boundaries and I would just go ahead and block them personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-17 17:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a very similar experience. I graduated from high school with honors and already having a college education set up and a ton of AP credit- I worked my butt off. My dad refused to go to my graduation saying it was dumb and pointless he didnt go to dinner with my grandparents after either. And I definitely didnt get a party or anything. Meanwhile when my GC younger brother graduated the next year it was a D's get degrees kind of graduation that he scraped together from online school bc he couldnt be bothered to go to an in person school because attending school every day was apparently a waste of his time. He had no future set up at all and yet my dad took him and a couple other guys out for a whole weekend long camping trip to celebrate. My dad doesnt understand why I see anything wrong with this because "it's a guy thing I couldnt take my daughter on a trip" and "he was thinking of going to the military so hed be moving far away" as if I wasnt dorming. (he didnt go btw).

Now I dont even want to go to my college graduation for my double degree because high school was such a bad experience and graduations just make me sad now especially seeing everyone else with their family and I know mine wouldn't even care let alone go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DAE have nightmares </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 17:42:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Background: at least my mother is narcissistic, not sure what my dad is but I do know hes an a-hole who abused me and my siblings pretty badly growing up. As the oldest I ended up more of a parent to my siblings than a sister Now that my siblings are older they're taking after my parents quite a bit. 

So within the past couple months I've decided to go no contact. It basically stemmed from my parents and siblings choosing an extended family member over me who was treating me horribly and was CONSTANTLY over my family home to the point where I couldn't even have a positive environment to share ultrasound pictures with my nmom. I explained to them that I could put up with a lot but not this and at this point I was tired of them watching her treat me horribly constantly and still being buddy buddy with her and that it was her or me because I was tired of being everyone's dog to kick. Long story short, they chose her with full knowledge of the fact that it would result in me going mo contact and them not meeting my future bb.

I'm getting through it this is the longest I've been able to go NC with them and I'm still doing really well other than struggling with the guilt of leaving my siblings in their clutches. What bothers me the most is these dreams I've been having since around the time I went NC. All of these dreams are either one of my family members screaming at and physically attacking me in front of a ton of other family as an audience. I always end up having to defend myself physically against my attacker with an audience just doing nothing about it. The other variation of dream is a family member attacking a DIFFERENT family member that I have protected in the past. Once again this happens in front of an audience of family who do nothing and I have to solely defend this person, often getting very physically harmed in the process. A lot of times it ends up in me having to kill the attacker?? Idk what that's about.

Either way, I only noticed how these dreams connect together today and I guess it makes sense a lot looking at the reasons for a lot of my issues with family members in the past along with the fact that everyone let my dad abuse us growing up and I was the only one doing anything about it. 

I can handle the NC but these dreams are exhausting and making things hard. Does anyone else have similar dreams? Especially after going NC?

TLDR: after going NC I keep having bad nightmares that seem to be based in my past trauma and relationships with family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Terrified of what will happen when I give birth </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 07:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm currently pregnant and the baby is due late this summer. I recently went from LC to NC with my parents. It started about two and a half months ago and eventually culminated in me having to block my parents and some other family (siblings and extended family) on everything to stop the harrassment. Since then things have been vaguely radio quiet (though I discovered Nmom has left some very interesting emails). From some aunts I still talk to I found out that my family is playing it off as pregnancy hormones. 

Basically, I know that once I actually have my baby things are going to explode 1. Because they won't have pregnancy hormones to try and blame it on anymore and 2. Theyll be obsessed with meeting my kid and how I'm keeping their grandchild away from then. In the past its something my parents have talked about as being such a bad thing to do to grandparents so I know they feel strongly about it.  Even within the first month while I was still in contact my mom wasnt respecting baby things, posting about my pregnancy before I had and without my permission and constantly talking and posting about what her grandparent name would be despite the fact that I told her I didn't like it.

I'm terrified of what's going to happen and them showing up at my apartment or the hospital (although I will be talking to the hospital about visitors and stuff to be careful). 

TLDR: Growing up I always told my parents one day I'd be gone and me and my kids wouldn't be in their life. Now its finally going to happen and I'm scared of their reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-01 21:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre as bland as an unseasoned white ladies thanksgiving turkey  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pregnant and lonely </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-24 19:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Moms help. I dont have anyone to talk to about my pregnancy and it sucks. Im the first of all my friends to get pregnant and I dont have any female adult role models in my life. Turns out I hate being pregnant. Im only 13 weeks along and I already wish it was over. I have such bad insomnia at night then Im exhausted during the day and its making me suffer in college and my internship. I just feel like my body is failing me and I have no one to turn to. I dont even know whats normal or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>